<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Were the last six weeks all a bad dream?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/were-the-last-six-weeks-all-a-bad-dream-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/were-the-last-six-weeks-all-a-bad-dream-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;For the last six weeks, everyone in markets has been contemplating a reordering of world markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, we&apos;re back to where we started in tariff rates and in markets. That has Deutsche Bank wonder: What was the point of all of this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They note that the latest data shows China exports to the US on a steady decline with April 2025 imports at the lowest in real terms since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;Previously, we were convinced they were likely
to be very hawkish towards China and the two nations would continue to decouple
and that the massive imbalance between the two nations&apos; manufacturing output
and the national security concerns would ensure the ideology remained
throughout the term,&quot; writes DB multi-asset strategist Jim Reid.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;I&apos;ll be honest – I have more questions than answers at
the moment but it seems that: (1) more pragmatic voices in the US
administration have taken control again; (2) the near-term economy is being
prioritised over the long-term security agenda; (3) the US needs trade to
continue for now, and perhaps overestimated the leverage high tariffs would
give them in extracting concessions.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;So were the last six weeks all a bad dream? Will the
unpredictable nature of US policy continue or are we now on a more conventional
path? Not sure I have the answers this morning but, if you&apos;re looking for
positives, US policy does seem to have galvanised Europe, is encouraging China
to rebalance towards consumption and Bessent has even discussed how the trade
deficit may be partly being caused by the fiscal deficit. So maybe US policy
has been a force for good?&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s a common sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices close higher. German Dax closes at a new record level.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/european-indices-close-higher-german-dax-closes-at-a-new-record-level-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/european-indices-close-higher-german-dax-closes-at-a-new-record-level-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Major European indices are closing higher on the day. The German DAX closed at a new all-time high at 23551.54. Spain&apos;s Ibex closed at its highest level since 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A snapshot of the close levels shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX +52.21 points or 0.22% at 23551.54.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC, +106.35 points or 1.37% at 7850.11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK&apos;s FTSE 100 +50.18 points or 0.59% at 8604.99.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex +101.22 points or 0.75% at 13655.31.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB +551.60 points or 1.40% at 39921.60&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the daily chart of the German DAX, the price is moving away from the swing high going back to March 6 at 23475&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD stretches above 1.4000 for first time since April 10</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-stretches-above-14000-for-first-time-since-april-10-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:39:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-stretches-above-14000-for-first-time-since-april-10-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;142&quot; data-end=&quot;530&quot;&gt;The USDCAD has extended its gains and pushed above the key 1.4000 level, reaching a high of 1.40043. The next upside target comes in at the 200-day moving average at 1.40106, followed by resistance at 1.40268, a prior swing area high. Beyond that, the 38.2% retracement of the decline from the March 2025 high sits at 1.40525, marking a more significant hurdle for buyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;532&quot; data-end=&quot;765&quot;&gt;The earlier dip in price found support at 1.3977, the April 15 swing high, where buyers leaned in and reasserted control. That successful retest reinforced the bullish bias and helped fuel the move back toward and through 1.4000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;767&quot; data-end=&quot;1040&quot;&gt;While the break above 1.4000 is constructive, buyers still have work to do. A sustained move above the 200-day moving average, and ultimately the 1.40525 retracement level, is needed to confirm a stronger upside shift. For now, momentum remains with the buyers.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff uncertainty will be a drag on competitive dynamics</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariff-uncertainty-will-be-a-drag-on-competitive-dynamics-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:32:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariff-uncertainty-will-be-a-drag-on-competitive-dynamics-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;If you&apos;re an executive right now, what are you focused on: tariffs or competing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Capitalism works best when companies have a clear set of rules and can fight for market share. Today&apos;s news is undoubtedly good on tariffs but it&apos;s a 90-day pause, similar to the &apos;liberation day&apos; climb-down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In today&apos;s environment there is so much uncertainty. There are few executives with international supply chains that are right now focused on gaining market share. Instead, they&apos;re trying to navigate changing rules, stockpile and manage inventories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, there are probably opportunities to undercut competitors but if competitors can&apos;t respond and the moves are temporary, does that really create sustained disinflation? I&apos;d argue that it simply leads to turmoil in pricing that resets with weaker competitive dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My guess is this is how the Fed sees it as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recipe right now isn&apos;t there for disinflation in the world as companies are writing tariff clauses into contracts and stuffing warehouses. Right now they have to decide if they want to pay 30% tariffs on Chinese goods or risk waiting around for a better/worse deal later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bull case now for risk assets and the US dollar is the massive tax cut package that Republicans are working on. I&apos;d say a good deal of that is already priced in but certainly not all of it. It&apos;s looking like it will be paid for via Medicaid cuts and massive deficits. Even with that it&apos;s mostly a continuation of the regime that&apos;s already in place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when you look out further at some point you need to price in a tightening fiscal regime. The US is running at deficit at 7% of GDP and tariffs and DOGE aren&apos;t going to pay for much at all. The Joint Congressional Committee on Taxation is just out with an analysis saying the tax bill will cost $4.9 trillion over 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;d imaging there will be cheers in markets when that&apos;s passed but at some point, it will need to be paid for so at some point you need to price in some level of austerity.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED’S KUGLER: I AM ONE OF THOSE WHO BELIEVES THERE COULD BE SOME PERMANENCY FROM PRICE INCREASES RELATED TO TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921947847651447018#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:17:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921947847651447018#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED’S KUGLER: I AM ONE OF THOSE WHO BELIEVES THERE COULD BE SOME PERMANENCY FROM PRICE INCREASES RELATED TO TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ breaks key moving averages, bullish trend in place</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nasdaq-breaks-key-moving-averages-bullish-trend-in-place-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nasdaq-breaks-key-moving-averages-bullish-trend-in-place-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;162&quot; data-end=&quot;501&quot;&gt;The NASDAQ Composite Index has broken back above the 200-day moving average (green line on the chart at 18,320.79) and 100-day moving average (blue line at 18,476.49)  —a technical development that marks a shift in the medium-term trend. These MA levels were broken for the last time (to the downside) on March 6 and had not traded above since that day. The price gapped above the MAs today off of the weekend news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;162&quot; data-end=&quot;501&quot;&gt;The NASDAQ index is currently up 630.2 or 3.5% at 18557.63 above both those moving averages&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;503&quot; data-end=&quot;802&quot;&gt;With the index breaking back above those MAs, they become the bias-defining levels today and going forward.  Staying above is more bullish with a swing area between 18599 and 18832 as the next area to get and stay above (see yellow area on the chart above).  A move above those levels takes the price back into the all-time upper extreme that peaked at 20204.58 back on December 16, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1003&quot; data-end=&quot;1015&quot;&gt;Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1016&quot; data-end=&quot;1291&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1016&quot; data-end=&quot;1091&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1018&quot; data-end=&quot;1091&quot;&gt;100-day and 200-day MAs between 18320.88 and 18,476.49 have been broken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1092&quot; data-end=&quot;1144&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1094&quot; data-end=&quot;1144&quot;&gt;Bullish bias now in place with buyers in control above the moving averages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1145&quot; data-end=&quot;1221&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1147&quot; data-end=&quot;1221&quot;&gt;Key upside targets are between swing area at 18598.87 and 18831.91&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The S&amp;amp;P index has also broken above its key 200-day moving average at 5750.18 and it&apos;s 100 day moving average at 5773.64. The current price trades at 5811.31 up 151.42 points or 2.67%. There is a swing area between 5782.02 and 5878.47 which if broken would take the price into the upper all-time extreme that peaked at 6147.43.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: BELIEVES RUSSIA WILL AGREE TO 30 DAY CEASEFIRE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921941129492128001#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:50:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921941129492128001#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: BELIEVES RUSSIA WILL AGREE TO 30 DAY CEASEFIRE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech sector surges: Investors flock to Apple and Amazon in today&apos;s bullish market</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-surges-investors-flock-to-apple-and-amazon-in-todays-bullish-market-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:46:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-surges-investors-flock-to-apple-and-amazon-in-todays-bullish-market-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s market is buzzing with positivity, driven by standout performances in the technology and consumer cyclical sectors. The technology sector is seeing remarkable gains, spearheaded by industry giants Apple (AAPL) and Microsoft (MSFT). Meanwhile, the consumer cyclical sector is thriving, with Amazon (AMZN) leading the charge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technology Advances: Apple, with an impressive increase of 5.17%, and Microsoft, up by 1.07%, are elevating the technology sector. Other notable contributors include Nvidia (NVDA) with a 3.23% rise and Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) which is up by 4.45%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consumer Cyclical Gains: Amazon is witnessing a substantial boost of 7.06%. Tesla (TSLA) follows closely with a gain of 5.46%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communication Services: This sector is also enjoying a favorable day, with Meta (META) jumping 5.65% and Google (GOOG) up by 2.56%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The overall market sentiment today is highly optimistic, fueled by robust earnings reports from key players and increasing consumer confidence. Investors are eagerly embracing tech stocks, indicating a strong belief in the sector&apos;s growth potential amid evolving market dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors might consider bolstering their portfolios with tech and consumer cyclical stocks given today&apos;s favorable movements. Specifically, Apple&apos;s and Amazon&apos;s strong performances suggest potential long-term growth. However, it&apos;s vital to remain vigilant and diversify holdings to mitigate risks, particularly considering the volatility in sectors like healthcare and utilities. Stay informed and responsive to real-time market shifts to ensure strategic decisions align with evolving trends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Explore &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/&quot;&gt;ForexLive&lt;/a&gt; for more insights and the latest updates on market activities. 📈📊&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIA PM MODI: NO NUCLEAR BLACKMAIL WILL BE TOLERATED BY INDIA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921939904042262880#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:45:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921939904042262880#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIA PM MODI: NO NUCLEAR BLACKMAIL WILL BE TOLERATED BY INDIA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIA PM MODI: PAKISTAN CONTACTED OUR MILITARY OPERATIONS CHIEF ON MAY 10</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921939428181774674#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:44:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921939428181774674#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIA PM MODI: PAKISTAN CONTACTED OUR MILITARY OPERATIONS CHIEF ON MAY 10&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump with more on China: I think we will have a deal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-with-more-on-china-i-think-we-will-have-a-deal-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:40:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-with-more-on-china-i-think-we-will-have-a-deal-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;I think we&apos;ll have a deal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China tariffs will go up without a deal, won&apos;t go all the way to 145%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;All the comments are so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Iran/Russia:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;So far Iran is acting intelligently&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Iran is being reasonable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Believes Russia will agree to a 30-day ceasefire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is the latest from Fox Business&apos; Charlie Gasparino:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; In talking to sources who run small businesses the pause w China came just as their company is were on the precipice of disaster since they source so much of their material from China and the containers coming from China were coming back empty. If you want to know why we were as desperate for a deal as the Chinese, it’s because small businesses — a key MAGA constituency— was about to get crushed&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: CHINA TARIFFS WON&apos;T GO BACK UP ALL THE WAY TO 145%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921937863559512453#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:37:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921937863559512453#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: CHINA TARIFFS WON&apos;T GO BACK UP ALL THE WAY TO 145%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: CHINA TARIFFS WILL GO UP WITHOUT A DEAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921937797675446498#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921937797675446498#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: CHINA TARIFFS WILL GO UP WITHOUT A DEAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: MAY HAVE GOOD RESULT OUT OF ISTANBUL MEETING

TRUMP: BELIEVE BOTH LEADERS WILL BE THERE

TRUMP: WAS THINKING ABOUT GOING TO ISTANBUL

TRUMP: THERE&apos;S A POSSIBILITY IF I THINK THINGS WILL HAPPEN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921937700589818117#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:37:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921937700589818117#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: MAY HAVE GOOD RESULT OUT OF ISTANBUL MEETING&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: BELIEVE BOTH LEADERS WILL BE THERE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: WAS THINKING ABOUT GOING TO ISTANBUL&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: THERE&apos;S A POSSIBILITY IF I THINK THINGS WILL HAPPEN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 falls into the opening gap</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-500-falls-into-the-opening-gap-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:36:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-500-falls-into-the-opening-gap-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The problem with this rally is that it was front-run hard. The tide really turned on the market after Bessent&apos;s private comments and the White House private meeting with Walmart, Target, Home Depot and other retailers. A hint of that was that shipping out of China has spiked in the past two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a lingering sense that too many people knew this was coming and that much of the buying the past three weeks was in anticipation of today. Yes, the details are probably better than expected but there may have been some massive leveraged trades betting on exactly this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now they&apos;re taking profits in an economy that&apos;s still wracked by turmoil and uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I still think the path is ultimately higher but is there enough here to chase markets to fresh all-time highs?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP VERY GOOD THINGS HAPPENING ON IRAN

TRUMP THEY ARE BEING VERY REASONABLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921937342777934127#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:35:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921937342777934127#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP VERY GOOD THINGS HAPPENING ON IRAN&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP THEY ARE BEING VERY REASONABLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: MANY OTHER DEALS COMING IN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921937081313415303#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:34:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921937081313415303#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: MANY OTHER DEALS COMING IN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD Technical Update: Sellers Return After 200-Day MA Rejection</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-technical-update-sellers-return-after-200-day-ma-rejection-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:32:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-technical-update-sellers-return-after-200-day-ma-rejection-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;193&quot; data-end=&quot;494&quot;&gt;The AUDUSD attempted a move higher and outside a swing area with a high at 0.64419. However, once again the high price stalled at the 200-day moving average, located near 0.6458, turning buyers into sellers. The price stalled near that MA on Thursday of last week (the price moved briefly above that level but quickly reversed). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;193&quot; data-end=&quot;494&quot;&gt;The rejection at this key level has pushed the pair back below the converged 100/200 hour MAa at 0.64349 and with that, back into the red-box range, suggesting a shift back to neutral-to-bearish bias in the short term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;496&quot; data-end=&quot;568&quot;&gt;With momentum now pointing lower, immediate support targets include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;569&quot; data-end=&quot;773&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;569&quot; data-end=&quot;601&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;571&quot; data-end=&quot;601&quot;&gt;The swing level at 0.63646&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;602&quot; data-end=&quot;650&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;604&quot; data-end=&quot;650&quot;&gt;The high of the lower swing area at 0.63437&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;651&quot; data-end=&quot;730&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;653&quot; data-end=&quot;730&quot;&gt;The 200-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, currently near 0.6325&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;731&quot; data-end=&quot;773&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;733&quot; data-end=&quot;773&quot;&gt;The low of the swing area at 0.63216&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;775&quot; data-end=&quot;1000&quot;&gt;A break below 0.63216 would increase bearish pressure and open the door for further declines with the 100-day MA at 0.6289 and the 38.2% of the move up from the April low at 0.62844.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;775&quot; data-end=&quot;1000&quot;&gt; Conversely, start to move back above the 100 bar MA on the 4-hour chart, and the 100/200 hour MAs at 0.64399 would disappoint the sellers.  A move back above the  200-day MA, would be a bigger disappointment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;775&quot; data-end=&quot;1000&quot;&gt;Sellers are making a play  but in the wake of the move higher that peaked last week at 0.65135, has left a number of targets that need to be broken to increase the bearish bias.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1002&quot; data-end=&quot;1014&quot;&gt;Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1015&quot; data-end=&quot;1217&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1015&quot; data-end=&quot;1071&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1017&quot; data-end=&quot;1071&quot;&gt;Rejection at the 200-day MA caps the upside at 0.6458. Bias shifted lower while below the 200-day MA, 100/200 hour MA and 100 bar MA on the 4-hour chart&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1072&quot; data-end=&quot;1116&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1074&quot; data-end=&quot;1116&quot;&gt;Price falls back into consolidation range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1117&quot; data-end=&quot;1169&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1119&quot; data-end=&quot;1169&quot;&gt;Support targets: 0.63646, 0.6347, 0.6335, 0.63216 (low of consolidation range going back to April 10).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1170&quot; data-end=&quot;1217&quot;&gt;Other lower target include the 200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart at 0.6325 adn then the 200 day MA at 0.6286.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) S&amp;P 500 PARES GAIN TO 2.4%, REACHES SESSION LOW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921936114861896072#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:30:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921936114861896072#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 PARES GAIN TO 2.4%, REACHES SESSION LOW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Kugler: Trade policy shifting but still likely to lead to higher prices and less GDP</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kugler-trade-policy-shifting-but-still-likely-to-lead-to-higher-prices-and-less-gdp-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:30:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kugler-trade-policy-shifting-but-still-likely-to-lead-to-higher-prices-and-less-gdp-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;It has become hard to judge the underlying growth of the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Labor market conditions mostly stable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supported keeping rates stable at current restrictive level, Fed in a good position to deal with change in macro outlook&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is straight out of the Fed choir book. The market is priced for a 45% chance of a cut in July and 81 bps in the year ahead (down from 131 bps three weeks ago).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;If tariffs are long lasting, the one issue I would be looking to is how supply chains get rearranged in the rest of the world&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m one of those who believes there could be some permanency on price increases related to tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WILL ADD ON TO TARIFFS IF COUNTRIES DON&apos;T ABIDE BY DRUG POLICY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921934251450044512#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:23:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921934251450044512#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WILL ADD ON TO TARIFFS IF COUNTRIES DON&apos;T ABIDE BY DRUG POLICY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WILL CUT OUT MIDDLEMEN IN DRUG SALES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921933805994008696#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:21:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921933805994008696#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WILL CUT OUT MIDDLEMEN IN DRUG SALES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: REPUBLICANS CAN DO BETTER THAN OBAMACARE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921932761675243885#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:17:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921932761675243885#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: REPUBLICANS CAN DO BETTER THAN OBAMACARE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨🚨 CHINA COMMERCE MINISTER: CHINA, US TRADE TALKS CREATED CONDITIONS FOR FURTHER BRIDGING DIFFERENCES AND DEEPENING COOPERATION - MINISTRY STATEMENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921932052204597467#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921932052204597467#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨🚨 CHINA COMMERCE MINISTER: CHINA, US TRADE TALKS CREATED CONDITIONS FOR FURTHER BRIDGING DIFFERENCES AND DEEPENING COOPERATION - MINISTRY STATEMENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: EU WILL HAVE TO PAY MORE FOR HEALTHCARE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921931869043458320#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921931869043458320#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: EU WILL HAVE TO PAY MORE FOR HEALTHCARE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: EU WILL COME DOWN A LOT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921931797664780729#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:13:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921931797664780729#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: EU WILL COME DOWN A LOT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: EU IS NASTIER THAN CHINA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921931713862680768#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:13:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921931713862680768#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: EU IS NASTIER THAN CHINA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: DRUG POLICY CHANGE WILL PAY FOR GOLDEN DOME</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921931244016689621#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:11:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921931244016689621#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: DRUG POLICY CHANGE WILL PAY FOR GOLDEN DOME&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: PRICES COULD COME DOWN FROM 59 TO 80 TO 90%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921930829497774269#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:09:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921930829497774269#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: PRICES COULD COME DOWN FROM 59 TO 80 TO 90%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: BROUGHT UP WEIGHT LOSS DRUGS WITH DRUG COMPANIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921930650354897170#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:09:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921930650354897170#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: BROUGHT UP WEIGHT LOSS DRUGS WITH DRUG COMPANIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: We achieved a total reset with China</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-we-achieved-a-total-reset-with-china-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 13:53:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-we-achieved-a-total-reset-with-china-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We&apos;re negotiating with India right now (on trade)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US helped a lot of with India-Pakistan ceasefire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Agreement doesn&apos;t cover steel, aluminum, cars or pharma&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says he spoke to Tim Cook this morning; Cook will built a lot in the USA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Talks in Geneva were friendly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We&apos;re not looking to hurt China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will speak to Xi at the end of the week maybe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China was honoring the &apos;phase 1&apos; deal until Biden came in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is a big incentive for China to stop sending fentanyl, I take them at their word they will make it stop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will no longer tolerate profiteering from big pharma&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drug policy change will pay for &apos;golden dome&apos; missile defense&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blow things up and then take credit for a &apos;total reset&apos;; I guess that&apos;s the art of the deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;I just called the Speaker of the House and I just called the leader, our leader in the Senate, John Thune..spoke to both of them. I said, when &quot;You&apos;re going to have to score two things. You&apos;re going to have to number one, score that hundreds of billions of dollars of tariff money is coming in. But even bigger than that, you&apos;re going to have to score that year. Your cost for Medicaid and Medicare and just basically pharmaceuticals and drugs is going down at a level that nobody has ever seen before. It&apos;ll pay for the Golden Dome.&quot; I see the Golden dome is there. See? That&apos;ll easily pay for the Golden Dome. And we&apos;ll have a lot of money left over.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;How many times is Trump going to count that tariff revenue? It&apos;s paying for tax cuts, subsidize for farmers and now for missile defense.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD moves higher with the dollar strength after US/China tariff suspension</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-moves-higher-with-the-dollar-strength-after-uschina-tariff-suspension-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 13:49:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-moves-higher-with-the-dollar-strength-after-uschina-tariff-suspension-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The USDCAD has moved higher in response to the lower China/US tariffs (or suspension of the tariffs) and the overall USD buying. The price has risen toward a cluse or MAs, swing and retracement targets starting with the: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;200 are moving average on the 4-hour chart at 1.39874.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The 200 day moving average of 1.40106,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swing area between 1.4009 and 1.40268, and the &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;38.2% retracement of the move down from the March high. That level comes in at 1.40525&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The high price has reached 1.39983 and is waffling above the high price from March 15 at 1.3977, and the overhead resistance near the aforementioned technical targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video, I go through the technical clues that are driving this currency pair. Be aware. Be prepared.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump set to speak on pharma</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-set-to-speak-on-pharma-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 13:39:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-set-to-speak-on-pharma-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Trump is set to talk about pharma at a press conference imminently. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The President wrote yesterday about a plan for prescription drugs that would shift costs to other countries. That has pharma companies struggling against a very strong tape today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t see much in the way of macro drivers in the pharma-specific comments but Trump will surely be asked about China so watch out for those comments.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF Technical Update: Price extends higher after breaking out of consolidation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-technical-update-price-extends-higher-after-breaking-out-of-consolidation-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 13:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-technical-update-price-extends-higher-after-breaking-out-of-consolidation-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;87&quot; data-end=&quot;226&quot;&gt;The USDCHF has made a notable technical breakout, moving above a key consolidation area and extending higher toward retracement resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;228&quot; data-end=&quot;511&quot;&gt;On the hourly chart, the price had been confined within a red-box consolidation zone, capped by resistance near 0.8333. After several failed attempts, the pair finally broke above the top of that box and found support on a retest, using the 0.8333 level as a base to push higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;513&quot; data-end=&quot;794&quot;&gt;On the 4-hour chart (see chart below), the pair surged into a key swing area between 0.8373 and 0.84087, which also includes the 200-bar moving average, currently near 0.8383. The price broke above the area with momentum today.  This zone is now a critical support area and represents close risk for buyers looking to maintain the bullish momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;796&quot; data-end=&quot;1017&quot;&gt;To the upside, the next major resistance comes at the 38.2% retracement of the move down from the January high, which is being tested near 0.84823. A move above this level would open the door for further upside extension and represents the minimum retracement target to get to and through if the buyers are to take more control. .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1019&quot; data-end=&quot;1031&quot;&gt;Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1032&quot; data-end=&quot;1272&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1032&quot; data-end=&quot;1090&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1034&quot; data-end=&quot;1090&quot;&gt;Breakout above hourly range high at 0.8333, now support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1091&quot; data-end=&quot;1164&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1093&quot; data-end=&quot;1164&quot;&gt;Support zone: 0.8373–0.84087 (includes 200-bar MA on 4-hour at 0.8383).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1165&quot; data-end=&quot;1208&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1167&quot; data-end=&quot;1208&quot;&gt;Resistance: 38.2% retracement at 0.84823.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1209&quot; data-end=&quot;1272&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1211&quot; data-end=&quot;1272&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;A hold above the 4-hour swing area support keeps the bias tilted higher, but getting above the 38.2% retracement is a required target for the buyers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold is being put to the test today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-is-being-put-to-the-test-today-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 13:00:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-is-being-put-to-the-test-today-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There are many winners in today&apos;s market action but there is a big loser as well: Gold. It&apos;s down $95 to $3228 today as the great decoupling may not happen after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news looks bad for gold but I&apos;m carefully watching the technicals. Gold has so far held the May 1 low of $3201 and that&apos;s a good sign for the bulls. We&apos;ve seen some heavy gold selling in the New York 9 am hour through the equity open in the past year so I think that&apos;s a delicate time. If it can hold here and if Trump strikes a less-aggressive tone on the trade war then I think we can see a deeper selloff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spoke with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kitco.com/news/article/2025-05-09/wall-street-balanced-between-bulls-bears-and-fence-main-street-maintains&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Kitco News&lt;/a&gt; on Friday and laid out how I was thinking:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Adam Button, head of currency strategy at Forexlive.com, said it&apos;s tough not to be bullish on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kitco.com/charts/gold&quot;&gt;gold &lt;/a&gt;these days, but the de-escalation between the United States and China has the potential to sap the yellow metal’s momentum.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;“The meeting this weekend is high stakes,” he said. “People are saying 50%, then Trump&apos;s saying 80% today. We’ve built in some expectation of lower tariffs between China and the U.S., and it’s tough to judge how much is priced in and what might be the effect. If we come out of the weekend at 50%, I think we&apos;re going to see gold sell off and we&apos;ll see the riskier assets continue [higher].”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;“I don&apos;t think 50% would be the end goal, but it would be pretty rapid progress and a nice sign for both sides.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Button said that gold is acting as the best financial barometer of the state of global trade these days. “Gold is clearly now finding itself as a trade on global trade, a ‘trade-war-on/trade-war-off’ asset,” he said. “For the week ahead, if China tariffs come down, if U.S. tariffs come down… I think that you don&apos;t have a meeting without a plan to offer something, so they’ve both ratcheted down a little bit. I think any progress in that direction is negative for gold for the week ahead.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;“I would say gold looks to be carving out a range at the top end,” Button added. “If you pull back, gold went from $2,500 to $3,500 in a straight line, and now it&apos;s consolidating in a $300 range at the top without a really big pullback. This is the best the bulls could hope for. It was nice to talk about $4,000 or $10,000 or whatever, but if gold can spend a month or two right around these levels, that&apos;s bullish long term.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-China breakthrough leads to a breakout</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-breakthrough-leads-to-a-breakout-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:34:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-breakthrough-leads-to-a-breakout-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;US tariffs on China are down to 30% while China tariffs on the US are set at 10%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even beyond the massive cut in tariffs, 20 percentage points of the US tariffs on China are due to fentanyl and I think there is a path to lowering or eliminating that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deal is for 90 days but Treasury Secretary Bessent said that could be extended so long as negotiations are headed in the right direction. I think that leaves importers in a tough spot as they will have to decide on whether to stockpile with 30% tariffs or risk a better/worse outcome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now though, there is a huge sigh of relief in markets with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up 3.2%, oil up 4%, USD/JPY up 280 pips and 2-year yields up 11 bps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The message there is that US, Chinese and global growth prospects just got much better. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today is a test: Can these moves be sustained or is there still some skepticism? That will tell us about the underlying strength of the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think you have to be optimistic here as it looks like Trump doesn&apos;t have the appetite for a trade war after all and he&apos;s pivoting toward opening up China for US companies. Was the Trump Put in all along?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive European FX news wrap: US, China strike deal to lower tariffs after talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-us-china-strike-deal-to-lower-tariffs-after-talks-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:15:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-us-china-strike-deal-to-lower-tariffs-after-talks-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Headlines:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-to-lower-tariffs-on-china-to-include-a-base-10-plus-20-fentanyl-levy-20250512/&quot;&gt;US to lower tariffs on China, to include a base 10% plus 20% fentanyl levy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-deal-reportedly-does-not-cover-de-minimis-exemption-for-e-commerce-shipments-20250512/&quot;&gt;US-China deal reportedly does not cover de minimis exemption for e-commerce shipments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-have-reached-agreement-with-china-on-a-90-day-pause-moving-down-tariff-levels-20250512/&quot;&gt;Bessent: We have reached agreement with China on a 90-day pause, moving down tariff levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/greer-we-have-a-constructive-path-forward-to-have-a-positive-conversation-with-china-20250512/&quot;&gt;Greer: We have a constructive path forward to have a positive conversation with China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-want-a-decoupling-with-china-for-strategic-necessities-20250512/&quot;&gt;Bessent: We want a decoupling with China for strategic necessities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-it-is-implausible-that-tariffs-on-china-go-below-10-20250512/&quot;&gt;Bessent: It is implausible that tariffs on China go below 10%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-i-could-see-a-trump-xi-call-happening-in-the-coming-weeks-months-20250512/&quot;&gt;Bessent: I could see a Trump-Xi call happening in the coming weeks, months&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-drug-prices-to-be-cut-by-59-plus-20250512/&quot;&gt;Trump: Drug prices to be cut by 59%, plus!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-wants-lower-interest-rates-but-hes-strategy-is-likely-to-lead-to-higher-rates-20250512/&quot;&gt;Trump wants lower interest rates but his strategy is likely to lead to higher rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-us-china-news-20250512/&quot;&gt;How have interest rates expectations changed after the US-China news?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-lombardelli-caution-remains-appropriate-20250512/&quot;&gt;BOE&apos;s Lombardelli: Caution remains appropriate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-lombardelli-latest-us-china-discussions-are-good-news-20250512/&quot;&gt;More from BoE&apos;s Lombardelli: Latest US-China discussions are good news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-greene-wage-inflation-measures-are-moving-in-the-right-course-but-still-too-high-20250512/&quot;&gt;BOE&apos;s Greene: Wage, inflation measures are moving in the right course but still too high&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-greene-disinflation-process-in-underway-20250512/&quot;&gt;More from BoE&apos;s Greene: Disinflation process in underway&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;USD leads, JPY lags on the day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;European equities higher; S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up 3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields up 7.6 bps to 4.451%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold down 3.0% to $3,224&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude up 4.0% to $63.50&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin down 0.5% to $103,794&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The big news of the day and likely for this week already is that the US and China have come to an agreement to de-escalate trade tensions while seeking further talks in the weeks/months ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The tariff levels for both sides are brought down by 115%. So, that means the US is still imposing 30% tariffs on China while China is imposing 10% tariffs on the US during this 90-day pause period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That said, the agreement today will not cover the de minimis exemption that was abolished as of 2 May and China is also still keeping their restriction on rare earth exports in the meantime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;US Treasury secretary Bessent had a lot to say during the session, reaffirming that the new mechanism in place for discussions will facilitate much calmer discussions and actions between both sides. He made sure markets know that the mechanism &quot;will avoid the type of escalation&quot; from last month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar and risk trades rallied on the news unsurprisingly and held gains throughout. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures were already up 1.5% before doubling gains to be up 3% now. Nasdaq futures are up 3.8% and poised to reenter a bull market again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As for the dollar, the gains were solid across the board. USD/JPY jumped up by a good 300 pips at the highs today, extending gains from around 146.20 to above 148.00 now on the day. Meanwhile, EUR/USD is down over 1% to 1.1100 and GBP/USD also down 1% to 1.3175 currently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides that, USD/CAD is up slightly by 0.3% and nudging closer to 1.4000 while AUD/USD is down 0.4% to 0.6390 after some stubbornness following the initial headlines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In other markets, bond yields are also racing higher on the optimism as markets pare back rate cut bets as well. Oil is a strong beneficiary as it climbs up by 4% to $63.50. And gold is one of the bigger casualties in all this, down over 3% to $3,224 on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USD moves higher after suspension of US/China tariffs. Stocks higher. USD higher.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-moves-higher-after-suspension-of-uschina-tariffs-stocks-higher-usd-higher-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:11:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-moves-higher-after-suspension-of-uschina-tariffs-stocks-higher-usd-higher-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The United States and China have agreed to a 90-day suspension of their tariffs, with the U.S. reducing tariffs on Chinese goods from 145% to 30%, while China will cut duties on American imports from 125% to 10%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both sides committed to continuing negotiations, with U.S. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent emphasizing a mutual interest in avoiding full economic decoupling. China will also suspend countermeasures, including export restrictions on rare earth materials. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the truce breaks a damaging impasse that halted many cross-border orders, the deal lacks concrete commitments from China on currency or trade imbalances, prompting skepticism about its long-term durability. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question is will the suspension lead to more businesses scrambling to take advantage of the temporary tariff relief, pushing up transport costs and inflation in the process (30% is still a BIG jump in costs), or will the 30% still be a game changer (i.e., still too high). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treas. Sec. Bessent is making the rounds and stated that the U.S. is aiming for a strategic decoupling from China in critical sectors such as steel, semiconductors, and select medicines to safeguard national interests. He noted that China now appears serious about stemming the flow of fentanyl into the U.S., and that both sides have established a mechanism to avoid further tariff escalation. Despite the decoupling goals, Bessent emphasized that the U.S. still wants American businesses to be able to sell into the Chinese market. He confirmed that significant progress was made during two days of talks and hinted that further meetings with Chinese counterparts are likely in the coming weeks, with future discussions expected to focus on non-tariff trade barriers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the weekend, President Trump also announced plans to reinstate his &quot;Most Favored Nation&quot; policy aimed at reducing prescription drug costs by tying U.S. prices to those in the lowest-paying countries. The original rule, finalized in 2020, targeted Medicare payments for drugs administered in doctors’ offices but was blocked by courts and later revoked by President Biden. In a Truth Social post, Trump claimed the new executive order—set to be signed Monday—would cut drug prices by 30% to 80%, though specific details on which drugs or payments would be affected remain unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks are sharply higher on all the news, with the futures implying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow Industrial average futures implying a gain of 1026 points. On Friday the index fell -119.11 or -0.29%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index futures implying a gain of 172 109 points. On Friday the index fell -4.03 points or -0.07%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq futures implying a gain of 790 points. On Friday the index was unchanged &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the European markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German Dax, +0.53% (traded to a new record today)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC, +1.37%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE 100, +0.49%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex, +0.56% (highest level since 2008)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB, +1.78% (highest level since 2007)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market, yields are higher &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield 3.93%, +10.0 basis points &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.090%, +10.3 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year yield 4.451%, +7.6 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year yield 4.81%, +4.9 basis points &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil up $2.50 or 4.0% to $63.54&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Silver is and $0.44 or -1.33% to $32.27&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold is down $108 or -3.26% to $3217.79&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin is trading up $164 at $104,293. On Friday the price closed at $102,991.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: I could see a Trump-Xi call happening in the coming weeks, months</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-i-could-see-a-trump-xi-call-happening-in-the-coming-weeks-months-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:59:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-i-could-see-a-trump-xi-call-happening-in-the-coming-weeks-months-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump viewed 80% as not being an embargo for China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We can always go back to 2 April level i.e. 54% tariffs for China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sees a phone call taking place before any meeting between Trump and Xi&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The current timeline for the status quo is 90 days. So, better get on it. But as mentioned, the 90 days is pretty much just an initial timeline. Unless talks implode between both sides, that can always be readjusted to a longer timeline. The question is if the can continues to be kicked down the road for long enough, will Trump lose patience?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: It is implausible that tariffs on China go below 10%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-it-is-implausible-that-tariffs-on-china-go-below-10-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:52:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-it-is-implausible-that-tariffs-on-china-go-below-10-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current tariffs level is a floor&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now, we have a process in place to avoid further escalation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This at least clears things up a bit on their current position at least. As a reminder, the US is now putting a 10% base level tariffs plus 20% tariffs due to the fentanyl issue (30% total) on China. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-deal-reportedly-does-not-cover-de-minimis-exemption-for-e-commerce-shipments-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;the de minimis exemption will not be restored&lt;/a&gt; as well even with the climb down. Meanwhile, China is putting a 10% base level tariffs on the US and have not pulled back on restricting rare earth exports from before &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-halts-rare-earth-exports-after-new-controls-raising-global-supply-concerns-20250413/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How is the China camp painting the trade deal situation back home?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-is-the-china-camp-painting-the-trade-deal-situation-back-home-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:47:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-is-the-china-camp-painting-the-trade-deal-situation-back-home-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;While China is also acknowledging the positive steps taken in seeking a trade deal, the nuance in how either the US or China is selling the narrative is also something important to be wary about. On paper, sure there are things to be optimistic as both sides seek de-escalation. However, the undertone is what will set the stage for further discussions and how fruitful that can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The US so far have pushed the narrative that both sides managed to see eye to eye in talks over the weekend. And that China has finally understood the US&apos; position on fentanyl and will do something about that. In the meantime, Bessent has been harping on the supposed mechanism for both sides to continue discussions moving forward. And he made sure markets know that with such a mechanism, retaliatory tariffs of the kind we saw last month will be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But how is China viewing all this instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;China&apos;s commerce ministry dubbed the deal as an &quot;important step&quot; in resolving the differences between the two countries via dialogue and consultation. Adding that it lays the groundwork for further cooperation. Note, there&apos;s no mention of fentanyl talks whatsoever here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And hours later, the message from the state media is making it clear how they see the situation as being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;This shows that China&apos;s firm countermeasures and resolute stance have been very effective. The countermeasures have had a material impact on the US and the US administration have reduced tariffs to the base level i.e. 10% after the talks.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides that, the commerce ministry also made sure to note that its restriction on rare earth exports will still be in place regardless of the agreement today. In case you missed it, this is related to the announcement last month &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-halts-rare-earth-exports-after-new-controls-raising-global-supply-concerns-20250413/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All this is not to say that there&apos;s two sides to the story though. At least this time around, the narratives from both sides are lining up much, much closer together than before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;However, it is evident that China is more reserved and cautiously optimistic. That said, optimistic is still optimistic especially after the height of tensions last month. And the joint statement today, which is a rarity on its own, reflects that as both sides are putting on a show to seek de-escalation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For just choosing to sit down and talk, China has definitely gotten a major concession from Trump. So, it&apos;s arguably clear who blinked first in this scenario. But at this point, it doesn&apos;t really matter who did. Egos aside, the development is a positive for markets and the global economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But in the bigger picture, can this be followed up by more positive correspondence and eventually an actual trade deal down the road? Or is this going to be the new normal with the US seeking sectoral tariffs/decoupling from China? We&apos;ll see in time.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: We want a decoupling with China for strategic necessities</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-want-a-decoupling-with-china-for-strategic-necessities-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:10:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-want-a-decoupling-with-china-for-strategic-necessities-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are going to protect our steel, semiconductor industries, selected medicines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Believe China is now serious about halting fentanyl flows into the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have a mechanism in place to avoid upwards tariffs pressure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We want American businesses to be able to sell to China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I imagine we will meet (with China) again in the next few weeks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We got a lot done over two days&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will see what we can do on non-tariff barriers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, earlier in the day he said that neither side are interested in decoupling. So, yeah. In any case, any real intentions will be buried by the wave of optimism across markets right now as both sides seek de-escalation. But for China, they certainly got a lot out of it by just deciding to sit down for a chat. Either way, it&apos;s still a positive for markets and the global economy.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Sentiment Now (... and watch these prices)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/market-sentiment-now-and-watch-these-prices-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:08:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/market-sentiment-now-and-watch-these-prices-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;&gt;Market Sentiment Snapshot for Traders and Investors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today’s financial markets are experiencing significant shifts driven primarily by the recent U.S.-China agreement on tariff reductions. Here is a detailed overview of the current sentiment across key financial instruments:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold (Bearish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold prices have dropped sharply, with futures plunging about 3%. This bearish momentum is largely a result of improved sentiment stemming from U.S.-China tariff cuts, reducing gold&apos;s attractiveness as a traditional safe-haven asset. Traders should monitor if uncertainties around these trade agreements resurface, potentially stabilizing or reversing gold&apos;s bearish trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GOLD HAS CROSSED DOWN 3320... But if it crosses above it, then we may have a dip in gold!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil (Bullish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil prices are strongly bullish, rising between 2% to over 3% today. Positive trade developments between the U.S. and China are fueling optimism for global economic growth and increased oil demand. However, the potential for higher crude oil oversupply due to increased OPEC production remains a notable risk that traders should watch closely, as it could temper current gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 (Bullish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. equity markets are firmly bullish, with stock futures significantly higher. This positive sentiment is primarily due to easing U.S.-China tensions and expectations of improved trade conditions. Investors are cautiously optimistic, awaiting further details to assess the sustainability of this rally. Equity investors should maintain vigilance for any signs of stalled trade progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch ES 5882 today... If we get there, profit takers may stop in. TRADE AT YOUR OWN RISK ONLY.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US Dollar Index (Bullish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar has surged to a one-month high, driven by the improving global growth outlook linked to U.S.-China tariff relief. The bullish sentiment is strong, but the market acknowledges that maintaining this momentum depends on continued progress in trade negotiations. Currency traders should watch for developments closely, as any negative shifts could swiftly impact the dollar’s current strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese Yen (Bearish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The yen is notably bearish today, experiencing significant selling pressure as investors pivot away from safe-haven currencies in favor of riskier assets amid reduced geopolitical tensions. The positive U.S.-China tariff developments have significantly diminished the yen&apos;s attractiveness, placing additional downward pressure on the currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Euro (Bearish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUR/USD has experienced considerable bearish pressure, breaking below key support and eyeing further declines towards the 1.09 handle. The euro’s weakness largely stems from the strengthened dollar. However, traders note that further downside may be limited, given the potential uplift in global economic sentiment from recent trade agreements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Euro futures CROSSED DOWN 1.1118... But if it crosses above it, then we may have a dip in Euro!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrencies (Bullish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrencies, led notably by Ethereum (ETH), are seeing a strong bullish sentiment. ETH has gained approximately 42% in the past five days, driven by improved investor optimism from U.S.-China tariff cuts and an overall increase in risk appetite. The crypto market broadly reflects this positive sentiment, indicating confidence in continued bullish momentum in the near term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If bitcoin futures reaches 103,500 (retracing down to there), then bulls may buy again!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Correlations and Market Dynamics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-spread=&quot;false&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk-On Sentiment: The simultaneous rise in stocks, the US dollar, cryptocurrencies, and oil underscores strong &quot;risk-on&quot; market sentiment driven by U.S.-China trade optimism. This is negatively impacting traditional safe-haven assets like gold and yen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inverse Correlation (Gold vs. Stocks &amp;amp; Crypto): Gold’s bearishness directly corresponds with bullish equity and cryptocurrency sentiment, as traders shift away from defensive positions to riskier assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dollar Strength vs. Euro and Yen Weakness: The robust US dollar rally directly pressures the euro and yen, highlighting their inverse correlation with risk-positive developments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actionable Insights for traders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traders and investors should remain adaptive, closely tracking updates from ongoing U.S.-China negotiations. Immediate bullish or bearish biases can swiftly shift, depending on trade-related news. Keeping an eye on further details and potential reversals will be crucial in managing risk and capturing opportunities in the current dynamic market environment. Watch some of the tips above for possible hints for the end of the moves, and possible trades... at your own risk only.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How have interest rates expectations changed after the US-China news?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-us-china-news-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-us-china-news-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 54 bps (92% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 45 bps (79% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 50 bps (84% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 39 bps (58% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 78 bps (98% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 69 bps (69% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 30 bps (96% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 19 bps (96% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the US-UK deal last week, we had some &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-first-trade-deal-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;hawkish repricing &lt;/a&gt;as the expectations for a 10% baseline tariff for everyone started to solidify. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, following the very positive US-China news this morning, the market is taking an even more hawkish view on future rates as positive expectations about global growth and potentially a surge in economic activity in the short-term will likely lead central banks to slow down the pace further. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-China deal reportedly does not cover de minimis exemption for e-commerce shipments</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-deal-reportedly-does-not-cover-de-minimis-exemption-for-e-commerce-shipments-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 10:51:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-deal-reportedly-does-not-cover-de-minimis-exemption-for-e-commerce-shipments-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The de minimis exemption is a rule which allowed for certain e-commerce shipments of goods at $800 or less to enter duty-free. The $800 is the threshold amount so to speak. Any shipments below that will not incur import charges basically. This allowed a supposed &quot;loophole&quot; for online retailers - particularly fast fashion from China - to have a stronger presence in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This exemption was removed by the White House last month &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/04/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-closes-de-minimis-exemptions-to-combat-chinas-role-in-americas-synthetic-opioid-crisis/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. And it looks like even with the trade deal announced today, that&apos;s not going to fall back into place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, in any case, online shopping from overseas will definitely be much more expensive for US consumers regardless of the deal today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;If you head over to the DHL sub-Reddit in the past two weeks, you can already see how much of a pain tariffs have become for US consumers. There&apos;s been countless cases of duties charged being much more than the entire item/product ordered itself. It goes to show where the pain really lies when it comes to tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
