<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. SENATE VOTES TO BLOCK CALIFORNIA&apos;S LANDMARK PLAN TO END THE SALE OF GASOLINE-ONLY VEHICLES BY 2035</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925570235089740040#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:11:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925570235089740040#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. SENATE VOTES TO BLOCK CALIFORNIA&apos;S LANDMARK PLAN TO END THE SALE OF GASOLINE-ONLY VEHICLES BY 2035&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KC Fed manufacturing index -10 vs -5 prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/kc-fed-manufacturing-index-10-vs-5-prior-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:03:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/kc-fed-manufacturing-index-10-vs-5-prior-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was -5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This has bounced around but it&apos;s above the -13 low in February.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JPMORGAN TO LEND MORE THAN $7 BILLION FOR OPENAI DATA CENTER - THE INFORMATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925568266052763934#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925568266052763934#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JPMORGAN TO LEND MORE THAN $7 BILLION FOR OPENAI DATA CENTER - THE INFORMATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP AIDE WITKOFF TO TRAVEL TO ROME ON FRIDAY FOR IRAN TALKS -SOURCE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925566542105760133#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:56:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925566542105760133#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP AIDE WITKOFF TO TRAVEL TO ROME ON FRIDAY FOR IRAN TALKS -SOURCE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD stuck in tight range as sellers eye a deeper push</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-stuck-in-tight-range-as-sellers-eye-a-deeper-push-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:54:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-stuck-in-tight-range-as-sellers-eye-a-deeper-push-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;239&quot; data-end=&quot;462&quot;&gt;The AUDUSD has been confined within a narrow 191-pip range between 0.63216 and 0.6513 over the last 28 trading days. That is a relatively tight range, indicative of a market that is unsure of the next shove.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;464&quot; data-end=&quot;859&quot;&gt;At the center of this range are the 100- and 200-hour moving averages, both of which are now nearly converged at 0.6439. Over the past several days, the price has been fluctuating above and below this moving average cluster, with each break lacking follow-through. Today, the pair has once again moved back below the MAs, tilting the short-term bias back to the downside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;861&quot; data-end=&quot;1300&quot;&gt;The key question now is: Can sellers hold the price below the MAs and build momentum? The next key technical target comes in at the upward sloping trend line and the recent swing low near 0.6388, which has acted as a floor since last Friday. A break below that level would open the door toward the 200-bar MA on the 4-hour chart at 0.63669. Below that, the support zone between 0.63216 and 0.63437 comes into focus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1302&quot; data-end=&quot;1610&quot;&gt;On the flip side, a move back above the 100/200-hour MAs at 0.6439 would shift attention to the 200-day moving average at 0.64532. The last four trading days have seen unsuccessful attempts to stay above that key long-term average, including a failed break again during today’s session highs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1617&quot; data-end=&quot;1660&quot;&gt;Key Technical Highlights (Updated):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1661&quot; data-end=&quot;2082&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1661&quot; data-end=&quot;1715&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1663&quot; data-end=&quot;1715&quot;&gt;Range: 0.63216 to 0.6513 (191 pips over 28 days)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1716&quot; data-end=&quot;1779&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1718&quot; data-end=&quot;1779&quot;&gt;Current resistance zone: 100/200-hour MAs near 0.6439&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1780&quot; data-end=&quot;1836&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1782&quot; data-end=&quot;1836&quot;&gt;Upside target if broken: 200-day MA at 0.64532. Tries above the 200 day MA have failed recently. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1837&quot; data-end=&quot;1906&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1839&quot; data-end=&quot;1906&quot;&gt;Initial support: 0.6388 (swing low/floor since last Friday)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1907&quot; data-end=&quot;1961&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1909&quot; data-end=&quot;1961&quot;&gt;Next support: 200-bar MA (4-hour) at 0.63669&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1962&quot; data-end=&quot;2009&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1964&quot; data-end=&quot;2009&quot;&gt;Broader support zone: 0.63216–0.63437&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2010&quot; data-end=&quot;2082&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2012&quot; data-end=&quot;2082&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 0.6439, with pressure building if 0.6388 fails&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2084&quot; data-end=&quot;2228&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;This technical standoff continues—momentum favors sellers, but they still need to take out key downside targets to gain clearer control.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants rise: Microsoft and Google lead today&apos;s market rally</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-giants-rise-microsoft-and-google-lead-todays-market-rally-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:46:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-giants-rise-microsoft-and-google-lead-todays-market-rally-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s stock market heatmap reveals a pronounced upward trend in the technology and communications sectors, with notable performances from key players. Here&apos;s a closer look at the dynamics shaping today&apos;s market landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;📈 Technology Sector: Microsoft (MSFT) and Nvidia (NVDA) are shining, up 1.24% and 1.07% respectively. This surge reflects renewed investor confidence in tech infrastructure and semiconductor innovation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;📊 Communication Services: Google (GOOG) leads the pack with a substantial 4.02% increase, suggesting robust growth potential in the internet content and information sector. Meta Platforms (META) also shows a positive uptick of 0.73%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;📉 Consumer Electronics: In contrast, Apple (AAPL) reports a dip of 0.81%, highlighting potential caution or strategic reassessment by investors in this segment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;⚙️ Industrials: Boeing (BA) impresses with a gain of 0.82%, standing out amid a generally flat performance across the industrials sector.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🏠 Real Estate: The sector sees slight gains, led by Public Storage (PSA) at 0.66%, signaling stable interest in real estate investments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The overall market sentiment today exhibits cautious optimism, driven largely by strength in tech and communications. With leading tech corporations demonstrating resilience and growth, there&apos;s a palpable sense of long-term bullishness. However, mixed results in consumer-related sectors suggest a more nuanced view of market conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investor reactions are cautious yet positive, particularly towards tech innovations and digital services which continue to attract significant capital. This trend indicates potential momentum in these sectors, especially with stability returning after recent volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With today’s insights in mind, investors might consider the following strategies:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diversification: Balance your portfolio by incorporating high-performing tech and communication service stocks while keeping an eye on emerging opportunities in real estate and industrials.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Risk Management: Monitor consumer electronics closely against market shifts that may affect major players like Apple.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Focus Areas: Given today&apos;s strong performances, prioritizing investments in innovative tech infrastructure and digital content service providers could be advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay connected with real-time updates and in-depth analyses at ForexLive.com to make informed decisions and capitalize on evolving market dynamics. 📊📰&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural gas prices slide after weekly inventory data</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/natural-gas-prices-slide-after-weekly-inventory-data-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:43:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/natural-gas-prices-slide-after-weekly-inventory-data-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;US natural gas prices are down about 2% today after a bearish inventory report. Stockpiles rose by 120 bcf compared to 115 bpc as we get ready for the summer power burn season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Natty is in an interesting spot at the moment and though prices have corrected since March, January futures remain just shy of $5 as LNG demand remains high and data center demand ramps up. The ongoing coal-to-gas switching is also continuing while lower oil prices mean less associated gas production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the best way to look at gas is via days of supply and this chart from TD highlights that we&apos;re about 18% below last year&apos;s level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best thing for gas prices from here would be a decline in WTI into the $50s as that&apos;s going to curb supply. Otherwise, it will all be about watching the weather and waiting for winter.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FXIFY Celebrates 2 Years as Industry&apos;s First and Oldest Broker-Backed Prop Firm</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/fxify-celebrates-2-years-as-industrys-first-and-oldest-broker-backed-prop-firm-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:32:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/fxify-celebrates-2-years-as-industrys-first-and-oldest-broker-backed-prop-firm-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;FXIFY, the oldest broker-backed prop firm, is proud to celebrate
its second anniversary, marking two years of industry-defining innovation,
trader-first policies, and rapid global growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its inception, FXIFY has paid out over $30 million to
its traders and now serves a global community of more than 200,000 active
users. In the first quarter of this year alone, a single trader received an
impressive $81,000 payout — a clear demonstration of the firm’s reliability and
commitment to delivering on payout promises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We didn’t create FXIFY to follow the crowd,” says Peter
Brown, Co-Founder of FXIFY. “We built it to fix what was broken. Traders were
being strung along with gimmicks and delays. So we brought in real
infrastructure, cut out the nonsense, and gave traders something they could
actually rely on.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FXIFY has led a shift in the industry by prioritising
transparency, efficiency, and speed. As the first and oldest broker-backed prop
firm, FXIFY introduced clear evaluation models and first payouts on demand
whilst eliminating common prop firm pain points like vague rules, delayed
payments, and inconsistent policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The platform supports multiple trading platforms familiar
to traders worldwide and offers flexible account structures suited to every
style and level. From instant funding programs to futures trading and classic
evaluation models, FXIFY has built an ecosystem that gives traders what they
need to grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its short history, FXIFY has already secured recognition
from International Business Magazine and ForexProp Reviews, among others, for
its outstanding contribution to the prop trading space. The firm’s highest
single payout to date stands at $117,000. One trader has successfully received
over 40 payouts — each one delivered on time — while another holds the title of
FXIFY’s longest continuously funded trader, with a duration of over 1 year and
7 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This performance is powered by a growing team of more than
100 staff across four international offices. With over two decades of combined
experience in both retail and institutional trading, FXIFY’s leadership team
brings industry knowledge and operational stability. That experience translates
into better trading infrastructure, faster response times, and a platform that
understands the real-world needs of traders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, FXIFY plans to roll out new and enhanced
trading programs and introduce additional platform integrations. The firm is
also building strategic third-party partnerships and expanding payment options
to deliver a smoother, more powerful user experience.“We’re deeply thankful for
our trading community&apos;s trust and support,” says Peter Brown. “Our traders have
driven our growth, and we’re excited to continue this journey together.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it enters year three, FXIFY continues to set the pace
for the industry — transforming what traders expect from a prop firm. With a
foundation of real infrastructure, fast payouts, and proven expertise, FXIFY is
not just keeping up with the market. It’s raising the bar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About FXIFY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FXIFY
(https://fxify.com/) is the industry’s oldest broker-backed prop firm,
empowering talented traders globally with access to trading capital. Offering a
comprehensive range of funded trader programs — including Instant Funding,
Futures-funded trading, and various evaluation models — FXIFY enables traders
to showcase their skills, earn up to a 90% Performance Split, and access
capital up to $400,000 with flexible, on-demand payout options.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MEXICAN PRESIDENT SHEINBAUM: WE HAD A CALL THIS MORNING WITH TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925559830883762606#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:30:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925559830883762606#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MEXICAN PRESIDENT SHEINBAUM: WE HAD A CALL THIS MORNING WITH TRUMP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG MET WITH JPMORGAN CEO JAMIE DIMON IN BEIJING - XINHUA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925559442793230476#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:28:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925559442793230476#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG MET WITH JPMORGAN CEO JAMIE DIMON IN BEIJING - XINHUA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD buyers lose momentum near 50% and shift focus back to key support zone</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/urusd-buyers-lose-momentum-near-50-and-shift-focus-back-to-key-support-zone-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:20:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/urusd-buyers-lose-momentum-near-50-and-shift-focus-back-to-key-support-zone-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;183&quot; data-end=&quot;445&quot;&gt;Yesterday, the EURUSD saw a bullish attempt as price moved above the 50% retracement level at 1.13183, but buyers failed to hold the break, turning momentum back toward the downside in the short term. That failure gave sellers a renewed edge, at least in the short term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;447&quot; data-end=&quot;832&quot;&gt;The pair is now approaching a key technical confluence area between 1.1258 and 1.12754. This zone has played a pivotal role recently—acting first as a floor, then as a ceiling, and now potentially a floor again. Within this range lies the rising 100-hour moving average and the broken 38.2% retracement of the move down from the April high —adding further weight to its importance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;834&quot; data-end=&quot;1132&quot;&gt;A hold above this support cluster keeps the pair in a neutral-to-bullish posture - negating the failure above the 50% retracement.  That potentially sets the stage for another upside attempt. However, a break below 1.1258 would shift the bias more clearly back to the downside, exposing further support levels at 1.1215 (the 200 hour MA) and a swing area between 1.11899 to 1.1213.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1134&quot; data-end=&quot;1158&quot;&gt;Key levels to watch:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1159&quot; data-end=&quot;1273&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1159&quot; data-end=&quot;1214&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1161&quot; data-end=&quot;1214&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.13183 (50% Fib), 1.1362 (highs from yesterday), 1.1378 (61.8% retracement)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1215&quot; data-end=&quot;1273&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1217&quot; data-end=&quot;1273&quot;&gt;Support: 1.1258–1.12754 (key zone), 1.12157 (rising 200 hour MA), 1.11899 to 1.1213 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1275&quot; data-end=&quot;1402&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;Momentum is turning, and how price behaves around 1.1258–1.12754 will be critical in determining the next directional move/bias.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SPOT GOLD  FALLS 1% TO $3,279.09/OZ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925553068705296511#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:03:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925553068705296511#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPOT GOLD  FALLS 1% TO $3,279.09/OZ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US APRIL EXISTING HOME SALES FALL 0.5% M/M; EST. 2.0% 

*US APRIL EXISTING HOME SALES AT 4M; EST. 4.10M</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925552433813430283#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:00:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925552433813430283#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US APRIL EXISTING HOME SALES FALL 0.5% M/M; EST. 2.0% &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*US APRIL EXISTING HOME SALES AT 4M; EST. 4.10M&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) OpenAI to Partner With U.A.E.&apos;s G42 to Build AI Data Center in Abu Dhabi -- WSJ

Project Is ChatGPT Maker&apos;s First Large Project Outside the U.S. -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925552387156062321#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:00:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925552387156062321#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenAI to Partner With U.A.E.&apos;s G42 to Build AI Data Center in Abu Dhabi -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Project Is ChatGPT Maker&apos;s First Large Project Outside the U.S. -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April existing home sales 4.00m vs 4.10m expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-existing-home-sales-400m-vs-410m-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-existing-home-sales-400m-vs-410m-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-existing-sales-for-march-402m-vs-413m-estimate-20250424/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior &lt;/a&gt;was 4.02m&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sales change -0.5% vs -5.9% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inventory at 4.4 months vs 4.0 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Median prices at $414K, up 1.8% y/y&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sales bottomed in the 3.90m range in 2023 and 2024. With borrowing rates now well-above 7%, I suspect we&apos;re headed back there.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 GERMAN FINANCE MINISTER: IF THERE IS NO AGREEMENT ON TARIFFS, THEN WE CAN EXPECT TURBULENCE ON THE MARKETS AGAIN VERY QUICKLY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925550237013168342#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:52:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925550237013168342#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 GERMAN FINANCE MINISTER: IF THERE IS NO AGREEMENT ON TARIFFS, THEN WE CAN EXPECT TURBULENCE ON THE MARKETS AGAIN VERY QUICKLY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KRAKEN TO LAUNCH TOKENIZED U.S. STOCKS FOR GLOBAL USERS

Kraken, a U.S.-based crypto exchange, will soon let non-U.S. users trade tokenized versions of popular U.S. stocks like Apple, Tesla, and Nvidia. These digital tokens, called xStocks, will trade 24/7 on the Solana blockchain, offering global investors easier and cheaper access to U.S. equities.

Key Details:
🔸 Launching in Europe, Latin America, Africa, and Asia in the coming weeks.
🔸 Not available to U.S. users.
🔸 Over 50 stocks and ETFs will be tokenized, including SPY and SPDR Gold Shares.
🔸 Tokens will be backed by actual shares, held by Kraken’s partner Backed Finance, and redeemable for cash.
🔸 Tokens can be held in digital wallets or used as collateral for crypto trades.

Why Tokenize Stocks?
Kraken says this allows 24/7 trading and avoids high fees and delays typical of international brokerage systems. Investors may eventually trade xStocks on other crypto platforms.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925549617589993683#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925549617589993683#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KRAKEN TO LAUNCH TOKENIZED U.S. STOCKS FOR GLOBAL USERS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Kraken, a U.S.-based crypto exchange, will soon let non-U.S. users trade tokenized versions of popular U.S. stocks like Apple, Tesla, and Nvidia. These digital tokens, called xStocks, will trade 24/7 on the Solana blockchain, offering global investors easier and cheaper access to U.S. equities.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Key Details:&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Launching in Europe, Latin America, Africa, and Asia in the coming weeks.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Not available to U.S. users.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Over 50 stocks and ETFs will be tokenized, including SPY and SPDR Gold Shares.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Tokens will be backed by actual shares, held by Kraken’s partner Backed Finance, and redeemable for cash.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Tokens can be held in digital wallets or used as collateral for crypto trades.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Why Tokenize Stocks?&lt;br&gt;
Kraken says this allows 24/7 trading and avoids high fees and delays typical of international brokerage systems. Investors may eventually trade xStocks on other crypto platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF bounces from key support and tests overhead resistance</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-bounces-from-key-support-and-tests-overhead-resistance-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:49:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-bounces-from-key-support-and-tests-overhead-resistance-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;168&quot; data-end=&quot;433&quot;&gt;The USDCHF found solid support yesterday at a key swing area near 0.81931 to 0.82120, a zone that had previously acted as a launchpad during the early May rally. Buyers leaned against that level yesterday, halting the recent downside momentum and triggering a bounce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;435&quot; data-end=&quot;837&quot;&gt;Today, the pair is moving modestly higher and is now testing a higher resistance zone — the swing area between 0.8272 and 0.82803. This level has been a recurring pivot in recent weeks (see red circles), with both buyers and sellers using it as a battleground. A break above this area would open the door toward the 100-hour MA (blue line currently near 0.8308) and the 38.2% retracement level of the May range at 0.83087.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;839&quot; data-end=&quot;1092&quot;&gt;Staying below 0.82803 keeps the near-term bias more neutral-to-bearish, especially as the price remains under the 100 hour MA, the 38.2% retracement and the downward sloping trendline. Conversely, a break above the current resistance zone could shift momentum further in favor of the bulls but with those targets looming above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1094&quot; data-end=&quot;1118&quot;&gt;Key levels to watch:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1119&quot; data-end=&quot;1260&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1119&quot; data-end=&quot;1168&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1121&quot; data-end=&quot;1168&quot;&gt;Support: 0.8257(50% retracement). 0.8193 to 0.8212 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1169&quot; data-end=&quot;1260&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1171&quot; data-end=&quot;1260&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.8272–0.82803 (current test), 0.8308 (100 hour MA, and 38.2% Fib), 0.83509 (200-hour MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1262&quot; data-end=&quot;1372&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;The pair is at a pivotal juncture — the response at current levels will help define the next directional bias.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) APPLE, TESLA, NVIDIA SHARES TO TRADE AS TOKENS ON KRAKEN: WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925548995574739367#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925548995574739367#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;APPLE, TESLA, NVIDIA SHARES TO TRADE AS TOKENS ON KRAKEN: WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA $NVDA - Kraken Plans Blockchain Versions of Tesla and Nvidia Shares for Non-U.S. Customers -- WSJ

Crypto Exchange Will Offer More Than 50 Tokenized Stocks and ETFs -- WSJ

Kraken Sees Tokens as an Easier Way for Foreign Investors to Trade U.S. Stocks -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925548858475487367#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:46:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925548858475487367#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt; - Kraken Plans Blockchain Versions of Tesla and Nvidia Shares for Non-U.S. Customers -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Crypto Exchange Will Offer More Than 50 Tokenized Stocks and ETFs -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Kraken Sees Tokens as an Easier Way for Foreign Investors to Trade U.S. Stocks -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GERMAN FINANCE MINISTER: ON MY CONVERSATIONS I HAVE SEEN AN INTEREST TO REACH A SOLUTION ON TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925548707082047876#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:46:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925548707082047876#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GERMAN FINANCE MINISTER: ON MY CONVERSATIONS I HAVE SEEN AN INTEREST TO REACH A SOLUTION ON TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US S&amp;P MAY SERVICES PMI AT 52.3; EST. 50.8 

*US S&amp;P MAY COMPOSITE PMI AT 52.1; PREV. 50.6 

*US S&amp;P MAY MANUFACTURING PMI AT 52.3; EST. 50.1</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925548657337573609#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:45:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925548657337573609#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US S&amp;amp;P MAY SERVICES PMI AT 52.3; EST. 50.8 &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*US S&amp;amp;P MAY COMPOSITE PMI AT 52.1; PREV. 50.6 &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*US S&amp;amp;P MAY MANUFACTURING PMI AT 52.3; EST. 50.1&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US May S&amp;P Global flash services PMI 52.3 vs 50.8 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-may-sp-global-flash-services-pmi-523-vs-508-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:45:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-may-sp-global-flash-services-pmi-523-vs-508-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 51.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing 52.3 vs 50.1 expected -- best one-month jump since June 2022&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior manufacturing was 50.7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite 52.1 vs 51.2 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;rise in
inventories of purchases was the largest recorded in
the 18-year survey history.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a nice rebound into solidly positive territory, no doubt due to lower tariffs and a rebound in the stock market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is worrisome, though not that surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;Average prices charged for goods and services jumped
higher in May, rising at a rate not witnessed since
August 2022. An especially steep rise was seen for manufacturers’
selling prices, which posted the largest monthly
increase since September 2022. Charges levied for
services rose to the greatest extent since April 2023
The latest rise in output prices was overwhelmingly
linked to tariffs, having directly driven up the cost of
imported inputs or caused suppliers to pass through
tariff-related cost increases. Manufacturing input costs
rose at the sharpest rate since August 2022 while
service sector costs rose at the fastest rate since June
2023&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is Chris Williamson,
Chief Business Economist at S&amp;amp;P Global Market
Intelligence&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;Business confidence has improved in May from the
worrying slump seen in April, with gloom about prospects
for the year ahead lifting somewhat thanks largely to the
pause on higher rate tariffs. Current output growth has
also picked up from April’s recent low, which had seen
the weakest rise for over one-and-a-half years, in
response to an upturn in demand.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“However, both sentiment and output growth remain
relatively subdued, and at least some of the upturn in
May can be linked to companies and their customers seeking to front-run further possible tariff-related
issues, most notably the potential for future tariff hikes
after the 90-day pause lapses in July. In particular,
concerns over tariff-related supply shortages and price
rises led to the largest accumulation of input inventories
recorded since survey data were first available 18 years
ago.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“Supply chain delays are now more prevalent than at any
time since the pandemic led to widespread shortages in
2022, and prices charged for both goods and services
have spiked higher as firms and their suppliers seek to
pass on tariff levies to customers. The overall rise in
prices charged for goods and services in May was the
steepest since August 2022, which is indicative of
consumer price inflation moving sharply higher.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stock futures flat. Urban Outfitters upbeat on the consumer</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stock-futures-flat-urban-outfitters-upbeat-on-the-consumer-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:26:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stock-futures-flat-urban-outfitters-upbeat-on-the-consumer-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Stocks appear to be keying off the dip in Treasury yields. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are now flat after a 30 point round trip in negative territory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bounce comes after US 30-year yields backed off the 2023 high of 5.17% and are down to 5.11%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One good sign I would note in the pre-market movers is Urban Outfitters, which is up +17% after strong earnings and revenue beat. The clothing company highlighted a strong consumer in something of a pushback to the weakness at Target yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Despite the noise in the headlines and the broader economic uncertainty, our customers continued to show resilience in Q1. We haven&apos;t seen any signs of a demand slowdown,&quot; said Richard Hayne, CEO. “May to date, we see the comp sales being very similar to the Q1 print.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company left its guidance unchanged and anticipates 10% global tariffs with 30% from China. The company said it was &quot;definitely considering&quot; raising prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are some other pre-market movers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advance Auto Parts +30% on smaller-than-expected loss and revenue beat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nike +1% after announcing return to Amazon and price hikes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Humana -6% on Medicare Advantage audit concerns&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;CVS Health -4% on Medicare audit news&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;UnitedHealth -3% on Medicare audit news&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analog Devices +3% after beating Q2 earnings and revenue estimates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lumen Technologies +9% after AT&amp;amp;T deal for fiber business&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;AT&amp;amp;T flat on Lumen acquisition news&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Snowflake +8% after earnings beat and strong guidance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sunrun -30% on Republican tax bill impact on clean energy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enphase, SolarEdge -17%, Array -10%, Nextracker -4%, First Solar -1% on solar sector selloff&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoom -1% despite earnings beat and solid forecast&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pitney Bowes +9% after naming Kurt Wolf as new CEO&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD bounces.  Price remains in up-and-down low area</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-bounces-price-remains-in-up-and-down-low-area-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:16:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-bounces-price-remains-in-up-and-down-low-area-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;114&quot; data-end=&quot;477&quot;&gt;The USDCAD broke above a key resistance level at 1.3904 on May 8, marking the end of a multi-week consolidation range. Two days later, the pair tested the 200-day moving average near 1.4015, a critical technical barrier. Sellers leaned against that level on back-to-back sessions, preventing a sustained breakout and triggering a reversal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;479&quot; data-end=&quot;845&quot;&gt;By May 14, the price had fallen back to retest the former breakout point at 1.3904. What had served as a ceiling turned into a floor — temporarily. However, that floor gave way in yesterday’s session, with the pair falling back into the prior consolidation zone between 1.37497 and 1.3904, where price had been trapped from April 16 to May 8.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;847&quot; data-end=&quot;1014&quot;&gt;Now, the old support at 1.3904 has reestablished itself as resistance. As long as the pair stays below 1.3904, the bias remains tilted to the downside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1016&quot; data-end=&quot;1425&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, watch 1.38607 for near-term support. This level marked swing highs on May 1, was broken on May 8 during the upside breakout, and acted as a launchpad for the May highs (as indicated by the green circles). In the current session, the latest bounce also stalled at that level. A move below 1.38607 could invite more selling pressure and further bearish momentum.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 PERSON SHOT BY SECURITY GUARDS OUTSIDE CIA HEADQUARTERS IN VIRGINIA -CNBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925539860846170329#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:10:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925539860846170329#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 PERSON SHOT BY SECURITY GUARDS OUTSIDE CIA HEADQUARTERS IN VIRGINIA -CNBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May Belgium business confidence -13.5 vs -14.0 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/may-belgium-business-confidence-135-vs-140-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/may-belgium-business-confidence-135-vs-140-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was -14.7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a leading indicator.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) THE U.S. GOVERNMENT WILL STOP PUTTING NEW PENNIES INTO CIRCULATION BY EARLY NEXT YEAR- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925534828100780044#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:50:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925534828100780044#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE U.S. GOVERNMENT WILL STOP PUTTING NEW PENNIES INTO CIRCULATION BY EARLY NEXT YEAR- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US dollar firms after initial jobless claims, 30-year yields can&apos;t crack 2023 high</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-dollar-firms-after-initial-jobless-claims-30-year-yields-cant-crack-2023-high-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-dollar-firms-after-initial-jobless-claims-30-year-yields-cant-crack-2023-high-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US dollar found some modest bids after initial jobless claims edged lower. The reading of 227K was slightly below the 230K consensus and 229K last week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been no sign of weakening in the US jobs market in the weekly data and that&apos;s likely to firm the Fed&apos;s resolve to wait before cutting rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar rose afterwards, climbing around a dozen pips against the yen, with the euro falling by a similar margin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bond market was another likely culprit. US 30-year yields tested the 2023 high of 5.17% just ahead of the data and reached 5.16% before pulling back a couple basis points. That may have eased some angst about runaway borrowing costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the 2023 high breaks, US long-term borrowing costs will be the highest since 2007 and that will be a tough blow for the housing market in particular.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US JOBLESS CLAIMS -2K TO 227K IN MAY-17 WK; SURVEY 230K

US MAY-10 WEEK CONTINUING CLAIMS +36K TO 1,903,000

US MAY-10 WEEK JOBLESS CLAIMS UNREVISED AT 229K</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925529735695626720#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:30:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925529735695626720#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US JOBLESS CLAIMS -2K TO 227K IN MAY-17 WK; SURVEY 230K&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
US MAY-10 WEEK CONTINUING CLAIMS +36K TO 1,903,000&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
US MAY-10 WEEK JOBLESS CLAIMS UNREVISED AT 229K&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US initial jobless claims 227K vs 230k estimate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-initial-jobless-claims-227k-vs-230k-estimate-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-initial-jobless-claims-227k-vs-230k-estimate-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior week initial jobless claims 229K&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Initial jobless claims 227K vs 230K estimate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;4 week moving average initial jobless claims 231.5K vs 230.5K last week&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior week continuing claims 1.881M revised to 1.867M&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continuing claims 1.903M vs 1.885M estimate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;4- week MA 1,887.5 vs 1,870M last week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The largest increases in initial claims for the week ending May 10 (last week) were in Massachusetts (+3,410), Virginia (+1,272),
Pennsylvania (+595), Illinois (+442), and Nebraska (+395), while the largest decreases were in Michigan (-5,827),
California (-1,861), Ohio (-868), New York (-859), and New Hampshire (-475). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The initial jobless claims data is for the job survey week.  The data is consistent with steady jobs report. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The continuing claims to move back above the 1.9 million level which is the second reading about that level in recent history&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The focus is on interest rates and they are not contributing with the 2 year down -1.9 basis points, but the 10-year up 1.6 basis points at 4.612% (the high yield reached 4.627%). That is the highest level since Feb 12. The high yield for the year was up at 4.809% back on January 13. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada April producer price index -0.8% m/m vs -0.5% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-producer-price-index-08-mm-vs-05-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:30:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-producer-price-index-08-mm-vs-05-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was +0.5%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;PPI y/y % vs 4.7% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raw materials price index -3.0% m/m vs -1.0% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raw materials price index -3.6% y/y vs +3.9% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The odds of a June Bank of Canada rate cut were at 32% before this report.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US 30-YEAR YIELD RISES TO 5.15%, HIGHEST SINCE OCTOBER 2023</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925529119363625450#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:28:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925529119363625450#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US 30-YEAR YIELD RISES TO 5.15%, HIGHEST SINCE OCTOBER 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USD is little changed to start the US session. What does the recent price action say?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-little-changed-to-start-the-us-session-what-does-the-recent-price-action-say-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:25:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-little-changed-to-start-the-us-session-what-does-the-recent-price-action-say-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The USD is mixed, but little changed vs the 3 major currency pairs to kickstart the US session .  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the major pairs:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;EURUSD is down -0.16% (higher USD)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;USDJPY is also down by -0.26% (lower USD)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;GBPUSD is unchanged.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest mover is the NZDUSD which has taken a tumble in the European morning session and is now down -0.59% (higher USD). The AUDUSD is down -0.20% (higher USD). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. House of Representatives narrowly passed the Tax and Spending Reconciliation Bill by a 215–214 vote, with Republicans Massie and Davidson voting against it and HFC Chair Harris abstaining by voting &quot;Present.&quot; Representatives Schweikert and Garbarino did not vote. The legislation now heads to various Senate committees and will eventually be debated and voted on in the full Senate—a process expected to take several weeks. If it passes, former President Trump will have his big beautiful bill, but will the markets like it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US yields are voting and it is not supportive.  On the longer end, yields moved up double digits yesterday with the yield curve steepening sharply. Looking at the treasury curve, the yield curve is steeper again with the 2-year down -2.7 basis points, while the 10 year is up 1.6 basis points. The 2-10 year spread is up to 62.5 basis points, just a few basis points from the 64.8 basis point recent high (and highest level since January 2022) reached on April 21.  The snapshot shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield 3.990%, -2.7 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.142%, -1.4 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10 year yield 4.612%, +1.6 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30 yar yield 5.144%, +5.6 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the US stock indices, the earlier pre-market gains are being eroded fast with the Nasdaq moving from about +40 points to down -92 points over just the last hour of trading&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow dow -221 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P down -28 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq -92 points.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil is down -$1.00 at $60.63. OPEC+ is discussing an increase in production for July. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold is down -$5.13 or -0.14% at $3312.60&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin is up $1000 at $110,704. A new record high was reached $111,888 before a modest rotation lower.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: SEND THIS BILL TO MY DESK AS SOON AS POSSIBLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925528247883763790#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:24:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925528247883763790#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: SEND THIS BILL TO MY DESK AS SOON AS POSSIBLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: GREAT JOB BY SPEAKER MIKE JOHNSON, HOUSE LEADERSHIP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925528207756853501#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 12:24:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925528207756853501#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: GREAT JOB BY SPEAKER MIKE JOHNSON, HOUSE LEADERSHIP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Waller: If tariffs are closer to 10%, then economy is good shape for 2H</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-waller-if-tariffs-are-closer-to-10-then-economy-is-good-shape-for-2h-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:55:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-waller-if-tariffs-are-closer-to-10-then-economy-is-good-shape-for-2h-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets are watching fiscal policy and have concerns.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets are looking for more fiscal discipline.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed won&apos;t buy bonds in primary auctions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hard data shows economy doing quite well, scant sign of tariff impact so far.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If tariffs are closer to 10%, then economy is good shape for 2H.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If tariffs settle down, Fed could be in position to cut in later part of the year.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Much more optimistic now relative to last month on tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Very hopeful the current path of administration is a good one.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Firms are pausing but not cancelling plans.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continue to believe tariffs will be a one time price increase.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Standard Fed playbook is to look through one time price impact.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Doesn&apos;t see much from tariffs to drive inflation persistently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Everyone in markets expected more fiscal restraint from tax bill.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As long as economy gets back on good path, could reinvigorate demand for US assets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shouldn&apos;t be new to those who read his April speech where he laid out his two scenarios. His scenario where tariffs settle around 10% on average or less is playing out, so he is less inclined to cut immediately and will wait for the second part of the year (which is still bad for long term bonds as inflation concerns remain high).&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB Accounts: Increased confidence inflation would return to target over the medium term.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecb-accounts-increased-confidence-inflation-would-return-to-target-over-the-medium-term-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:35:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecb-accounts-increased-confidence-inflation-would-return-to-target-over-the-medium-term-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Members expressed increased confidence that inflation would return to target over the medium term.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Members attached a higher probability to the possibility that the trade shock would be inflationary beyond the short term.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Increased confidence that inflation would return to target in line with the March baseline projections.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This pointed to upside risks to inflation in the medium to long term.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty, the appreciation of the Euro and the decline in oil and gas prices, would further dampen the inflation outlook in the near term.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A cut at the present meeting could be seen as frontloading.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A few members noted that they could have felt comfortable with a 50 basis point rate cut.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Market-based indicators pointed to a tightening of financial conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wanted to avoid the perception that the neutral level of interest rates was the end point of the current cycle.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Disinflation to dominate in short term due to Euro.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Euro Area had built up some resistance to shocks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Euro seem to turn into safe-haven currency.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Inflation was expected to hover close to the inflation target of 2% for the remainder of the year.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the equivalent of the FOMC Meeting Minutes. It&apos;s not a market moving release and the data is stale by the time it gets released.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full accounts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecb.europa.eu/press/accounts/2025/html/ecb.mg250522~31b2c664d4.en.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive European FX news wrap: The US House passes Trump&apos;s tax bill</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-the-us-house-passes-trumps-tax-bill-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:30:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-the-us-house-passes-trumps-tax-bill-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-minister-no-change-to-japans-stance-of-demanding-elimination-of-us-tariffs-20250522/&quot;&gt;Japan Eco Minister: No change to Japan&apos;s stance of demanding elimination of US tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-passes-the-trump-tax-bill-and-sends-it-to-the-senate-20250522/&quot;&gt;The US House passes the Trump tax bill and sends it to the Senate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-holzmann-the-euros-importance-as-a-global-currency-is-set-to-increase-20250522/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Holzmann: The Euro&apos;s importance as a global currency is set to increase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-vujcic-eurozone-growth-positive-but-low-20250522/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Vujcic: Eurozone growth positive but low&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rbas-hauser-australian-exporters-upbeat-about-resilience-of-china-demand-20250522/&quot;&gt;RBA&apos;s Hauser: Australian exporters upbeat about resilience of China demand&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-may-flash-services-pmi-502-vs-500-expected-20250522/&quot;&gt;UK May flash services PMI 50.2 vs 50.0 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-ifo-business-climate-index-875-vs-874-expected-20250522/&quot;&gt;Germany May Ifo business climate index 87.5 vs 87.4 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-flash-services-pmi-489-vs-503-expected-20250522/&quot;&gt;Eurozone May flash services PMI 48.9 vs 50.3 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-flash-manufacturing-pmi-488-vs-489-expected-20250522/&quot;&gt;Germany May flash manufacturing PMI 48.8 vs 48.9 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-flash-services-pmi-474-vs-475-expected-20250522/&quot;&gt;France May flash services PMI 47.4 vs 47.5 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-business-confidence-97-vs-99-expected-20250522/&quot;&gt;France May business confidence 97 vs 99 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/opec-discusses-another-411k-bd-output-hike-in-july-20250522/&quot;&gt;OPEC+ discusses another 411K B/D output hike in July&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/boj-noguchi-recent-rise-in-long-term-rates-likely-wont-have-impact-on-bond-taper-plan-20250522/&quot;&gt;BoJ Noguchi: Recent rise in long-term rates likely won&apos;t have impact on bond taper plan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-mimura-says-japan-us-did-not-discuss-fx-levels-at-finance-ministers-meeting-20250522/&quot;&gt;Japan&apos;s Mimura says Japan, US did not discuss FX levels at finance ministers&apos; meeting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/north-korea-fires-multiple-cruise-missiles-toward-east-sea-20250522/&quot;&gt;North Korea fires multiple cruise missiles toward East Sea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been a more lively session in terms of data releases as we got the Flash PMIs for Eurozone and the UK. The data was overall disappointing but there were some glimpse of improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main event was the US House vote on Trump&apos;s tax bill which passed and sent long term Treasury yields to new highs. The US 30yr yield is now close to the 2023 high. US indices reacted positively to the news but eventually gave everything back. The US Dollar weakened. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, the focus will switch to the US Flash PMIs where business sentiment and inflation details will be scanned. The market is pricing 51 bps of easing for the Fed in 2025 but that could be lowered with good economic data or lack of progress on inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Eco Minister: No change to Japan&apos;s stance of demanding elimination of US tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-minister-no-change-to-japans-stance-of-demanding-elimination-of-us-tariffs-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:06:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-minister-no-change-to-japans-stance-of-demanding-elimination-of-us-tariffs-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan&apos;s Economy Minister Akazawa is scheduled to visit the US from Friday-Sunday for tariff negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US House passes the Trump tax bill and sends it to the Senate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-passes-the-trump-tax-bill-and-sends-it-to-the-senate-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:57:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-passes-the-trump-tax-bill-and-sends-it-to-the-senate-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US House passes the Trump tax bill and sends it to the Senate. That&apos;s a win for Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion to recommit failed, now the House is voting on the tax bill</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/motion-to-recommit-failed-now-the-house-is-voting-on-the-tax-bill-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:51:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/motion-to-recommit-failed-now-the-house-is-voting-on-the-tax-bill-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Motion to recommit failed, now the House is voting on the tax bill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow live &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mXUsahxtDJI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US House is voting</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-is-voting-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:29:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-is-voting-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US House is voting...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First the motion to recommit, then comes passage of the reconciliation package.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;h/t &lt;a href=&quot;https://x.com/JakeSherman/status/1925497874097356962&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Jake Sherman&lt;/a&gt; on X&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can follow live &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mXUsahxtDJI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House to vote on the &quot;big, beautiful bill&quot; shortly</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-to-vote-on-the-big-beautiful-bill-shortly-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:10:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-to-vote-on-the-big-beautiful-bill-shortly-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Schedule per Haley Talbot (CNN) post on X (ET time):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Approx 5:30 – 6:00 am, vote on the following:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1) Motion to Recommit
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2) Passage of H.R. 1 - One Big Beautiful Bill Act
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3) H.R. 1701 - Strategic Ports Reporting Act 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walk off the floor: 6:00 – 6:30am 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recess begins, members return June 3rd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can follow live&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mXUsahxtDJI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt; here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Holzmann: The Euro&apos;s importance as a global currency is set to increase</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-holzmann-the-euros-importance-as-a-global-currency-is-set-to-increase-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:46:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-holzmann-the-euros-importance-as-a-global-currency-is-set-to-increase-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Euro&apos;s importance as a global currency is set to increase.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Frequent shifts in trade policy have fuelled economic uncertainty, undermining stability and resulting in tangible losses for all parties involved.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It makes economic forecasts more complex and policy decision more challenging in an already uncertain environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These policies certainly lead to volatility in the short term.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
