<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs scale back on Fed rate cut projections amid latest tariff developments</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-scale-back-on-fed-rate-cut-projections-amid-latest-tariff-developments-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 04:19:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-scale-back-on-fed-rate-cut-projections-amid-latest-tariff-developments-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Amid the latest agreement struck between the US and China, Goldman Sachs is now seeing the probability of a recession in the US over the next 12 months at 35%. Their previous projection was 45%. Given that, they are now expecting the Fed to only deliver one rate cut this year as compared to their previous forecast of three rate cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Meanwhile, the firm also raises its year-end target for the S&amp;amp;P 500 to 6,100 now - up from 5,900 previously.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 13 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-13-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:54:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-13-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There aren&apos;t any major expiries to take note of on the board for today. As such, traders will be sticking to the broader risk mood as the key driver of trading sentiment. After the bustling gains in risk yesterday, we&apos;re seeing things settle down a bit. And that&apos;s also leading to some cooling off in the dollar gains so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That&apos;s the main factor that will drive price action in the session ahead, to see if the mood music from yesterday will continue or if we&apos;re going to settle down to digest the situation a bit more. But coming up later, there is the US CPI report to watch out for as an added key risk event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBS sees better growth prospects for China as tariffs impact eases</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ubs-sees-better-growth-prospects-for-china-as-tariffs-impact-eases-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:23:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ubs-sees-better-growth-prospects-for-china-as-tariffs-impact-eases-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With that, UBS is forecasting the Chinese economy to grow between 3.7% to 4.0% in 2025. That is an upgrade from their previous forecast of 3.4% &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ubs-has-cut-its-china-gdp-growth-forecast-to-34-for-2025-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; last month.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China  President Xi Jinping says that tariff and trade wars produce no winners</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-jinping-says-that-tariff-and-trade-wars-produce-no-winners-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 02:54:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-jinping-says-that-tariff-and-trade-wars-produce-no-winners-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping stated that tariff and trade wars produce no winners, emphasizing that global peace, stability, and development can only be achieved through international cooperation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;He warned that acts of bullying and domination will ultimately lead to isolation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;62&quot; data-end=&quot;174&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;64&quot; data-end=&quot;174&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China backs Latin America and the Caribbean in strengthening their role in global multilateral institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;175&quot; data-end=&quot;317&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;177&quot; data-end=&quot;317&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Beijing remains committed to mutual support with Latin American countries on key issues tied to their core interests and major priorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;318&quot; data-end=&quot;470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;320&quot; data-end=&quot;470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China aims to expand collaboration with the region across sectors including infrastructure, agriculture, food security, energy, and mineral resources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;318&quot; data-end=&quot;470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;320&quot; data-end=&quot;470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China to offer 66 billion yuan credit line to support Latin America and Caribbean countries:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping is delivering a speech at the opening ceremony of the fourth ministerial meeting of the China-CELAC (Community of Latin American and Caribbean States) Forum in Beijing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Yen rebound on Kato comment; China signal CNY support</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-yen-rebound-on-kato-comment-china-signal-cny-support-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 02:48:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-yen-rebound-on-kato-comment-china-signal-cny-support-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-sasac-calls-for-advancement-of-major-projects-aligned-with-national-priorities-20250513/&quot;&gt;ICYMI China SASAC calls for advancement of major projects aligned with national priorities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-is-building-megaports-in-south-america-to-feed-its-need-for-crops-20250513/&quot;&gt;China is building megaports in South America to feed its need for crops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-dep-gov-uchida-says-there-is-upside-downside-risk-from-us-tariffs-on-japans-prices-20250513/&quot;&gt;BoJ Dep Gov Uchida says there is upside &amp;amp; downside risk from US tariffs on Japan&apos;s prices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-april-business-confidence-1-prior-4-20250513/&quot;&gt;Australian April business confidence -1 (prior -4)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-central-rate-at-71991-vs-estimate-at-72180-20250513/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY central rate at 7.1991 (vs. estimate at 7.2180)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-wants-to-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250513/&quot;&gt;Japan finance minister Kato wants to discuss FX with Bessent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-westpac-consumer-sentiment-may-2025-22-prior-60-20250513/&quot;&gt;Australia Westpac Consumer Sentiment (May 2025) +2.2% (prior -6.0%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-april-summary-shows-uncertainty-a-high-priority-discussion-item-20250512/&quot;&gt;BoJ April Summary  shows uncertainty a high priority discussion item&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-foreign-minister-meets-brazil-counterpart-in-beijing-20250512/&quot;&gt;China’s foreign minister meets Brazil counterpart in Beijing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/the-trump-put-is-alive-and-well-says-bofa-after-us-china-trade-ceasefire-boosts-stocks-20250512/&quot;&gt;&quot;The Trump Put is alive and well&quot; says BofA after US - China trade ceasefire boosts stocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-representative-greer-if-things-dont-work-out-china-tariffs-can-go-back-up-20250512/&quot;&gt;U.S. Trade Representative Greer: If things don’t work out, China tariffs can go back up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-consumer-spending-shows-its-biggest-increase-since-june-2023-20250512/&quot;&gt;UK April consumer spending shows its biggest increase since June 2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/deutsche-sees-first-fed-cut-in-december-despite-trade-relief-20250512/&quot;&gt;Deutsche sees first Fed cut in December despite trade relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/citi-trims-near-term-gold-target-sees-consolidation-at-30003300oz-20250512/&quot;&gt;Citi trims near-term gold target, sees consolidation at $3,000–$3,300/oz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-citi-forecasts-a-july-federal-reserve-rate-cut-instead-of-in-june-20250512/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Citi forecasts a July Federal Reserve rate cut instead of in June&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-massive-across-the-board-on-trade-war-relief-20250512/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Massive across the board on trade war relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trumps-hassett-says-there-are-24-countries-lined-up-for-trade-talks-over-the-next-weeks-20250512/&quot;&gt;Trump&apos;s Hassett says there are 24 countries lined up for trade talks over the next weeks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expect-a-federal-reserve-rate-cut-now-in-december-instead-of-in-july-20250512/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs expect a Federal Reserve rate cut now in December, instead of in July&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-close-sharply-higher-on-us-china-tariff-news-20250512/&quot;&gt;US stocks close sharply higher on US China tariff news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-tuesday-13-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250512/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Tuesday, 13 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;216&quot; data-end=&quot;305&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;After Monday’s sharp swings, Asia markets settled into a more subdued session on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;307&quot; data-end=&quot;731&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Japanese yen found some relief, rebounding from early highs above 148.40 to around 147.75. The move was spurred by comments from Japan’s Finance Minister Kato, who said he hopes to speak with U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent on FX matters during the upcoming G7 meetings in Banff, Canada (May 20–22). The remarks were seen as a subtle warning about the yen’s recent weakness and a possible prelude to verbal intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;733&quot; data-end=&quot;1181&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Earlier in the session, the Bank of Japan released its “Summary of Opinions” from the April 30–May 1 policy meeting, with members emphasizing heightened uncertainty—particularly around U.S. trade policy. The tone underscored the Bank’s cautious stance, suggesting limited scope for near-term action until global developments stabilise. Since then, the U.S.-China trade talks have yielded a modest tariff rollback and a 90-day pause in new measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1183&quot; data-end=&quot;1379&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;BoJ Deputy Governor Uchida echoed the theme of uncertainty in separate remarks, but reiterated that the Bank still expects to raise rates gradually if the economy and inflation evolve as forecast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1381&quot; data-end=&quot;1596&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In China, the yuan strengthened after the People’s Bank of China set the daily USD/CNY reference rate below 7.2 for the first time since April 7, signalling support for currency stability amid easing trade tensions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1598&quot; data-end=&quot;1817&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Australian data offered a slightly improved but still cautious tone. Consumer confidence edged higher from previous lows, while business confidence ticked up modestly. Business conditions, however, slipped on the month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1819&quot; data-end=&quot;1898&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Elsewhere in FX, major currency pairs excluding the yen traded in tight ranges.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI China SASAC calls for advancement of major projects aligned with national priorities</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-sasac-calls-for-advancement-of-major-projects-aligned-with-national-priorities-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 02:24:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-sasac-calls-for-advancement-of-major-projects-aligned-with-national-priorities-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;173&quot; data-end=&quot;490&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China’s State-owned Assets Supervision and Administration Commission (SASAC) has called on central state-owned enterprises (SOEs) to accelerate innovation and strengthen their role in strategic and emerging industries, as part of efforts to meet 2025 targets and prepare for the 15th Five-Year Plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;492&quot; data-end=&quot;851&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;At an expanded Party Committee meeting, SASAC emphasized the need to implement key directives from the CPC Central Committee and the State Council, urging SOEs to focus on high-quality development and national strategic priorities. Officials called for a fact-based review of SOE performance under the current 14th Five-Year Plan to help guide future reforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;853&quot; data-end=&quot;1193&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Commission highlighted growing external uncertainties and shifts in global technology and industry, stressing the importance of forward-looking strategies in SOE reform, governance, and Party building. It also urged enterprises to enhance their contribution to “new quality productive forces” and prioritize localization in key sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1195&quot; data-end=&quot;1462&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;SOEs were directed to optimize their presence in strategic emerging and future industries, accelerate breakthroughs in critical and core technologies, and reinforce their role in supporting national security, industrial resilience, and technological self-sufficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1464&quot; data-end=&quot;1685&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;SASAC also called for greater momentum in advancing major national projects and leveraging SOEs’ capabilities in strategic, foundational, and frontier sectors to consolidate the leadership role of the state-owned economy.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is building megaports in South America to feed its need for crops</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-is-building-megaports-in-south-america-to-feed-its-need-for-crops-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 01:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-is-building-megaports-in-south-america-to-feed-its-need-for-crops-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China is building megaports in South America to feed its need for crops - China has reassured its citizens they would have enough to eat without U.S. crops. It will have to unclog Latin America’s largest port first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wall Street Journal is gated,&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/world/americas/china-is-building-megaports-in-south-america-to-feed-its-need-for-crops-8831748e&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt; link here&lt;/a&gt; if you can access. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China state grain trader Cofco plans world’s biggest export terminal in Brazil to substitute U.S. soybeans and other foodstuffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China is investing in South American infrastructure to secure agricultural imports.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Santos, Brazil’s main port for exports to China, is struggling with capacity and infrastructure.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Brazil’s fertilizer supply issues and soil nutrient depletion pose challenges to increased crop production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I speculated earlier on this, it seems pretty obvious. What else is China gonna do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-foreign-minister-meets-brazil-counterpart-in-beijing-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China’s foreign minister meets Brazil counterpart in Beijing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;And, last week:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-intends-to-buy-around-us900-million-of-soybeans-corn-vegetable-oil-from-argentina-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China intends to buy around US$900 million of soybeans, corn, vegetable oil from Argentina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoJ Dep Gov Uchida says there is upside &amp; downside risk from US tariffs on Japan&apos;s prices</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-dep-gov-uchida-says-there-is-upside-downside-risk-from-us-tariffs-on-japans-prices-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 01:48:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-dep-gov-uchida-says-there-is-upside-downside-risk-from-us-tariffs-on-japans-prices-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bank of Japan deputy governor Uchida:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US tariffs put downward pressure on Japan’s economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There are both upside, downside risks from US tariffs on Japan’s prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s economic growth to slow to around potential before accelerating again as overseas growth resumes moderate growth path&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s output gap to remain around current levels, after which it will resume improvement toward end of BOJ’s 3-year projection period through fiscal 2027&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It sounds like Uchida is uncertain of where to go with policy from here? At least in the near to medium term. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ahh, here is some more, a little more confident on hikes now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BOJ expected to keep raising interest rates if economy, prices improve as we project&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s underlying inflation, medium- and long-term inflation expectations will likely stagnate temporarily&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But even during that period, wages are expected to continue rising as Japan’s job market very tight, firms likely to continue passing on rising labour costs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Once global economy resumes uptrend, Japan’s economy likely to recover and heighten underlying inflation, inflation expectations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty surrounding our forecasts is extremely high, so we will determine without pre-conception whether our forecasts will materialise&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong yen has negative impact on exports, big manufacturers’ profits but improves households’ real income and pushes up retailers’ profits via falling import costs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid FX moves make it difficult for firms to set business plans, heighten uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, USD/JPY has dribbled lower since Kato&apos;s verbal intervention efforts a little while ago:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-wants-to-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan finance minister Kato wants to discuss FX with Bessent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian April business confidence -1 (prior -4)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-april-business-confidence-1-prior-4-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 01:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-april-business-confidence-1-prior-4-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;National Australia Bank business survey for April 2025 (survey conducted at the end of that month)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;business confidence -1 (prior -4)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;business conditions +2 (prior +3), well below the long-run average&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the sub measures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; sales index held relatively steady at +5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;employment relatively steady at +4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;profitability down 4 points to -4, NAB point to higher purchase costs pressuring margins&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;fall of 6 points in the capital spending index to a below average +1, NAB says firms staying away from new investment due to uncertainty over US trade policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Reserve Bank of Australia is expected to cut interest rates again when it meets on May 20. This should help support sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC sets USD/ CNY central rate at 7.1991 (vs. estimate at 7.2180)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-central-rate-at-71991-vs-estimate-at-72180-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 01:15:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-central-rate-at-71991-vs-estimate-at-72180-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mid-rate today is the strongest (for CNY) since April 7. It&apos;s the first setting below 7.2 since that date also. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous close was 7.2075&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC injected 180bn yuan via 7-day reverse repos at 1.40%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;405bn yuan mature today
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;net drains 225bn yuan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan finance minister Kato wants to discuss FX with Bessent</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-wants-to-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:44:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-wants-to-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan finance minister Kato &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Making preparations to join G7 meetings in Banff&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If have a chance, hope to have a meeting with U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent to discuss forex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Possible to discuss tariff deal if meeting with Bessent is realised&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will closely monitor U.S.-China tariff deal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Won’t comment on forex levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will closely watch out markets developments caused by U.S.-China tariff deal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yen lost ground since the weekend&apos;s US-China tariff trim-and-pause:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-massive-across-the-board-on-trade-war-relief-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Massive across the board on trade war relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-us-china-strike-deal-to-lower-tariffs-after-talks-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;ForexLive European FX news wrap: US, China strike deal to lower tariffs after talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Westpac Consumer Sentiment (May 2025) +2.2% (prior -6.0%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-westpac-consumer-sentiment-may-2025-22-prior-60-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:32:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-westpac-consumer-sentiment-may-2025-22-prior-60-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Australia Westpac Consumer Sentiment stays deeply pessimistic (below 100)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;+2.2% m/m in May to 92.1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior -6% to 90.1&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+12% y/y &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;WPAC says confidence was given a boost by &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;a clear election win result&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;a more confident view on the prospect of interest rate cuts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier from Australia we had the weekly ANZ-Roy Morgan Australian consumer confidence index:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;+0.8 points last week&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;hit an 11-week high of 88.3 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;inflation expectations are part of the survey, these fell 0.4% to 4.5%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Reserve Bank of Australia is on track to cut its cash rate next week. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC is expected to set the USD/CNY reference rate at 7.2180 – Reuters estimate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72180-reuters-estimate-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:23:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72180-reuters-estimate-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China USD/CNY reference rate is due around 0115 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news ICYMI:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-massive-across-the-board-on-trade-war-relief-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Massive across the board on trade war relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-us-china-strike-deal-to-lower-tariffs-after-talks-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;ForexLive European FX news wrap: US, China strike deal to lower tariffs after talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How the process works:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type=&quot;disc&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily midpoint setting: Each morning, the PBOC sets a midpoint for the yuan against a basket of currencies, primarily the US dollar. The central bank takes into account factors such as market supply and demand, economic indicators, and international currency market fluctuations. The midpoint serves as a reference point for that day&apos;s trading.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The trading band: The PBOC allows the yuan to move within a specified range around the midpoint. The trading band is set at +/- 2%, meaning the yuan could appreciate or depreciate by a maximum of 2% from the midpoint during a single trading day. This range is subject to change by the PBOC based on economic conditions and policy objectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intervention: If the yuan&apos;s value approaches the limit of the trading band or experiences excessive volatility, the PBOC may intervene in the foreign exchange market by buying or selling the yuan to stabilize its value. This helps maintain a controlled and gradual adjustment of the currency&apos;s value.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoJ April Summary  shows uncertainty a high priority discussion item</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-april-summary-shows-uncertainty-a-high-priority-discussion-item-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:55:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-april-summary-shows-uncertainty-a-high-priority-discussion-item-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bank of Japan Summary of Opinions at the Monetary Policy Meeting on April 30 and May 1, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.boj.or.jp/en/mopo/mpmsche_minu/opinion_2025/opi250501.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;full text is here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Headlines via Reuters:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: BOJ likely to keep raising interest rates in accordance with improvements in economy, prices
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: No change to BOJ’s rate-hike stance as real interest rates deeply negative but must scrutinise risks
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: Uncertainty surrounding economy, price outlook high, likelihood of achieving price goal not as high as in past&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: BoJ has little choice but to take wait-and-see stance until developments surrounding U.S. trade policy stabilise to some extent&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: BoJ will enter temporary pause in rate hikes but shouldn’t slide into excessive pessimism, must guide policy nimbly and flexibly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: Chance of Japan’s underlying inflation faltering is small&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: U.S. trade policy development could turn positive or negative any time, which means BOJ’s policy path could change any time as well&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: Our projections have been severely jolted by US trade policy with higher US tariffs likely to weigh on Japan’s economy, prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: Must be mindful of upside risks to prices if global supply chains are disrupted&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One member said: From long-term perspective, U.S. tariff policy and ensuing uncertainty likely won’t affect Japan’s underlying inflation, potential growth rate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Putting all of this together it appears the BoJ is intent on hiking rates, but the question is when. Given the developments over the weekend, is the 90-day trim-and-pause with China enough to give the BoJ confidence to hike?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;The Bank of Japan (BOJ) releases a &quot;Summary of Opinions&quot; after each monetary policy meeting. It serves as a record of the discussion and views of the Policy Board members on various economic and financial issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key points about the Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The summary includes the views of the Policy Board members on economic conditions, both domestically and globally. This includes assessments of economic growth, inflation, and employment trends, among other indicators.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The summary also outlines the Policy Board members&apos; views on the effectiveness of the BOJ&apos;s current monetary policy measures, including interest rate policy, asset purchases, and yield curve control. Members may discuss the pros and cons of these policies and their potential impact on the economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The summary includes discussions on the outlook for monetary policy and the potential risks to the economy. Board members may express their views on the appropriate timing and direction of future policy changes, as well as the potential impact of external factors such as global economic conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The summary also includes any dissenting views among the Policy Board members. If a member disagrees with the majority view on a particular issue, they may express their own opinion and rationale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a few week&apos;s time we&apos;ll get the Minutes of this meeting. The Minutes are a more detailed record of the discussions and decisions made during the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Minutes include a more complete record of the views expressed, including any dissents or alternative opinions that may not be included in the summary.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Summary of Opinions is typically released a few days after the policy meeting, while the Minutes are published about a month later. This means that the Summary of Opinions can provide more up-to-date information on the BOJ&apos;s current stance and view on the economy and monetary policy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Summary of Opinions is usually written in a more accessible language, making it easier to understand the BOJ&apos;s views on monetary policy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Minutes, on the other hand, are often more technical and may require a deeper understanding of economics and financial markets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Summary of Opinions is typically shorter than the Minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s foreign minister meets Brazil counterpart in Beijing</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-foreign-minister-meets-brazil-counterpart-in-beijing-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:46:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-foreign-minister-meets-brazil-counterpart-in-beijing-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China’s foreign minister meets Brazil counterpart in Beijing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China’s foreign minister, meeting Brazil counterpart: both agreed to uphold multilateralism, uphold universally recognized international rules, jointly defend the legitimate rights and interests of the global South&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;exchanged views on the Ukraine crisis, expressed support for direct dialogue and negotiation between Russia and Ukraine&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reuters with the headline points on the meeting. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;The Trump Put is alive and well&quot; says BofA after US - China trade ceasefire boosts stocks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/the-trump-put-is-alive-and-well-says-bofa-after-us-china-trade-ceasefire-boosts-stocks-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:28:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/the-trump-put-is-alive-and-well-says-bofa-after-us-china-trade-ceasefire-boosts-stocks-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bank of America analysts suggest that Monday’s market rally, sparked by news of a U.S.-China tariff agreement, may reflect the so-called “Trump put” — the notion that Trump will act to limit stock market declines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; “The recent news flow on trade suggests that de-escalation is likely to continue.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;The Trump put is alive and well.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“The administration is incentivised to avoid a recession, and more trade deals are likely forthcoming.”
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysts go on to day that despite recent deals with China and the U.K., the 10% baseline tariff introduced on April 2 is “likely here to stay.” That view was echoed by Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick, who said Sunday that the baseline tariff is expected “to be in place for the foreseeable future.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets are very forgiving. They&apos;ll punish you for stuffing things up, but if you move to fix it, all is forgiven! Tariffs are still the highest since WW2 so there is still some work to be done.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Trade Representative Greer: If things don’t work out, China tariffs can go back up</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-representative-greer-if-things-dont-work-out-china-tariffs-can-go-back-up-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:21:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-representative-greer-if-things-dont-work-out-china-tariffs-can-go-back-up-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;U.S. Trade Representative Greer:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China has agreed to remove countermeasures
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Outcome of China tariff talks ‘pragmatic’
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If things don’t work out, China tariffs can go back up &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greer sounds like the sad sack in the room. Markets liked the news:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ICYMI:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-massive-across-the-board-on-trade-war-relief-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Massive across the board on trade war relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-us-china-strike-deal-to-lower-tariffs-after-talks-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;ForexLive European FX news wrap: US, China strike deal to lower tariffs after talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. TRADE REPRESENTATIVE GREER: CHINA HAS AGREED TO REMOVE COUNTERMEASURES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922068851912552645#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:18:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922068851912552645#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. TRADE REPRESENTATIVE GREER: CHINA HAS AGREED TO REMOVE COUNTERMEASURES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK April consumer spending shows its biggest increase since June 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-consumer-spending-shows-its-biggest-increase-since-june-2023-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:08:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-consumer-spending-shows-its-biggest-increase-since-june-2023-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;146&quot; data-end=&quot;341&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;UK consumers delivered a strong rebound in spending last month, with April retail sales jumping sharply thanks to Easter timing and unusually sunny weather.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;343&quot; data-end=&quot;1348&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;343&quot; data-end=&quot;519&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;345&quot; data-end=&quot;519&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The British Retail Consortium reported a 7.0% year-on-year rise in total retail sales, up from 1.1% in March — the strongest annual gain for any month since the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;520&quot; data-end=&quot;588&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;522&quot; data-end=&quot;588&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Like-for-like sales rose 6.8%, compared to just 0.9% in March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;589&quot; data-end=&quot;737&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;591&quot; data-end=&quot;737&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Clothing sales were a standout, driven by the sunniest April on record since 1910&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;738&quot; data-end=&quot;840&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;740&quot; data-end=&quot;840&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Averaging March and April to smooth Easter-related distortions, sales were up 4.3% year-on-year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;843&quot; data-end=&quot;1032&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Separately, Barclaycard data showed consumer card spending rose 4.5% year-on-year, the largest increase since June 2023 and the first time in over two years that spending growth outpaced inflation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;343&quot; data-end=&quot;1348&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1033&quot; data-end=&quot;1186&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1035&quot; data-end=&quot;1186&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;household confidence remained steady, with 70% of consumers feeling stable about their finances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche sees first Fed cut in December despite trade relief</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/deutsche-sees-first-fed-cut-in-december-despite-trade-relief-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/deutsche-sees-first-fed-cut-in-december-despite-trade-relief-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;A significant reduction in U.S.-China trade barriers may ease the risk of a severe supply-driven inflation shock. However, Deutsche Bank economists caution that inflation remains persistent enough to keep the Federal Reserve from rushing into rate cuts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the trade war is de-escalating, &quot;policies are likely to keep inflation at uncomfortably high levels for the Fed,&quot; the analysts note.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; &quot;This announcement therefore reinforces our view that the Fed is going to be slow to cut rates this year.&quot; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deutsche continues to expect the Fed’s first rate cut to come no earlier than December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expect-a-federal-reserve-rate-cut-now-in-december-instead-of-in-july-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs expect a Federal Reserve rate cut now in December, instead of in July&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-citi-forecasts-a-july-federal-reserve-rate-cut-instead-of-in-june-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Citi forecasts a July Federal Reserve rate cut instead of in June&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citi trims near-term gold target, sees consolidation at $3,000–$3,300/oz</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/citi-trims-near-term-gold-target-sees-consolidation-at-30003300oz-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:59:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/citi-trims-near-term-gold-target-sees-consolidation-at-30003300oz-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;
Citi has lowered its 0–3 month gold price target to $3,150/oz, down from a previous forecast, citing expectations of consolidation following recent gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analysts at the bank now anticipate the metal will trade in a range of $3,000 to $3,300/oz in the near term&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite today&apos;s fall, support for gold is continuing with ongoing macro uncertainty and central bank demand among the drivers. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI - Citi forecasts a July Federal Reserve rate cut instead of in June</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-citi-forecasts-a-july-federal-reserve-rate-cut-instead-of-in-june-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:43:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-citi-forecasts-a-july-federal-reserve-rate-cut-instead-of-in-june-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Citigroup economists have moved their forecast for the next Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) rate cut to July, from June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the announcement that the US will reduce its 145% tariff rate on Chinese goods to 30% for 90 days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Citi expects cuts at each meeting between July and January, totalling 125 basis points. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This call from Citi is very much at odds with that from Goldman Sachs:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expect-a-federal-reserve-rate-cut-now-in-december-instead-of-in-july-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs expect a Federal Reserve rate cut now in December, instead of in July&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a market! &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Massive across the board on trade war relief</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-massive-across-the-board-on-trade-war-relief-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:25:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-massive-across-the-board-on-trade-war-relief-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-we-achieved-a-total-reset-with-china-20250512/&quot;&gt;Trump: We achieved a total reset with China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-with-more-on-china-i-think-we-will-have-a-deal-20250512/&quot;&gt;Trump with more on China: I think we will have a deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolbee-tariffs-on-china-would-still-have-a-stagflationary-impulse-20250512/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Goolbee: Tariffs on China would still have a stagflationary impulse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/fed-senior-loan-officer-opinion-survey-on-bank-lending-practices-released-20250512/&quot;&gt;Fed: Senior Loan Officer Opinion Survey on Bank Lending Practices released&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-federal-budget-258b-vs-256b-expected-20250512/&quot;&gt;US April federal budget +258B vs +256B expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-we-shouldnt-overreact-to-individual-announcements-20250512/&quot;&gt;ECBs Nagel: We shouldn&apos;t overreact to individual announcements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-taylor-we-are-a-long-way-from-neutral-level-of-interest-rates-20250512/&quot;&gt;BOE Taylor: We are a long way from neutral level of interest rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kugler-trade-policy-shifting-but-still-likely-to-lead-to-higher-prices-and-less-gdp-20250512/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Kugler: Trade policy shifting but still likely to lead to higher prices and less GDP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 up 3.3%, Nasdaq up 4.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold down $90 to $3233&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude oil up 94-cents to $61.96&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields up 9.8 bps to 4.47%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;USD leads, JPY lags&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a huge day in terms of market moves, as you can see from the bullet points above. In terms of news flow though it was light in North American trade as the data and Fedspeak calendar was mostly bare. Trump did a victory lap and showed no sign of hesitancy or reversing his position. We can only hope that he&apos;s fallen in love with green on the tape once again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s some irony in celebrating a &apos;total reset&apos; when it was Trump that lit the fire six weeks ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t think anyone in markets has a great deal of confidence in where this is all headed or what will come next but for now there is a clear push to de-escalate. If you take a longer view, there&apos;s a good argument that the early moves were an attempt to stake out a minimalist negotiating position in order to negotiate back to a 10% tariff that at least some countries (like the UK) will swallow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were surely be more bumps in the road and there was some early profit taking in stock markets before the late bids re-emerged. The FX market was steadier though with USD/JPY barely backing off after rising above 148.00. The big moves in most pairs came today before European trading though we did see some continued selling of commodity currencies again the dollar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big losers on the day were CHF and JPY, which is what you would expect in this environment. The market feels much better about the chances for global GDP growth and a re-coupling of world&apos;s two-largest economies in the 90 days ahead. I certainly don&apos;t believe that all the angst about Trump has dissipated but it&apos;s fair to price in something of Trump put again. I don&apos;t think it ever had to be this volatile but Trump has never been a stranger to drama.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *COINBASE GLOBAL SET TO JOIN S&amp;P 500

$COIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922038165398839438#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:16:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922038165398839438#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*COINBASE GLOBAL SET TO JOIN S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s Hassett says there are 24 countries lined up for trade talks over the next weeks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trumps-hassett-says-there-are-24-countries-lined-up-for-trade-talks-over-the-next-weeks-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trumps-hassett-says-there-are-24-countries-lined-up-for-trade-talks-over-the-next-weeks-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Hassett is Trump&apos;s director of the National Economic Council, a senior economic adivser:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rebooting the relationship with China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Greer, Bessent will continue talks with China
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets could expect ‘normalization’ of things&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;24 trade talks lined up over the next weeks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hassett was speaking in an interview on CNBC. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *GOLDMAN NOW SEES NEXT FED RATE CUT IN DECEMBER INSTEAD OF JULY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922033143437054343#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922033143437054343#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*GOLDMAN NOW SEES NEXT FED RATE CUT IN DECEMBER INSTEAD OF JULY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs expect a Federal Reserve rate cut now in December, instead of in July</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expect-a-federal-reserve-rate-cut-now-in-december-instead-of-in-july-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:52:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expect-a-federal-reserve-rate-cut-now-in-december-instead-of-in-july-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs citing trade war developments:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In light of these developments and the meaningful easing in financial conditions over the last month, we are raising our 2025 growth forecast by 0.5pp to 1% Q4/Q4 and reducing our 12-month recession odds to 35%. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now forecast a December FOMC rate cut instead of July&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;We have lowered our core PCE inflation path to peak at 3.6% (vs. 3.8% previously)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wall Street Journal&apos;s Timiraos with the info. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier GS analysis of the trade war ceasefire:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; The large reduction in the US tariff rate on China should only have a limited impact on the overall US effective tariff rate.”
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Sees “only a small (less than 2pp) decrease to the US’ current effective tariff rate from the relaxation in China tariffs.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;

“After accounting for a reduction of that magnitude, the full set of US tariffs would still be considerably higher and broader than expected by markets at the start of the year.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the trade war ceasefire is good news, Trump stepping back from the brink of economic catastrophe at home and abroad, tariffs are still high - the highest since WW2. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks close sharply higher on US China tariff news</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-close-sharply-higher-on-us-china-tariff-news-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:30:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-close-sharply-higher-on-us-china-tariff-news-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The major US stock indices are sharply higher on US/China tariff news. Over the weekend the US slashed tariffs for the next 90-days on China goods from 145% to 30% inclusive of a 20% tariff due to fentanyl. The news led to sharp buying which did not abate. The broader S&amp;amp;P and Nasdaq indices had their 2nd best days going back to 2022.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final numbers are showing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average rose 1160.7 2.2 or 2.81% to 42,410.10.  That was the second-best day going back to November 6, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index rose 184.28 points or 3.26% at 5844.19. That was the 2nd-best % day going back to November 10.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index rose 779.43 points or 4.35% at 18708.34. That was the second-best day since November 30.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Russell 2000 rose 16.12 points or 3.42% at 2092.19. For that index, it was a second-best day since November 6, 2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the bigger winners today included:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;73&quot; data-end=&quot;111&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;75&quot; data-end=&quot;111&quot;&gt;Shopify Inc   +13.71%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;112&quot; data-end=&quot;150&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;114&quot; data-end=&quot;150&quot;&gt;First Solar  +11.07%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;151&quot; data-end=&quot;181&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;153&quot; data-end=&quot;181&quot;&gt;Block   +9.29%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;182&quot; data-end=&quot;219&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;184&quot; data-end=&quot;219&quot;&gt;Lam Research   +9.18%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;220&quot; data-end=&quot;256&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;222&quot; data-end=&quot;256&quot;&gt;Amazon.com   +8.09%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;257&quot; data-end=&quot;297&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;259&quot; data-end=&quot;297&quot;&gt;Meta Platforms   +7.92%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;298&quot; data-end=&quot;327&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;300&quot; data-end=&quot;327&quot;&gt;Arm   +7.77%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;328&quot; data-end=&quot;359&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;330&quot; data-end=&quot;359&quot;&gt;Micron   +7.49%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;360&quot; data-end=&quot;396&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;362&quot; data-end=&quot;396&quot;&gt;Papa John’s   +7.26%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;397&quot; data-end=&quot;429&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;399&quot; data-end=&quot;429&quot;&gt;Gilead   +7.12%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;430&quot; data-end=&quot;461&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;432&quot; data-end=&quot;461&quot;&gt;FedEx   +6.94%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;462&quot; data-end=&quot;491&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;464&quot; data-end=&quot;491&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;Tesla   +6.82%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at some of the other leading gainers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alphabet +3.74%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft, +2.40%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nvidia, + 5.44%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nike  +7.34%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) AMAZON STRIKES A NEW PARTNERSHIP WITH FEDEX AFTER UPS PULLBACK - BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922026103784321333#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:28:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922026103784321333#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AMAZON STRIKES A NEW PARTNERSHIP WITH FEDEX AFTER UPS PULLBACK - BUSINESS INSIDER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *UAE CHIP DEAL &apos;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS&apos; OF GPUS: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922016641228976315#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:50:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922016641228976315#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*UAE CHIP DEAL &apos;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS&apos; OF GPUS: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US MULLS LARGE CHIP SALE TO EMIRATI AI FIRM G42: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922016471397372338#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:50:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922016471397372338#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US MULLS LARGE CHIP SALE TO EMIRATI AI FIRM G42: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TAX BILL OMITS TRUMP PROPOSAL FOR MILLIONAIRE TAX BRACKET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922003610021310516#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:59:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922003610021310516#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TAX BILL OMITS TRUMP PROPOSAL FOR MILLIONAIRE TAX BRACKET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *REPUBLICAN TAX BILL RAISES DEBT LIMIT BY $4 TRILLION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922003557055639806#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:58:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922003557055639806#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*REPUBLICAN TAX BILL RAISES DEBT LIMIT BY $4 TRILLION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PENTAGON CANCELS ALL GENDER AFFIRMING HEALTHCARE FOR TRANSGENDER TROOPS AS IT MOVES TO KICK THEM OUT OF THE MILITARY, MEMO SEEN BY REUTERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002831847854223#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002831847854223#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PENTAGON CANCELS ALL GENDER AFFIRMING HEALTHCARE FOR TRANSGENDER TROOPS AS IT MOVES TO KICK THEM OUT OF THE MILITARY, MEMO SEEN BY REUTERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GOP TAX BILL CALLS TO END ELECTRIC VEHICLE TAX CREDIT EARLY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002171203055726#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:53:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002171203055726#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GOP TAX BILL CALLS TO END ELECTRIC VEHICLE TAX CREDIT EARLY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE REPUBLICANS SEEK &quot;ENHANCED DEDUCTION&quot; FOR SENIOR CITIZENS BY $4,000, WITH EXCEPTIONS -BILL TEXT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002130732245429#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:53:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002130732245429#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE REPUBLICANS SEEK &quot;ENHANCED DEDUCTION&quot; FOR SENIOR CITIZENS BY $4,000, WITH EXCEPTIONS -BILL TEXT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GOOLSBEE: TARIFFS WILL STILL HAVE STAGFLATIONARY IMPLUSE: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922000611878355067#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:47:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922000611878355067#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GOOLSBEE: TARIFFS WILL STILL HAVE STAGFLATIONARY IMPLUSE: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL INCLUDES EXEMPTION ON WORKERS&apos; OVERTIME PAY, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922000568353980860#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922000568353980860#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL INCLUDES EXEMPTION ON WORKERS&apos; OVERTIME PAY, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL WOULD EXEMPT WORKERS&apos; TIPS FROM INCOME TAX, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921999715534561550#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:43:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921999715534561550#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL WOULD EXEMPT WORKERS&apos; TIPS FROM INCOME TAX, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HOUSE REPUBLICANS RELEASE TEXT OF TAX BILL SOUGHT BY TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921998714861662449#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:39:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921998714861662449#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HOUSE REPUBLICANS RELEASE TEXT OF TAX BILL SOUGHT BY TRUMP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $AAPL - APPLE PLANS AI-POWERED BATTERY MANAGEMENT MODE FOR DEVICES IN IOS 19</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921994052645408782#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:21:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921994052645408782#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AAPL&quot;&gt;$AAPL&lt;/a&gt; - APPLE PLANS AI-POWERED BATTERY MANAGEMENT MODE FOR DEVICES IN IOS 19&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. POSTS $258B APRIL BUDGET SURPLUS, UP 23%

Strong tax payments and record import tariffs boosted the U.S. April surplus to $258B, Treasury reported.

🔸 $16B in customs duties, up $9B from last year.
🔸 U.S. collected $500M/day from tariffs, far below Trump&apos;s $2B/day claim.
🔸 Tariff revenue will fall as U.S.-China agreed to cut tariffs (U.S. to 30%, China to 10%) for 90 days.

For fiscal 2025 (Oct-Apr):

🔸 Deficit: $1.049T, up 23%.
🔸 Receipts: $3.11T, Outlays: $4.16T — both April records.
🔸 Adjusted for timing effects, the deficit rose 4%.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921989411522146372#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921989411522146372#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. POSTS $258B APRIL BUDGET SURPLUS, UP 23%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Strong tax payments and record import tariffs boosted the U.S. April surplus to $258B, Treasury reported.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 $16B in customs duties, up $9B from last year.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 U.S. collected $500M/day from tariffs, far below Trump&apos;s $2B/day claim.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Tariff revenue will fall as U.S.-China agreed to cut tariffs (U.S. to 30%, China to 10%) for 90 days.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
For fiscal 2025 (Oct-Apr):&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Deficit: $1.049T, up 23%.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Receipts: $3.11T, Outlays: $4.16T — both April records.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Adjusted for timing effects, the deficit rose 4%.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US BUDGET SURPLUS RISES 23% TO $258 BILLION IN APRIL, CUSTOMS REVENUE SURGES

The U.S. government posted a $258 billion budget surplus for April, up 23% from a year earlier, reflecting strong tax receipts in the final month of the tax season and surging collections of import duties, the Treasury Department said on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921988910256738470#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921988910256738470#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US BUDGET SURPLUS RISES 23% TO $258 BILLION IN APRIL, CUSTOMS REVENUE SURGES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The U.S. government posted a $258 billion budget surplus for April, up 23% from a year earlier, reflecting strong tax receipts in the final month of the tax season and surging collections of import duties, the Treasury Department said on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA TRADE EASING DOESN&apos;T MEAN A QUICK FED CUT: DEUTSCHE BANK

A big drop in U.S.-China trade barriers lessens the prospects of a serious inflationary supply crunch. Even so, inflation remains stubborn enough that the Fed probably still won&apos;t be in a rush to cut interest rates, economists at Deutsche Bank write. Despite the trade war&apos;s easing, &quot;policies are likely to keep inflation at uncomfortably high levels for the Fed,&quot; Deutsche&apos;s team suggests. &quot;This announcement therefore reinforces our view that the Fed is going to be slow to cut rates this year.&quot; Deutsche&apos;s baseline assumption is that the Fed&apos;s next rate cut won&apos;t come before December</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921976766329192614#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:12:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921976766329192614#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA TRADE EASING DOESN&apos;T MEAN A QUICK FED CUT: DEUTSCHE BANK&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
A big drop in U.S.-China trade barriers lessens the prospects of a serious inflationary supply crunch. Even so, inflation remains stubborn enough that the Fed probably still won&apos;t be in a rush to cut interest rates, economists at Deutsche Bank write. Despite the trade war&apos;s easing, &quot;policies are likely to keep inflation at uncomfortably high levels for the Fed,&quot; Deutsche&apos;s team suggests. &quot;This announcement therefore reinforces our view that the Fed is going to be slow to cut rates this year.&quot; Deutsche&apos;s baseline assumption is that the Fed&apos;s next rate cut won&apos;t come before December&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED’S KUGLER: I AM ONE OF THOSE WHO BELIEVES THERE COULD BE SOME PERMANENCY FROM PRICE INCREASES RELATED TO TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921947847651447018#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:17:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921947847651447018#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED’S KUGLER: I AM ONE OF THOSE WHO BELIEVES THERE COULD BE SOME PERMANENCY FROM PRICE INCREASES RELATED TO TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
