<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank Chief Economist Lane speaking Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-centralbank-chief-economist-lane-speaking-friday-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:26:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-centralbank-chief-economist-lane-speaking-friday-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Lane may give some clues about the next European Central Bank rate move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1500 GMT/1100 US Eastern time:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Participation by ECB board member Philip Lane in Policymaker Panel: &quot;Central Bank Communications and Uncertainty&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; at 2nd Thomas Laubach Research Conference organised by the Federal Reserve Board in Washington D.C.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Japan Policy Board member Nakamura Toyoaki is speaking soon</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-policy-board-member-nakamura-toyoaki-is-speaking-soon-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:12:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-policy-board-member-nakamura-toyoaki-is-speaking-soon-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll be interested in his take on today&apos;s awful GDP number out of Japan:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he addresses it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We might have to wait for any following Q&amp;amp;A. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI: Wisconsin sells entire bitcoin ETF position after early bet on BlackRock fund</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/icymi-wisconsin-sells-entire-bitcoin-etf-position-after-early-bet-on-blackrock-fund-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/icymi-wisconsin-sells-entire-bitcoin-etf-position-after-early-bet-on-blackrock-fund-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;152&quot; data-end=&quot;541&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;ICYMI, overnight reports that the State of Wisconsin Investment Board (SWIB) has exited its position in BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF (IBIT), divesting over six million shares during the first quarter of 2025. According to a recent filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, SWIB no longer holds any spot Bitcoin ETF exposure, marking a full retreat from the $355 million stake it previously held.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;543&quot; data-end=&quot;911&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Wisconsin had been among the first U.S. state pension managers to venture into Bitcoin-backed ETFs, initially purchasing $164 million worth of shares when the funds launched in early 2024. The move had positioned the state as an early adopter of crypto exposure for retirees, but the latest filings confirm a complete liquidation of that position within just one year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;543&quot; data-end=&quot;911&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Info via crypot media outlets. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan economy minister Akazawa: Govt will continue to demand review of U.S. tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japaneconomyministerakazawagovtwillcontinuetodemandreviewofustariffs-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:30:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japaneconomyministerakazawagovtwillcontinuetodemandreviewofustariffs-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan economy minister Akazawa remarks after the poor economic data earlier from Japan:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improvements in job, income conditions likely to underpin moderate economic recovery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be mindful of downside risks to economy from U.S. trade policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hit to consumption, household sentiment from sustained price rises also becoming downside risk to Japan’s economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Govt will continue to demand review of U.S. tariffs, take all necessary steps to offer liquidity aid to impacted firms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No notable impact of US tariffs on Japan’s Q1 GDP, will scrutinise various data that will become available to gauge impact on economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Domestic demand rose in Q1, while negative external demand contribution was due to rise in imports
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Government has no plan now to compile fresh stimulus package but will coordinate appropriately with ruling coalition&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Akazawa sais its important to communicate closely with other countries, when asked whether Japan was ready to coordinate with countries with big automobile plants like Mexico, Canada&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY update:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1938 (vs. estimate at 7.2085)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71938-vs-estimate-at-72085-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71938-vs-estimate-at-72085-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous close was 7.2067&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC injected 106.5bn yuan via 7-day reverse repos at 1.40%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0bn yuan mature today&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;net injection 106.5bn yuan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs raises its 12-month target for MSCI Asia-Pacific ex-Japan to 660 from 620</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/goldman-sachs-raises-its-12-month-target-for-msci-asia-pacific-ex-japan-to-660-from-620-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:14:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/goldman-sachs-raises-its-12-month-target-for-msci-asia-pacific-ex-japan-to-660-from-620-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs raises its 12-month target for MSCI Asia-Pacific ex-Japan to 660 from 620&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;90&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The MSCI Asia-Pacific ex-Japan Index is a widely followed stock market benchmark that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;92&quot; data-end=&quot;476&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;92&quot; data-end=&quot;239&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;94&quot; data-end=&quot;239&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Tracks the performance of large- and mid-cap stocks across developed and emerging markets in the Asia-Pacific region excluding Japan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;240&quot; data-end=&quot;409&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;242&quot; data-end=&quot;409&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Includes countries such as China, South Korea, Taiwan, India, Australia, Hong Kong, Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand, the Philippines, and New Zealand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;410&quot; data-end=&quot;476&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;412&quot; data-end=&quot;476&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Is maintained by MSCI Inc., a leading global index provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;779&quot; data-end=&quot;969&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Why exclude Japan?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;779&quot; data-end=&quot;969&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Japan has a large, mature, and heavily weighted stock market. Excluding it allows investors to focus on emerging and developing Asia-Pacific economies without Japan dominating the index.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP Morgan analysts expect Bitcoin to outperform gold for the rest of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-analysts-expect-bitcoin-to-outperform-gold-for-the-rest-of-the-year-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:59:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-analysts-expect-bitcoin-to-outperform-gold-for-the-rest-of-the-year-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;JP Morgan analysts expect Bitcoin to outperform gold for the rest of the year.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Citing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;debasement trade&quot; where investors buy gold and Bitcoin as a hedge against weakening international currencies has turned into a zero-sum game in 2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;gold was gaining, and Bitcoin was losing ... until recently&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;since April’s peak, gold prices have declined Bitcoin has gained&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;flow of money taken out of gold exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and being poured into spot bitcoin and crypto funds since April&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;JP Morgan also note&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Hampshire crypto bill - state can invest up to 10% of its public funds in Bitcoin and precious metals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Arizona also passed a similar law&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;as more US states rule to invest in Bitcoin, it could act as a “sustained positive” catalyst&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can track this call &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/LiveCharts&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;using our free charts&lt;/a&gt;, here is BTC/XAU: &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore’s April exports surge 12.4%, beating expectations but outlook remains cautious</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/singapores-april-exports-surge-124-beating-expectations-but-outlook-remains-cautious-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:45:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/singapores-april-exports-surge-124-beating-expectations-but-outlook-remains-cautious-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;176&quot; data-end=&quot;480&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Singapore’s non-oil domestic exports jumped 12.4% in April compared to a year earlier, far exceeding expectations and marking a sharp acceleration from March’s 5.4% rise. The latest figures, released Friday by Enterprise Singapore, showed strong gains across both electronic and non-electronic shipments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;482&quot; data-end=&quot;750&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The result came well above the 4.3% year-on-year increase forecast in a Reuters poll and reflected solid demand from key trading partners including the U.S., Japan, and regional economies such as Taiwan and South Korea. However, exports to China and Malaysia declined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;752&quot; data-end=&quot;1267&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Despite the upside surprise, the broader outlook remains clouded by escalating global trade tensions, particularly in light of new tariffs imposed by the United States. Singapore, whose economy is heavily reliant on external trade, has been flagged as vulnerable to a global slowdown. In response, the government recently formed an economic resilience taskforce and warned that a recession cannot be ruled out. Last month, it revised its full-year GDP forecast down to a range of 0% to 2%, from a previous 1% to 3%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan finmin Kato: Will seek to have a meeting with Bessent, discuss FX and other matters</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finmin-kato-will-seek-to-have-a-meeting-with-bessent-discuss-fx-and-other-matters-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:25:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finmin-kato-will-seek-to-have-a-meeting-with-bessent-discuss-fx-and-other-matters-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan finmin Kato:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Convinced that Bessent is a reliable counterpart able to have constructive dialogue, will continue to closely coordinate with him&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Reaffirmed with Bessent in talks on April 24 that excessive Forex volatility has averse impact on economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will continue talks with him based on this understanding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will seek to have a meeting with Bessent, discuss FX and other matters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY update, a little lower now following the poor GDP data:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC is expected to set the USD/CNY reference rate at 7.2085 – Reuters estimate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72085-reuters-estimate-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:23:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72085-reuters-estimate-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China USD/CNY reference rate is due around 0115 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How the process works:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type=&quot;disc&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily midpoint setting: Each morning, the PBOC sets a midpoint for the yuan against a basket of currencies, primarily the US dollar. The central bank takes into account factors such as market supply and demand, economic indicators, and international currency market fluctuations. The midpoint serves as a reference point for that day&apos;s trading.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The trading band: The PBOC allows the yuan to move within a specified range around the midpoint. The trading band is set at +/- 2%, meaning the yuan could appreciate or depreciate by a maximum of 2% from the midpoint during a single trading day. This range is subject to change by the PBOC based on economic conditions and policy objectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intervention: If the yuan&apos;s value approaches the limit of the trading band or experiences excessive volatility, the PBOC may intervene in the foreign exchange market by buying or selling the yuan to stabilize its value. This helps maintain a controlled and gradual adjustment of the currency&apos;s value.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Prime Minister &amp; Mexican President to strengthen economies against future shocks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canadian-prime-minister-mexican-president-to-strengthen-economies-against-future-shocks-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:22:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canadian-prime-minister-mexican-president-to-strengthen-economies-against-future-shocks-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney discussed with Mexican President Sheinbaum the imperative to strengthen their respective economies against future shocks according to a prime minister’s office readout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USMCA free trade agreement was trampled on in the Trump tariff trade war. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>75bp of Reserve Bank of Australia rate cuts to come (Reuters poll)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/75bp-of-reserve-bank-of-australia-rate-cuts-to-come-reuters-poll-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:11:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/75bp-of-reserve-bank-of-australia-rate-cuts-to-come-reuters-poll-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Reuters poll of analysts re expecations of what&apos;s to come from the RBA:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reserve Bank of Australia to cut cash rate to 3.85% on May 20, say 42 of 43 economists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;one forecasts 50 bps cut (of the big 4 Australian banks ANZ, CBA and WPAC are tipping a 25bp cut next week, NAB a 50bp cut)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;to cut cash rate to 3.35% by end of 2025 according to the median forecast&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the report, Reuters quote ANZ:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;  &quot;Following tariff news at the start of April, we shifted our
expectations. We&apos;re expecting the cash rate will go to 3.35%
now. That shift was really a rough lesson of a very changing,
uncertain global environment where global growth was likely to
slow,&quot; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; &quot;There are indications some of those tariff announcements
are going to be wound back but the big question is how this
actually shakes consumer confidence and how businesses are
feeling... There is some clear softness in the business
environment, which would support a rate cut from the RBA next
week.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD/JPY little changed after the economic contraction data from Japan, JPY up a little</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdjpy-little-changed-after-the-economic-contraction-data-from-japan-jpy-up-a-little-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdjpy-little-changed-after-the-economic-contraction-data-from-japan-jpy-up-a-little-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Even before Trump&apos;s tariff war hit in full Japan&apos;s economy shrunk:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;While everyone around the globe was cranking up exports ahead of the tariffs and jamming the pipelines to the us ... Japan exports were -0.6% q/q.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I post USD/JPY is showing just a touch lower, but not yet to a new session low:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:50:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japanese economic growth data for Q1 2025 (January - March) - recovery in Japan proving tenuous once again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-0.2% q/q for real GDP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;vs. expected -0.1% and prior +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-0.7% annualised q/q, first fall in a year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;expected -0.2%, prior +2.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; Private Consumption 0.0% q/q&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;expected +0.1%, prior +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; Capital Expenditure +1.4% q/q a bright point in the data &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;expected +0.8%, prior +0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;More:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;External demand contribution to GDP -0.8%, vs. expected -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Exports -0.6% q/q&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Domestic demand contribution to GDP +0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;GDP deflator +3.3% y/y (this is an inflation indicator) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A shrinking economy ... even before the trade war hit in force ... is going to cause consternation at the Bank of Japan. It&apos;ll delay further rate hikes. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan finance minister Kato says will discuss FX with Bessent</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-says-will-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:46:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-says-will-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan finance minister Kato &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;will discuss FX with Bessent in line with points agreed in prior talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FX should be determined by market&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;excessive FX moves damage economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FT: Trump administration split on timing of adding Chinese chipmakers to export blacklist</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ft-trump-administration-split-on-timing-of-adding-chinese-chipmakers-to-export-blacklist-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:10:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ft-trump-administration-split-on-timing-of-adding-chinese-chipmakers-to-export-blacklist-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Financial Times is gated, but in brief:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump administration plans to put a number of Chinese chipmaking companies on an export blacklist (the “entity list”)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;timing of the move has been complicated by the trade deal agreed by China and the US in Geneva at the weekend&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;some Trump administration officials have argued that putting export controls on critical Chinese groups now could jeopardise the trade negotiations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand April Manufacturing PMI shows an uptick in expansion to 53.9 vs. prior 53.2</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-april-manufacturing-pmi-shows-an-uptick-in-expansion-to-539-vs-prior-532-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-april-manufacturing-pmi-shows-an-uptick-in-expansion-to-539-vs-prior-532-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;BNZ – BusinessNZ Performance of Manufacturing Index (PMI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;April comes in at 53.9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;up from 53.2 in March&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; fourth month in a row showing expansion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; above the average of 52.5 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;BusinessNZ’s Director, Advocacy Catherine Beard:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“All of the sub-index values were in expansion during April.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;BNZ’s Senior Economist Doug Steel:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“activity is not surging, but a manufacturing recovery seems to be underway with the PMI having improved substantially from its low of 41.4 last June. That said, there remain questions around how sustainable it is given uncertainty stemming from offshore”.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSBC modelling sees USD/JPY trading a 141 - 149 range (there&apos;s a but)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/hsbc-modelling-sees-usdjpy-trading-a-141-149-range-theres-a-but-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:42:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/hsbc-modelling-sees-usdjpy-trading-a-141-149-range-theres-a-but-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;HSBC argue for further yen recovery vs the USD citing &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;heightened U.S. policy uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;resumption of pessimism toward the U.S. economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;renewed expectations of Fed easing soon&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;HSBC are tracking trade developments, noting market sensitivity &quot;to headlines about U.S.-Japan trade talks, especially regarding FX discussions” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HSBC’s modelling indicates 141-149 range for USD/JPY, though analysts do recognise risks for both overshooting and undershooting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I stuck in lines around 141 and 149, just using eyeballing ... it looks like we don&apos;t have to worry about over and undershooting those levels for a while to come yet. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia financial media reports that “Australia won’t join Trump trade war on China”</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-financial-media-reports-that-australia-wont-join-trump-trade-war-on-china-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:12:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-financial-media-reports-that-australia-wont-join-trump-trade-war-on-china-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;A piece in today&apos;s Australian Financial Review on Australia not joining in on Trump&apos;s trade attack on China. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade Minister Don Farrell spoke in an interview with the AFR (gated): &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;reluctant to be part of a US campaign
against China on trade, given that Australian exports to China are worth almost 10 times that to the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“China is our
largest trading partner. Chinese trade is almost 10 times more
valuable to Australia”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don’t want to do less business
with China, we want to do more business with China.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;

We’ll make
decisions about how we continue to engage with China based on our
national interests and not on what the Americans may or may not
want.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AFR is gated, here is the link if you can access it for much more. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Deputy Treasury Secretary says not concerned about persistent increases in prices</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-deputy-treasury-secretary-says-not-concerned-about-persistent-increases-in-prices-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-deputy-treasury-secretary-says-not-concerned-about-persistent-increases-in-prices-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;U.S. Deputy Treasury Secretary Faulkender spoke in an interview with Bloomberg TV:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;not concerned about persistent increases in prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;expects inflation will return to target level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US economy building foundation to accelerate in H2 this year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;confident that August timeline is earliest we have to worry about X date&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan, US to resume tariff talks after G7 summit as Akazawa plans Washington visit</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-us-to-resume-tariff-talks-after-g7-summit-as-akazawa-plans-washington-visit-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:09:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-us-to-resume-tariff-talks-after-g7-summit-as-akazawa-plans-washington-visit-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan, US to resume tariff talks after G7 summit as Akazawa plans Washington visit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan and the United States are preparing for a third round of negotiations over trade tariffs, aiming to resume talks later this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The discussions are part of ongoing efforts to ease tensions following recent U.S. tariff hikes under the Trump administration. Japan’s chief negotiator, Ryosei Akazawa, is expected to travel to the U.S. for the talks shortly after attending the upcoming Group of Seven (G7) meeting of finance ministers and central bank governors. That summit, set to be held next week, is likely to feature prominently in setting the tone for bilateral discussions, with both sides under pressure to find common ground on trade imbalances and tariff rollbacks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Akazawa will attend the summit for finance ministers and central bankers being held Banff, Alberta, Canada on  May 20 -22. This is being held ahead of the 2025 G7 Leaders’ Summit, which will be in Kananaskis, Alberta, Canada from June 15 to 17.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s Akazawa in the hat!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea April export prices have shown their slowest rise y/y since December 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/south-koreaapril-exportpriceshave-shown-their-slowestriseyysincedecember-2023-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:07:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/south-koreaapril-exportpriceshave-shown-their-slowestriseyysincedecember-2023-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;South Korea April data, comes via the Bank of Korea:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Export prices in won terms +0.7% y/y vs revised +6.4% in March, export prices slowest rise y/y since December 2023&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Import prices in won terms -2.3% y/y vs revised +3.4% in March, import prices fastest drop y/y since October 2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Korea says April Foreign net investment in local stocks -13.59 trln won vs -1.64 trln won in March
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;says April Foreign net investment in local bonds +11.26 trln won vs +5.87 trln won in March&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;KRW update:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Dip in PPI pulls down USD/JPY</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-dip-in-ppi-pulls-down-usdjpy-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:41:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-dip-in-ppi-pulls-down-usdjpy-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-retail-sales-01-vs-00-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;US April retail sales +0.1% vs 0.0% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-ppi-24-vs-25-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;US April PPI +2.4% vs +2.5% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-initial-jobless-claims-229k-versus-229k-estimate-20250515/&quot;&gt;US initial jobless claims 229K versus 229K estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/philadelphia-fed-business-index-for-may-40-vs-110-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;Philadelphia Fed Business index for May -4.0 vs -11.0 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-may-nahb-housing-market-index-34-vs-40-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;US May NAHB housing market index 34 vs 40 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-industrial-production-00-vs-02-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;US April industrial production 0.0% vs +0.2% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/empire-manufacturing-index-for-may-92-vs-100-estimate-20250515/&quot;&gt;Empire manufacturing index for May -9.2 vs -10.0 estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-q2-rises-to-25-from-23-prior-20250515/&quot;&gt;Atlanta Fed GDPNow Q2 rises to 2.5% from 2.3% prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eus-sefcovic-agreed-with-us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-to-accelerate-trade-talks-20250515/&quot;&gt;EU&apos;s Sefcovic agreed with US Commerce Secretary Lutnick to accelerate trade talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-business-inventories-for-march-01-vs-02-estimate-20250515/&quot;&gt;US business inventories for March 0.1% vs 0.2% estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-mexico-cuts-benchmark-interest-rate-to-85-from-90-20250515/&quot;&gt;Bank of Mexico cuts benchmark interest rate to 8.5% from 9.0%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-says-economy-is-on-a-solid-footing-trade-clouds-the-outlook-20250515/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Barr says economy is on a solid footing, trade clouds the outlook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-powell-discusses-mon-pol-framework-doesnt-comment-on-the-outlook-for-rates-20250515/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Powell discusses mon pol framework, doesn&apos;t comment on the outlook for rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-wholesale-trade-02-vs-03-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;Canada March wholesale trade 0.2% vs -0.3% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/walmart-offers-a-major-warning-on-prices-20250515/&quot;&gt;Walmart offers a major warning on prices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude oil down $1.42 to $61.77&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields down 9 bps to 4.43%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold up $60 to $3234&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CHF leads, NZD lags&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 up 0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We got a full slate of data today and most of the numbers were close to estimates but PPI stood out as a softer indication and that led to Fed rate cut odds ticking higher, especially further out the curve. It also lent some relief in bonds as yields fell 7-11 bps across the curve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar continues to differ in its reaction function to yield moves, suggesting that fiscal policy is increasingly seen as off-base. Despite falling yields, the US dollar rose and it&apos;s been the opposite on days when yields have risen. That&apos;s something Deutsche Bank &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-losing-its-appetite-to-fund-us-twin-deficits-deutsche-bank-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;raised the alarm &lt;/a&gt;on today and a critical dynamic to watch as the US budget drama plays out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US retail sales data was somewhat comforting as it showed strong spending in bars and restaurants, which is typically one of the first things to go. Walmart did offer a stark warning about price rises though so that should keep the Fed in watch-and-wait mode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Canadian dollar was something of an outperformer in North American as oil and commodity prices rebounded from the earlier lows. Part of that was a bounce in oil prices after Iran said it hadn&apos;t received an deal offers from the United States. The risk picture also lent some support, though that wasn&apos;t seen in the other commodity currencies.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Chance To Nominate Your Candidate for the Industry’s Most Creditable Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/last-chance-to-nominate-your-candidate-for-the-industrys-most-creditable-awards-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:38:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/last-chance-to-nominate-your-candidate-for-the-industrys-most-creditable-awards-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The nomination period for the UF AWARDS Global 2025 is coming to an end on 30th of May, which means your window for recommending your brand as a nominee is quickly closing!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The UF AWARDS and their recipients receive an incredible level of coverage within the industry. Meaning that even brands that don’t win still receive an unprecedented boost to their profiles, and it can help bolster their reputation, since the stringent selection process only allows the most competitive companies to progress to the next stage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Prove your brand is a market leader&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Distinguishing yourself in such a densely populated and competitive market can be extremely challenging. Modern consumers are discerning and often immune to catchy marketing taglines and slogans, even more so if they are industry insiders. So, how do you convince them to work with you? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;With proof. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://uf-awards.com/cyprus2025/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;UF AWARDS&lt;/a&gt; are not only one of the market&apos;s most credible and covered awards events, but they can also help brands establish or expand their footprint in existing regions or when entering a new market through increased global brand exposure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;As one of the industry’s most well-established awards, the UF AWARDS bring an unparalleled level of recognition to brands that innovate, disrupt the status quo, and propel the industry forward. The nominees include some of the financial service industry’s and FinTech world’s biggest and boldest. Past winners have included agile start-ups, FinTech firms that offer industry-critical software, and companies that are household names. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Winning a UF AWARD Global title shows that your company can stand shoulder to shoulder with some of the leading B2B and B2C brands in its sector and head and shoulders above the rest on the global stage. It lends credibility to a brand, increases a company&apos;s visibility, and can be used on marketing creatives to prove to potential clients that they offer leading products and services. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Multiple award categories&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://uf-awards.com/cyprus2025/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;UF AWARDS Global&lt;/a&gt; offer multiple award categories that top-tier financial service and FinTech companies can be nominated for. This means that B2C and B2B companies can be enlisted for outstanding features, products, and services they offer, facing direct competitors, instead of competing against companies and firms that may not even share the same segment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Additionally, nominees can be recommended for multiple awards if their offerings align with the respective requirements.. For example, a brand may be nominated as “Best Trading Platform” as well as “Best Customer Support”. The category winners are decided on by a public vote, which ensures impartiality, credibility, and that they are awarded based purely on merit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;How to nominate your favorite brand&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Your last chance to nominate a brand for the UF AWARDS Global is the 30th of May 2025. Here’s how to &lt;a href=&quot;https://uf-awards.com/cyprus2025/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;submit a nomination&lt;/a&gt; or recommend a brand as a nominee:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Register on the Awards website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Once registered and logged in, select the category of your brand you wish to nominate from the dropdown - Broker Awards or B2B Awards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Next, click on the Award title that best describes the scope of your business, and nominate the company worthy of the title. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Once the nominees are submitted, the voting will open on the 3rd and close on the 11th of June. The awards will be announced during the Award ceremony taking place on the 18th of June. For more information about the award categories and to submit nominations, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://uf-awards.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;uf-awards.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Good luck to all nominees, and we look forward to seeing you at the award ceremony!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP Morgan CEO Dimon says US recession risks remain high amid deficits and inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-ceo-dimon-says-us-recession-risks-remain-high-amid-deficits-and-inflation-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:36:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-ceo-dimon-says-us-recession-risks-remain-high-amid-deficits-and-inflation-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;462&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Equity markets seem to have shaken off the risk, Jamie Dimon with a caution, ICYMI.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;462&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dimon says a U.S. recession is still a live risk. The JPMorgan Chase CEO told Bloomberg that surging federal deficits, persistent inflation and the prospect of higher long-term interest rates could yet tip the economy into contraction. “I wouldn’t take it off the table at this point,” he said, adding that he relies on his bank’s economists for precise forecasts and cannot predict “how big it will be or how long it will last” if a downturn materialises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;464&quot; data-end=&quot;862&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;JPMorgan’s research team this week trimmed its recession probability to “below 50 percent,” having previously expected a slump soon after the Trump administration’s early-April tariff blitz. Chief U.S. economist Michael Feroli acknowledged that risks remain “elevated,” but Dimon cautioned that even the current uncertainty is enough to make businesses hesitate before committing to new investment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *NVIDIA REPORTS 7% STAKE IN COREWEAVE IN 13G</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923114324479869131#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:32:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923114324479869131#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*NVIDIA REPORTS 7% STAKE IN COREWEAVE IN 13G&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *ACKMANS PERSHING EXITS NKE IN Q1:13F

$NKE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923108871356166577#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:10:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923108871356166577#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*ACKMANS PERSHING EXITS NKE IN Q1:13F&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NKE&quot;&gt;$NKE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *S&amp;P 500 CLOSES UP 0.3%, NASDAQ FALLS 0.2%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923106366782079010#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923106366782079010#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*S&amp;amp;P 500 CLOSES UP 0.3%, NASDAQ FALLS 0.2%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HHS TO STOP RECOMMENDING ROUTINE COVID SHOTS FOR CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923103658792616242#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:50:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923103658792616242#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HHS TO STOP RECOMMENDING ROUTINE COVID SHOTS FOR CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *META TO DELAY ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP: WSJ

*META&apos;S &apos;BEHEMOTH&apos; WAS INTERNALLY SLATED FOR APRIL RELEASE: WSJ

*META ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP AI MODEL DELAYED TO FALL OR LATER: WSJ

$META</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923096475015274849#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:21:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923096475015274849#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*META TO DELAY ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*META&apos;S &apos;BEHEMOTH&apos; WAS INTERNALLY SLATED FOR APRIL RELEASE: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*META ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP AI MODEL DELAYED TO FALL OR LATER: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23META&quot;&gt;$META&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *COINBASE HACKERS HAD ACCESS TO CUSTOMER DATA SINCE JANUARY

$COIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923092251049177096#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923092251049177096#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*COINBASE HACKERS HAD ACCESS TO CUSTOMER DATA SINCE JANUARY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *STATE OF WISCONSIN INVESTMENT BOARD EXITS BITCOIN ETF POSITION: SEC FILING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923090409468711385#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923090409468711385#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*STATE OF WISCONSIN INVESTMENT BOARD EXITS BITCOIN ETF POSITION: SEC FILING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US-UAE AI CAMPUS WILL PARTNER WITH &apos;SEVERAL&apos; US COMPANIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085920363831532#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:39:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085920363831532#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US-UAE AI CAMPUS WILL PARTNER WITH &apos;SEVERAL&apos; US COMPANIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *DOJ PROBING IF HARVARD ADMISSIONS DEFRAUDED GOVERNMENT: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085187870576740#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085187870576740#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*DOJ PROBING IF HARVARD ADMISSIONS DEFRAUDED GOVERNMENT: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *STATE DEPARTMENT IS LEADING CAMPAIGN ACCUSING EUROPE OF LIMITING FREE SPEECH AND PROMOTING CENSORSHIP -- WSJ

*ADMINISTRATION SEES EU AS PART OF ‘GLOBAL CENSORSHIP-INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX’ HURTING U.S. TECH -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085085919641778#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085085919641778#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*STATE DEPARTMENT IS LEADING CAMPAIGN ACCUSING EUROPE OF LIMITING FREE SPEECH AND PROMOTING CENSORSHIP -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*ADMINISTRATION SEES EU AS PART OF ‘GLOBAL CENSORSHIP-INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX’ HURTING U.S. TECH -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *RUSSIA DEPLOYS 640,000 TROOPS IN WAR AGAINST UKRAINE: MILITARY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923074660993835285#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:55:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923074660993835285#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*RUSSIA DEPLOYS 640,000 TROOPS IN WAR AGAINST UKRAINE: MILITARY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE LEGAL HEAD CALLS SEC INVESTIGATION A RELIC OF PAST ADMINISTRATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923072444299915747#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:46:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923072444299915747#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE LEGAL HEAD CALLS SEC INVESTIGATION A RELIC OF PAST ADMINISTRATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE CHIEF LEGAL OFFICER: REPORTED SEC INVESTIGATION IS A HOLD-OVER FROM PRIOR ADMINISTRATION ABOUT A METRIC WE STOPPED REPORTING 2.5 YEARS AGO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923072369427354065#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923072369427354065#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE CHIEF LEGAL OFFICER: REPORTED SEC INVESTIGATION IS A HOLD-OVER FROM PRIOR ADMINISTRATION ABOUT A METRIC WE STOPPED REPORTING 2.5 YEARS AGO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $NVDA - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $COIN - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt; - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade

🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:54:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
