<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says that 80% tariffs on China &quot;seems right&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-that-80-tariffs-on-china-seems-right-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:28:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-that-80-tariffs-on-china-seems-right-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;&quot;80% Tariff on China seems right! Up to Scott B.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I&apos;m not sure how exactly it is up to Bessent when Trump himself is already saying that it should be 80%. Funny. US futures are hitting a bit of a whipsaw on the headline here but at the balance, is nudging lower. Gold is also catching a bid, touching a high of $3,338 while USD/JPY is now down 0.5% to 145.10 on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: 80% tariff on China seems right</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-80-tariff-on-china-seems-right-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:28:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-80-tariff-on-china-seems-right-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;80% tariff on China seems right, up to Scott Bessent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is in stark contrast to earlier reports suggesting that the US could lower tariffs on China to 50-54%. He added that it&apos;s up to the US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent to decide the appropriate rate, as he&apos;s the one in charge of trade negotiations with China, but it still shows that Trump is favouring a more aggressive approach.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More from Fed&apos;s Kugler: Our policy right now is moderately restrictive</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-feds-kugler-our-policy-right-now-is-moderately-restrictive-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:26:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-feds-kugler-our-policy-right-now-is-moderately-restrictive-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our policy right now is moderately restrictive.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The labour market is stable and has been resilient.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Q1 GDP showed the real side of the economy is resilient.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scenarios are important amid high degrees of uncertainty.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says that China should open up its market to the US</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-that-china-should-open-up-its-market-to-the-us-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:24:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-that-china-should-open-up-its-market-to-the-us-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;CHINA SHOULD OPEN UP ITS MARKET TO USA — WOULD BE SO GOOD FOR THEM!!! CLOSED MARKETS DON’T WORK ANYMORE!!!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Is this perhaps a hint of what he is going to put his focus on today?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: CLOSED MARKETS DON&apos;T WORK ANYMORE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920801712324935998#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:23:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920801712324935998#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: CLOSED MARKETS DON&apos;T WORK ANYMORE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: CHINA SHOULD OPEN UP ITS MARKET TO USA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920801654133117246#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:22:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920801654133117246#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: CHINA SHOULD OPEN UP ITS MARKET TO USA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S KUGLER: OUR POLICY RIGHT NOW IS MODERATELY RESTRICTIVE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920801199051198541#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:21:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920801199051198541#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S KUGLER: OUR POLICY RIGHT NOW IS MODERATELY RESTRICTIVE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investor Alert for Monday: U.S.-China Tariff Talks Start This Weekend. Monday Volatility?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/investor-alert-for-monday-us-china-tariff-talks-start-this-weekend-monday-volatility-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:18:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/investor-alert-for-monday-us-china-tariff-talks-start-this-weekend-monday-volatility-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;95&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Markets on Edge as U.S.-China Tariff Talks Loom — and Limited Progress May Disappoint Investors
Investors are entering the weekend with caution as U.S.-China trade talks are scheduled, with expectations centered around potential tariff reductions. Markets have partially priced in a move from the current 145% peak tariff rate on Chinese imports to something in the 50% range. However, recent commentary from U.S. officials and analysts suggests little substantive progress is likely this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;517&quot; data-end=&quot;1013&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Financial Implications:
If the talks result only in an agreement to keep talking — without a concrete reduction in tariffs — equity markets may react negatively on Monday. The S&amp;amp;P 500 has already staged a strong 13–14% rally, and positioning remains slightly long-to-neutral. Failure to deliver a tangible outcome could trigger a pullback, particularly given how much optimism is now priced in. Conversely, even a small policy shift toward a 50–60% tariff rate could sustain risk sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1015&quot; data-end=&quot;1041&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Investors and Traders, Have the Following in Mind:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1042&quot; data-end=&quot;1461&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1042&quot; data-end=&quot;1141&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1044&quot; data-end=&quot;1141&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The S&amp;amp;P 500 is up 13–14% since recent lows, and April marked its second-best month of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1142&quot; data-end=&quot;1234&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1144&quot; data-end=&quot;1234&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Current tariffs on some Chinese goods peak at 145%; Some analysts anticipate a drop to 50–60%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1235&quot; data-end=&quot;1296&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1237&quot; data-end=&quot;1296&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A baseline global tariff rate of 10% is under discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1297&quot; data-end=&quot;1366&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1299&quot; data-end=&quot;1366&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Some companies have removed forward guidance, citing uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1367&quot; data-end=&quot;1461&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1369&quot; data-end=&quot;1461&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Airlines, autos, and consumer durables may feel the pinch from persistent price pressures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1463&quot; data-end=&quot;1894&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Investor Takeaway:
With markets trading just 3.7% below pre-April highs, the risk-reward balance going into the weekend skews slightly bearish if no progress is made. A delay or disappointment could revive volatility early next week, especially with CPI and a court ruling on tariff powers due May 13. Investors should be prepared for a market response that reflects how real the outcomes of this weekend&apos;s meetings appear. On the other hand, Trump may push forward with continued momentum after the US-UK deal, disappointing the short sellers betting on a disappointment. Monday&apos;s stock market open will be quite interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINESE PREMIER LI QIANG CHAIRS STATE COUNCIL MEETING: CCTV</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920800188668461286#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:17:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920800188668461286#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINESE PREMIER LI QIANG CHAIRS STATE COUNCIL MEETING: CCTV&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this the playbook for US trading later before the weekend?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/is-this-the-playbook-for-us-trading-later-before-the-weekend-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 10:54:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/is-this-the-playbook-for-us-trading-later-before-the-weekend-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The US-UK trade deal agreement stole the spotlight yesterday but it hardly was what led Wall Street to rally. The framework for the deal lacked meaningful details but is at least a step in the right direction. Instead, the most important headline was arguably these remarks by Trump:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;TRUMP: BETTER GO OUT AND BUY STOCKS NOW &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;TRUMP: THE STOCK MARKET WILL REALLY RALLY NOW&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That turned the more tepid mood after the US-UK trade announcement to a strong rally before US stocks ended the day with middling gains. The mood music was also affected by other headlines, with talk of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-template-for-10-tariffs-is-probably-the-lowest-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;10% blanket tariffs being the floor for any deal&lt;/a&gt; and perhaps more importantly the report by the Wall St Journal suggesting that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/white-house-weighing-plan-to-slash-china-tariffs-to-as-low-as-50-report-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US is looking to cut China tariffs to as low as 50%&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The latter is perhaps the most important headline to watch out for as we gear towards US-China talks over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With Trump having touted to &quot;go out and buy stocks&quot;, one can expect him to deliver something in the day ahead to vindicate his own message. And a show of goodwill by lowering China tariffs might be just that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And let&apos;s face it, markets will lap it all up as the buy the rumour trade goes into overdrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;However, make no mistake. Even at 50-60% tariff levels, there&apos;s still much pain and friction still in play with regards to US-China trade. Sure, there are exemptions and workarounds to circumvent the tariffs. And the 10% blanket tariffs elsewhere are basically an off-ramp for Trump as trade with China is facing a stall. It essentially allows for US firms to seek alternatives and substitutes but again, these things take time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The thing here is that while markets might find comfort in Trump offering &quot;relief&quot; on tariffs and a &quot;friendlier&quot; gesture towards China before talks, it&apos;s still a big question mark as to whether Beijing will be willing to see that as a positive step. If anything, one would expect China to want all tariffs taken off the table before sitting down to talk. And that&apos;s a risk to watch out for going into the talks over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So even with a supposed gesture of goodwill by reducing tariffs to 50-60%, it&apos;s not necessarily going to be an inviting proposition for China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The bigger picture points to some form of further decoupling between the two countries and that&apos;s not optimistic for the global economy. But again, that&apos;s something that markets will need time to digest and to see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;When you take a step back, it&apos;s rather amazing what Trump has managed to achieved in the last month or so. He has pretty much hoodwinked markets into accepting 10% blanket tariffs as a good thing, not to mention the likely further decoupling between US and China in the meantime. It&apos;s pretty much Stockholm syndrome at its finest and given the playbook above, it wouldn&apos;t be surprising to see markets take to it again later today.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Kugler: The US labour market is stable, close to maximum employment</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-kugler-the-us-labour-market-is-stable-close-to-maximum-employment-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-kugler-the-us-labour-market-is-stable-close-to-maximum-employment-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The US labour market is stable, close to maximum employment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Past two recoveries suggest 3.5% unemployment sustainable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;She delivered a very comprehensive speech on the topic of &quot;Assessing Maximum Employment&quot; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/speech/kugler20250509a.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Such speeches are always a learning experience for the newcomers.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Barr: We need to be in a wait and see approach</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-we-need-to-be-in-a-wait-and-see-approach-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 10:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-we-need-to-be-in-a-wait-and-see-approach-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Fair to say that uncertainty around tariffs have raised risks to higher inflation, lower growth&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Growth has been strong over the last year and remains so today&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This just continues from his earlier remarks &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-monetary-policy-is-in-a-good-position-to-adjust-as-conditions-unfold-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Barkin: Tariffs to lead to higher inflation and lower growth in US and abroad</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-barkin-tariffs-to-lead-to-higher-inflation-and-lower-growth-in-us-and-abroad-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 10:18:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-barkin-tariffs-to-lead-to-higher-inflation-and-lower-growth-in-us-and-abroad-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs to lead to higher inflation and lower growth in US and abroad.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump tariffs are without modern precedent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Given economic strength, monetayr policy is in a good position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m concerned that tariffs will lead to higher unemployment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economic outlook clouded by trade policies that have increased uncertainty, hurt consumers and business sentiment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are just token remarks by Barkin as nobody at the Fed seems to be willing to offer anything in terms of forward guidance or at least personal expectations. Only Fed&apos;s Waller laid out what would be his strategy depending on the tariffs outcome and right now his &quot;more hawkish&quot; scenario is playing out. It remains to be seen though if other countries will accept the 10% tariff rate or take a harder stance.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Barr: Monetary policy is in a good position to adjust as conditions unfold</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-monetary-policy-is-in-a-good-position-to-adjust-as-conditions-unfold-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 09:57:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-monetary-policy-is-in-a-good-position-to-adjust-as-conditions-unfold-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Economic outlook clouded by trade politics that have increased uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Tariffs to lead to higher US inflation, lower growth starting later this year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Fed may be in a difficult position if both inflation and unemployment rise&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Equally concerned tariffs will lead to higher unemployment as economy slows&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Tariffs could create persistent upward pressure on inflation by disrupting supply chains&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Too soo to know how tariffs will affect the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There&apos;s nothing new here that hasn&apos;t already been said or needs clarification. The Fed dug in and held its ground this week and the comments above reflect that position, as policymakers continue to mull over the impact of Trump&apos;s tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC reaffirms that it will implement moderately loose monetary policy</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-reaffirms-that-it-will-implement-moderately-loose-monetary-policy-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 09:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-reaffirms-that-it-will-implement-moderately-loose-monetary-policy-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will expand domestic demand, stabilise expectations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will maintain ample liquidity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To grasp the strength and pace of policy implementation with flexibility&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will keep prices at reasonable levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will further improve framework of interest rate adjustment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To maintain yuan exchange rate basically stable at reasonable, balanced level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;These are the usual volley of comments by the PBOC. It comes after taking big action earlier this week as seen &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-1-uschina-to-meet-on-trade-2-china-rate-cuts-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU&apos;s von der Leyen says had a good conversation with Trump</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eus-von-der-leyen-says-had-a-good-conversation-with-trump-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 09:50:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eus-von-der-leyen-says-had-a-good-conversation-with-trump-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;But if I go to the White House, I want to have a package, solution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In other words, there&apos;s really not much to talk about for now between the EU and the US on any deal.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How have interest rates expectations changed after the first trade deal?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-first-trade-deal-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-first-trade-deal-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 68 bps (83% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 56 bps (89% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 56 bps (79% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 42 bps (54% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 100 bps (99% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 71 bps (66% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 35 bps (89% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 13 bps (97% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We can see that compared to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-interest-rate-expectations-for-the-major-central-banks-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Wednesday&apos;s update&lt;/a&gt;, the market is repricing expectations on a more hawkish side across the board. This is because the certainty around the 10% global rate has increased after the US-UK trade deal and it&apos;s also the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/federal-reserve-governor-wallers-strategy-for-dealing-with-tariffs-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;&quot;more hawkish&quot; scenario&lt;/a&gt; for the Fed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have now reached the peak in the &quot;de-escalation trade&quot; and the focus will likely switch to the language from other countries, especially the EU. Will they take a harder stance and oppose categorically the 10% floor? &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India reportedly offers to cut tariffs gap by two-thirds to seal trade deal with the US</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-reportedly-offers-to-cut-tariffs-gap-by-two-thirds-to-seal-trade-deal-with-the-us-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-reportedly-offers-to-cut-tariffs-gap-by-two-thirds-to-seal-trade-deal-with-the-us-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It is being reported that India is offering to slash its tariffs gap with the US to below 4% (currently 13%) in exchange for an exemption to Trump&apos;s tariffs. To achieve that, India is said to be offering to reduce duties to zero on 60% of tariff lines in the first phase of the deal. This will help to reduce the average tariff differential between the two countries by about 9% in favour of the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For some context, India was slapped with an initial 26% tariffs before the 90-day pause as they run a large trade surplus of $45.7 billion with the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;One of the sources also add that India has offered preferential access to almost 90% of goods imported from the US, including the reduced tariffs. And considering where they are in talks, India and Japan are the next two countries in line to finalise a deal. The source says that &quot;we will see which one crosses the line first&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I&apos;m not sure being able to brag about getting a deal that quickly is all that is cracked up to be in this circumstance. It&apos;s more important to be getting the right deal. And what this says essentially is that India is asking for a full tariffs exemption while offering a host of concessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;We&apos;ll see how that works since Trump and Lutnick have both said that 10% tariffs are &quot;the best&quot; one can get. It&apos;s amazing how at the end of this all, Trump has hoodwinked the world into accepting 10% blanket tariffs across the board as being a good thing. Talk about Stockholm syndrome.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoE&apos;s Bailey: Our commitment to the 2% inflation target is unwavering</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-bailey-our-commitment-to-the-2-inflation-target-is-unwavering-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:44:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-bailey-our-commitment-to-the-2-inflation-target-is-unwavering-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our commitment to the 2% inflation target is unwavering.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It is good we have a diversity of views on MPC.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will use scenarios as vehicles for exploring risks around the baseline and accomodating differences of views on the committee.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The latest choice of BoE scenarios does not mean inflation risk skewed in one direction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are on course to put inflation surge firmly behind us.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Global economic environment is likely to continue to be challenging and less predictable that it was in the past.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK-US trade deal will leave effective tariff rate higher than where they started.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK-US Trade Deal &apos;Good News&apos;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economic impact of tariffs on UK depends a lot on what rest of the world agrees with the US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are putting quite a bit of weight on forward-looking survey evidence showing easing wage inflation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a reminder, the BoE cut the bank rate by 25 bps as expected yesterday with a &quot;more hawkish&quot; vote split as two members, including BoE&apos;s Mann, voted for no change. The market now sees a less dovish path for the central bank with 56 bps of easing priced in by year-end.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Simkus: Eurozone inflation depends on EU retaliation to the US</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-simkus-eurozone-inflation-depends-on-eu-retaliation-to-the-us-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:23:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-simkus-eurozone-inflation-depends-on-eu-retaliation-to-the-us-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurozone inflation depends on EU retaliation to the US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Geopolitics since the starts of the year is bad news for the economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is downward pressure on inflation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Need to watch for China goods rerouting to Europe.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB June projections may be a little bit worse.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;June ECB cut is needed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is no central scenario for ECB rates.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s unclear if a post-June cut will be in July or September.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are more or less there on inflation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Quite high chances we&apos;ll be undershooting on inflation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that the US has made it clear that the 10% tariff rate is the floor, the ball is in EU&apos;s court. Will they take a more hawkish stance?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nippon Steel says position on planned acquisition of US Steel remains unchanged</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/nippon-steel-says-position-on-planned-acquisition-of-us-steel-remains-unchanged-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:49:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/nippon-steel-says-position-on-planned-acquisition-of-us-steel-remains-unchanged-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Taking all stake continues to be the starting point for negotiations with the US government&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;We are presenting a range of proposals in talks with the US government&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;CFIUS expected to make a recommendation to US Steel deal to Trump by 21 May&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;A decision by Trump is expected by 5 June&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;At least now we have some key dates to attach to how things are playing out on this matter. As a reminder, Biden blocked the deal as one of his final acts as president. And in his most recent comments last month, Trump said that &quot;we don&apos;t want to see it go to Japan&quot;. So, there&apos;s that.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We might have reached the peak in the de-escalation trade</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/we-might-have-reached-the-peak-in-the-de-escalation-trade-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:33:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/we-might-have-reached-the-peak-in-the-de-escalation-trade-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;If this trade deal with the UK was announced two or three weeks ago, I would have said that it&apos;s really good for the markets and would have been very upbeat on risk sentiment. The context is a bit different now, in my opinion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recall back in the middle of April, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/federal-reserve-governor-wallers-strategy-for-dealing-with-tariffs-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Waller&lt;/a&gt; outlined his strategy to deal with tariffs. He had two scenarios in mind: tariffs around 25% on average and tariffs around 10%. The second scenario is the one that is playing out and it involves the Fed being less inclined to cut rates faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the market is taking this first trade deal as the more hawkish scenario for the Fed and the pricing is converging towards the original Fed&apos;s baseline of two rate cuts in 2025 (the pricing is now showing 68 bps by year-end compared to 80 bps at the start of the week). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem here is that with new information throughout the weeks, the 10% has become a &quot;meh&quot; outcome. After April 9 pause, the market rallied on expectations that eventually the US would have gone for 10% reciprocal tariffs and would have lowered the tariffs on China back to the original 50-60% rate. This is what the whole &quot;de-escalation trade&quot; was based on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have now reached the peak in this trade because the US said that the 10% will be the floor for all other deals and we got a report from New York Post yesterday saying that the US is considering lowering the tariffs on China to 50-54%. Recall, the market was expecting 10% global tariffs and 50% on China before the April 2 surprise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this should now be priced in and the market&apos;s reaction to the news of the US lowering tariffs on China could be a hint. In fact, you would have expected a strong rally, but the market actually went in the opposite way. Nonetheless, this has opened up for a weekend risk scenario in which the market opens up with a positive gap next week, so the selling pressure into the weekend could be limited (I mean it doesn&apos;t look good from a risk management perspective for the bears).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what makes this first trade deal a &quot;meh&quot; outcome is that not only we have some overstretched positioning but we also have the risk of retaliation now. The EU has been repeating that they won&apos;t accept the 10% tariff rate and has been threatening a retaliation in case negotiations fail. But the US is saying that 10% is the best anyone can get and tariffs could be even higher. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next week will be the tell. If we open up with a positive gap and the stock market then performs badly throughout the week, then it could be a signal that we have indeed reached the peak (at least in the short term). I would expect the bears to seize the opportunity and start selling at the start of the week. You either catch the top or you get it wrong, but from a risk/reward perspective it doesn&apos;t look bad at all. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equities open higher to start the final day of the week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-open-higher-to-start-the-final-day-of-the-week-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:10:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-open-higher-to-start-the-final-day-of-the-week-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;US futures are also keeping steadier, with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures seen up 0.1%. The US-UK trade deal agreement yesterday helped to steady the ship but it was mostly comments from Trump that caused markets to rally. His mentions of &quot;better go out and buy stocks now&quot; and &quot;the stock market will really rally now&quot; were what got the animal spirits pumped up.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDJPY Technical Analysis – Waller’s scenario #2 is playing out. Now what?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-wallers-scenario-2-is-playing-out-now-what-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:00:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-wallers-scenario-2-is-playing-out-now-what-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD got a boost across
the board yesterday on positive expectations about the first trade deal that
eventually was revealed to be with the UK. Trump &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-reached-breakthrough-deal-with-uk-20250508/&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt;
that tariffs on cars and steel will be lowered but the most important part was
that the 10% “global tariff” will remain in place. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US officials
highlighted that the 10% is going to be the floor and the trade deal with the
UK is going to be the baseline for all other deals. There’s a risk now that we
reached the peak in de-escalation and other countries might not like the 10%
floor, especially the EU. For now, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/federal-reserve-governor-wallers-strategy-for-dealing-with-tariffs-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Federal Reserve Governor Waller’s scenario&lt;/a&gt;
#2 is playing out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recall, that he said 10% or
lower tariffs would make him less inclined to cut rates faster. This is now triggering
a repricing in interest rates as the market scaled back the easing expectations
to 68 bps by year-end. We were at more than 80 bps at the start of the week. It
gave also the greenback a boost as the market unwound the crowded dollar
shorts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the JPY side, the
currency has been driven mainly by global events rather than domestic
fundamentals. Alongside the Swiss Franc, it’s been the favoured safe haven in
the currencies space amid the swings in risk sentiment. On the monetary policy
front, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;BoJ&lt;/a&gt; kept interest rates unchanged as expected and
delivered a dovish message. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was then echoed by BoJ
Governor Ueda which placed a great deal on trade developments. In summary, the
central bank is likely to go faster on rate hikes in case we get a good trade
deal and delay rate adjustments in case the trade deal disappoints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that USDJPY continues to erase the April losses and it’s now approaching
the major trendline. The sellers will likely lean on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt; with a defined risk above it to
position for a drop back into the 140.00 handle, while the buyers will look for
a break higher to increase the bullish bets into the 151.00 handle next. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see that we have now an upward trendline defining the bullish structure on this
timeframe. From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a better
risk to reward setup around the trendline, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into new lows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor upward trendline defining the bullish momentum on this
timeframe. The buyers will likely continue to lean on the trendline to keep pushing
into new highs, while the sellers will look for a break lower to extend the
pullback into the next trendline. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Rehn: Disinflation is on track and the growth outlook is weakening</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-rehn-disinflation-is-on-track-and-the-growth-outlook-is-weakening-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-rehn-disinflation-is-on-track-and-the-growth-outlook-is-weakening-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The usual commentary is continuing by the ECB for the time being. Traders are pricing in a ~90% probability of a rate cut for their next policy decision in June. So, there&apos;s not much change to the rhetoric and narrative for now.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China foreign ministry reaffirms that US should respect international trade rules</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-foreign-ministry-reaffirms-that-us-should-respect-international-trade-rules-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:48:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-foreign-ministry-reaffirms-that-us-should-respect-international-trade-rules-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This is as what you&apos;d expect from China ahead of the talks tomorrow. The question now is, are we going to see the US drop its tariff levels before both sides sit down at the table over the weekend? It&apos;s certainly a consideration, particularly after this report &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/white-house-weighing-plan-to-slash-china-tariffs-to-as-low-as-50-report-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That will help to at least try and build a starting point for trade discussions. But knowing China, they won&apos;t accept anything less than going back to where things were before. So, we&apos;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:21:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, we have a pretty empty agenda with just a couple of low tier data releases that won&apos;t be market-moving. In the American session, we get the Canadian Employment report which is expected to show 2.5K jobs added in April and the Unemployment Rate to tick higher to 6.8% vs. 6.7% prior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s the day after the outline of the first trade deal and we have expectations for the US lowering the tariffs on China over the weekend so that&apos;s gonna be the main theme going into the weekend. As always, watch out for tariff related news throughout the day, especially potential retaliatory threats from other countries (EU) as the US stated that the 10% rate is going to be the floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:40 GMT/04:40 ET - BoE&apos;s Bailey (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;09:55 GMT/05:55 ET - Fed&apos;s Barr (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10:45 GMT/06:45 ET - Fed&apos;s Kugler (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:30 GMT/08:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Barkin (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:30 GMT/08:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Williams (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;14:00 GMT/10:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Goolsbee (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;15:30 GMT/11:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Waller (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;23:45 GMT/19:45 ET - Fed&apos;s Cook (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;23:45 GMT/19:45 ET - ECB&apos;s Schnabel (neutral - voter)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +0.3% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-03-in-early-european-trading-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:09:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-03-in-early-european-trading-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are seen up 0.1% following the gains yesterday, though the run higher in Wall Street was rather middling in the end. Looking to the day ahead, all eyes will be on any headlines in the build up to US-China talks over the weekend. You can surely expect Trump to say something before we wrap things up on the week.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 9 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-9-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 05:31:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-9-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There are a couple to take note of on the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The first one is for EUR/USD at the 1.1200 mark. Amid a firmer dollar, the expiries here could help to act as a bit of a floor for price action before we get to US trading. That is considering the likely quieter period in European trading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Then, there is one for USD/JPY at the 145.00 level but it isn&apos;t one that ties to any technical significance. But the expiries could also keep a floor on price action, amid some extension of the range in play during the session ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;However, dollar and broader risk sentiment remains the bigger driver at the moment. So if we do see risk pick up, expect that to underpin the greenback as well with the expiries taking a backseat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All eyes today though will be on any follow up trade headlines ahead of US-China talks over the weekend. That overrides everything else before we look to close out the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *EL SALVADOR BUYS MORE BITCOIN: THE BITCOIN OFFICE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920595591895175500#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 21:44:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920595591895175500#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*EL SALVADOR BUYS MORE BITCOIN: THE BITCOIN OFFICE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *LUTNICK: IF COUNTRIES OPEN MARKET, BEST THEY CAN DO IS 10%

*LUTNICK: DE-ESCALATION, BRINGING RATES DOWN IS GOAL FOR CHINA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920574832124559833#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:21:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920574832124559833#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*LUTNICK: IF COUNTRIES OPEN MARKET, BEST THEY CAN DO IS 10%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*LUTNICK: DE-ESCALATION, BRINGING RATES DOWN IS GOAL FOR CHINA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) LUTNICK ON TARIFFS: AS YOU GET TO BIGGER ECONOMIES, MORE WORK, TAKES TIME</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920574546169475078#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:20:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920574546169475078#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LUTNICK ON TARIFFS: AS YOU GET TO BIGGER ECONOMIES, MORE WORK, TAKES TIME&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *LUTNICK ON TRADE DEALS: THINK WE&apos;LL GET THERE BY JULY 8</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920574498685723085#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:20:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920574498685723085#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*LUTNICK ON TRADE DEALS: THINK WE&apos;LL GET THERE BY JULY 8&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *VANCE: MUSK IS NOT DISAPPEARING, MORE WASTE CAN BE FOUND</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920565913989833106#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:46:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920565913989833106#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*VANCE: MUSK IS NOT DISAPPEARING, MORE WASTE CAN BE FOUND&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP SEEKS TAX HIKE ON WEALTHY WHO EARN $2.5 MILLION OR MORE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920565006715748663#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:42:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920565006715748663#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP SEEKS TAX HIKE ON WEALTHY WHO EARN $2.5 MILLION OR MORE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) VANCE: TRUMP IS RIGHT ABOUT JEROME POWELL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920564923832139945#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:42:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920564923832139945#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;VANCE: TRUMP IS RIGHT ABOUT JEROME POWELL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) VANCE SAYS U.S. WOULD WALK AWAY FROM RUSSIA, UKRAINE TALKS IF IT CONCLUDES RUSSIA IS NOT ENGAGING &apos;IN GOOD FAITH&apos; -FOX NEWS INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920564815732392387#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:41:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920564815732392387#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;VANCE SAYS U.S. WOULD WALK AWAY FROM RUSSIA, UKRAINE TALKS IF IT CONCLUDES RUSSIA IS NOT ENGAGING &apos;IN GOOD FAITH&apos; -FOX NEWS INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) S&amp;P: TARIFF UNCERTAINTY COULD PUSH BACK FED RATE MOVES TO LATE 2025</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920564721989656715#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:41:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920564721989656715#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P: TARIFF UNCERTAINTY COULD PUSH BACK FED RATE MOVES TO LATE 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP ADMIN WEIGHS CHINA TARIFF CUTS AHEAD OF SWISS TALKS: NYP

 *CHINA TARIFFS COULD BE SLASHED TO 50%-54% NEXT WEEK: NYP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920559663889695073#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:21:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920559663889695073#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP ADMIN WEIGHS CHINA TARIFF CUTS AHEAD OF SWISS TALKS: NYP&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
 *CHINA TARIFFS COULD BE SLASHED TO 50%-54% NEXT WEEK: NYP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CELSIUS FOUNDER ALEX MASHINSKY GETS 12 YEARS FOR CRYPTO FRAUD</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920559436432650426#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920559436432650426#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CELSIUS FOUNDER ALEX MASHINSKY GETS 12 YEARS FOR CRYPTO FRAUD&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) META IN TALKS TO DEPLOY STABLECOINS AFTER ABANDONING LANDMARK CRYPTO PROJECT: FORTUNE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920556210136240232#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:07:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920556210136240232#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;META IN TALKS TO DEPLOY STABLECOINS AFTER ABANDONING LANDMARK CRYPTO PROJECT: FORTUNE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *NAVARRO: WE&apos;RE GOING TO TAKE GOOD CARE OF BOEING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920550851849937363#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:46:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920550851849937363#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*NAVARRO: WE&apos;RE GOING TO TAKE GOOD CARE OF BOEING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: I DON&apos;T THINK I WILL TALK TO PUTIN IN SAUDI ARABIA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920544857258406075#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:22:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920544857258406075#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: I DON&apos;T THINK I WILL TALK TO PUTIN IN SAUDI ARABIA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ON ELECTION OF AMERICAN POPE:  LOOK FORWARD TO MEETING POPE LEO XIV. IT WILL BE A VERY MEANINGFUL MOMENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920530899080249782#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:27:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920530899080249782#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ON ELECTION OF AMERICAN POPE:  LOOK FORWARD TO MEETING POPE LEO XIV. IT WILL BE A VERY MEANINGFUL MOMENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ON ELECTION OF AMERICAN POPE:  IT IS SUCH AN HONOR TO REALIZE THAT HE IS THE FIRST AMERICAN POPE.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920530837537231048#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:26:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920530837537231048#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ON ELECTION OF AMERICAN POPE:  IT IS SUCH AN HONOR TO REALIZE THAT HE IS THE FIRST AMERICAN POPE.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
