<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>What if you took the Trump trade quite literally?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-if-you-took-the-trump-trade-quite-literally-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:28:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-if-you-took-the-trump-trade-quite-literally-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Here&apos;s a graphical depiction of the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Trump&apos;s statements about buying stocks in the last few weeks:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And now, markets are rallying further as the US and China lower tariffs in favour of discussions - at least for the next 90 days. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up over 2.5% on the day, we&apos;re slated to open just above the 5,800 mark. If that holds, Trump&apos;s message from Thursday last week will again yield another positive follow through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And if you really took to his first message of it being &quot;THIS IS A GREAT TIME TO BUY!!!&quot; before the reciprocal tariffs pause announcement, the return would&apos;ve been roughly 16% as we get to the open later today.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More from BoE&apos;s Lombardelli: Latest US-China discussions are good news</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-lombardelli-latest-us-china-discussions-are-good-news-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-lombardelli-latest-us-china-discussions-are-good-news-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Latest US-China discussions are good news, if reports are accurate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Progress on domestic inflation, not US tariffs, was the main factor behind my rate vote.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trade policy uncertainty will continue until there&apos;s a permanent solution.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK GDP data is volatile, makes it hard to gauge if weakness is due to demand or supply.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US-China news is without a doubt the news of the day and most likely of the week. They brought down tariffs by much more than expected, so that&apos;s a positive for global growth expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It could end up fuelling some inflation in the short-term, so that&apos;s going to be something to watch out for because it could force the central banks to take a longer pause on rate adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrimeXBT Introduces VIP Tiers with Up to 50% Trading Fee Discounts for Active Traders</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/primexbt-introduces-vip-tiers-with-up-to-50-trading-fee-discounts-for-active-traders-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:21:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/primexbt-introduces-vip-tiers-with-up-to-50-trading-fee-discounts-for-active-traders-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;PrimeXBT, a
regulated multi-asset broker, has announced the launch of its VIP Tiers, a
trading-based rewards system designed to lower trading costs for high-volume
traders. With discounts of up to 50% now available, the new system brings
enhanced flexibility and cost efficiency to trading across a wide range of
markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VIP Tiers are applied automatically based on a trader&apos;s
30-day cumulative trading volume across Crypto Futures, Forex, and CFDs on
Indices, Commodities, Stocks, and Crypto. Traders who reach the volume
milestone for VIP Tier 1 are instantly upgraded, unlocking a 25% discount on
Crypto Futures and CFD trading costs. The tier status remains locked for 30
days but can still be upgraded to VIP Tier 2, offering a 40% discount on Crypto
Futures and a 50% discount on CFD trading costs, once the trading volume criteria
is met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to PrimeXBT, the introduction of VIP Tiers gives
traders a clear and motivating way to lower trading costs the more they trade.
The tier system is designed to be accessible for active retail traders while
also catering to institutional participants across diverse markets. The broker
views this launch as a major step toward creating a more inclusive and
rewarding environment for high-volume traders of all kinds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This update reflects PrimeXBT’s ongoing commitment to
competitive conditions and long-term client trust. By providing full insight
into how trading fee discounts are calculated and when they apply, the company
strengthens its promise of fairness and clarity across its trading platforms. To
learn more, users can visit PrimeXBT website (https://primexbt.com).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About PrimeXBT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PrimeXBT is a
leading Crypto and CFD broker that offers an all-in-one trading platform to
buy, sell, and store Cryptocurrencies, and trade over 150 popular markets,
including Crypto Futures and CFDs on Crypto, Forex, Indices, Commodities, and
Stocks using both fiat and Crypto funds. Since its founding in 2018, PrimeXBT
has grown exponentially, serving 1,000,000+ traders in 150+ countries
worldwide. With an aim of making investing available to all, PrimeXBT lowers
the barriers to entry, providing easy and secure access to the financial
markets with industry-leading trading conditions and innovative tools. Clients
engage with a regulated financial services provider recognized for its
reliability and commitment to offering cost-efficient trading solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The content provided here is for informational purposes
only and is not intended as personal investment advice and does not constitute
a solicitation or invitation to engage in any financial transactions,
investments, or related activities. Past performance is not a reliable
indicator of future results. The financial products offered by the Company are
complex and come with a high risk of losing money rapidly due to leverage.
These products may not be suitable for all investors. Before engaging, you should
consider whether you understand how these leveraged products work and whether
you can afford the high risk of losing your money. The Company does not accept
clients from the Restricted Jurisdictions as indicated on its website. Some
products and services, including MT5, may not be available in your
jurisdiction. The applicable legal entity and its respective products and
services depend on the client’s country of residence and the entity with which
the client has established a contractual relationship during registration.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOE&apos;s Lombardelli: Caution remains appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-lombardelli-caution-remains-appropriate-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-lombardelli-caution-remains-appropriate-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Evidence suggests that policy is still restrictive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wage growth is still too high for on target inflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wages is my main focus when looking for disinflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Further gradual disinflation progress and trade developments made 25 bps rate cut appropriate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just some token remarks here and ones that won&apos;t matter all too much as trade headlines are drowning out everything else at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNB total sight deposits w.e. 9 May CHF 453.2 bn vs CHF 454.1 bn prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-9-may-chf-4532-bn-vs-chf-4541-bn-prior-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-9-may-chf-4532-bn-vs-chf-4541-bn-prior-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Domestic sight deposits CHF 444.8 bn vs CHF 443.1 bn prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just some light changes in sight deposits in the past week. But the SNB can definitely take in some comfort now from the latest developments today surely.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best case scenario for the US Dollar is playing out</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-best-case-scenario-for-the-us-dollar-is-playing-out-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-best-case-scenario-for-the-us-dollar-is-playing-out-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Last week, I&apos;ve laid out a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-could-be-dead-wrong-on-rate-cuts-if-this-scenario-plays-out-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;case&lt;/a&gt; where the market could end up being &quot;dead wrong&quot; on interest rates expectations and that scenario is playing out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 10% baseline tariff rate on UK last week, kind of made me to turn up my nose, but the US-China announcement is much better than everyone expected and it will likely lead to positive global growth expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main point is that we&apos;ve been hearing and seeing from the economic reports that businesses 
are cautious due to tariff uncertainty and that&apos;s holding back activity.
 With such positive resolutions, economic activity will pick up fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fed could be even more constrained because there will be upward 
pressure on inflation and the economic data will start to show a strong 
rebound in activity justifying a cautious approach to rate adjustments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They will definitely deliver at least one rate cut, but they could end up with just that one cut in 2025. At the peak of the risk off sentiment last month, the market was pricing like 5 rate cuts by year-end and now we are back to 2 rate cuts (55 bps).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, we are back to where we were before the April 2 announcement and how the economy evolves from now on will determine if we indeed get just one cut or the two the Fed projected in December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this is of course a positive for the US Dollar in the short-term, especially since the USD short trade was one of the most crowded ones, but once we are done with the repricing in interest rates expectations, the focus will turn back to global growth and the positive sentiment could weigh on the greenback again.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: UK, Switzerland have moved to the front of the queue on trade deals</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-uk-switzerland-have-moved-to-the-front-of-the-queue-on-trade-deals-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:36:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-uk-switzerland-have-moved-to-the-front-of-the-queue-on-trade-deals-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s a chance if we can open up trade to China, we could have more fair trade towards the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China has not yet rebalanced towards a consumption-oriented economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And that&apos;s the end of the press conference. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are up 2.8% on the day, up from around 1.5% gains before the joint statement and briefing. Meanwhile, the dollar is much higher across the board with USD/JPY near 147.50 - up 1.5% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar surges higher as US, China bring down tariff levels for further talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-surges-higher-as-us-china-bring-down-tariff-levels-for-further-talks-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:33:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-surges-higher-as-us-china-bring-down-tariff-levels-for-further-talks-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;USD/JPY is now up nearly 1.5% on the day to 147.50 as the dollar is jumping higher across the board. EUR/USD is also marked down by over 1% now to 1.1120 with GBP/USD down 0.8% to test waters back under 1.3200 on the day. This comes with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures bordering on 3% gains while gold is down 2.9% on the day to $3,229 currently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The moves here are coming as the US and China issues a joint statement in confirming that both sides are reducing the reciprocal/retaliatory tariff levels by 115%. On the US side, they&apos;ll still be charging China with 30% tariffs overall. On the Chinese side, they&apos;ll be charging the US with 10% base level tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All of this of course will be for 90 days, for now at least, as both sides seek to engage on further trade talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I would say barring any major implosion in talks, that 90 days is subjective and can be kicked down the road unless one side loses patience with the other. And we all know who is more likely to be the one that does. So, just be wary of that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For now at least, it&apos;s all sunshine again in markets as the biggest known unknown sees a significant de-escalation. That being said, it&apos;s all about perception isn&apos;t it? Even with the tariffs reduction here, the effective tariff rate in the US is still going to be the highest since the 1940s. So, make what you will of that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But for market sentiment, this market has been desperate for good news from US-China relations for quite a number of weeks now. And now that we finally get it, you can see the sort of elation in the immediate aftermath at least.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greer: We have a constructive path forward to have a positive conversation with China</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/greer-we-have-a-constructive-path-forward-to-have-a-positive-conversation-with-china-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/greer-we-have-a-constructive-path-forward-to-have-a-positive-conversation-with-china-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This agreement is about reciprocal tariffs, which are now at 10% each&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We ended up with a result that is very good for the US and China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There was no discussion on currency (Bessent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It is the first time that the Chinese understood the US&apos; position on fentanyl (Bessent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are leaving with a very good mechanism to avoid the kind of escalation we saw in the past weeks (Bessent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar and risk trades are continuing to ramp higher on the headlines here as both Bessent and Greer are painting a very optimistic picture of what took place over the weekend and how things might pan out moving forward. USD/JPY is now up 1.3% to 147.20 while S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are nearing 3% gains on the day now.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: We have reached agreement with China on a 90-day pause, moving down tariff levels</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-have-reached-agreement-with-china-on-a-90-day-pause-moving-down-tariff-levels-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:09:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-have-reached-agreement-with-china-on-a-90-day-pause-moving-down-tariff-levels-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both sides will move reciprocal/retaliatory tariffs down by 115%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both sides very committed to 90-day pause period (Greer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An effective trade embargo was not sustainable practice for both sides (Greer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Throughout the trade process, we have had a plan in place&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;And now, we have a mechanism for continued talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The consensus this weekend is that neither side wants a decoupling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We do want more balanced trade, would like to see China open to more US goods&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As negotiations move forward, think there is a possibility to see purchase agreements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Look forward to very good discussions now that there is the mechanism in place for talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s a significant climb down from a trade embargo of course. But again, now all of this hinges on how talks will develop over the next 90 days. But unless things really go south, that timeline is one that I expect can be postponed time and time again. In the meantime though, Trump has done quite the job in hoodwinking the world into accepting the highest effective tariff levels in the US since the 1940s (even with this latest reduction) as being a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *S&amp;P 500 UP 2.5%, NASDAQ UP 3.1% AFTER US-CHINA TARIFF REDUCTION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921824299620450796#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:06:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921824299620450796#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*S&amp;amp;P 500 UP 2.5%, NASDAQ UP 3.1% AFTER US-CHINA TARIFF REDUCTION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *BESSENT SAYS NEITHER US NOR CHINA WANT TO DECOUPLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921824190153335016#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921824190153335016#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*BESSENT SAYS NEITHER US NOR CHINA WANT TO DECOUPLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US to lower tariffs on China, to include a base 10% plus 20% fentanyl levy</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-to-lower-tariffs-on-china-to-include-a-base-10-plus-20-fentanyl-levy-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-to-lower-tariffs-on-china-to-include-a-base-10-plus-20-fentanyl-levy-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US to modify application of the rate of duty on articles of China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This will be for an initial period of 90 days&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China will also suspend its tariffs on the US for an initial period of 90 days&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Only a 10% base tariffs rate will be applied&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A mechanism to continue discussions about economic and trade relations is established&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These discussions may be conducted alternately in China and the US, or in an agreed third country&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both sides may conduct working-level consultations on relevant economic and trade issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/articles/2025/05/joint-statement-on-u-s-china-economic-and-trade-meeting-in-geneva/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Full statement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Risk is ramping up on the headlines here with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures now up by 2.5% on the day. Essentially, the US to cut tariffs on China from 145% to 30%. Meanwhile, China is lowering theirs from 125% to 10%. This will apply for a period of 90 days for now as both sides look to discuss further on how to seek further progress in trade negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US TO CUT TARIFFS ON CHINESE GOODS TO 30% FROM 145% FOR 90 DAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921823273337167882#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921823273337167882#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US TO CUT TARIFFS ON CHINESE GOODS TO 30% FROM 145% FOR 90 DAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA TO LOWER TARIFFS ON US GOODS TO 10% FROM 125% FOR 90 DAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921823088166977844#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921823088166977844#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA TO LOWER TARIFFS ON US GOODS TO 10% FROM 125% FOR 90 DAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch: Bessent and Greer to brief on US-China talks in Geneva</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/watch-bessent-and-greer-to-brief-on-us-china-talks-in-switzerland-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:59:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/watch-bessent-and-greer-to-brief-on-us-china-talks-in-switzerland-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – Positive trade talks weigh on the precious metal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-positive-trade-talks-weigh-on-the-precious-metal-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:58:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-positive-trade-talks-weigh-on-the-precious-metal-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold ended the last week
negatively, as first the positive expectations for the US-UK trade deal, and
then for the US-China talks over the weekend, weighed on the precious metal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the bigger picture, gold
remains in an uptrend as real yields will likely continue to fall amid Fed
easing. But in the short-term positive news on the trade front or a hawkish Fed
could trigger more downside for gold as the market prices out stagflationary
fears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that gold continues to pull back amid the positive news on the trade front.
From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a better risk to
reward setup around the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt;, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into the 2957 level next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see the price fell all the way back to the key &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-support-and-resistance-20220405/&quot;&gt;support&lt;/a&gt; around the 3258 level. This is where we can
expect the buyers to step in with a defined risk below the level to position
for a rally back into the 3367 resistance. The sellers, on the other hand, will
look for a break lower to increase the bearish bets into the major trendline
next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor downward trendline now defining the current pullback. If
the price gets there, we can expect the sellers to lean on the trendline with a
defined risk above it to position for further downside. The buyers, on the
other hand, will look for a break higher to increase the bullish bets into new
highs. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we get the US-China trade talks briefing. Tomorrow,
we have the US CPI report. On Thursday, we get the latest US Jobless Claims
figures, the US PPI and the US Retail Sales data. On Friday, we conclude the
week with the University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq Analysis for Today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/nasdaq-analysis-for-today-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:30:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/nasdaq-analysis-for-today-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;&gt;Nasdaq Analysis for Today: Bulls Take Charge Post US-China Trade Talks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current Nasdaq Futures Price: $20,558 (+2.1% from Friday&apos;s close)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Context After US-China Trade Talks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasdaq futures are bullishly positioned today following moderately positive news from the weekend’s US-China trade talks. The optimistic sentiment has investors seeking opportunities to &quot;buy the dip&quot; rather than anticipating a bearish reversal. With a favorable geopolitical backdrop, the tradeCompass today underscores strategic entry points leveraging volume profile and VWAP indicators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Educational Insight: Volume Profile and VWAP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volume Profile:
Volume Profile visually represents trading activity at specific price levels, revealing where significant trading volume occurred. The Point of Control (POC) highlights the price level with the highest traded volume, often serving as strong support or resistance. The Value Area (VA), comprising approximately 70% of trading activity, indicates prices viewed as fair value by market participants. Traders use these zones to identify high-probability trade entries and exits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP (Volume Weighted Average Price):
VWAP shows the average price at which transactions occur throughout the trading day, adjusted by volume. Acting as a benchmark, prices above the VWAP signal bullish strength, while those below suggest bearish pressure. Traders often look to join bullish trends on pullbacks toward the VWAP or its standard deviation bands, as it reflects a fair market valuation supported by volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Bullish Entry Points for Nasdaq Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering today&apos;s bullish bias, traders could target the following support levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,495 - Today&apos;s Developing VWAP: Ideal for initial pullback entry, representing fair intraday pricing supported by volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,450 - Today&apos;s POC &amp;amp; Semi-Round Number: Offers even stronger support due to high accumulated volume and psychological significance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,425 - Today&apos;s Value Area Low: Represents the lower bound of fair value, providing attractive risk-reward potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,327 - May 8th Value Area High: Deep pullback level providing excellent bullish re-entry potential if reached.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intraday Bullish Targets for Nasdaq Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should bullish momentum continue, traders may aim for these price levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,572 &amp;amp; $20,613: Immediate upside targets at today&apos;s 2nd and 3rd upper VWAP standard deviations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,725: Further bullish target corresponding to the January 13 pivot low, achievable with sustained buying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Longer-term traders can also monitor the psychological $21,000 target, potentially within reach this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearish Reversal Scenario (Lower Probability)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While currently less likely, prudent traders must remain prepared for potential reversals. Watch for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decisive bearish signal would be two consecutive 30-minute candle closes below $20,300. Such a move would invalidate today&apos;s bullish scenario.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key bearish targets in this scenario: $20,270, $20,215 (May 2 POC), $20,167 (Friday&apos;s VWAP), and ultimately $19,855–$19,800 in a deeper bearish move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;tradeCompass Summary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bias: Bullish after positive US-China trade discussions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Entries: Look to buy dips around volume-supported key levels ($20,495, $20,450, and $20,425).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Targets: Immediate bullish targets at VWAP upper deviations ($20,572 &amp;amp; $20,613), and potential higher swing target at $20,725.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caution Point: Monitor the critical $20,300 level closely as a bullish-bearish pivot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trader Education Recap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Utilize Volume Profile to pinpoint market-validated fair value zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use VWAP to confirm intraday price strength and optimize your entry points around its dynamic bands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Always remain adaptive, setting stop-losses and adjusting positions if the market narrative changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: Use this analysis as orientation. Always trade at your own risk, using a disciplined strategy tailored to your risk tolerance and trading style.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-China tariff reductions reportedly will exceed 100%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-tariff-reductions-reportedly-will-exceed-100-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:28:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-tariff-reductions-reportedly-will-exceed-100-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Phoenix TV is out with the headline, citing a source familiar with the matter. This is also being aired across Twitter/X now but there&apos;s yet to be a more credible source echoing the headline yet. Just be wary of that in case. But if true, that&apos;s a significant reduction as there was some expectation that tariffs will be reduced to around 50-60% - which is still a relative disruption. So if the tariff levels are to be below that, it will be a much welcome stance in facilitating negotiations between the two sides.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:11:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Today, the calendar is empty on the data front as we will just hear from some central bank members. It would have been a boring day if it wasn&apos;t for the US-China trade talks statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 07:00 GMT/03:00 ET, we have the US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent briefing on the US-China trade talks held in Switzerland over the weekend. This is going to be the main event of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sentiment is positive going into the event as both sides delivered upbeat remarks. Nonetheless, we might have reached the peak in the &quot;de-escalation trade&quot;, so we will likely need very good news to keep the party going. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:00 GMT/04:00 ET - BoE&apos;s Lombardelli (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10:30 GMT/06:30 ET - BoE&apos;s Greene (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:50 GMT/08:50 ET - BoE&apos;s Mann (hawkish - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;16:00 GMT/12:00 ET - BoE&apos;s Taylor (dovish - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +1.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-11-in-early-european-trading-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:09:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-11-in-early-european-trading-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +1.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are also up 1.5% on the day, largely holding gains much compared to the dollar from earlier in the day. All eyes will be on Bessent&apos;s brief later at the top of the hour as we also await the joint statement from both US and China after the talks over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heads up: Bessent to speak on China talks at 0700 GMT</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-bessent-to-speak-on-china-talks-at-0700-gmt-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:33:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-bessent-to-speak-on-china-talks-at-0700-gmt-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just a heads up as there will be headline risk to watch out for soon enough. Coincidentally, the timing also matches up with when China will normally comment on international affairs. So, do be on the lookout for that as well. This was Bessent&apos;s remarks yesterday on the matter:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“I’m happy to report that we made substantial progress between the United States and China in the very important trade talks. First, I want to thank our Swiss host. The Swiss government has been very kind in providing us this wonderful venue, and I think that led to a great deal of productivity we’ve seen. We will be giving details tomorrow, but I can tell you that the talks were productive. We had the vice premier, two vice ministers, who were integrally involved, Ambassador Jamieson, and myself. And I spoke to President Trump, as did Ambassador Jamieson, last night, and he is fully informed of what is going on. So, there will be a complete briefing tomorrow morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Outlook for the week of 12th - 16th May</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-12th-16th-may-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:24:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-12th-16th-may-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Monday will be a light day in terms of scheduled economic events. On Tuesday, Japan will release the BoJ summary of opinions; in the U.K., we’ll get the claimant count change, the average earnings index 3m/y, and the unemployment rate. In the U.S., the main focus will be on the inflation data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, Australia will release the wage price index q/q and on Thursday the employment change and the unemployment rate. Also on Thursday, in the U.K. we&apos;ll get the GDP m/m and the preliminary GDP q/q figures and in the U.S., the PPI m/m, retail sales m/m and unemployment claims. Fed Chair Powell will speak at the Second Thomas Laubach Research Conference in Washington, D.C. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, on Friday, we’ll get the preliminary UoM consumer sentiment and inflation expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the U.S., the consensus for the core CPI m/m is 0.3% vs. the prior 0.1%; for the CPI m/m, it is 0.3% vs. the prior -0.1%; and the CPI y/y is expected to remain unchanged at 2.4%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month’s decline in the monthly reading was due to softness in volatile categories such as energy, travel, and lodging, which are areas affected by economic uncertainty, government austerity, and anticipation of tariff changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While similar headwinds persisted into April, seasonal patterns and the early effects of tariffs, particularly on auto prices, may begin to push core goods inflation higher, according to analysts from Wells Fargo. However, the full impact of the tariff policies will not yet be visible in inflation this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Australia, the consensus for the wage price index q/q is 0.8% vs. the prior 0.7%. In the December quarter, wage growth came in below analyst forecasts and the market consensus.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, annual wage inflation declined from 3.6% to 3.2% in the previous quarter. This week’s data is not expected to show improvement, and the outlook remains subdued; however, the annual rate is expected to hold steady at 3.2%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consensus for the employment change in Australia is 20.9K vs. the prior 32.2K, while the unemployment rate is expected to remain unchanged at 4.1%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; In March, employment rose by 32.2K, but was flat in Q1 2025 overall. According to Westpac analysts, the uneven monthly prints likely reflect softer population growth, which has also contributed to a decline in labour force participation from recent highs. Given the ongoing moderation in population growth, a modest employment increase in April is likely to keep the employment-to-population ratio steady. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent labour force data has shown a notable shift in participation, with the rate falling from a peak of 67.2% in January to a more stable 66.7–66.8% range in recent months. This emerging downtrend appears cyclical, likely reflecting reduced pressure on households to seek additional work as inflation eases and cost-of-living concerns begin to subside. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The expectation for participation to remain at 66.8%, along with an unchanged unemployment rate at 4.1%, reflects the resilience of the labour market amid softer population and employment growth, according to Westpac. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of monetary policy, the RBA will continue monitoring labour market data alongside inflation, which has been softening. The bank is expected to proceed with gradual rate cuts of likely one per quarter, with analysts forecasting additional 25 bps cuts at the August and November meetings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the U.S., the consensus for core retail sales m/m is 0.3% vs. the prior 0.5%, while retail sales m/m are expected to be flat at 0.0% vs. the prior 1.4%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent rise in retail sales was largely driven by households accelerating big-ticket purchases, especially autos, in anticipation of upcoming tariffs, evidenced by a 5.3% surge in vehicle sales. However, strength extended beyond tariff-sensitive categories: restaurant spending rose 1.8%, and the control group (which feeds directly into GDP) posted a solid 0.4% gain, suggesting underlying consumer momentum remains strong, according to Wells Fargo analysts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, the sustainability of consumer spending will depend on whether March’s strength was primarily due to front-loaded demand. If purchases for big-ticket items like vehicles were pulled forward, it could lead to softer spending in the coming months as households scale back. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, early reports indicate that auto sales remained robust in April, likely delaying any major slowdown. As a result, retail sales for April are expected to post a modest overall gain, with non-auto categories rising a steady 0.3%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Gina Constantin at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One good reason to be optimistic of US-China talks over the weekend</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/one-good-reason-to-be-optimistic-of-us-china-talks-over-the-weekend-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:13:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/one-good-reason-to-be-optimistic-of-us-china-talks-over-the-weekend-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;When Trump talks something up, you can bet that there&apos;s always going to be exaggeration to the story. Not least with talks with China, we&apos;ve already gotten a precedent for that back in 2019. This time around is no different of course as he said that both sides &quot;had a very good meeting&quot; over the weekend. However, the big difference this time is actually the response from the Chinese camp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;More often than not, you&apos;ll see China refute claims by the US on how talks are progressing. Or even denying the fact that any talks were taking place, as they did in the weeks prior to this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But now, both sides are expected to produce a joint statement - which is a rarity on its own - after talks in Switzerland. And China is sounding rather upbeat about the situation as well, which supports Trump&apos;s narrative too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The timing of the statement remains unclear but China is saying that: &quot;If the dish is delicious, then the timing is not a matter.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Adding that: &quot;No matter when this statement is released, it&apos;s going to be big news and good news for the world.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With headlines like that, it is little wonder to see why risk trades are looking more exuberant to start the new week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All that being said, the devil will still be in the details. Most reports are indicating that there is some form of agreement of sorts, but the Chinese state media has said that both sides have agreed to &quot;establish an economic and trade consultation mechanism&quot;. And that this will be the main platform as the US and China now move towards negotiating their positions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In other words, the positive thing now is that both sides are showing keen interest to engage in further talks. However, there&apos;s still some ways to go before expecting any grand deal or the likes of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the meantime, we&apos;ll have to see what this means on the existing 145% tariffs. Trump touted &quot;a total reset&quot; but it&apos;s still not clear if that means in both sides&apos; intentions to negotiate or whether that applies to existing tariff levels as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;My guess would be the joint statement should allude to some form of easing on tariffs as both sides seek to negotiate progress by a certain timeline. But again, whether or not there will be actual progress, remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Come what may, we might just get a repeat of the Phase One trade deal from Trump&apos;s first term. And that was a complete failure to say the least. Six years down the road, and we&apos;re still talking about further decoupling between both countries. Nothing&apos;s changed.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Analysis for Today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-analysis-for-today-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:10:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-analysis-for-today-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Analysis for Today: tradeCompass Highlights Critical Levels Near $104,265&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s Bitcoin Futures (BTC) are trading at approximately $104,265, slightly below today&apos;s Volume Weighted Average Price (VWAP) at $104,530, signaling mild intraday bearish momentum. However, since the trading session is still developing, this early bearish signal remains tentative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;tradeCompass Levels for May 12, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish Above: $104,735&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Positioned above today&apos;s developing Value Area High (VAH) at $104,630.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More importantly, above the third upper standard deviation of Friday’s VWAP, indicating significant bullish momentum if crossed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$105,200 - Below today&apos;s second VWAP deviation, providing a cautious first profit-taking zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$105,540 - Just under today&apos;s third VWAP deviation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$108,200 - A more ambitious target assuming bullish continuation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearish Below: $103,920&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Located below the first upper deviation of Friday&apos;s VWAP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below today&apos;s Value Area Low (VAL) at $104,070, signaling potential bearish sentiment if breached.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearish Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$103,590 - Near Friday&apos;s VWAP, suggesting a moderate initial downside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$103,140 - Just above Friday&apos;s VAL.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$102,360 - Above Thursday&apos;s VAH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$101,850 - Near Thursday&apos;s Point of Control (POC), where high volume indicates strong historical trading interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$100,450 - Just above Thursday&apos;s VWAP, crucially close to the psychologically significant $100,000 level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding Volume Profile and VWAP in tradeCompass Analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volume Profile:
Volume profile analysis helps traders visualize areas of significant buying and selling activity at specific price levels. Levels with high traded volume, known as &quot;Points of Control&quot; or &quot;Value Areas,&quot; often act as strong support or resistance due to the accumulated market interest. Traders monitor these areas carefully to predict price reversals or continuations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP (Volume Weighted Average Price):
VWAP represents the average price weighted by volume throughout the trading session. It&apos;s a critical benchmark for institutional traders and is often used as a dynamic support or resistance level. Standard deviation bands around VWAP indicate normal trading ranges, providing actionable insights into potential price extremes. Crossing these bands can signal robust momentum and trend shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Context: Revisiting the $100K Level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin recently surpassed the major psychological level of $100,000. Historically, price tends to revisit significant milestones before confirming directional moves. Market makers utilize these levels to trigger stop orders, thereby increasing trading volatility. Consequently, despite the recent bullish breakout, a retest around $100K remains highly probable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium-term sentiment is slightly bearish, suggesting possible consolidation or pullback before any sustained upward movement. However, the longer-term perspective still favors an eventual revisit of the all-time high near $110,150.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Practical Application of tradeCompass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use the provided bullish and bearish thresholds strategically:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch how price action unfolds near these key levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider partial profit-taking at designated targets to manage risk effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintain flexibility in trading strategies, adapting to real-time market signals and volume indications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Always manage your risk prudently, using tradeCompass as a directional guide complemented by your personalized trading tactics and timeframes.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 12 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-12-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 04:53:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-12-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There are a couple to take note of on the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The first being for EUR/USD at the 1.1250 level. It isn&apos;t one that ties to any technical significance but the expiries do sit nearby the gap closure level after the pair opened with a gap down today. The dollar is in a better spot amid positive news from US-China talks over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I wouldn&apos;t place too much emphasis on the expiries today as such, with headline risks being paramount. We&apos;re still waiting for the joint-statement by the US and China on what the next steps will be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There&apos;s also one for USD/JPY at the 145.65 level but again, it&apos;s not one that ties to any technical significance either. As such, the impact of the expiries might be more muted as dollar and risk sentiment remain bigger drivers of how price action will behave in the session(s) ahead. That especially with headline risks also still taking center stage at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For now, the risk mood remains optimistic as equities race higher but dollar gains have not been all too material. There&apos;s a difference in levels to the exuberance so we&apos;ll have to see who has it right at the end of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs has raised its forecast for China&apos;s yuan</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-has-raised-its-forecast-for-chinas-yuan-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 03:34:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-has-raised-its-forecast-for-chinas-yuan-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs forecasts USD/CNY to dropping to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; 7.20 in 3 months &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;7.10 in six months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;7 over the next 12 months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs sees China&apos;s exports remaining strong. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; “The undervalued levels of the currency, both on a real trade-weighted basis but especially versus the dollar, all point to the possibility for a stronger onshore yuan as a potential offset to tariff reductions” &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Info comes via a Bloomberg (gated) piece on a GS note on Friday. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: US &amp; China officials upbeat on trade talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-us-china-officials-upbeat-on-trade-talks-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 03:24:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-us-china-officials-upbeat-on-trade-talks-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-ibit-sees-the-longest-streak-of-net-inflow-this-year-so-far-20250512/&quot;&gt;BlackRock&apos;s spot bitcoin ETF, IBIT, sees the longest streak of net inflow this year so far&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-england-speakers-monday-lombardelli-greene-mann-taylor-20250512/&quot;&gt;Bank of England speakers Monday: Lombardelli, Greene, Mann, Taylor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-autos-agriculture-airplane-parts-are-all-separate-from-security-matters-20250512/&quot;&gt;Japan PM Ishiba: Autos, agriculture, airplane parts are all separate from security matters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72066-vs-estimate-at-72429-20250512/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.2066 (vs. estimate at 7.2429)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-forecasts-brentwti-average-6056-in-the-rest-of-2025-and-5652-in-2026-20250512/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs forecasts - Brent/WTI average $60/56 in the rest of 2025, and $56/52 in 2026&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/awaiting-the-joint-statement-from-china-and-the-us-on-geneva-trade-talks-no-time-set-20250512/&quot;&gt;Awaiting the joint statement from China and the US on Geneva trade talks - no time set&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-april-bank-loans-rise-slower-than-march-march-current-account-surplus-as-expected-20250512/&quot;&gt;Japan: April bank loans rise slower than March; March current account surplus as expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korean-initial-exports-data-for-may-down-238-yy-in-first-10-days-of-the-month-20250512/&quot;&gt;South Korean initial exports data for May - down 23.8% y/y in first 10 days of the month&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-monday-12-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Monday, 12 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-hiring-outlook-hits-post-covid-low-as-employer-confidence-weakens-20250511/&quot;&gt;UK hiring outlook hits post-COVID low as employer confidence weakens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-for-chinese-president-xi-to-speak-publicly-on-may-13-20250511/&quot;&gt;Heads up for Chinese President Xi to speak publicly on May 13&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-prescription-drug-and-pharma-prices-will-be-reduced-almost-immediately-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trump says prescription drug and pharma prices will be reduced almost immediately&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-equity-index-futures-liking-the-vibes-from-us-and-china-officials-20250511/&quot;&gt;US equity index futures liking the vibes from US and China officials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/globex-is-open-us-equity-index-futures-open-higher-20250511/&quot;&gt;Globex is open! US equity index futures open higher.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ft-chinese-companies-accelerating-a-purge-of-foreign-components-from-their-supply-chains-20250511/&quot;&gt;FT: Chinese companies accelerating a purge of foreign components from their supply chains&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-chinese-cpi-and-ppi-data-over-the-weekend-showed-risk-of-further-deflation-spiral-20250511/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Chinese CPI and PPI data over the weekend showed risk of further deflation spiral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-geneva-trade-talk-meeting-a-first-step-differences-frictions-remain-win-win-20250511/&quot;&gt;China says Geneva trade talk meeting a first step; differences &amp;amp;frictions remain; win-win&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/no-details-on-us-china-trade-talks-but-both-us-and-china-officials-are-upbeat-20250511/&quot;&gt;No details on US-China trade talks but both US and China officials are upbeat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-he-is-about-to-make-one-of-the-most-important-and-impactful-tweet-ever-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trump says he is about to make &quot;one of the most important and impactful&quot; tweet ever!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/monday-open-levels-indicative-fx-prices-may-12-2025-usdjpy-up-eurusd-down-20250511/&quot;&gt;Monday open levels, indicative FX prices, May 12, 2025 - USD/JPY up, EUR/USD down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/trump-tweets-great-progress-in-us-china-trade-talks-but-final-deal-remains-uncertain-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trump Tweets &quot;Great Progress&quot; in U.S.-China Trade Talks - But Final Deal Remains Uncertain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-sends-a-positive-message-on-trade-with-china-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trump sends a positive message on trade with China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-and-pakistan-declare-immediate-ceasefire-20250510/&quot;&gt;India and Pakistan declare immediate ceasefire&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-there-is-a-baseline-of-10-tariffs-but-could-be-excemptions-20250509/&quot;&gt;Trump: There is a baseline of 10% tariffs but could be excemptions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-canadian-jobs-market-continues-to-crack-20250509/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Canadian jobs market continues to crack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
US
and China initial trade talks wrapped up in Geneva on Sunday with
positive comments coming from both sides. In summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
China
side:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
	a
	mechanism for further talks has been agreed (agreed to establish a
	&apos;China-US trade consultation mechanism&apos;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
	the
	joint statement to come will be &quot;good news for the world&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
US
side:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
	Bessent
	said there had been &quot;substantial progress&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
	Greer
	said that &quot;perhaps the differences were not so large as maybe
	thought&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
two will issue a joint statement on Monday, no time for it has been
confirmed, where more details are promised. US equity futures gapped
higher upon reopening for the week and have not shown much
retracement at all. Hopes are up for substantive details of
improvement in China-US trade relations. Hopes have risen before and
dashed, so we’ll how this goes today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Across
FX USD/JPY gapped higher and has partially retraced. EUR/USD gapped
lower and has fully filled that gap. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Oil
gapped higher and has retraced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Further,
Fed rate cut bets faded back a little and gold dipped. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Also
of news, Trump says he’ll sign an executive order, at 9 am US
Eastern time on Monday, slashing US prescription drug prices by up to
80%,. Trump wants to align US prices with the world’s lowest,
calling it a long-overdue fix for fairness. Aligning US prices with
the world’s lowest sounds a very ambitious goal. Doubts have been
raised about courts blocking such moves. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;From
Japan today we had Prime Minister  Ishiba saying that the he would
not accept a trade agreement with the US that excludes auto tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock&apos;s spot bitcoin ETF, IBIT, sees the longest streak of net inflow this year so far</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-ibit-sees-the-longest-streak-of-net-inflow-this-year-so-far-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 02:28:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-ibit-sees-the-longest-streak-of-net-inflow-this-year-so-far-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Crypto &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theblock.co/post/353873/goldman-sachs-boosts-ibit-holdings-by-28-as-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-logs-longest-inflow-streak-of-2025&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;media &lt;/a&gt;with the report:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Goldman Sachs is now the largest holder of shares of IBIT, BlackRock’s spot bitcoin ETF, after boosting its holdings by 28% over the course of 2025’s first quarter. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
IBIT’s 20-day streak of net inflows is the longest such streak for any spot bitcoin ETF in 2025, drawing in over $5 billion over the period. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BTC update, such flows helping to underpin the price:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: PRESCRIPTION DRUG AND PHARMACEUTICAL PRICES WILL BE REDUCED, ALMOST IMMEDIATELY, BY 30% TO 80%

TRUMP: U.S. WILL PAY THE SAME PRICE AS THE NATION THAT PAYS THE LOWEST PRICE ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.

TRUMP: WILL SIGN ORDER AT WHITE HOUSE AT 9 A.M. ON MONDAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921694636399026416#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:31:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921694636399026416#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: PRESCRIPTION DRUG AND PHARMACEUTICAL PRICES WILL BE REDUCED, ALMOST IMMEDIATELY, BY 30% TO 80%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: U.S. WILL PAY THE SAME PRICE AS THE NATION THAT PAYS THE LOWEST PRICE ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: WILL SIGN ORDER AT WHITE HOUSE AT 9 A.M. ON MONDAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: PRESCRIPTION DRUG &amp; PHARMA PRICES WILL BE REDUCED 30-80%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921694261151482212#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:29:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921694261151482212#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: PRESCRIPTION DRUG &amp;amp; PHARMA PRICES WILL BE REDUCED 30-80%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. 10-YEAR TREASURY FUTURES FALL 9 TICKS, FED FUND FUTURES FURTHER TRIM RATE CUTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921688786032836844#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:08:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921688786032836844#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. 10-YEAR TREASURY FUTURES FALL 9 TICKS, FED FUND FUTURES FURTHER TRIM RATE CUTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) DOLLAR UP 0.5% AT 146.20 YEN IN EARLY TRADE AMID US-CHINA TRADE HOPES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921680053743632839#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 21:33:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921680053743632839#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DOLLAR UP 0.5% AT 146.20 YEN IN EARLY TRADE AMID US-CHINA TRADE HOPES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RELEASE OF ISRAELI-AMERICAN HOSTAGE EDAN ALEXANDER TO HAPPEN ON TUESDAY, SOURCE FAMILIAR WITH THE MATTER TELLS REUTERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921648656618336725#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 19:28:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921648656618336725#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RELEASE OF ISRAELI-AMERICAN HOSTAGE EDAN ALEXANDER TO HAPPEN ON TUESDAY, SOURCE FAMILIAR WITH THE MATTER TELLS REUTERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINESE OFFICIAL IN GENEVA SAYS PROGRESS IN US TRADE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921636363788591264#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:39:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921636363788591264#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINESE OFFICIAL IN GENEVA SAYS PROGRESS IN US TRADE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA, US AGREED TO ESTABLISH TRADE CONSULTATION MECHANISM: RTRS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921636317282128354#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:39:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921636317282128354#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA, US AGREED TO ESTABLISH TRADE CONSULTATION MECHANISM: RTRS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: BOTH SIDES AGREED TO ESTABLISH CHINA-U.S. TRADE CONSULTATION MECHANISM</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921636066735313078#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921636066735313078#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: BOTH SIDES AGREED TO ESTABLISH CHINA-U.S. TRADE CONSULTATION MECHANISM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: BOTH SIDES REACHED IMPORTANT CONSENSUS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921636000129786365#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921636000129786365#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: BOTH SIDES REACHED IMPORTANT CONSENSUS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: TRADE TALKS WERE CONSTRUCTIVE, MADE SUBSTANTIVE PROGRESS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921635937659813970#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:38:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921635937659813970#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: TRADE TALKS WERE CONSTRUCTIVE, MADE SUBSTANTIVE PROGRESS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: ON CHINA-U.S. TRADE TALKS, BOTH SIDES HAD IN-DEPTH EXCHANGE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921635875655458839#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:37:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921635875655458839#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: ON CHINA-U.S. TRADE TALKS, BOTH SIDES HAD IN-DEPTH EXCHANGE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA OFFICIALS HOLD PRESS CONFERENCE IN GENEVA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921635729123238297#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:37:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921635729123238297#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA OFFICIALS HOLD PRESS CONFERENCE IN GENEVA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: NEXT TRUTH WILL BE ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT EVER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921634572158079220#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:32:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921634572158079220#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: NEXT TRUTH WILL BE ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT EVER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ZELENSKIY SAYS: I WILL MEET PUTIN IN TURKEY ON THURSDAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921612432838959406#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 17:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921612432838959406#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ZELENSKIY SAYS: I WILL MEET PUTIN IN TURKEY ON THURSDAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: STARTING TO DOUBT THAT UKRAINE WILL MAKE A DEAL WITH PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921605758677922082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 16:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921605758677922082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: STARTING TO DOUBT THAT UKRAINE WILL MAKE A DEAL WITH PUTIN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *GREER: THIS WAS A VERY CONSTRUCTIVE 2 DAYS

*GREER: DIFFERENCES NOT AS GREAT AS PREVIOUSLY THOUGHT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921595928005193922#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:59:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921595928005193922#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*GREER: THIS WAS A VERY CONSTRUCTIVE 2 DAYS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*GREER: DIFFERENCES NOT AS GREAT AS PREVIOUSLY THOUGHT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
