<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US APRIL ISM SERVICES PMI RISES TO 51.6 FROM 50.8; EST. 50.2

US ISM SERVICES PRICE INDEX CLIMBS TO HIGHEST SINCE JAN. 2023</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919391808347324512#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:00:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919391808347324512#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US APRIL ISM SERVICES PMI RISES TO 51.6 FROM 50.8; EST. 50.2&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
US ISM SERVICES PRICE INDEX CLIMBS TO HIGHEST SINCE JAN. 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>April ISM services 51.6 vs 50.2 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/april-ism-services-516-vs-502-expected-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/april-ism-services-516-vs-502-expected-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/march-ism-services-508-vs-530-expected-20250403/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior &lt;/a&gt;was 50.8&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prices paid: 65.1 vs. 60.9 prior
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New orders: 52.3 vs. 50.4 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Employment: 49.0 vs. 46.2 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;whitespace-normal break-words&quot; index=&quot;3&quot;&gt;Business activity 53.7 vs 55.9 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;whitespace-normal break-words&quot; index=&quot;4&quot;&gt;Supplier deliveries 51.3 vs 50.6 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;whitespace-normal break-words&quot; index=&quot;5&quot;&gt;Inventories 53.4 vs 50.3 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;whitespace-normal break-words&quot; index=&quot;6&quot;&gt;Backlog of orders 48.0 vs 47.4 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;whitespace-normal break-words&quot; index=&quot;7&quot;&gt;New export orders 48.6 vs 45.8 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;whitespace-normal break-words&quot; index=&quot;8&quot;&gt;Imports 44.3 vs 52.6 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;whitespace-normal break-words&quot; index=&quot;9&quot;&gt;Inventory sentiment 56.1 vs 56.6 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comments in the report&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Sales and traffic have improved on track with year-over-year 
seasonal trends. We seem to be outperforming some of the publicly traded
 restaurants reporting results.” [Accommodation &amp;amp; Food Services]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Tariffs are negatively impacting small business customers. Many 
small business customers source their products from China. They cannot 
afford to compete in the marketplace sourcing from other countries. We 
could not move products fast enough to beat the tariff starting dates.” 
[Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing &amp;amp; Hunting]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Business is steady.” [Construction]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“There is great concern at my institution (medical school with a 
research institute and hospital) that changes from the current 
administration will severely and adversely affect many of the 
populations we are trying to help live healthier lives.” [Educational 
Services]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“We are actively reviewing the impact of tariffs. We are seeing some
 vendors increasing their prices, and we are actively pushing back on 
those increases. We expect our vendors to honor our contracted pricing.”
 [Health Care &amp;amp; Social Assistance]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Generally, pricing is lower, but there is some uncertainty of actual, final costs due to tariffs.” [Other Services]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Our business is in a state of crises with uncertainty caused by 
both the ongoing trade war and the threats to federal funding of 
programs.” [Public Administration]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Uncertainty remains the dominating theme as the U.S. government has
 been maddeningly inconsistent with tariff implementation.” [Real 
Estate, Rental &amp;amp; Leasing]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Tariffs and concerns about government grants still impacting our 
procurement operations. Some projects are slowing or being held off to 
ensure we have funds to complete the current work.” [Transportation 
&amp;amp; Warehousing]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;“The tariff uncertainty is causing a lot of consumption of human 
capital. We are starting to see some tariff charges, some are 
significant given the price of the highly specialized units that were 
ordered over two years ago. Based on our spend over the last couple of 
years, we will have to adjust our capital and operations and maintenance
 plans.” [Utilities]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;re seeing some bids in the US dollar in response to this report. USD/JPY is up to 143.90 from 143.66 while the euro has fallen 15 pips.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD runs above 200 day MA.  On pace for first close above since November 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-runs-above-200-day-ma-on-pace-for-first-close-above-since-november-2024-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:57:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-runs-above-200-day-ma-on-pace-for-first-close-above-since-november-2024-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;136&quot; data-end=&quot;551&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The AUDUSD is surging higher today and has convincingly broken above its 200-day moving average at 0.6461—a key technical milestone. On Friday, the pair briefly traded above this level for the first time since November 8, 2024, but bullish momentum faded, and the price settled back into a familiar swing area between 0.6427 and 0.6441. The Friday close landed near the upper end of that zone at 0.6441.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;553&quot; data-end=&quot;804&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In early Asian trading today, the low dipped to 0.64337, within that same swing zone, before buyers stepped back in. The price reclaimed the 200-day MA, briefly pulled back to retest it, then based and pushed to a fresh session high at 0.6493.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;806&quot; data-end=&quot;1074&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;With the pair now holding above the 200-day MA for a sustained period, 0.6461 becomes a key bias-defining support level. As long as the price remains above, the upside bias stays intact. Sellers gain no technical traction unless price breaks back below that level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1076&quot; data-end=&quot;1244&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the daily chart, the next upside target lies at the November 29 swing high of 0.65277, followed by the 61.8% retracement and high from November 25 at 0.6549 (see the chart below).&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. S&amp;P GLOBAL APRIL FINAL COMPOSITE PMI AT 50.6 (VS FLASH 51.2)

U.S. S&amp;P GLOBAL APRIL FINAL SERVICES PMI AT 50.8 (VS FLASH 51.4)</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919387927802446020#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:45:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919387927802446020#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. S&amp;amp;P GLOBAL APRIL FINAL COMPOSITE PMI AT 50.6 (VS FLASH 51.2)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
U.S. S&amp;amp;P GLOBAL APRIL FINAL SERVICES PMI AT 50.8 (VS FLASH 51.4)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April S&amp;P Global final services PMI 50.8 vs 51.4 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-sp-global-final-services-pmi-508-vs-514-prelim-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:45:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-sp-global-final-services-pmi-508-vs-514-prelim-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prelim was 51.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-march-sp-global-final-services-pmi-544-vs-543-prelim-20250403/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior &lt;/a&gt;was 54.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 50.6 vs 51.2 prelim and 53.5 prior -- weakest since Sept 2023&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slower activity growth was linked to similarly weaker gains
in new work during April&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expansion in staffing was &apos;marginal&apos;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The rate of inflation eased considerably from
March’s one-and-a-half year high to its weakest of 2025 so far&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, sentiment was at its lowest
level for two-and-a-half years and amongst the weakest since
the height of the pandemic in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chris Williamson, Chief Business Economist at S&amp;amp;P Global
Market Intelligence
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;While tariff announcements mean manufacturing dominates
the news, a worrying backstory is developing in the vastly
larger services economy, where business activity and hiring
have come closer to stalling in April amid plunging business
confidence.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;Business and consumer facing service providers alike, and
especially financial services firms, are reporting markedly
weaker growth prospects, citing intensifying uncertainty over
the economic outlook amid recent tariff announcements and
ongoing federal spending cuts.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&quot;A key area of weakness is slumping exports of services, which
is now falling at rate not seen since 2022, but domestic demand
is also reportedly waning as confidence slides lower.
&quot;Higher prices paid for imports due to tariffs are also driving
up service sector firms’ costs, feeding though to higher prices,
notably in consumer-facing industries such as restaurants and
hotels.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;The resulting bottom line from the services sector is a
heightened risk of stalling growth and rising inflation, or
stagflation.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PRICE HIKES FROM TARIFFS EXPECTED TO APPEAR IN MAY INFLATION REPORT: TD COWEN

The first signs of tariffs costs being passed through to consumers are expected to show up in the May inflation report, TD Cowen analysts say in a research note. The bulk of the impact should come over the summer as businesses and retailers begin to run out of low-cost inventories, the analysts say. Core inflation levels should remain subdued again in April, they say, due to a cooling in travel and hotel rates, and elevated retail inventories. Already-stretched consumers are in a difficult spot, facing either higher prices due to new tariffs or absorbing increased costs from shipping surcharges, the analysts say.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919387611568779301#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:44:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919387611568779301#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PRICE HIKES FROM TARIFFS EXPECTED TO APPEAR IN MAY INFLATION REPORT: TD COWEN&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The first signs of tariffs costs being passed through to consumers are expected to show up in the May inflation report, TD Cowen analysts say in a research note. The bulk of the impact should come over the summer as businesses and retailers begin to run out of low-cost inventories, the analysts say. Core inflation levels should remain subdued again in April, they say, due to a cooling in travel and hotel rates, and elevated retail inventories. Already-stretched consumers are in a difficult spot, facing either higher prices due to new tariffs or absorbing increased costs from shipping surcharges, the analysts say.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, NASDAQ DOWN 1.01 PCT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919387309872460126#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:42:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919387309872460126#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, NASDAQ DOWN 1.01 PCT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada April S&amp;P Global services PMI 41.5 vs 41.2 prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-sp-global-services-pmi-415-vs-412-prior-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:30:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-sp-global-services-pmi-415-vs-412-prior-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In March this index fell to 41.2 from 46.6, which was the lowest reading since June 2020. It bounced slightly here but that&apos;s hardly reassuring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite index 41.7 vs 42.0 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Job losses were recorded for
a fourth successive month&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A lack of present incoming new work meant firms were
generally willing to let employees leave without replacing
them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Firms chose on average to reduce
their selling prices for the first time in nearly four years&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Panellists reported that sales volumes had continued to
deteriorate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Backlogs of work were nonetheless reduced
markedly again as capacity remained more than sufficient to
deal with current workloads&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sure sounds like a recession and that the BOC needs to get ahead of the curve. This report doesn&apos;t get a great deal of attention in the market but maybe it should.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Smith, Economics Director at S&amp;amp;P Global Market
Intelligence, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“Canada’s service sector economy faced another
challenging month, with activity declining steeply and
new business volumes again down sharply. Firms again
linked these weak trends to widespread economic and
political uncertainty, in turn linked to trade policies
and, at the time of survey data collection, the general
election.
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“Service providers are hopeful that a more stable
business environment will have emerged in a year’s
time, but presently, given the lack of new work and
excess capacity at units, job losses were again reported.
Moreover, adding to the woes of service providers,
firms felt compelled to reduce their output charges for
the first time in over four years – despite input price
inflation remaining elevated as suppliers were again
reported to be reevaluating their list prices.”&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) APOLLO CEO ROWAN: WHAT TRUMP ADMIN IS DOING ON TARIFFS IS RIGHT BUT THE APPROACH IS WRONG</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919381693590385112#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:20:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919381693590385112#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;APOLLO CEO ROWAN: WHAT TRUMP ADMIN IS DOING ON TARIFFS IS RIGHT BUT THE APPROACH IS WRONG&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) APOLLO CEO ROWAN: IT IS POSSIBLE US WILL HAVE TWO QUARTERS OF NEGATIVE GROWTH</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919381574857920665#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:20:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919381574857920665#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;APOLLO CEO ROWAN: IT IS POSSIBLE US WILL HAVE TWO QUARTERS OF NEGATIVE GROWTH&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD sellers stay in control as moving averages cap rallies</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-sellers-stay-in-control-as-moving-averages-cap-rallies-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:19:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-sellers-stay-in-control-as-moving-averages-cap-rallies-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;153&quot; data-end=&quot;436&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCAD continues to trade with a bearish tilt as the 100-hour (1.38197) and 200-hour (1.38394) moving averages act as a ceiling for price action. Each of the last three upside attempts has stalled near these levels, reinforcing their role as risk-defining resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;438&quot; data-end=&quot;652&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;While lows have edged slightly lower, downside momentum has been limited. Still, the inability to build sustainable upside suggests sellers remain in control, especially while price stays below the moving averages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;654&quot; data-end=&quot;764&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A move above 1.38394 would shift the near-term bias, but until then, rallies remain opportunities for sellers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;654&quot; data-end=&quot;764&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Taking a broader look at the daily chart, the next key target below the low price from Friday comes in at 1.37415 which represents the 61.8% retracement of the move up from the 2023 low. It is also near swing lows from mid-October before the price started to race into the upside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;654&quot; data-end=&quot;764&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Another broader look from the daily chart has the back within the up-and-down consolidation range that prevailed from September 2022 until November 2024 (see red box on the chart below).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;766&quot; data-end=&quot;781&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;782&quot; data-end=&quot;905&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;782&quot; data-end=&quot;865&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;784&quot; data-end=&quot;865&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance (risk/bias-defining): 1.38197 (100-hour MA), 1.38394 (200-hour MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;866&quot; data-end=&quot;905&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;868&quot; data-end=&quot;905&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.3781 (low from April 14), 1.37698 (low from April 30), 1.37593 (low from May 2)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) APOLLO GLOBAL MANAGEMENT CEO MARC ROWAN: TRUMP TARIFFS HAVE GROUND THINGS TO A HALT IN SHORT TERM- CNBC INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919380497613881437#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:15:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919380497613881437#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;APOLLO GLOBAL MANAGEMENT CEO MARC ROWAN: TRUMP TARIFFS HAVE GROUND THINGS TO A HALT IN SHORT TERM- CNBC INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump&apos;s 100% Tariff on Foreign Movies: Impact on Entertainment Industry and NFLX Stock</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/trumps-100-tariff-on-foreign-movies-impact-on-entertainment-industry-and-nflx-stock-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:09:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/trumps-100-tariff-on-foreign-movies-impact-on-entertainment-industry-and-nflx-stock-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Investor Alert: 100% Tariff on Foreign Movies Announced&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former President Donald Trump has announced intentions to impose a 100% tariff on movies produced abroad entering the United States. Trump cited significant incentives offered by other countries to attract American filmmakers and studios, describing this as a threat to national security and domestic industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Commerce and the U.S. Trade Representative have been instructed to initiate this tariff process immediately. This development could significantly impact entertainment industry economics, international trade relations, and stock valuations within media and film production companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors should closely monitor companies heavily involved in international film production and distribution, as they could face increased costs and potential revenue disruption if such tariffs come into effect. Conversely, purely domestic studios and content producers might see relative benefits from reduced foreign competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;&gt;Following the announcement by former President Donald Trump regarding a proposed 100% tariff on foreign-produced movies entering the United States, significant industry concerns have emerged around implementation specifics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key questions being raised include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-spread=&quot;false&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will movies partially produced overseas, including those with some filming or post-production activities abroad, fall under this tariff?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are television series and streaming content, notably productions from major international operations like Netflix, subject to these tariffs?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The context behind this tariff originates from recent discussions at Mar-a-Lago involving actors Jon Voight, Sylvester Stallone, and Mel Gibson, aiming to address the decline in U.S. entertainment industry employment. Initially, the discussions centered around enhancing federal tax incentives for domestic film production. The tariff proposal appears to be an escalation, potentially designed to aggressively redirect production back to the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors should anticipate significant scrutiny and debate over the tariff’s specifics, and closely monitor responses from major media and streaming companies with significant international footprints. The policy could potentially reshape competitive dynamics within the entertainment sector, impacting both domestic and global media markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt; for further updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or should you buy the dip later at NFLX stock? Join us at investingLive Stocks Telegram Channel &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/investingLiveStocks&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;https://t.me/investingLiveStocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF fades after testing key resistance; sellers back in control</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-fades-after-testing-key-resistance-sellers-back-in-control-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-fades-after-testing-key-resistance-sellers-back-in-control-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;149&quot; data-end=&quot;264&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCHF continues to struggle with upside momentum after repeated failures near key technical resistance levels last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;266&quot; data-end=&quot;556&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Last week, the pair attempted to break above the high extreme at 0.8333 and move toward the 38.2% retracement of the March–April decline at 0.83505, but sellers held firm. That resistance zone has capped gains on multiple occasions, as shown by the numbered rejections on the chart (see red numbered circles).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;266&quot; data-end=&quot;556&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Having said that, the move lower on Friday also held the support against key swing area between 0.8195 and 0.8212 before rebounding toward the new convergences of 100 and 200 hour moving averages currently at 0.8257 and 0.8263 (blue and green lines on the chart above).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;558&quot; data-end=&quot;823&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Earlier today, USDCHF briefly traded above its 100-hour (blue) and 200-hour (green) moving averages, but bullish momentum quickly faded. The pair has since rotated back lower and now trades below both moving averages, signaling a more bearish bias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;825&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The pair also sits in the lower half of its recent consolidation range, underscoring the bearish tilt in the near term. The inability to sustain gains above the moving averages keeps sellers in control, with focus now on the support zone near 0.8195–0.8212. A break below this area could open the door toward the next swing area and lows from late April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1189&quot; data-end=&quot;1214&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1215&quot; data-end=&quot;1382&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1215&quot; data-end=&quot;1281&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1217&quot; data-end=&quot;1281&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.8257 (100 hour moving average), 0.82636 (200 hour moving average)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1334&quot; data-end=&quot;1382&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1336&quot; data-end=&quot;1382&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 0.8195-0.8212 (swing area support)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA’S INDUSTRIAL POLICY CLOSES TECH GAP, U.S. STUDY FINDS

A U.S. Chamber of Commerce–commissioned study finds that China’s decade-old “Made in China 2025” plan—once downplayed by Beijing—has been highly effective in reducing its reliance on imports and boosting global competitiveness in key tech sectors. Despite U.S. pressure during the 2018–2019 trade war, the strategy continued, backed by massive state support, tax breaks, and investment.

The report shows China has sharply cut import dependence in sectors like medical devices and renewables, and gained global market share in shipbuilding and robotics. Only a few areas, like commercial aircraft, still lag behind.

Experts warn this state-led model challenges the West, especially as subsidized Chinese goods flood global markets. The U.S. faces pressure to respond, but it’s unclear whether future trade talks will target these industrial policies directly.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919377904535752864#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919377904535752864#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA’S INDUSTRIAL POLICY CLOSES TECH GAP, U.S. STUDY FINDS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
A U.S. Chamber of Commerce–commissioned study finds that China’s decade-old “Made in China 2025” plan—once downplayed by Beijing—has been highly effective in reducing its reliance on imports and boosting global competitiveness in key tech sectors. Despite U.S. pressure during the 2018–2019 trade war, the strategy continued, backed by massive state support, tax breaks, and investment.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The report shows China has sharply cut import dependence in sectors like medical devices and renewables, and gained global market share in shipbuilding and robotics. Only a few areas, like commercial aircraft, still lag behind.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Experts warn this state-led model challenges the West, especially as subsidized Chinese goods flood global markets. The U.S. faces pressure to respond, but it’s unclear whether future trade talks will target these industrial policies directly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🔸 GOLDMAN SACHS EXPECTS THREE FED RATE CUTS

Goldman Sachs forecasts 25bp rate cuts in July, September, and October, citing recession risks from tariffs and trade uncertainty. Chief economist Jan Hatzius notes the Fed remains more cautious than markets expect. While the Fed has a higher bar for cuts than in 2019, Goldman believes rising unemployment could still prompt action—even with high inflation.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919373805194985729#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:49:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919373805194985729#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🔸 GOLDMAN SACHS EXPECTS THREE FED RATE CUTS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Goldman Sachs forecasts 25bp rate cuts in July, September, and October, citing recession risks from tariffs and trade uncertainty. Chief economist Jan Hatzius notes the Fed remains more cautious than markets expect. While the Fed has a higher bar for cuts than in 2019, Goldman believes rising unemployment could still prompt action—even with high inflation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US dollar slides as the ISM services report highlights Monday&apos;s agenda</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-dollar-slides-as-the-ism-services-report-highlights-mondays-agenda-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-dollar-slides-as-the-ism-services-report-highlights-mondays-agenda-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Happy Monday, unless you&apos;re &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-announces-more-tariffs-plans-100-tariff-on-all-movies-produced-overseas-20250504/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;part of the foreign film industry&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar is sliding today as we&apos;re reminded that the Commander in Chief is making it up as he goes along. EUR/USD is at he best levels of the day, up 60 pips to 1.1355 while USD/JPY edges below Friday&apos;s low and is down 117 pips to 143.75.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks look set to end a 9-day winning streak with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures down 0.8%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main item on the agenda is the 10 am ET release of the ISM services report for April. This one should capture the mood after tariffs but given that the manufacturing numbers held up ok and all indications are that services spending is fine, the stakes here are fairly low. The consensus is 50.2, down from 50.8 previously.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JAPAN CHIP TRADER RESTAR GIRDS FOR TRUMP TARIFFS WITH OVERSEAS EXPANSION - NIKKEI</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919368209708327371#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:26:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919368209708327371#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JAPAN CHIP TRADER RESTAR GIRDS FOR TRUMP TARIFFS WITH OVERSEAS EXPANSION - NIKKEI&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SPOT GOLD ROSE NEARLY 2.5% INTRADAY TO $3,320/OUNCE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919366964885025205#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:21:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919366964885025205#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPOT GOLD ROSE NEARLY 2.5% INTRADAY TO $3,320/OUNCE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USD is lower to kickstart the new trading day.A technical review of the 3 major pairs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-lower-to-kickstart-the-new-trading-daya-technical-review-of-the-3-major-pairs-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:16:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-lower-to-kickstart-the-new-trading-daya-technical-review-of-the-3-major-pairs-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The USD is lower to kickstart the new trading day. US stocks are lower. Yields are lower as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;83&quot; data-end=&quot;645&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;EURUSD:
Last week, the EURUSD fell below key daily support between 1.1271 and 1.12754, but the April 15 low at 1.12657 provided a firm floor, preventing further downside. The pair rebounded, and Friday&apos;s price action confirmed support held. In today’s trading, we&apos;ve seen a continuation of that bounce, with the pair moving higher from Friday’s close toward the 100-hour moving average at 1.1336 and the 200-hour moving average at 1.13515. A break above these levels would tilt the bias more bullishly, while holding below keeps sellers in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;647&quot; data-end=&quot;1261&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;USDJPY:
On Friday, USDJPY moved higher to test the 200-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, where momentum stalled. The pair then rotated lower but recovered into the midpoint of the day’s trading range by the weekly close. In today&apos;s session, the downside rotation has resumed, and the pair is now testing its rising 100-hour moving average at 143.83. This level is the key short-term barometer. A move below would be more bearish and shift focus to the 200-hour moving average at 143.37. Holding above, however, keeps buyers in play with potential for a move back toward the 144.50 area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;647&quot; data-end=&quot;1261&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;GBPUSD:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;647&quot; data-end=&quot;1261&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The GBPUSD is trading near the high for the day with the 100/200 hour MAs being tested at 1.33249.  The price is testing that level to start the US session for the week. Move above would be a more bullish tilt after holding those MAs on Thursday and Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;647&quot; data-end=&quot;1261&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A snapshot of the US stock market to start the new trading day is showing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industial average -275 points. On Friday the index rose 564.47 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index -48 points. Last Friday the index rose 82.53 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index -212 points. Last Friday the index rose 266.99 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market yields are mostly lower:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 year yield 3.795%, -4.5 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 year yield 3.895%, -3.6 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10 year yield 4.306% -1.4 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30 year yield 4.802%, +0.7 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says a deal with the US is achievable if the aim is to prevent nuclear arms</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/iran-says-a-deal-with-the-us-is-achievable-if-the-aim-is-to-prevent-nuclear-arms-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:11:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/iran-says-a-deal-with-the-us-is-achievable-if-the-aim-is-to-prevent-nuclear-arms-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;This comment shows why it&apos;s so hard to make a deal. It&apos;s so tough for Iran to trust that the US isn&apos;t trying to disarm them as a first step towards regime change. But the US can&apos;t trust Iran because it&apos;s building a nuclear weapon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately what happens probably comes down to one person -- Trump -- and his willingness to believe Iran or his willingness to go to war.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *IRAN: DEAL WITH US ACHIEVABLE IF AIM IS TO PREVENT NUCLEAR ARMS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919363496019370391#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:08:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919363496019370391#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*IRAN: DEAL WITH US ACHIEVABLE IF AIM IS TO PREVENT NUCLEAR ARMS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive European FX news wrap: Dollar remains soft, gold pushes up while oil slumps</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-dollar-remains-soft-gold-pushes-up-while-oil-slumps-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-dollar-remains-soft-gold-pushes-up-while-oil-slumps-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Headlines:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-pushes-back-above-3300-on-the-day-20250505/&quot;&gt;Gold pushes back above $3,300 on the day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-struggle-continues-as-opec-moves-to-further-boost-production-20250505/&quot;&gt;Oil struggle continues as OPEC+ moves to further boost production&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rate-expectations-changed-after-the-us-nfp-report-20250505/&quot;&gt;How have interest rate expectations changed after the US NFP report?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/vietnam-says-first-tariffs-negotiation-with-the-us-to-take-place-this-week-20250505/&quot;&gt;Vietnam says first tariffs negotiation with the US to take place this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-cpi-00-vs-02-yy-expected-20250505/&quot;&gt;Switzerland April CPI 0.0% vs +0.2% y/y expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-sentix-investor-confidence-81-vs-125-expected-20250505/&quot;&gt;Eurozone May Sentix investor confidence -8.1 vs -12.5 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-central-bank-plays-down-speculation-after-currency-surge-20250505/&quot;&gt;Taiwan central bank plays down speculation after currency surge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-central-bank-confirms-intervening-in-the-market-today-20250505/&quot;&gt;Taiwan central bank confirms intervening in the market today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-panetta-protectionism-threatens-to-weaken-prosperity-20250505/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Panetta: Protectionism threatens to weaken prosperity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/pboc-governor-pan-global-economic-uncertainties-are-rising-20250505/&quot;&gt;PBoC Governor Pan: Global economic uncertainties are rising&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;JPY leads, USD lags on the day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;European equities mixed; S&amp;amp;P 500 futures down 0.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields down 2 bps to 4.300%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold up 2.2% to $3,312.05&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude down 1.4% to $57.45&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin down 1.7% to $94,111&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It was a quieter session as markets will be looking to ease into the week ahead. Trade headlines continue to be the main thing to watch out for but later in the week, we&apos;ll also have the Fed policy decision in focus. Or should I say, Trump&apos;s reaction to the Fed keeping interest rates on hold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar is once again on the weaker side, with a surge in the Taiwanese dollar earlier in the day sparking speculation of revaluation among currencies against the greenback. Still, the dollar struggled against the majors with USD/JPY slipping back under 144.00 and EUR/USD keeping around 1.1340 currently - up 0.4% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In terms of data, we had Swiss inflation which missed on estimates. Headline annual inflation touched 0% for the first time since March 2021. And that is starting to put the focus back on deflation in Switzerland, which is likely to see negative rates return by the SNB to try and counteract that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides that, there wasn&apos;t too much else as we continue to wait on how trade talks are going between the US and the rest of the world. Coming up later this week, Vietnam will be meeting with US officials to discuss their terms. So, look out for that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the equities space, European indices aren&apos;t doing all too much amid a more mixed mood. But US futures are down, though it comes after a nine-day win streak. It is arguably just a breather as it is already a rarity to see nine straight days of gains, let alone ten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In other markets, gold is once again lighting up in a push above $3,300 while oil is pressured as OPEC+ seeks to boost output further and that saw prices open with a gap down by over 3% earlier before paring some of that losses.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $MSTR - MICROSTRATEGY PURCHASES 1,895 BITCOINS BETWEEN Apr 28 - May 04 AT AN AVERAGE OF $95,167 (TOTAL: $180.30M)</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919361854238835008#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:01:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919361854238835008#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23MSTR&quot;&gt;$MSTR&lt;/a&gt; - MICROSTRATEGY PURCHASES 1,895 BITCOINS BETWEEN Apr 28 - May 04 AT AN AVERAGE OF $95,167 (TOTAL: $180.30M)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PRESIDENTIAL SCHEDULE – MAY 5, 2025

🔸 9:00 AM – In-Town Pool Call (White House)
🔸 1:00 PM – Sports Announcement (Oval Office, Press Pool)
🔸 3:00 PM – Signs Executive Orders (Oval Office, Closed Press)
🔸 3:30 PM – Welcomes Returned Citizen (Oval Office, Closed Press)
🔸 6:55 PM – Departs for Trump National Golf Club (South Lawn, Open Press)
🔸 7:10 PM – Arrives at Golf Club (Closed Press)
🔸 7:30 PM – Attends MAGA Inc. Dinner (Closed Press)
🔸 9:20 PM – Departs Golf Club for White House (Closed Press)
🔸 9:35 PM – Arrives at White House (South Lawn, Open Press)</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919357897378611458#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:45:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919357897378611458#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENTIAL SCHEDULE – MAY 5, 2025&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 9:00 AM – In-Town Pool Call (White House)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 1:00 PM – Sports Announcement (Oval Office, Press Pool)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 3:00 PM – Signs Executive Orders (Oval Office, Closed Press)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 3:30 PM – Welcomes Returned Citizen (Oval Office, Closed Press)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 6:55 PM – Departs for Trump National Golf Club (South Lawn, Open Press)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 7:10 PM – Arrives at Golf Club (Closed Press)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 7:30 PM – Attends MAGA Inc. Dinner (Closed Press)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 9:20 PM – Departs Golf Club for White House (Closed Press)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 9:35 PM – Arrives at White House (South Lawn, Open Press)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - SPAIN NEW TESLA REGISTRATIONS FALL 16.6% Y/Y IN JAN-APRIL WHILE ELECTRIC CARS AS A WHOLE RISE  54% - ANFAC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919346833609937387#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919346833609937387#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - SPAIN NEW TESLA REGISTRATIONS FALL 16.6% Y/Y IN JAN-APRIL WHILE ELECTRIC CARS AS A WHOLE RISE  54% - ANFAC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EARTHQUAKE FELT IN TAIPEI, TAIWAN - WITNESSES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919345917401923895#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 10:58:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919345917401923895#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EARTHQUAKE FELT IN TAIPEI, TAIWAN - WITNESSES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why knowing the market&apos;s expectations is critical for trading success</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/why-knowing-the-markets-expectations-is-critical-for-trading-success-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 10:36:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/why-knowing-the-markets-expectations-is-critical-for-trading-success-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;If you&apos;ve ever wondered why I publish the interest rates expectations for major central banks so regularly, then this article will clear things up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main thing driving market prices is expectations. The market&apos;s ebb and flow is guided by the pricing and repricing of future expectations. This doesn&apos;t mean it&apos;s always right, in fact, there are times when it&apos;s wrong, and those times offer trading opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conditions change, and when they change the market readjusts its expectations which is then reflected in asset prices. That&apos;s why you should never trade the present because the present is already in the price. It&apos;s what the market has priced in the prior days, weeks or months depending on the underlying reasons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing the underlying expectations is critical for trading success. If you have a good understanding of what&apos;s already expected by the market, you can not only spot the changes and make money, but you can also avoid trading what&apos;s already priced in and preserve your capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had some great examples in April. Before the &quot;Liberation Day&quot;, the market was expecting around 50% tariffs for China and 10% reciprocal tariffs for all the other countries. When Trump announced much higher than expected tariffs, the market started to price in potential retaliations, a global slowdown and even a recession.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By April 9 those were the underlying expectations, but they changed once again when Trump announced the pause for negotiations. From that point onward, the market started to price in de-escalation and price out the negative outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market didn&apos;t care much about the economic data not only because it was old news by then, but also because it didn&apos;t have the power to change expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you know what&apos;s priced in, then you should focus on what new developments could trigger a change in those expectations. That change will drive prices and you will be able to capitalise on it. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold pushes back above $3,300 on the day</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-pushes-back-above-3300-on-the-day-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 10:08:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-pushes-back-above-3300-on-the-day-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;You can&apos;t keep the gold bugs down for too long it would seem. The drop last week was a testing one but the 50.0 Fib retracement level held, at least on the daily chart as seen above. That is leading to a solid rebound this week with price now looking for a firm run back above the $3,300 level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The jump takes out both the 100 and 200-hour moving averages at $3,270 and $3,294 respectively as well. That shifts the near-term bias to being more bullish again currently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the bigger picture, the same drivers that have led to gold&apos;s surge in March and April are all still playing out. There&apos;s still some reservations on how Trump&apos;s tariff plans are going to play out and US-China relations continue to be one that doesn&apos;t look like it will be resolved soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;On the latter, there is hopeful optimism that tariff levels will be reduced to around 50% to 60%. Sure, that&apos;s an improvement to the current situation. But it begs the question, doesn&apos;t this all just mean that tariffs are here to stay? And if so, the long-term negative impact is something that broader markets will have to consider - which I believe we are nowhere near considering as of now.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How have interest rate expectations changed after the US NFP report?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rate-expectations-changed-after-the-us-nfp-report-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 10:05:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rate-expectations-changed-after-the-us-nfp-report-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 80 bps (99% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 60 bps (95% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 90 bps (97% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 45 bps (57% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 108 bps (98% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 72 bps (69% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 37 bps (96% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 8 bps (98% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We can see that compared to last &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-sees-more-fed-rate-cuts-after-the-weak-us-gdp-but-it-could-be-wrong-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Thursday&apos;s update&lt;/a&gt;, the market trimmed the easing bets for the Fed as a resilient labour market gives the central bank a reason to keep interest rates steady as they await more developments on the tariff side. A rate cut in June has now less than 50% chances as the market sees a rate cut in July as most likely. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 80 bps priced in by year-end could see further adjustment as the Fed on Wednesday is likely to reiterate that two rate cuts remain the base case unless the labour market weakens meaningfully. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Shines, Crypto Cools, and European Indices Surge: easyMarkets Q1 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/gold-shines-crypto-cools-and-european-indices-surge-easymarkets-q1-2025-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 09:55:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/gold-shines-crypto-cools-and-european-indices-surge-easymarkets-q1-2025-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Leading CFD Broker, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.easymarkets.com/au/?utm_source=forexlive&amp;amp;utm_medium=press+release&amp;amp;utm_content=easymarkets+homepage&amp;amp;utm_campaign=q1+trading+trends+and+triumphs+article+2025&amp;amp;utm_ef_channel=push&amp;amp;gid=6601483&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;easyMarkets&lt;/a&gt;,
released its Q1 2025 market recap, revealing key trends in global trading
behaviours and highlighting significant developments across various
sectors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·     
Gold, Nasdaq, and EURUSD remain the top
assets for the third consecutive quarter, with gold reaching near-record
highs, closing in on $3,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·     
The crypto market saw a decline in Q1 2025
after strong momentum in 2024, as regulatory expectations for the crypto sector
were not met. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·     
European indices surged, driven by
increased defence spending amidst rising geopolitical tensions, attracting
attention from traders seeking new opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·     
The Asia Pacific region saw a marked
increase in trading volumes, with local traders actively shaping global trends
in traditional assets and global indices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Platform upgrades and risk management shifts: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;easyMarkets launched key upgrades to its web and mobile
platform, enhancing the overall user experience. In addition, the company
observed a slight decline in the use of Guaranteed Stop Loss orders, indicating
that traders are adjusting their risk management strategies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nikos Antoniades, CEO of easyMarkets, commented: “Our
clients’ shift from crypto to European indices highlights how quickly they are
adapting to macroeconomic developments. At easyMarkets, we are committed to
providing the tools and stability traders need to stay agile in a fast-moving
market.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As global geopolitical tensions and U.S. political
developments continue to shape market sentiment, easyMarkets is confident that
its clients will continue to capitalise on new opportunities in Q2 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on easyMarkets&apos; Q1 2025 performance and
trends, [click &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.easymarkets.com/au/about/company/easymarkets-q1-2025-recap-familiar-strengths-and-unexpected-opportunities/?utm_source=forexlive&amp;amp;utm_medium=press+release&amp;amp;utm_content=easymarkets+article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=q1+trading+trends+and+triumphs+article+2025&amp;amp;utm_ef_channel=push&amp;amp;gid=6601484&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;
to read the full article]. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ABOUT easyMarkets     &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;easyMarkets, founded in 2001, is an award-winning global
broker. One of the first to offer an online experience with innovative risk
management tools, including Guaranteed Stop Loss with No Slippage* and
easyTrade. easyMarkets provides its sizeable clientele with a streamlined,
accessible, and flexible trading experience. Offering over 275 tradeable
instruments, tight fixed spreads, and 24/5 dedicated support to traders around
the world, easyMarkets continues to revolutionize the trading sector by providing
unparalleled security and safeguards for client funds and consistently
prioritizing client commitment and satisfaction.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Guaranteed Stop Loss with no Slippage is only available on
easyMarkets web &amp;amp; app trading platform. Activate with wider spread for
total risk control. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam says first tariffs negotiation with the US to take place this week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/vietnam-says-first-tariffs-negotiation-with-the-us-to-take-place-this-week-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 09:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/vietnam-says-first-tariffs-negotiation-with-the-us-to-take-place-this-week-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;They are part of the six countries that the US had shortlisted to be a priority for trade negotiations. So, yeah. The first round of talks is expected on 7 May. For some context, the other countries on that list are India, Japan, South Korea, Indonesia, and the UK. So, let&apos;s see how things go later in the week.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan central bank confirms intervening in the market today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-central-bank-confirms-intervening-in-the-market-today-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 09:34:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-central-bank-confirms-intervening-in-the-market-today-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have intervened appropriately&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But degree of intervention in FX market is smaller than usual&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have warned those who are trying to speculate in the market&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Small and medium-sized exporters joined larger firms in selling US dollar positions today&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;They don&apos;t manipulate but they do intervene. Same difference, no? In any case, this will be an interesting spot with regards to dollar sentiment so just keep an eye out in the days ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar stays pinned down on the session</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-stays-pinned-down-on-the-session-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 09:15:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-stays-pinned-down-on-the-session-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s a brand new week but we&apos;re seeing the same old story play out as it has been in the past few weeks. The dollar is once again on the backfoot as risk sentiment cools off as well on the day. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down 0.9% but it&apos;s a mere breather after nine straight days of gains. And even during that period, the dollar has struggled to keep its footing for the most part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;USD/JPY is now down 0.7% on the day to 143.95 while EUR/USD is up 0.3% to 1.1336 on the day. USD/CHF is also down 0.3% to 0.8243 after a brief jump earlier to 0.8270 following the Swiss inflation data. Meanwhile, AUD/USD is up 0.6% to 0.6483 and threatening a technical break to the upside above its 200-day moving average:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The 0.6500 mark will see some offers in play but as things stand, dollar sentiment remains the prime driver of price action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s early in the week but trade headlines will continue to dominate proceedings and drive further changes in the dollar through the week. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/surging-twd-fuelling-revaluation-talk-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;latest situation involving Taiwan&lt;/a&gt; is certainly keeping things interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;If we are to start crossing the boundaries of revaluation in currencies with regards to trade talks, it will have a lot of spillover effects. That especially when it comes to broader sentiment involving the dollar and emerging markets in Asia as well. That&apos;s something to be mindful of in the days ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Panetta: Protectionism threatens to weaken prosperity</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-panetta-protectionism-threatens-to-weaken-prosperity-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 09:00:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-panetta-protectionism-threatens-to-weaken-prosperity-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protectionism threatens to weaken prosperity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;All economists agree that free trade is much better for economic growth than protectionism. With free trade you have better efficiency through comparative advantage, access to larger markets, increased competition, lower inflation, more foreign investment and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBoC Governor Pan: Global economic uncertainties are rising</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/pboc-governor-pan-global-economic-uncertainties-are-rising-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:44:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/pboc-governor-pan-global-economic-uncertainties-are-rising-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Global economic uncertainties are rising.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Calls on Asian countries to work together to deal with tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are just token remarks. There have been some positive signs on US-China tariff talks but more concrete resolutions would be welcomed.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan central bank plays down speculation after currency surge</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-central-bank-plays-down-speculation-after-currency-surge-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:42:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-central-bank-plays-down-speculation-after-currency-surge-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Urges market commentators not to speculate on Taiwan dollar situation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Urges companies not to listen to untrue analysis, sell US dollar positions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taiwan does not manipulate exchange rate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Volatility of Taiwan dollar against US dollar has spiked&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;That as foreign fund inflows to Taiwan stocks and firms&apos; expectations of currency appreciating&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Central bank not involved in tariff talks, meaning no discussion on exchange rate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;From earlier: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/surging-twd-fuelling-revaluation-talk-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Surging TWD fuelling revaluation talk&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/mufg-on-the-taiwan-dollar-move-a-19-standard-deviation-event-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;MUFG on the Taiwan dollar move a &quot;19-standard-deviation event&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There&apos;s no doubt that it was a rather outsized move and the fact that the central bank did not come in to support the market earlier fueled intense speculation that a currency revaluation is part of trade talks. The Taiwan central bank is also out saying that they are not involved in tariff talks and that there has been no discussion on the exchange rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The worrying part of this now is that what does this actually mean for domestic players? Exporters and life insurance firms are being caught out here as they are underhedged. The latter due to their exposure in US bonds naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s going to be an interesting next few days at least.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FMAS:25 to Take Place in Cape Town in Just 1 Month!</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/fmas25-to-take-place-in-cape-town-in-just-1-month-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:32:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/fmas25-to-take-place-in-cape-town-in-just-1-month-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.financemagnates.com/event/FMAS25/register?RefId=Media+Partners&amp;amp;utm_campaign=webpage%2520banners&amp;amp;utm_medium=Forex%2520Live&amp;amp;utm_source=registration&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Finance Magnates Africa Summit&lt;/a&gt;, the biggest event in Africa for the online trading industry, has found a new home in Cape Town. On the 29th &amp;amp; 30th of May, FMAS:25 will welcome the local and international attendees to Cape Town International Convention Centre (CTICC). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;As the financial hub of South Africa, Cape Town offers the ideal setting to host the renowned event. The city offers a more diverse range of companies within the industry, attracting an even larger number of brokers in particular.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;This is especially great news for traders hoping to access recognised and trusted brands from across the world. They can expect to find leading firms like Exness, XM &amp;amp; TDM, seeking eager traders to offer their services to. The efficiency of networking cannot be understated. &lt;a href=&quot;https://events.financemagnates.com/event/FMAS25/register?RefId=Media+Partners&amp;amp;utm_campaign=webpage%2520banners&amp;amp;utm_medium=Forex%2520Live&amp;amp;utm_source=registration&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;FMAS:25&lt;/a&gt; provides traders the chance to meet and connect with an unmatched number of brokers face-to-face, in one single venue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Among the various advantages that &lt;a href=&quot;https://events.financemagnates.com/event/FMAS25/register?RefId=Media+Partners&amp;amp;utm_campaign=webpage%2520banners&amp;amp;utm_medium=Forex%2520Live&amp;amp;utm_source=registration&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;FMAS:25&lt;/a&gt; offers, one of the most notable benefits is its dedication to empowering traders with educational opportunities and insights. Traders can explore a variety of panels providing in-depth analysis, strategies and success stories over the course of 2 days, led by experts such as Robert Van Eyden, CEO of Scope Markets South Africa, and Terence Hove, Senior Financial Markets Strategist at Exness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.financemagnates.com/event/FMAS25/register?RefId=Media+Partners&amp;amp;utm_campaign=webpage%2520banners&amp;amp;utm_medium=Forex%2520Live&amp;amp;utm_source=registration&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;FMAS:25&lt;/a&gt; will also host a highly anticipated industry networking event, an Official Closing Party taking place at HALO Nightclub in Cape Town. Famous for being one of the hottest venues in the city, HALO brings a touch of electric energy blended perfectly with beautiful decor. The event is an exclusive opportunity to meet industry experts while having a drink at one of the most iconic nightclubs in Cape Town.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;With reputable, award-winning brands exhibiting their services at the summit, FMAS:25 is officially the largest summit of its kind in Africa after having sold out a record number of booths. The summit elevates the status of both Cape Town and South Africa as a premium fintech platform, providing both networking and learning opportunities free of charge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;This is your chance to pick up skills crucial to your trading journey and take advantage of a truly booming African market. It’s an unmissable experience that no other event could possibly match in scale or quality. Online registrations are still open, so make sure you book your&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.financemagnates.com/event/FMAS25/register?RefId=Media+Partners&amp;amp;utm_campaign=webpage%2520banners&amp;amp;utm_medium=Forex%2520Live&amp;amp;utm_source=registration&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt; free pass today&lt;/a&gt;! &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone May Sentix investor confidence -8.1 vs -12.5 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-sentix-investor-confidence-81-vs-125-expected-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:30:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-sentix-investor-confidence-81-vs-125-expected-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -19.5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That&apos;s a modest bounce after the plunge in the previous month, owing to fears surrounding Trump&apos;s tariffs. That said, investor sentiment remains at a low level but at least the outsized fears have diminished. The expectations index also jumped up to 19.6, up from 3.8 in April previously. Sentix notes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;This is remarkable, as it shows that investors have largely abandoned the recession fears they expressed last month. The main victims of Trump&apos;s tariffs policy are the US economy, and ,to some extent, the economies of China and Switzerland.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The S&amp;P 500 erased the entire drop since April 2. Now what?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-sp-500-erased-the-entire-drop-since-april-2-now-what-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:20:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-sp-500-erased-the-entire-drop-since-april-2-now-what-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;It was another good day for the US stock markets last Friday as the S&amp;amp;P 500 index extended the gains following the positive NFP report and managed to erase the entire drop since &quot;Liberation Day&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question now is how much further this rally can go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer revolves around the first trade deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We erased all the losses because the market expected de-escalation and eventually much lower tariff rates given the 10% baseline adopted after the pause. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s pretty obvious now that the Fed won&apos;t do anything unless the labour market weakens notably and by then it will be already late. So, the ball remains in Trump&apos;s court. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The path of least resistance remains to the upside but we are now at a point where a disappointment could hurt sentiment and trigger another correction to the downside. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We were told that the first trade deal would have been announced by the end of this week. If we don&apos;t get anything, then the market might take it as a disappointment and further gains would start to be questioned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Judging by the comments from other countries, 10% might now be seen as too high anyway, so higher tariff rates will likely trigger another selloff on expectations of retaliations and more uncertainty. That&apos;s the worst case scenario.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best case scenario would be 5% or lower rates, in which instance we would have very high chances of seeing the S&amp;amp;P 500 rallying into a new all-time high. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A return to negative rates looks to be a given now for the SNB</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/a-return-to-negative-rates-look-to-be-a-given-now-for-the-snb-20250505/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 08:10:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/a-return-to-negative-rates-look-to-be-a-given-now-for-the-snb-20250505/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With the latest inflation reading &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-cpi-00-vs-02-yy-expected-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, it looks like the SNB will have little choice but to mark a return back to negative rates. Headline annual inflation is back to zero for the first time since March 2021 while core annual inflation is also slowly nudging lower. If you strip out rent from the price calculation, inflation is in fact already in negative territory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The worst part in all this is that a stronger Swiss franc will only add further downside pressure to imported inflation - which has been negative for 18 straight months now. The signs are all pointing to deflation returning and the SNB has to step up to the plate to try and not fall back into the rabbit hole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The current policy rate is at 0.25% with the next meeting set for 19 June. A 25 bps rate cut is fully priced in for that but at this stage, I would argue that one shouldn&apos;t rule out a 50 bps move (~8% priced in). The Swiss central bank has to act to send a strong message but considering the global outlook, even that might not be enough to stop this tidal wave from continuing to build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar&apos;s plight has only exacerbated safety flows into the franc currency and even if the SNB resorts to intervention efforts, it will be tough to stem the tide. They are definitely in an unenviable position at the moment. And still, they will have little choice but to accept a return to negative rates or the backlash would be even worse to deal with.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS HE DID OFFER MEXICO TO SEND U.S. TROOPS TO HELP &apos;TAKE CARE OF THE CARTELS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919178738987590119#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:54:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919178738987590119#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS HE DID OFFER MEXICO TO SEND U.S. TROOPS TO HELP &apos;TAKE CARE OF THE CARTELS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) UKRAINE LAUNCHES DRONE ATTACK TARGETING MOSCOW, MAYOR OF THE RUSSIAN CAPITAL SAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919177399335350695#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:48:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919177399335350695#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UKRAINE LAUNCHES DRONE ATTACK TARGETING MOSCOW, MAYOR OF THE RUSSIAN CAPITAL SAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS MEETING WITH MANY COUNTRIES, INCLUDING CHINA, ON TRADE DEALS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919177297149477357#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:48:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919177297149477357#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS MEETING WITH MANY COUNTRIES, INCLUDING CHINA, ON TRADE DEALS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ASKED IF ANY TRADE DEALS ARE COMING THIS WEEK: COULD VERY WELL BE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919176857007571114#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 23:46:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919176857007571114#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ASKED IF ANY TRADE DEALS ARE COMING THIS WEEK: COULD VERY WELL BE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
