<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>B2BROKER Launches First-Ever Turnkey Liquidity Provider Solution</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/b2broker-launches-first-ever-turnkey-liquidity-provider-solution-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 08:11:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/b2broker-launches-first-ever-turnkey-liquidity-provider-solution-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;B2BROKER, a leading
global fintech solutions provider, has announced the launch of Liquidity
Provider Turnkey, a comprehensive solution designed to help financial
institutions seamlessly enter the Prime-of-Prime (PoP) space. The product
arrives at a time when market activity in both forex and digital assets
continues to rise, the financial market becomes more inclusive, and brokers and
other financial market players are searching for new business models, which
will allow them to grow and become successful serving professional clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As regulatory standards tighten and technology demands
intensify, the market for ready-made solutions is rapidly expanding. While
turnkey solutions for launching retail brokerages have become relatively
common, there has been no comparable infrastructure for setting up a liquidity
provider business – until recently. B2BROKER’s new offering fills this gap by
delivering the industry’s first fully-integrated, ready-to-deploy solution for
financial companies looking to become institutional liquidity providers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, this path has required significant capital
investment — often in the millions — along with deep technical expertise,
robust risk controls, and strong executive oversight. This development will
significantly lower the barrier to entry and eliminate the need to build
infrastructure from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liquidity Provider Turnkey enables brokers to launch their
own PoP liquidity business with a suite of institutional-grade features,
including access to over 1,500 trading instruments across 10 asset
classes such as forex, crypto, equities, and commodities. The solution
includes a unified margin account, robust NOP, and deep integration
with key technology providers including PrimeXM, oneZero, Centroid,
FXCubic, and B2CONNECT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Built for simplicity and speed, the product removes the
technical and operational barriers traditionally associated with launching a
liquidity provider business. Features include dynamic margining, real-time
balance monitoring, and built-in KYC, all underpinned by 24/7
technical support and compliance consulting for Tier-1 and Tier-2
jurisdictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We see growing demand from financial companies looking to
move into the institutional liquidity space, and our turnkey solution provides
them with the tools and infrastructure to make that transition successfully,”
said John Murillo, Chief Dealing Officer at B2BROKER. “Our aim is to make
institutional expansion accessible, fast, and scalable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The solution is built for financial institutions seeking a
fast operational launch without building infrastructure from the ground up.
This includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·       Retail
brokers expanding into institutional markets;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·       Proprietary
trading firms looking to internalize liquidity and monetize trading flow;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·       Asset
managers and hedge funds leveraging market expertise for liquidity provision;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·       IB and
agent networks transitioning to full-service liquidity providers;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·       Fintechs
entering the B2B trading infrastructure space;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;·       Banks
diversifying their business models and revenue streams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond core trading infrastructure, Liquidity Provider
Turnkey includes a customizable website, SEO optimization, payment
integrations, and a centralized CRM system for full operational
control. It’s also bundled with B2BROKER’s industry-leading payment technology,
including B2BINPAY and EQWIRE, which support multi-currency accounts, automated
deposit/withdrawal flows, and crypto processing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The business model enables clients to generate revenue
through spreads, swaps, commissions, and treasury operations, while maintaining
a risk-free LP model. Additional cross-selling opportunities through
B2BROKER’s product ecosystem—such as B2CORE, B2TRADER, and B2COPY—further
enhance monetization and long-term business development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Liquidity Provider Turnkey, B2BROKER poses itself as a
market innovator, offering brokers a fast, compliant, and tech-forward path to
becoming institutional liquidity providers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About B2BROKER&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;B2BROKER (https://b2broker.com) is a global fintech
solutions provider for financial institutions. It delivers liquidity, trading
technology, payment solutions, and brokerage infrastructure through a network
of specialised entities. Founded in 2014, with key hubs in London, Limassol,
Hong Kong, and Dubai, the company operates in 11 countries, serving clients
across Europe, the Middle East, and Asia. B2BROKER serves brokers, exchanges,
hedge funds, proprietary trading firms, and other financial institutions.
Leveraging its extensive network and ecosystem-driven approach, the company
provides scalable solutions that help clients streamline operations, maximise
efficiency, and drive growth.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Rehn: June cut &apos;appropriate&apos; if data confirm stabilisation of inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-rehn-june-cut-appropriate-if-data-confirm-stabilisation-of-inflation-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:58:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-rehn-june-cut-appropriate-if-data-confirm-stabilisation-of-inflation-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;June cut &apos;appropriate&apos; if data confirm stabilisation of inflation, weak growth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Given the uncertain environment, the ECB should stick to its data-dependent approach.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next inflation data for the Eurozone should be key but I still think that a cut in June would be taken as a mistake by the market and lead to further rise in long term yields.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Futures Analysis Today – tradeCompass Forecast (May 23, 2025)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-futures-analysis-today-tradecompass-forecast-may-23-2025-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 07:53:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-futures-analysis-today-tradecompass-forecast-may-23-2025-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;785&quot; data-end=&quot;854&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Futures Analysis for Today with tradeCompass (May 23, 2025)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;856&quot; data-end=&quot;905&quot;&gt;TradeCompass Summary for Bitcoin Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;907&quot; data-end=&quot;1284&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;907&quot; data-end=&quot;944&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;909&quot; data-end=&quot;944&quot;&gt;Current Price (MBT) at the time of this analysis: $110,970&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;945&quot; data-end=&quot;1005&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;947&quot; data-end=&quot;1005&quot;&gt;Intraday Bias: Bearish below $111,383 (today’s VWAP)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1006&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1008&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot;&gt;Bullish Threshold: $111,800 and above&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1052&quot; data-end=&quot;1109&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1054&quot; data-end=&quot;1109&quot;&gt;Bearish Threshold: Below today’s VWAP of $111,383&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1110&quot; data-end=&quot;1191&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1112&quot; data-end=&quot;1191&quot;&gt;Key Bearish Targets: $110,470 → $109,715 → $108,750 → $106,875 → $106,500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1192&quot; data-end=&quot;1284&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1194&quot; data-end=&quot;1284&quot;&gt;Key Bullish Targets (only above $111,800): $112,000 → $112,500 → $113,320 → $117,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1291&quot; data-end=&quot;1355&quot;&gt;Market Context and Directional Bias for Bitcoin Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1357&quot; data-end=&quot;1631&quot;&gt;At the time of this analysis, micro Bitcoin futures (MBT) are trading at $110,970, marking a 0.42% decline from the previous day’s close. From a tradeCompass perspective, this places Bitcoin in a short-term intraday bearish bias, as price is currently:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1633&quot; data-end=&quot;1771&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1633&quot; data-end=&quot;1671&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1635&quot; data-end=&quot;1671&quot;&gt;Below today’s VWAP of $111,383&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1672&quot; data-end=&quot;1714&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1674&quot; data-end=&quot;1714&quot;&gt;Below yesterday’s VWAP of $111,157&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1715&quot; data-end=&quot;1771&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1717&quot; data-end=&quot;1771&quot;&gt;Below yesterday’s Value Area Low (VAL) of $110,930&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1773&quot; data-end=&quot;2071&quot;&gt;The confluence of multiple VWAPs and the VAL acting as overhead resistance strengthens the bearish outlook. Until we see a sustained break above $111,800 (the first upper deviation of today’s VWAP), the default plan remains to favor short setups and partial profit-taking at logical levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2078&quot; data-end=&quot;2138&quot;&gt;Key Levels and Partial Profit Targets for Bitcoin Futures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2140&quot; data-end=&quot;2189&quot;&gt;Bearish Scenario (Active below $111,383 VWAP)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-start=&quot;2191&quot; data-end=&quot;2928&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2191&quot; data-end=&quot;2341&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2194&quot; data-end=&quot;2341&quot;&gt;$110,470 – Just above yesterday’s first lower VWAP deviation. Often attracts responsive buyers, making it a smart first scale-out for shorts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2342&quot; data-end=&quot;2453&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2345&quot; data-end=&quot;2453&quot;&gt;$109,715 – Near the second lower VWAP deviation. A deeper target indicating stronger bearish momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2454&quot; data-end=&quot;2552&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2457&quot; data-end=&quot;2552&quot;&gt;$108,750 – Above May 21st&apos;s Value Area High, likely to draw short-term positioning exits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2553&quot; data-end=&quot;2698&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2556&quot; data-end=&quot;2698&quot;&gt;$106,875 – Just above the Point of Control (POC) from May 21. A natural support zone where profit-taking and buyer defense often emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2699&quot; data-end=&quot;2928&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2702&quot; data-end=&quot;2766&quot;&gt;$106,500 – A major level with multiple-day confluence:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;2770&quot; data-end=&quot;2928&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2770&quot; data-end=&quot;2784&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2772&quot; data-end=&quot;2784&quot;&gt;May 21 VAL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2788&quot; data-end=&quot;2802&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2790&quot; data-end=&quot;2802&quot;&gt;May 20 POC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2806&quot; data-end=&quot;2820&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2808&quot; data-end=&quot;2820&quot;&gt;May 19 VAH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2824&quot; data-end=&quot;2928&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2826&quot; data-end=&quot;2928&quot;&gt;May 12 VAH
This area could trigger significant position reshuffling and possible bounce behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2930&quot; data-end=&quot;2978&quot;&gt;Bullish Scenario (Only valid above $111,800)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-start=&quot;2980&quot; data-end=&quot;3390&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2980&quot; data-end=&quot;3086&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2983&quot; data-end=&quot;3086&quot;&gt;$112,000 – Close-by target and round number psychological level; sits just below yesterday’s VAH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;3087&quot; data-end=&quot;3164&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3090&quot; data-end=&quot;3164&quot;&gt;$112,500 – Aligned with the third upper VWAP deviation of today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;3165&quot; data-end=&quot;3272&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3168&quot; data-end=&quot;3272&quot;&gt;$113,320 – Matches yesterday’s third upper VWAP deviation, where profit-taking is likely to occur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;3273&quot; data-end=&quot;3390&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3276&quot; data-end=&quot;3390&quot;&gt;$117,000 – Long-term runner target for bullish continuation; previously discussed in longer-horizon forecasts: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-price-forecast-also-using-liquidation-levels-20250522/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Price Forecast - Also Using Liquidation Levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3397&quot; data-end=&quot;3467&quot;&gt;Educational Insight: VWAP and Value Area in Bitcoin Futures Trading&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3469&quot; data-end=&quot;3699&quot;&gt;The Volume-Weighted Average Price (VWAP) provides an intraday fair value by weighting price by volume. When price trades below VWAP, it often signals institutional selling pressure; above VWAP suggests buyer dominance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3701&quot; data-end=&quot;3961&quot;&gt;VWAP standard deviations help define dynamic zones of price extension or mean reversion. These bands expand during volatile sessions and contract in consolidation, helping intraday traders determine high-probability reversal or continuation points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3963&quot; data-end=&quot;4066&quot;&gt;Complementing this, the Volume Profile outlines areas where trading activity was most concentrated:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;4068&quot; data-end=&quot;4319&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;4068&quot; data-end=&quot;4144&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;4070&quot; data-end=&quot;4144&quot;&gt;Value Area High (VAH): Top of the 70% value zone; acts as resistance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;4145&quot; data-end=&quot;4237&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;4147&quot; data-end=&quot;4237&quot;&gt;Point of Control (POC): The most actively traded price; often acts as a price magnet&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;4238&quot; data-end=&quot;4319&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;4240&quot; data-end=&quot;4319&quot;&gt;Value Area Low (VAL): Bottom of the value zone; typically acts as support&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;4321&quot; data-end=&quot;4497&quot;&gt;Understanding where Bitcoin is in relation to these zones allows traders to position around acceptance vs rejection levels, increasing the odds of well-timed entries and exits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;4504&quot; data-end=&quot;4570&quot;&gt;tradeCompass Methodology and Risk Management for Bitcoin Futures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;4572&quot; data-end=&quot;4796&quot;&gt;The tradeCompass methodology is designed to simplify complex price action into clear directional thresholds and logical partial targets. This minimizes emotional trading and overtrading by enforcing discipline:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;4798&quot; data-end=&quot;5336&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;4798&quot; data-end=&quot;4918&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;4800&quot; data-end=&quot;4918&quot;&gt;Only one trade per direction per day: Once partial targets are hit, wait for a full reset before reversing bias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;4919&quot; data-end=&quot;5063&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;4921&quot; data-end=&quot;5063&quot;&gt;Stop-loss placement must respect the compass: Never place a stop beyond the opposite threshold — a breach invalidates the trade premise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;5064&quot; data-end=&quot;5228&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5066&quot; data-end=&quot;5228&quot;&gt;Adapt your entry confirmation: Some traders use candle closes above/below thresholds, others wait for a momentum burst. Choose what suits your risk profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;5229&quot; data-end=&quot;5336&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5231&quot; data-end=&quot;5336&quot;&gt;Move stops after partial exits: Reduce risk exposure while allowing the rest of the trade to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5343&quot; data-end=&quot;5390&quot;&gt;Clarification for Traders Using tradeCompass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5392&quot; data-end=&quot;5551&quot;&gt;This tradeCompass analysis should be read as a navigation map, not a directional prediction. The key is how price behaves near the mapped levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;5553&quot; data-end=&quot;5803&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;5553&quot; data-end=&quot;5684&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5555&quot; data-end=&quot;5684&quot;&gt;If Bitcoin futures stay below VWAP and fail to reclaim it intraday, short setups toward lower partial targets remain valid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;5685&quot; data-end=&quot;5803&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5687&quot; data-end=&quot;5803&quot;&gt;If price breaks above $111,800 and holds, that shifts the bias — and bullish targets can be pursued accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5805&quot; data-end=&quot;5915&quot;&gt;The real value lies in reacting to price with a structured plan, not in forecasting with blind conviction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5922&quot; data-end=&quot;5950&quot;&gt;Disclaimer for Bitcoin Traders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;5952&quot; data-end=&quot;6263&quot;&gt;This content is provided as decision-support, not investment advice. Bitcoin futures are volatile instruments and carry significant risk. The tradeCompass system provides a structured framework to define intraday opportunity zones — but outcomes depend on market behavior and personal trade execution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;6265&quot; data-end=&quot;6345&quot;&gt;Always trade at your own risk. Stay informed, stay patient, and trade smart.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France May consumer confidence 88 vs 93 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-consumer-confidence-88-vs-93-expected-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:45:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-consumer-confidence-88-vs-93-expected-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 92 (revised to 91)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumer confidence has been falling steadily since the start of the year amid the trade war. We haven&apos;t reached the trough yet but things could start to reverse in the next months. We&apos;ll see. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Q1 final GDP 0.4% vs 0.2% q/q expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-q1-final-gdp-04-vs-02-qq-expected-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:00:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-q1-final-gdp-04-vs-02-qq-expected-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s even better than the preliminary estimates and makes sense given the ECB rate cuts and fiscal boost. We should see even better figures going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK April retail sales +1.2% vs +0.2% m/m expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-retail-sales-12-vs-02-mm-expected-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 06:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-retail-sales-12-vs-02-mm-expected-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.4% (revised to +0.1%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Retail sales +5.0% vs +4.5% y/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.6% (revised to +1.9%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Retail sales ex autos, fuel +1.3% vs 0.3% m/m expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.5% (revised to +0.2%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Retail sales ex autos, fuel +5.3% vs +4.4% y/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +3.3% (revised to +2.6%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are very strong numbers. Not sure why the BoE keeps cutting when they are so far from their target.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Stournaras: I see a June rate cut and then pause</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-stournaras-i-see-a-june-rate-cut-and-then-pause-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 05:56:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-stournaras-i-see-a-june-rate-cut-and-then-pause-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; I see a June rate cut and then pause.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;After June, the next fully priced in cut is in December.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 23 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-23-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 05:14:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-23-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;EUR/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1400 (EUR 1.25bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1345
(EUR 882mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1330 (EUR 964mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1300 (EUR 1.84bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1275 (EUR 1.50 bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
145.00
(US$ 2.81bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
144.00 (US$ 2.37bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;143.00 (US$ 1.76bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;GBP/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3600 (GBP 379mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3500 (GBP 227mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3400 (GBP 298mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CHF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8300 (CHF 285mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8250 (CHF 494mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.4015
(US$ 1.67bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3870 (US$ 575mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3565 (US$ 795mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6530 (AUD 981mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6475 (AUD 600mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6435 (AUD 845mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6375 (AUD 683mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;NZD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.5860 (NZD 603mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:24:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, the main highlight is the UK April Retail Sales report. Retail Sales ex-Fuel Y/Y is expected at 4.4% vs. 3.3% prior, while the M/M figure is seen at 0.3% vs. 0.5% prior. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Retail sales rose for the third consecutive month in March and the data has been generally good. This is generally a market moving release for the GBP but it shouldn&apos;t change anything in terms of interest rates expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we get the Canadian Retail Sales data. The Retail Sales ex-Autos M/M is expected at 0.0% vs. 0.5%. Same as for the UK data, the report shouldn&apos;t change anything for rates expectations after the recent upside surprise in the Canadian inflation data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:30 GMT/04:30 ET - ECB&apos;s Lane (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;13:45 GMT/09:35 ET - Fed&apos;s Musalem (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;14:30 GMT/10:30 ET - BoE&apos;s Pill (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;16:00 GMT/12:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Cook (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;16:15 GMT/12:15 ET - ECB&apos;s Schnabel (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pushes EU to cut tariffs or face extra duties - FT</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-pushes-eu-to-cut-tariffs-or-face-extra-duties-ft-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:11:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-pushes-eu-to-cut-tariffs-or-face-extra-duties-ft-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump pushes EU to cut tariffs or face extra duties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US trade representative Greer preparing to tell EU counterpart Sefcovic that recent &quot;explanatory note&quot; falls short of US expectations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US negotiators to tell Brussels they expect unilateral concessions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, it&apos;s been pretty clear that trade deals with EU and Japan were going to be harder since the two countries took a more hardline stance on tariffs compared to UK for example. The EU has been repeating that they won&apos;t accept 10% as a baseline for tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Japan core CPI rising fastest in two years</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-japan-core-cpi-rising-fastest-in-two-years-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 04:02:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-japan-core-cpi-rising-fastest-in-two-years-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-our-stance-on-us-tariffs-20250523/&quot;&gt;Japan PM Ishiba: No change to our stance on U.S. tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-prime-minister-ishiba-held-phone-talks-with-trump-20250523/&quot;&gt;Japan Prime Minister Ishiba held phone talks with Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-council-for-promotion-of-international-trade-president-met-with-jp-morgan-ceo-dimon-20250523/&quot;&gt;China Council for Promotion of International Trade president met with JP Morgan CEO Dimon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/irans-foreign-minister-lays-down-conditions-for-a-deal-with-the-us-ahead-of-weekend-talks-20250523/&quot;&gt;Iran&apos;s Foreign Minister lays down conditions for a deal with the US ahead of weekend talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/sp-500-futures-analysistoday-20250523/&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 Futures Analysis Today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/tsmc-warns-us-chip-tariffs-could-undermine-its-arizona-investment-20250523/&quot;&gt;TSMC warns US chip tariffs could undermine its Arizona investment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-vice-foreign-minister-ma-zhaoxu-us-deputy-sec-state-landau-spoke-thursday-20250523/&quot;&gt;Chinese Vice Foreign Minister Ma Zhaoxu &amp;amp; US Deputy Sec State Landau spoke Thursday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-usd-is-losing-some-ground-in-asian-trade-20250523/&quot;&gt;The USD is losing some ground in Asian trade&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71919-vs-estimate-at-72151-20250523/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1919 (vs. estimate at 7.2151)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-akazawa-japan-to-request-elimination-of-us-tariffs-but-want-to-reach-agreement-20250523/&quot;&gt;Japan Akazawa: Japan to request elimination of US tariffs, but want to reach agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/major-us-banks-are-exploring-whether-to-team-up-to-issue-a-joint-stablecoin-20250523/&quot;&gt;Major US banks are exploring whether to team up to issue a joint stablecoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-new-farm-minister-aims-to-cut-5kg-rice-prices-below-3000-20250523/&quot;&gt;Japan&apos;s new farm minister aims to cut 5kg rice prices below ¥3,000&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-economy-minister-akazawaheading-back-to-the-us-around-may-30-for-more-trade-talks-20250523/&quot;&gt;Japan economy minister Akazawa heading back to the US around May 30 for more trade talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-chair-powell-is-speaking-on-sunday-20250523/&quot;&gt;Federal Reserve Chair Powell is speaking on Sunday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-economy-to-worsen-in-h2-2025-payback-time-20250522/&quot;&gt;US economy to worsen in H2 2025 ... &apos;payback&apos; time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/japan-april-cpi-remains-well-above-the-bank-of-japan-target-rate-20250522/&quot;&gt;Japan April CPI remains well above the Bank of Japan target rate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-consumer-confidence-improves-a-little-in-may-still-deeply-pessimistic-at-20-20250522/&quot;&gt;UK consumer confidence improves a little in May, still deeply pessimistic at -20&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdeputysecretaryofstatespokewithchinesecounterpartonthursday-20250522/&quot;&gt;US Deputy Secretary of State spoke with Chinese counterpart on Thursday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-retail-sales-q1-2025-07-yy-prior-02-08-qq-expected-01-20250522/&quot;&gt;New Zealand Retail Sales Q1 2025 0.7% y/y (prior 0.2%), 0.8% q/q (expected 0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/ubs-lifts-sp-500-target-on-strong-earnings-and-economic-outlook-20250522/&quot;&gt;UBS lifts S&amp;amp;P 500 target on strong earnings and economic outlook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-lagarde-says-must-question-links-of-dependency-that-we-have-with-the-united-states-20250522/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Lagarde says must question links of dependency that we have with the United States&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-highlights-signs-of-recovery-and-renewed-foreign-interest-in-china-20250522/&quot;&gt;JP Morgan highlights signs of recovery and renewed foreign interest in China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/icymi-morgan-stanley-expects-the-sp-500-to-reach-6500-by-mid-2026-20250522/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Morgan Stanley expects the S&amp;amp;P 500 to reach 6,500 by mid-2026&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/us-supreme-court-allows-trump-to-fire-heads-of-independent-agencies-does-not-apply-to-fed-20250522/&quot;&gt;US Supreme Court allows Trump to fire heads of independent agencies, does not apply to Fed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-friday-23-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250522/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Friday, 23 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-kato-there-were-comments-from-some-g7-countries-about-need-to-ensure-fiscal-health-20250522/&quot;&gt;Japan Kato: There were comments from some G7 countries about need to ensure fiscal health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-says-shared-with-g7-that-should-be-highly-committed-to-price-stability-20250522/&quot;&gt;BoJ Governor Ueda says shared with G7 that should be highly committed to price stability&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/stocks-close-mixed-with-the-dow-and-sp-little-changed-nasdaq-higher-20250522/&quot;&gt;Stocks close mixed with the Dow and S&amp;amp;P little changed. Nasdaq higher.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/reserve-bank-of-new-zealand-expected-to-cut-its-cash-rate-on-may-28-almost-unanimous-view-20250522/&quot;&gt;Reserve Bank of New Zealand expected to cut its cash rate on May 28, almost unanimous view&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-yields-reverse-lower-bitcoin-hits-record-near-112k-20250522/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Yields reverse lower, bitcoin hits record near $112K&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;317&quot; data-end=&quot;630&quot;&gt;The US dollar lost ground across the major FX board during the session. Concerns over US debt persist following the Moody’s downgrade, and while the House’s passage of Trump’s tax bill on Thursday may offer a short-term economic boost, it has reignited worries about the long-term consequences of ballooning debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;632&quot; data-end=&quot;1007&quot;&gt;From Canada, where the G7 is finishing, we heard again from Bank of Japan Governor Ueda. He reaffirmed the Bank’s hands-off stance on Japanese Government Bonds, even as yields on super-long dated securities climb to record highs. His comments align with those of BoJ Board member Noguchi, who said the Bank should only ramp up bond purchases during “severe market disruption.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1009&quot; data-end=&quot;1254&quot;&gt;Japan&apos;s April inflation data came in later, with core consumer prices rising 3.5% year-on-year—the fastest pace in over two years. This puts pressure on the BoJ to consider rate hikes, though Trump’s tariff war is posing new headwinds to growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1256&quot; data-end=&quot;1564&quot;&gt;On trade, Economy Minister Akazawa is due back in Washington around May 30 for a fourth round of talks. Both he and Prime Minister Ishiba reiterated Japan’s demand for US tariff removal, while also emphasising Japan’s national interests. Akazawa expressed a desire to reach an agreement—but it won’t be easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking to the weekend, indirect nuclear talks between Iran and the US are set to resume in Rome. Iran’s Foreign Minister laid out stark terms:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Zero nuclear weapons = we DO have a deal. Zero enrichment = we do NOT have a deal.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Expect headlines early Monday in Asian markets, with oil likely to react.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1878&quot; data-end=&quot;2082&quot;&gt;Also on deck is a speech from Fed Chair Jerome Powell on Sunday. While he’s unlikely to address the economic outlook or policy directly (see earlier post for context), it’s worth noting he’ll be speaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2084&quot; data-end=&quot;2361&quot;&gt;Lastly, US debt concerns continue to ripple globally. Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas Governor Eli Remolona is reportedly considering reducing Philippine holdings of US Treasuries, according to Bloomberg, following the Moody’s downgrade. If he’s thinking it, others likely are too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUR/USD rose during the session:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan PM Ishiba: No change to our stance on U.S. tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-our-stance-on-us-tariffs-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 03:31:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-our-stance-on-us-tariffs-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan PM Ishiba on his call with Trump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No change to our stance on U.S. tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Discussed U.S. tariffs with President Trump&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Discussed diplomacy, security with Trump as well&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There might be occasion where I’ll visit U.S. for in-person talks with President Trump&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No change to our stance of demanding elimination of tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No change to our policy of talking with U.S. on creating U.S. jobs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier from Japan re tariffs talks:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-economy-minister-akazawaheading-back-to-the-us-around-may-30-for-more-trade-talks-20250523/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Japan economy minister Akazawa heading back to the US around May 30 for more trade talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-akazawa-japan-to-request-elimination-of-us-tariffs-but-want-to-reach-agreement-20250523/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Japan Akazawa: Japan to request elimination of US tariffs, but want to reach agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Prime Minister Ishiba held phone talks with Trump</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-prime-minister-ishiba-held-phone-talks-with-trump-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:56:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-prime-minister-ishiba-held-phone-talks-with-trump-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan Prime Minister Ishiba, Trump held phone talks, a 45 minute conversation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jiji with the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is ahead of the next round of talks stating next week:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-economy-minister-akazawaheading-back-to-the-us-around-may-30-for-more-trade-talks-20250523/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan economy minister Akazawa heading back to the US around May 30 for more trade talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He is sticking to his guns:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-akazawa-japan-to-request-elimination-of-us-tariffs-but-want-to-reach-agreement-20250523/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan Akazawa: Japan to request elimination of US tariffs, but want to reach agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Council for Promotion of International Trade president met with JP Morgan CEO Dimon</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-council-for-promotion-of-international-trade-president-met-with-jp-morgan-ceo-dimon-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:53:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-council-for-promotion-of-international-trade-president-met-with-jp-morgan-ceo-dimon-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China Council for Promotion of International Trade president met with JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; on May 22&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;exchanged views on promoting exchanges between China, U.S. business communities and deepening cooperation in financial investment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I posted earlier on JP Morgan ramping up their view on China:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-highlights-signs-of-recovery-and-renewed-foreign-interest-in-china-20250522/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;JP Morgan highlights signs of recovery and renewed foreign interest in China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran&apos;s Foreign Minister lays down conditions for a deal with the US ahead of weekend talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/irans-foreign-minister-lays-down-conditions-for-a-deal-with-the-us-ahead-of-weekend-talks-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:33:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/irans-foreign-minister-lays-down-conditions-for-a-deal-with-the-us-ahead-of-weekend-talks-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;77&quot; data-end=&quot;284&quot;&gt;Iran’s Foreign Minister announced via social media that he is heading to Rome for a fifth round of indirect talks with the United States, underscoring the urgency and clarity of Tehran’s negotiating stance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;286&quot; data-end=&quot;708&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;In the message, he framed the path to a potential agreement in blunt terms: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;286&quot; data-end=&quot;708&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;“Zero nuclear weapons = we DO have a deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;286&quot; data-end=&quot;708&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;Zero enrichment = we do NOT have a deal.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;286&quot; data-end=&quot;708&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;The remarks suggest that while Iran remains open to diplomacy, it is unwilling to forgo uranium enrichment—long a sticking point in nuclear negotiations. The talks come amid renewed efforts to revive diplomacy and break the deadlock over Iran’s nuclear program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;286&quot; data-end=&quot;708&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;The outcome of the talks should influence oil early in the new week. Its probably likely that the deadlock will persist. We&apos;ll see. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 Futures Analysis Today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/sp-500-futures-analysistoday-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 02:09:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/sp-500-futures-analysistoday-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;123&quot; data-end=&quot;188&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 Futures Analysis – tradeCompass for May 23, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;190&quot; data-end=&quot;310&quot;&gt;Current price at the time of this analysis: $5,857
Bearish Below: $5,860
Bullish Above: $5,865
Bias: Bearish at current level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;312&quot; data-end=&quot;600&quot;&gt;The S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are trading in bearish territory today, just under the $5,860 key threshold. According to the Trade Compass methodology, we maintain a bearish outlook while price remains below this level, with a potential shift to bullish bias only if price sustains above $5,865.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;607&quot; data-end=&quot;656&quot;&gt; S&amp;amp;P 500 Futures Today - Bearish Scenario &amp;amp; Partial Profit Targets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;658&quot; data-end=&quot;870&quot;&gt;Trade Compass emphasizes partial profit-taking to manage risk and lock in gains incrementally. Whether you&apos;re trading 1 E-mini contract, 10 micro contracts, or using CFDs, you can apply this approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;872&quot; data-end=&quot;899&quot;&gt;Bearish Profit Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-start=&quot;900&quot; data-end=&quot;1227&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;900&quot; data-end=&quot;962&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;903&quot; data-end=&quot;962&quot;&gt;$5,855 – Near current price. Conservative first target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;963&quot; data-end=&quot;1028&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;966&quot; data-end=&quot;1028&quot;&gt;$5,850 – Semi-round number. May act as short-term support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1029&quot; data-end=&quot;1070&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1032&quot; data-end=&quot;1070&quot;&gt;$5,837 – Just above May 12th VWAP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1071&quot; data-end=&quot;1126&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1074&quot; data-end=&quot;1126&quot;&gt;$5,827 – Just above the May 12th Value Area Low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1127&quot; data-end=&quot;1227&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1130&quot; data-end=&quot;1227&quot;&gt;$5,810 – Close to a major low on May 12 and just above the $5,800 psychological round number.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1229&quot; data-end=&quot;1379&quot;&gt;Stop Management Tip: After reaching the second target ($5,850), consider adjusting stops to breakeven or better on the remainder of your position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1386&quot; data-end=&quot;1428&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 Futures Today - Bullish Scenario if Price Reverses&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1430&quot; data-end=&quot;1579&quot;&gt;Despite the bearish context, the Trade Compass remains open to reversals. Should price break and hold above $5,865, here are the bullish targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-start=&quot;1581&quot; data-end=&quot;1780&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1581&quot; data-end=&quot;1637&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1584&quot; data-end=&quot;1637&quot;&gt;$5,882 – Just below the May 21st Value Area High.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1638&quot; data-end=&quot;1693&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1641&quot; data-end=&quot;1693&quot;&gt;$5,904 – Also aligned with a key May 21st level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1694&quot; data-end=&quot;1780&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1697&quot; data-end=&quot;1780&quot;&gt;$5,947 – Longer-term runner target, just under May 21st Point of Control (POC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1782&quot; data-end=&quot;1879&quot;&gt;This setup offers bulls a high-probability progression if key levels are reclaimed with strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1886&quot; data-end=&quot;1949&quot;&gt;Investor Note: Watch S&amp;amp;P 500 Futures and a Potential Bounce Between $5,800–$5,815&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1951&quot; data-end=&quot;2247&quot;&gt;For longer-term traders and investors, $5,800 to $5,815 is a key area to monitor. This zone may trigger a moderate to strong bounce, especially after several days of retracement. It may not signal an immediate trend reversal, but it&apos;s worth watching for a potential base-building process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2254&quot; data-end=&quot;2507&quot;&gt;Reminder: This is not financial advice. Always trade at your own risk and with a structured plan.
Stay updated on ForexLive.com, and note we are transitioning to investingLive.com to serve you with even broader insights across markets.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSMC warns US chip tariffs could undermine its Arizona investment</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tsmc-warns-us-chip-tariffs-could-undermine-its-arizona-investment-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:53:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tsmc-warns-us-chip-tariffs-could-undermine-its-arizona-investment-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;67&quot; data-end=&quot;508&quot;&gt;Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co. (TSMC) has warned that proposed U.S. tariffs on foreign-made chips could jeopardize its massive US$165 billion investment in advanced semiconductor manufacturing facilities in Arizona. In a public comment submitted to the U.S. Commerce Department, the company cautioned that reduced demand resulting from the tariffs could impact the viability of its U.S. operations, according to a report by PC Mag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;510&quot; data-end=&quot;899&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;TSMC highlighted that its Arizona fabs will eventually account for about 30% of the company’s global capacity for cutting-edge 2nm and more advanced chips—enough to meet projected U.S. demand. The chipmaker also confirmed it has begun construction on a third fabrication plant in the state, which will initially produce 2nm chips and later adopt its next-generation A16 process technology. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;510&quot; data-end=&quot;899&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) is the world’s largest contract chipmaker and a key player in the global semiconductor supply chain. It produces advanced chips for major tech firms like Apple, NVIDIA, and AMD, and is known for leading-edge manufacturing technologies such as 3nm and 2nm process nodes.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Vice Foreign Minister Ma Zhaoxu &amp; US Deputy Sec State Landau spoke Thursday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-vice-foreign-minister-ma-zhaoxu-us-deputy-sec-state-landau-spoke-thursday-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:53:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-vice-foreign-minister-ma-zhaoxu-us-deputy-sec-state-landau-spoke-thursday-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;A statement from the US Department of State:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deputy Secretary Landau’s Call with Chinese Executive Vice Foreign Minister Ma Zhaoxu &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deputy Secretary of State Christopher Landau spoke today with Chinese Executive Vice Foreign Minister Ma Zhaoxu. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; They acknowledged the importance of the bilateral relationship to the people of both countries and the world, discussed a wide range of issues of mutual interest, and agreed on the importance of keeping open lines of communication.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;China&apos;s Foreign Ministry issued a similar readout. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not a lot to go on!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USD is losing some ground in Asian trade</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-usd-is-losing-some-ground-in-asian-trade-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:44:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-usd-is-losing-some-ground-in-asian-trade-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The USD is slipping vs. other major FX in Asia trade. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apart from what has been posted there isn&apos;t any fresh news. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUR, AUD, CAD, GBP, NZD all higher. USD/JPY and USD/CHF are losing a few tics also. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUR/USD:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1919 (vs. estimate at 7.2151)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71919-vs-estimate-at-72151-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:15:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71919-vs-estimate-at-72151-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous close was 7.2060&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC injected 142.5bn yuan via 7-day reverse repos at 1.40%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;106.5bn yuan matured today&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;net injection 36bn yuan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Akazawa: Japan to request elimination of US tariffs, but want to reach agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-akazawa-japan-to-request-elimination-of-us-tariffs-but-want-to-reach-agreement-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:14:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-akazawa-japan-to-request-elimination-of-us-tariffs-but-want-to-reach-agreement-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan tariff negotiator Akazawa is heading to the US for a fourth round:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-economy-minister-akazawaheading-back-to-the-us-around-may-30-for-more-trade-talks-20250523/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan economy minister Akazawa heading back to the US around May 30 for more trade talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Says today:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;no change to Japan’s stance to request elimination of US tariffs but want to reach agreement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan has its own interests to protect &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major US banks are exploring whether to team up to issue a joint stablecoin</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/major-us-banks-are-exploring-whether-to-team-up-to-issue-a-joint-stablecoin-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 01:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/major-us-banks-are-exploring-whether-to-team-up-to-issue-a-joint-stablecoin-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/finance/banking/crypto-stablecoin-big-banks-a841059e&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/a&gt; (gated) report. Major U.S. banks are exploring a joint stablecoin to compete with the crypto industry.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Banks see an opportunity in using stablecoins for faster transactions, like in cross-border payments, but there are still security and regulatory concerns.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
One possible model discussed would allow other banks to use the stablecoin.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The bank consortium discussions are in early, conceptual stages and could change.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conversations have so far involved companies co-owned by JPMorgan Chase,  Bank of America, Citigroup, Wells Fargo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A stablecoin is a type of cryptocurrency designed to maintain a stable value by being pegged to a reserve asset, such as a fiat currency like the US dollar. It aims to combine the stability of traditional money with the efficiency of digital assets.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan&apos;s new farm minister aims to cut 5kg rice prices below ¥3,000</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-new-farm-minister-aims-to-cut-5kg-rice-prices-below-3000-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:51:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-new-farm-minister-aims-to-cut-5kg-rice-prices-below-3000-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan&apos;s new Agriculture
Minister Shinjiro Koizumi said on Friday he aimed to get rice on
store shelves for under 3,000 yen for a 5-kg bag&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Report via Japanese media, Jiji.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;plans to bypass auctions, selling stockpiled rice directly to retailers to curb inflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the price at present is north of 4000 yen for a 5 kg bag, but don&apos;t quote me on that. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PM Ishiba welcoming the new minister. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The previous minister, Taku Eto, said in a speech:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“I’ve never bought rice. My supporters have given me so much rice that I have so much I could sell it.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;That didn&apos;t do well with the Japanese public, sick of seeing prices jump higher. Eto resigned on 21 May.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan economy minister Akazawa heading back to the US around May 30 for more trade talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-economy-minister-akazawaheading-back-to-the-us-around-may-30-for-more-trade-talks-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:45:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-economy-minister-akazawaheading-back-to-the-us-around-may-30-for-more-trade-talks-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan tariff negotiator Akazawa intends to visit the US around May 30 for fourth round of talks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reuters with the info citing unnamed sources &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Chair Powell is speaking on Sunday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-chair-powell-is-speaking-on-sunday-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:31:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-chair-powell-is-speaking-on-sunday-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;On Sunday at 1940 GMT / 1440 US Eastern time &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell gives Baccalaureate remarks before the Princeton University Baccalaureate Ceremony, in Princeton, N.J&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the venue and event, perhaps he won&apos;t be making comments on his outlook for the economy nor monetary policy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, if he does, that time is well before markets open here in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1940 GMT / 1440 US Eastern time on Sunday is Monday morning in Asia:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;6.40 am in New Zealand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;4.40 am in Sydney&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3.40 am in Tokyo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.40 am in Singapore/Hong Kong &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are always &apos;weekend&apos; markets but these are devoid of wholesale interest, that won;t get active until New Zealand kicks off. Even then its super thin until Tokyo arrives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ForexLive (me, in the case of Monday morning) will be on deck from 6am Sydney time. Ever since Trump took office, Monday mornings have become great again, usually with volatility from weekend news and comments and what you. Be sure to join us! &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) APPLE SET TO EXPAND INDIA SUPPLY CHAIN THROUGH $1.5BN FOXCONN PLANT - FT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925709299344380111#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:24:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925709299344380111#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;APPLE SET TO EXPAND INDIA SUPPLY CHAIN THROUGH $1.5BN FOXCONN PLANT - FT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *PALANTIR&apos;S KARP SELLS $50.4 MILLION IN SHARES

*PALANTIR&apos;S COHEN SELLS $43.5 MILLION IN SHARES

*PALANTIR&apos;S SANKAR SELLS $21.2 MILLION IN SHARES

*PALANTIR&apos;S GLAZER SELLS $4.32 MILLION IN SHARES

$PLTR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925709153449771323#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:23:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925709153449771323#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*PALANTIR&apos;S KARP SELLS $50.4 MILLION IN SHARES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*PALANTIR&apos;S COHEN SELLS $43.5 MILLION IN SHARES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*PALANTIR&apos;S SANKAR SELLS $21.2 MILLION IN SHARES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*PALANTIR&apos;S GLAZER SELLS $4.32 MILLION IN SHARES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23PLTR&quot;&gt;$PLTR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *JAPAN APRIL CORE CONSUMER PRICES RISE 3.5% Y/Y; EST. +3.4%

*JAPAN APRIL CPI EX-FRESH FOOD, ENERGY RISES 3% Y/Y; PREV. 2.9%

*JAPAN APRIL OVERALL CONSUMER PRICES RISE 3.6% Y/Y; EST. +3.5%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925697752375161013#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:38:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925697752375161013#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*JAPAN APRIL CORE CONSUMER PRICES RISE 3.5% Y/Y; EST. +3.4%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*JAPAN APRIL CPI EX-FRESH FOOD, ENERGY RISES 3% Y/Y; PREV. 2.9%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*JAPAN APRIL OVERALL CONSUMER PRICES RISE 3.6% Y/Y; EST. +3.5%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) UBS GLOBAL WEALTH MANAGEMENT RAISES YEAR-END S&amp;P 500 PRICE TARGET TO 6,000, INITIATES JUNE 2026 TARGET OF 6,400</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925675258377281903#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:08:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925675258377281903#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UBS GLOBAL WEALTH MANAGEMENT RAISES YEAR-END S&amp;amp;P 500 PRICE TARGET TO 6,000, INITIATES JUNE 2026 TARGET OF 6,400&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP TO INVOKE WARTIME ACT OVER US URANIUM DEPENDENCE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925667862405902546#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:39:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925667862405902546#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP TO INVOKE WARTIME ACT OVER US URANIUM DEPENDENCE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP TO SIGN ORDERS TO BOOST NUCLEAR POWER AS SOON AS FRIDAY, SOURCES SAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925666450879950935#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:33:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925666450879950935#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP TO SIGN ORDERS TO BOOST NUCLEAR POWER AS SOON AS FRIDAY, SOURCES SAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *ONLYFANS IN TALK FOR SALE AT 8B VALUATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925661899783372803#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:15:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925661899783372803#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*ONLYFANS IN TALK FOR SALE AT 8B VALUATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) APPLE AIMS TO DEBUT SMART GLASSES BY END OF ’26, TAKING ON META</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925629635271839894#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:07:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925629635271839894#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;APPLE AIMS TO DEBUT SMART GLASSES BY END OF ’26, TAKING ON META&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. STOCKS EXTEND GAINS, NASDAQ UP 1.00%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925629279150211098#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925629279150211098#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. STOCKS EXTEND GAINS, NASDAQ UP 1.00%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED’S PERLI: SEEING SOME ‘EARLY’ SIGNS OF PRESSURE IN REPO MARKETS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925627814193070204#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925627814193070204#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED’S PERLI: SEEING SOME ‘EARLY’ SIGNS OF PRESSURE IN REPO MARKETS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) X USERS REPORT OUTAGES, ACCORDING TO DOWNDETECTOR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925627678276702297#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:59:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925627678276702297#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;X USERS REPORT OUTAGES, ACCORDING TO DOWNDETECTOR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S WILLIAMS: CITES &apos;UNFAIR TRADING PRACTICES IN CHINA&apos;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925626723300700393#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:56:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925626723300700393#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S WILLIAMS: CITES &apos;UNFAIR TRADING PRACTICES IN CHINA&apos;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HARVARD UNIVERSITY SAYS DHS MOVE TO BLOCK INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS IS &apos;UNLAWFUL&apos; -STATEMENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925618614792593623#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:23:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925618614792593623#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HARVARD UNIVERSITY SAYS DHS MOVE TO BLOCK INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS IS &apos;UNLAWFUL&apos; -STATEMENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US HALTS HARVARD’S ABILITY TO ENROLL INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS:NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925608791195701675#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:44:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925608791195701675#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US HALTS HARVARD’S ABILITY TO ENROLL INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS:NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE ON THE INCOME CAP: TRUMP IS SATISFIED WITH WHERE THE BILL LANDED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925606943487336864#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:37:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925606943487336864#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE ON THE INCOME CAP: TRUMP IS SATISFIED WITH WHERE THE BILL LANDED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE: TRUMP EXPECTS SENATE TO GET BUSY ON TAX BILL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925606803057901584#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925606803057901584#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE: TRUMP EXPECTS SENATE TO GET BUSY ON TAX BILL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE: DISCUSSED POTENTIAL DEAL WITH IRAN

WHITE HOUSE: TRUMP BELIEVES THINGS MOVING IN RIGHT DIRECTION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925605220660236763#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:30:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925605220660236763#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE: DISCUSSED POTENTIAL DEAL WITH IRAN&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
WHITE HOUSE: TRUMP BELIEVES THINGS MOVING IN RIGHT DIRECTION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *LEAVITT: ABSURD TO SAY TRUMP PROFITING FROM PRESIDENCY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925605119489397062#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:30:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925605119489397062#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*LEAVITT: ABSURD TO SAY TRUMP PROFITING FROM PRESIDENCY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *LEAVITT: TRUMP IS ABIDING BY CONFLICT OF INTEREST LAWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925605110412947558#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:30:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925605110412947558#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*LEAVITT: TRUMP IS ABIDING BY CONFLICT OF INTEREST LAWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
