<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: I BELIEVE IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922605634966466569#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:51:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922605634966466569#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: I BELIEVE IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINESE ROBOTAXI OPERATOR http://PONY.AI REPORTS FIRST FIRE- CNBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922605446038180242#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:50:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922605446038180242#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINESE ROBOTAXI OPERATOR &lt;a href=&quot;http://PONY.AI&quot;&gt;PONY.AI&lt;/a&gt; REPORTS FIRST FIRE- CNBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - TESLA SHARES UP 1.7% PREMARKET FOLLOWING 21.3% CLIMB IN PAST FIVE SESSIONS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922605160271855964#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:49:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922605160271855964#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - TESLA SHARES UP 1.7% PREMARKET FOLLOWING 21.3% CLIMB IN PAST FIVE SESSIONS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A: EBC and International University of Ulaanbaatar’s Vision for Mongolia’s Youth</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/qa-ebc-and-international-university-of-ulaanbaatars-vision-for-mongolias-youth-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:48:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/qa-ebc-and-international-university-of-ulaanbaatars-vision-for-mongolias-youth-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebcfin.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;EBC Financial Group&lt;/a&gt; has partnered with the International University of Ulaanbaatar (IUU) to bridge
the gap between academic learning and real-world financial experience for
Mongolia’s youth. This collaboration aims to nurture the next generation of
finance professionals through internships, mentorship, and industry-academia
initiatives. Below, we answer key questions about the partnership, its
objectives, and the benefits for students and the broader financial sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is EBC
investing in Mongolia’s youth?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EBC recognises
Mongolia as a dynamic emerging market with a new generation eager to contribute
to the global financial sector. However, there is a gap between academic
learning and practical industry experience. By investing in Mongolia’s youth,
EBC aims to bridge this gap, nurture local talent, and help build a stronger
financial ecosystem for the country’s future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does the
partnership with the International University of Ulaanbaatar (IUU) involve?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EBC has signed
a Joint Cooperation Agreement with IUU to create meaningful opportunities for students.
The partnership delivers up to 10 annual internship positions at EBC’s Mongolia
office, allowing selected students to gain hands-on experience in a global
financial environment. In addition, EBC will engage with&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IUU through
lectures, workshops, and events, bringing industry expertise directly into the
classroom and fostering industry-academia collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How can
students benefit from this collaboration?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students
benefit through:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Internships: Practical experience at
EBC’s Mongolia office, with the potential for outstanding
interns to secure further opportunities within the company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Mentorship: Guidance from EBC
professionals to help navigate career choices and build professional
networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Skill Development: Access to
industry-led workshops and real-world exposure to trading, risk
management, and financial technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;•Career
Pathways: The partnership helps students become
job-ready and competitive in the global
marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How does this
fit into EBC’s global ESG goals?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This
collaboration is part of EBC’s broader mission to foster financial talent,
promote industry academia collaboration, and demonstrate leadership in ESG
(Environmental, Social, and Governance) principles. By investing in Mongolia’s
youth and supporting education, EBC is building a more robust and innovative financial
sector while advancing social responsibility and sustainable growth in emerging
markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New Standard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through its
partnership with the International University of Ulaanbaatar, EBC is empowering
Mongolia’s next generation of financial leaders. By combining practical
experience, mentorship, and global engagement, EBC and IUU are setting a new
standard for industry-academic collaboration and youth development in the
region.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: I&apos;m a big crypto fan</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-a-big-crypto-fan-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-a-big-crypto-fan-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m a big crypto fan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He&apos;s giving some general comments on various topics but given the positive sentiment in the market I wouldn&apos;t be surprised to see Bitcoin rallying just on this single comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More comments:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m a believer in AI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We lead China in cryptocurrency.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: CHUCK SCHUMER HAS &quot;BECOME A PALESTINIAN&quot;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922599028858003677#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:25:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922599028858003677#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: CHUCK SCHUMER HAS &quot;BECOME A PALESTINIAN&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: IM A BIG CRYPTO FAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922598955440845156#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:24:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922598955440845156#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: IM A BIG CRYPTO FAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: DOESN&apos;T KNOW IF PUTIN WILL SHOW UP FOR TALKS ON UKRAINE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922598457371443639#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:22:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922598457371443639#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: DOESN&apos;T KNOW IF PUTIN WILL SHOW UP FOR TALKS ON UKRAINE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil is back at the key resistance zone as a breakout becomes likely</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-is-back-at-the-key-resistance-zone-as-a-breakout-becomes-likely-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:46:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-is-back-at-the-key-resistance-zone-as-a-breakout-becomes-likely-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The crude oil market has been battered by negative news on both the demand and supply side in April and that weighed a lot on prices. More recently, the demand side of the equation started to improve as positive developments on the trade front made the market to expect better global growth ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, we might have a doube bottom but we will need a break above the resistance to confirm that. Fundamentally, the uptrend should remain intact as long as things continue to improve. In my opinion, a rally to 72.00 looks very likely now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can see that the price is back at the key resistance zone around the 64.00 level. This is where we can expect the sellers to step in with a defined risk above the level to position for a drop back into the 55.00 level. The buyers, on the other hand, will look for a break higher to increase the bullish bets into the major trendline around the 67.00 level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can see that we have an upward trendline defining the bullish momentum. If we get a pullback, we can expect the buyers to lean on the trendline with a defined risk below it to position for a break above the resistance. The sellers, on the other hand, will look for a break lower to increase the bearish bets into the 55.00 level next. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GOOLSBEE: RIGHT NOW IS A TIME FOR THE FED TO WAIT FOR MORE INFORMATION, TRY TO GET PAST THE NOISE IN THE DATA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922587247318061471#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:38:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922587247318061471#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GOOLSBEE: RIGHT NOW IS A TIME FOR THE FED TO WAIT FOR MORE INFORMATION, TRY TO GET PAST THE NOISE IN THE DATA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Goolsbee: It will take time for current inflation trends to show up in the data</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolsbee-it-will-take-time-for-current-inflation-trends-to-show-up-in-the-data-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolsbee-it-will-take-time-for-current-inflation-trends-to-show-up-in-the-data-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some part of April inflation represents lagged nature of data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed is still very much holding its breath&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Right now is a time for the Fed to wait for more information, try to get past the noise in the data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Cannot jump to conclusions about long-term trends given all the short-term volatility present&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s task is to be a steady hand and not to respond to daily gyrations of stock market, policy pronouncements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;His comments continue to reaffirm that the Fed is still very much in wait-and-see mode. And that will certainly continue to irk Trump, with his latest disdain towards Fed chair Powell coming yesterday &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/trump-tells-powell-to-cut-rates-let-it-all-happen-it-will-be-a-beautiful-thing-20250513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GOOLSBEE: IT WILL TAKE TIME FOR CURRENT INFLATION TRENDS TO SHOW UP IN THE DATA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922587113205150140#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:37:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922587113205150140#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GOOLSBEE: IT WILL TAKE TIME FOR CURRENT INFLATION TRENDS TO SHOW UP IN THE DATA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S GOOLSBEE: SOME PART OF APRIL INFLATION REPRESENTS LAGGED NATURE OF DATA; FED STILL HOLDING ITS BREATH - NPR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922587055348973688#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:37:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922587055348973688#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S GOOLSBEE: SOME PART OF APRIL INFLATION REPRESENTS LAGGED NATURE OF DATA; FED STILL HOLDING ITS BREATH - NPR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN SAYS PUTIN&apos;S OFFER OF DIRECT TALKS IN ISTANBUL BETWEEN RUSSIA AND UKRAINE ON THURSDAY STANDS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922584549323685975#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:27:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922584549323685975#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN SAYS PUTIN&apos;S OFFER OF DIRECT TALKS IN ISTANBUL BETWEEN RUSSIA AND UKRAINE ON THURSDAY STANDS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN SAYS THE RUSSIAN DELEGATION WILL BE IN ISTANBUL ON THURSDAY AND WAIT FOR THE UKRAINIAN DELEGATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922584429953790461#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:27:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922584429953790461#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN SAYS THE RUSSIAN DELEGATION WILL BE IN ISTANBUL ON THURSDAY AND WAIT FOR THE UKRAINIAN DELEGATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No monetary policy comments by Waller in his speech in Morocco</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/no-monetary-policy-comments-by-waller-in-his-speech-in-morocco-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:17:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/no-monetary-policy-comments-by-waller-in-his-speech-in-morocco-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;If you&apos;re waiting on this, then it&apos;s a bit of a dud. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/speech/waller20250514a.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Here&apos;s&lt;/a&gt; the full speech. It&apos;s an awards ceremony so I&apos;m not sure if there will be a Q&amp;amp;A of sorts after his prepared speech here.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China April M2 money supply +8.0% vs +7.3% y/y expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-april-m2-money-supply-80-vs-73-yy-expected-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-april-m2-money-supply-80-vs-73-yy-expected-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +7.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New yuan loans ¥280.0 billion vs ¥700.0 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior ¥3.64 trillion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;After the big surge in March, new bank loans in China fell off with the reading even coming in well below estimates. The ramp up in Q1 comes as policymakers were ramping up stimulus in preparations of a trade war with the US. So, there&apos;s that. Still, outstanding yuan loans are seen up 7.2% year-on-year as of April.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Nagel: Euro will become stronger as a reserve currency in the coming years</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-euro-will-become-stronger-as-a-reserve-currency-in-the-coming-years-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-euro-will-become-stronger-as-a-reserve-currency-in-the-coming-years-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dollar is very important for the world financial system&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But the role of the euro will become stronger as a reserve currency over the next few years&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, the dollar has certainly lost some credibility and allure in the last two months. And this week&apos;s price action itself underscores that sentiment, with the big gains on Monday quickly being erased yesterday and today. But in terms of wider acceptance for payments, the euro itself has struggled over the past decade while dollar usage continues to dominate. The single currency used to command 30% to 35% of the share of international payments via SWIFT. However, that share has now dropped to around 21% to 23% in the past two years. Here&apos;s the latest breakdown from January this year:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of NFTs: Beyond Digital Art</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/the-future-of-nfts-beyond-digital-art-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/the-future-of-nfts-beyond-digital-art-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There was a time — not
long ago, and not far from here — when a JPEG of a cartoon animal could be sold
for the price of a London flat. At first, it looked like a digital renaissance,
then perhaps something more suspect. Now, with the early dust settled, what’s
left is not exactly a crash, but a pause. And in that pause, something more
sober and arguably more interesting has begun to form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NFTs — those
much-maligned and much-misunderstood tokens — are edging toward a broader
cultural role. Not just in art galleries or Twitter avatars, but in ownership
structures, digital identity, and software licensing. They are becoming less
about hype and more about utility. And as collectors shift from sensation to
substance, so too does the shape of the ecosystem. It’s not glamorous, but then
again, neither was the internet when it was mostly message boards and mailing
lists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quiet Commerce&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a quiet
diligence to the way people browse an &lt;a href=&quot;https://magiceden.io/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;NFT marketplace&lt;/a&gt; now. Less of the
speculative fervour. More patience. You’ll find a mix of seasoned collectors
and quiet optimists poring over contract terms, metadata, and artist track
records — more interested in provenance than promise. The hype hasn’t
disappeared, but it has been diluted. Replaced by a kind of forensic curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And with this shift
comes a new kind of discernment. The term &quot;NFT marketplace&quot; used to
conjure a carnival — neon, noise, velocity. Now, it&apos;s more like a secondhand
bookshop: considered, maybe a bit dusty, but sincere. People still look for beauty,
of course, but they&apos;re also looking for function. Access passes, tokenised
experiences, licencing rights. All hidden in plain sight if you know what to
look for. It&apos;s not about flipping anymore. It&apos;s about belonging. About a future
version of ownership that doesn’t feel like ownership at all — just
participation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Frame&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art is still the entry
point for many, and that’s fine. But NFTs are beginning to stretch beyond the
screen. They&apos;re in concert tickets, digital diplomas, domain names. Not always
called NFTs, mind you — sometimes rebranded, renamed, obscured under new language.
But the structure’s the same. A unique, verifiable token stored on a chain.
It’s not the label that matters anymore. It’s the quiet infrastructure behind
it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A growing number of
creative professionals — writers, musicians, developers — are beginning to
explore NFTs as a licensing tool. One token, one licence, no intermediaries.
It&apos;s less a revolution than a workaround. A way of owning your own distribution
without chasing ad revenue or algorithmic favour. Again, not particularly
flashy. But durable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Long View&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;re at the point now
where it&apos;s no longer &quot;What can NFTs do?&quot; but &quot;What should they
do?&quot; The tech adapts. But the culture surrounding it will decide its next
chapter. Two things loom largest: integration or isolation. Either NFTs are a
quiet component of broader systems — part of how we manage identity, contracts,
access — or they become an isolate for digital collectibles with a shrinking
audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The signs point to the
former. Financial institutions are exploring tokenisation. Universities are
testing on-chain certification. Artists are licensing exclusive works through
tokens that act as both proof and access. Slowly, NFTs are becoming less about
speculation and more about structure. A digital filing cabinet of sorts — part
record, part key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin, and the Rest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From time to time,
Bitcoin enters the conversation again. Not directly, but always there in the
background. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency&quot;&gt;The original token&lt;/a&gt;, the benchmark, the
baseline. Discussions around Bitcoin still dominate much of the financial
commentary — and not without reason. Its price movements shape sentiment across
the board. If &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/crypto-takes-another-bath-on-trump-tariff-tade-war-20250402/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin &lt;/a&gt;rallies, interest in adjacent
tokens, including NFTs, often follows. But that correlation is weakening. NFTs,
at least the more functional ones, are beginning to detach from Bitcoin’s
volatility. Not entirely, but enough to chart a slightly different course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And for all the
obsession with the valuations, many in the NFT space have learned to tune it
out. They keep one eye on the charts, yes — everyone does — but their focus is
elsewhere: on deliverables, communities, and contracts. The NFT crowd, in its
quieter corners, is maturing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Function Before Fame&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most promising use
cases now are the ones no one’s bragging about. Backend permissions for
software. Tickets that can’t be faked. Proof of attendance. Proof of
authorship. These are small, infrastructural things — not front-page headlines,
but foundations. And often, that’s where long-term value lives. Not in the
aesthetic but the administrative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is not to say the
art is done. It isn’t. But it’s becoming something else — less performative,
more embedded. NFT projects that succeed in 2025 and beyond will likely be the
ones you don’t even notice. They’ll sit quietly under the products and services
you use every day. Invisible, but integral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the End, Ownership&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At its heart, the NFT &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2021/apr/03/non-fungible-tokens-digital-art-artists&quot;&gt;is still about ownership&lt;/a&gt;. Just not in the way
it was sold to us a few years ago. It&apos;s not about bragging rights or early
adoption. It’s about clarity. Who made this? Who owns it? Who can use it, and
how? It’s about drawing lines — gently — in a digital world that’s long been boundaryless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That might not be the
revolution people were promised. But it might be the one they actually needed.
Something less cinematic. More lived-in. NFTs not as statement pieces but as
tools. Quiet, purposeful, and — in time — indispensable.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE SPOKESPERSON: SYRIA&apos;S PRESIDENT AL-SHARAA TOLD U.S. TRUMP HE INVITES AMERICAN COMPANIES TO INVEST IN SYRIAN OIL AND GAS SECTOR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922571395944321202#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:35:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922571395944321202#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE SPOKESPERSON: SYRIA&apos;S PRESIDENT AL-SHARAA TOLD U.S. TRUMP HE INVITES AMERICAN COMPANIES TO INVEST IN SYRIAN OIL AND GAS SECTOR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD is approaching a key resistance amid some dollar weakness</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-is-approaching-a-key-resistance-amid-some-dollar-weakness-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:34:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-is-approaching-a-key-resistance-amid-some-dollar-weakness-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There was no catalyst for the sudden weakness in the US Dollar but this move could offer a great opportunity for dollar bulls. The short dollar trade is still a bit overcrowded and there are good reasons to see Treasury yields moving higher in the next weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m starting to doubt that we even get more than one rate cut this year but for the market to price that in we will likely need stronger 
economic data or more hawkish Fed comments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fed&apos;s Waller is set to speak in a bit. Let&apos;s see if he&apos;s going to deliver some hawkish comments (keep in mind he might not comment on monetary policy at all at this event) and give the greenback another boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can see that the pair is approaching a key resistance zone around the 1.1275 level where we can find the confluence of the old support and the downward trendline. If the price gets there, we can expect the sellers to step in with a defined risk above the trendline to position for a drop into the 1.10 handle. The buyers, on the other hand, will want to see the price breaking higher to invalidate the bearish setup and start targeting the 1.15 handle next.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S COMMERCE MINISTRY: EXPORT CONTROL ON STRATEGIC MINERALS RELATES TO NATIONAL SECURITY AND DEVELOPMENT INTERESTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922568439526261210#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:23:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922568439526261210#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S COMMERCE MINISTRY: EXPORT CONTROL ON STRATEGIC MINERALS RELATES TO NATIONAL SECURITY AND DEVELOPMENT INTERESTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Nagel: There is a good probability we will get to 2% inflation target</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-there-is-a-good-probability-we-will-get-to-2-inflation-target-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:22:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-there-is-a-good-probability-we-will-get-to-2-inflation-target-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current uncertainty will be the new &quot;normal&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Central banks have to get used to managing it&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expect there to be new staff projections in June&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But we don&apos;t know the exact impact from tariffs on inflation and the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;June rate decision depends on incoming data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;At least he&apos;s trying to paint a bit more of an honest picture with these remarks. But at the end of the day, groupthink is a main issue with central banks. When the going gets tough, everyone defers to the majority view to not be &quot;wrong&quot; and to not jeopardise their reputation. Pfft. Anyway, markets are pricing in ~81% odds of a 25 bps rate cut in June currently.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP:  IN THE FUTURE WE WILL CONTINUE TO ADD MORE COUNTRIES TO THE ABRAHAM ACCORDS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922567616339595293#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:20:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922567616339595293#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP:  IN THE FUTURE WE WILL CONTINUE TO ADD MORE COUNTRIES TO THE ABRAHAM ACCORDS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: LIFTING SANCTIONS ON SYRIA TO GIVE THEM A FRESH START</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922566846407925886#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:17:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922566846407925886#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: LIFTING SANCTIONS ON SYRIA TO GIVE THEM A FRESH START&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: EXPLORING NORMALIZING RELATIONS WITH SYRIA&apos;S GOVERNMENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922566672805773684#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:16:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922566672805773684#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: EXPLORING NORMALIZING RELATIONS WITH SYRIA&apos;S GOVERNMENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German economy ministry: A renewed weakening of the economy cannot be ruled out</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/german-economy-ministry-a-renewed-weakening-of-the-economy-cannot-be-ruled-out-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:13:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/german-economy-ministry-a-renewed-weakening-of-the-economy-cannot-be-ruled-out-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Business expectations remain gloomy, particularly in export-oriented manufacturing sector&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Inflation likely to remain in the region of 2% for the remainder of the year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Trade and economic policy uncertainty remains significantly elevated&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just some token remarks there from Germany. Despite some improvement to the outlook, the backdrop remains challenging for Europe&apos;s largest economy. Not least with inflationary pressures still holding up for the time being.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: I WANT TO MAKE A DEAL WITH IRAN, BUT FOR THAT TO HAPPEN IT MUST STOP SUPPORTING TERROR AND NOT HAVE A NUCLEAR WEAPON</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922565795164352793#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:12:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922565795164352793#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: I WANT TO MAKE A DEAL WITH IRAN, BUT FOR THAT TO HAPPEN IT MUST STOP SUPPORTING TERROR AND NOT HAVE A NUCLEAR WEAPON&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF returns inside the big range as the short positioning in the USD unwinds</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdchf-returns-inside-the-big-range-as-the-short-positioning-in-the-usd-unwinds-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:11:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdchf-returns-inside-the-big-range-as-the-short-positioning-in-the-usd-unwinds-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US Dollar has been under strong selling pressure for a
 few months and eventually became one of the most crowded trades. When you get at such overstretched levels, as soon as 
conditions change, the repricing in expectations can lead to notable corrections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the last few weeks, the positive news on the trade front started to boost the greenback as the market begun to unwind those crowded dollar shorts amid a more hawkish repricing in rate cuts expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the peak of the trade war fears, the market went 
to price in as far as five rate cuts by the end of 2025, and now 
following the US-China news, we are down to just two rate cuts (which 
was the Fed&apos;s base case in December 2024).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We should see further gains for the greenback as the market might even 
start to doubt the need for two rate cuts, but for that, stronger 
economic data or more hawkish Fed comments might be needed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can see the big range between the 0.8350 support and the 0.9250 resistance. The pair broke below the support during the April&apos;s risk-off flows but has now bounced back inside the range. We can see that we have a major trendline defining the bearish trend and from a risk management perspective, the sellers will have a better risk to reward setup around the trendline to position for further downside. The buyers, on the other hand, will want to see the price breaking higher to start targeting the 0.9250 resistance next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we are seeing a pullback after the spike triggered by the US-China news on Monday. The buyers will likely pile in around the 0.8330-0.8380 price area to position for a rally into the major trendline. The sellers, on the other hand, will look for a break lower to extend the pullback into the upward trendline around the 0.8260 level.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar selling picks up to start the session</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-selling-picks-up-to-start-the-session-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:09:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-selling-picks-up-to-start-the-session-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar is down across the board to start European morning trade, as the selling from yesterday carries over. Despite the Monday jump, the dollar has failed to sustain the momentum with price action now starting to turn back against the currency. EUR/USD as seen above is now back above 1.1200 as the near-term bias switches back to being more neutral and closes in on filling the gap lower from the start of the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;USD/JPY is also down 0.8% to 146.30 currently and contesting a break blower below its own 100-hour moving average of 146.58.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Elsewhere, we&apos;re seeing GBP/USD extend higher to 1.3350 and AUD/USD also moving closer towards a test of the 0.6500 level. The latter though has large option expiries at the figure level that could limit gains until we get to US trading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/mufg-we-expect-limited-usd-upside-as-tariff-de-escalation-faces-structural-hurdles-20250513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Here&apos;s a couple of reasons&lt;/a&gt; why the dollar is struggling despite equities and the risk mood holding their ground from the recent trade news.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices open little changed to kick start the day</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-open-little-changed-to-kick-start-the-day-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:06:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-open-little-changed-to-kick-start-the-day-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The overall risk mood is keeping steadier, with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures seen up 0.16% currently. There&apos;s not too much action in the major currencies space as well, with the dollar keeping mostly rangebound against the others. USD/JPY did dip lower to 146.85 earlier but is now holding around 147.07 - down 0.2% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs lifts forecast for European, UK stocks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-lifts-forecast-for-european-uk-stocks-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:00:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-lifts-forecast-for-european-uk-stocks-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs is now seeing the Stoxx 600 index hitting a target of 570 in the next 12 months - up from 520 previously. Meanwhile, they are also seeing the UK FTSE hit a target of 8,800 in the next 12 months now - up from 8,500 previously.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain April final CPI +2.2% vs +2.2% y/y prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-final-cpi-22-vs-22-yy-prelim-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 07:00:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-final-cpi-22-vs-22-yy-prelim-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HICP +2.2% vs +2.2% y/y prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Core annual inflation is seen nudging higher to 2.4%, up from 2.0% in March. So, that&apos;s another thorn in the side to the ECB with the German report indicating the same trend.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – We continue to price out the stagflationary risk</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-we-continue-to-price-out-the-stagflationary-risk-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:59:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-we-continue-to-price-out-the-stagflationary-risk-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold continues to pull back
amid the positive global growth expectations following the much better than
expected US-China news on Monday. These expectations are also leading to a more
hawkish repricing in interest rates and the pricing out of stagflationary risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the bigger picture, gold
remains in an uptrend as real yields will likely continue to fall amid Fed
easing. But in the short-term the repricing in rate cuts expectations will
likely keep a lid on gold upside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that gold continues to pull back amid the positive sentiment on the trade
front. From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a better risk
to reward setup around the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt;, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into the 2957 level next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see the price fell below the key &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-support-and-resistance-20220405/&quot;&gt;support&lt;/a&gt; around the 3258 level and after a retest,
continued lower. The sellers will keep on pushing towards the major trendline,
while the buyers will want to see the price rising back above the 3258 level to
start targeting the 3367 level next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor downward trendline defining the bearish momentum. The
sellers will likely continue to lean on the trendline to keep pushing into new
lows, while the buyers will look for a break higher to pile in for a rally back
into the 3367 level. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we have Fed’s Waller speaking. Tomorrow, we get the
latest US Jobless Claims figures, the US PPI and the US Retail Sales data. On
Friday, we conclude the week with the University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment
report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:16:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;We have an empty calendar today on the data front, so at best the focus will be on central bank speakers as we try to gauge their next moves following the recent developments on the trade front.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most important one should be Fed&apos;s Waller, who recently become one of the most dovish members. He laid out two scenarios last month. In the first scenario, the average global tariff rate would be above 20% and he would be willing to look through inflation and cut rates on a slowdown in the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the second scenario, the average global tariff rate would be 10% and he would be willing to hold rates steady for longer and cut in the latter half of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second scenario is what is playing out and it will be interesting to hear whether he confirms that and switches back to a more hawkish stance. Remember that the market is sensitive to Waller&apos;s views because he acted as a leading indicator for Fed&apos;s policy since 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;07:15 GMT/03:15 ET - BoE&apos;s Breeden (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;09:15 GMT/05:15 ET - Fed&apos;s Waller (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:40 GMT/08:40 ET - ECB&apos;s Cipollone (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;13:10 GMT/09:10 ET - Fed&apos;s Jefferson (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;21:40 GMT/17:40 ET - Fed&apos;s Daly (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOE&apos;s Mann: UK labour market has been more resilient than expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-mann-uk-labour-market-has-been-more-resilient-than-expected-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:07:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-mann-uk-labour-market-has-been-more-resilient-than-expected-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Worried that household inflation expectations have increased&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Need to see loss of pricing power by firms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But goods price inflation is going up&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;She&apos;s turned back to the hawkish side, having voted to keep the bank rate unchanged last week. Yesterday, she defended her position in saying that they will stop using restrictive language &quot;when it is appropriate&quot;. Adding that &quot;somebody has got to pay for volatility&quot; amid the risk and uncertainty in markets at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures -0.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:05:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This follows from the solid showing in Wall Street again, with dip buyers turning things around in US trading. The S&amp;amp;P 500 has now turned positive on the year as Trump continues to talk up the market. He said yesterday that &quot;the market will go higher&quot;. For now, the overall risk mood is calmer with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up just 0.1% currently.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany April final CPI +2.1% vs +2.1% y/y prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-final-cpi-21-vs-21-yy-prelim-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 06:00:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-final-cpi-21-vs-21-yy-prelim-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HICP +2.2% vs +2.2% y/y prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The downside to the report is that core annual inflation is seen ticking higher again to 2.9%. That is up from 2.6% in March. It&apos;s a bump in the road and acts as thorn in the side to the ECB in pursuing further rate cuts. That especially as global trade developments look to stabilise for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China grants first rare earth export permits since adding restrictions last month - report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-grants-first-rare-earth-export-permits-since-adding-restrictions-last-month-report-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 05:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-grants-first-rare-earth-export-permits-since-adding-restrictions-last-month-report-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;However, not to the US though. One of the sources said that the permits were issued to suppliers for customers in Europe and Vietnam. As a reminder, China stepped up their rare earth export controls by restricting a further seven minerals last month &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-halts-rare-earth-exports-after-new-controls-raising-global-supply-concerns-20250413/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It is reported that there is at least four permits granted in this latest batch. Baotou Tianhe Magnetics is one of those suppliers who received a license for Volkswagen in late April. The supplier is one which makes the magnets used in electric and hybrid car motors. But the sources say that Volkswagen had reached out to Beijing for help in trying to make that happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Typically, it takes about two to three months for China to filter through requests for the permits. And since imposing the added restrictions last month, this batch of permits are the first ones to be granted. But again, it doesn&apos;t seem like any US clients are part of the list whatsoever. And I wouldn&apos;t expect that to change unless there is some real progress during this 90-day negotiation timeline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Even if export controls fall short of an outright ban, it&apos;s safe to say that there is an unofficial ban for exporting to the US for the time being.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar gets a check back as early week momentum falters</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-gets-a-check-back-as-early-week-momentum-falters-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:35:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-gets-a-check-back-as-early-week-momentum-falters-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar was the laggard in trading yesterday as it surrendered a large chunk of the gains from Monday. And that comes despite a continued bid in equities and with Treasury yields pushing higher as well. The latter is going to be a key focus as long-end yields are starting to near the April highs again. Traders look to be turning their attention to the deficit and tax cuts as we buy a bit of reprieve from trade drama.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Going back to the dollar though, it struggled despite the conditions in broader markets. One can point to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-core-cpi-28-vs-28-yy-expected-20250513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US CPI report&lt;/a&gt; yesterday being cooler than expected. But again, remember that we haven&apos;t seen any major impact from tariffs just yet. In any case, the dollar lost modest ground and we&apos;re now starting to see near-term technical levels get called into question:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;EUR/USD is less than 0.5% down from the close on Friday as it nudges back towards the 1.1200 level. That now brings up a test of the 100-hour moving average (red line) at 1.1197. Break above that and the 1.1200 level and the near-term bias switches back to being more neutral. Hold below and the near-term bias keeps more bearish instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, that&apos;s a key test of resolve for dollar buyers as we approach mid-week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides that, USD/JPY is also trading more sluggishly as it is starting to test waters below 147.00. Its own 100-hour moving average is seen at 146.45 currently and that will be one to watch if the dollar continues to sag. That said, there is some balancing act for the pair here with yields continuing to chase higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Elsewhere, GBP/USD has already recovered its opening gap lower from the start of the week to return above 1.3300. It is the same for AUD/USD as well with the pair now up to 0.6475 on the day. In the case of the aussie, another test of 0.6500 looks to be beckoning and a breakout there could lead to stronger gains in the second half of the week.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 14 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-14-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:04:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-14-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There are a couple to take note of on the board for the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The first one is for EUR/USD at the 1.1175 level. It&apos;s not one that holds any technical significance but could help to provide a floor for price action with the dollar coming back under pressure after the swing yesterday. Even though the strong buying momentum in equities continued, the greenback was left to suffer after the US CPI report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The expiries above may help to keep price action somewhat underpinned at least, with EUR/USD buyers now testing the 100-hour moving average near 1.1200 going into the session ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Then, there are ones for AUD/USD at the 0.6475 and 0.6500 levels. They don&apos;t hold much technical significance as well but the expiries could well act as magnetic poles in keeping price action more limited between the two levels in the session ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Yen adds on a few points on a subdued day otherwise</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-yen-adds-on-a-few-points-on-a-subdued-day-otherwise-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 03:48:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-yen-adds-on-a-few-points-on-a-subdued-day-otherwise-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/fitch-ratings-says-australias-banks-resultsshow-resilience-20250514/&quot;&gt;Fitch Ratings says Australia&apos;s banks&apos; results show resilience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bank-of-england-wednesday-two-pills-and-a-baileys-20250514/&quot;&gt;Bank of England Wednesday - two Pills and a Baileys&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-internet-giant-baidu-preparing-to-test-driverless-ride-hailing-service-in-europe-20250514/&quot;&gt;Chinese internet giant Baidu preparing to test driverless ride-hailing service in Europe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/chinese-company-linked-to-tiktok-bought-300000000-of-trump-coin-20250514/&quot;&gt;Chinese company linked to TikTok  bought $300,000,000 of $TRUMP Coin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/brazils-lula-want-to-create-a-currency-that-does-not-make-us-dependent-one-currency-20250514/&quot;&gt;Brazil’s Lula: Want to create a currency that does not make us dependent on one currency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-q1-wage-price-index-09-qq-expected-08-20250514/&quot;&gt;Australian Q1 wage price index +0.9% q/q (expected +0.8%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/lula-brazilstrengtheningrelationswithchina-brazilnotafraidofusretaliation-20250514/&quot;&gt;Lula: Brazil strengthening relations with China: Brazil not afraid of US retaliation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-the-relationship-with-china-is-excellent-20250514/&quot;&gt;Trump says the relationship with China is excellent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-mid-point-today-at-71956-vs-estimate-at-71813-20250514/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY mid-point today at 7.1956 (vs. estimate at 7.1813)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-unveils-325-billion-lifeline-for-small-firms-facing-us-tariff-threat-20250514/&quot;&gt;South Korea unveils $3.25 billion lifeline for small firms facing U.S. tariff threat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/tether-purchased-more-than-4800-bitcoinat-average-us95319-20250514/&quot;&gt;Tether purchased more than 4,800 Bitcoin at average US$95,319&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/recapping-japan-april-wholesale-inflation-cost-of-inputs-not-a-lot-changed-20250514/&quot;&gt;Recapping Japan April wholesale inflation - cost of inputs not a lot changed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-accepts-qatar-plane-will-be-used-by-our-government-as-a-temporary-air-force-one-20250513/&quot;&gt;Trump accepts Qatar plane &quot;will be used by our Government as a temporary Air Force One&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-data-april-ppi-02-mm-expected-02-40-yy-expected-40-20250513/&quot;&gt;Japan data - April PPI +0.2% m/m (expected +0.2%) &amp;amp; +4.0% y/y (expected +4.0%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/ubs-downgrades-us-equities-to-neutral-but-12-month-view-is-for-higher-20250513/&quot;&gt;UBS downgrades US equities to Neutral, but 12 month view is for higher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-april-unemployment-rate-27-expected-3-prior-29-20250513/&quot;&gt;South Korea April unemployment rate 2.7% (expected 3%, prior 2.9%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-retail-sales-indicator-april-03-yy-prior-16-00-mm-prior-08-20250513/&quot;&gt;New Zealand retail sales indicator, April: -0.3% y/y (prior -1.6) &amp;amp; 0.0% m/m (prior -0.8%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-views-equity-market-performance-as-a-real-time-barometer-of-his-performance-20250513/&quot;&gt;Trump views &quot;equity market performance as a real time barometer of his performance&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-goldman-sachs-forecasts-sp-500-as-high-as-6500-20250513/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Goldman Sachs forecasts S&amp;amp;P 500 as high as 6500&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/iran-wants-concrete-guarantees-before-reaching-an-agreement-with-the-us-20250513/&quot;&gt;Iran wants &apos;concrete guarantees&apos; before reaching an agreement with the US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/iran-and-europe-will-meet-on-friday-20250513/&quot;&gt;Iran and Europe will meet on Friday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/hassett-says-when-trump-returns-hell-announce-the-next-trade-deal-20250513/&quot;&gt;Hassett says when Trump returns he&apos;ll announce the next trade deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-private-survey-of-inventory-shows-headline-crude-oil-build-vs-draw-expected-20250513/&quot;&gt;Oil: private survey of inventory shows headline crude oil build vs draw expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-is-positive-on-the-year-20250513/&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P is positive on the year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-us-dollar-sellers-return-after-lower-cpi-20250513/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: US dollar sellers return after lower CPI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/financial-times-reports-that-china-has-criticized-the-trade-deal-between-the-us-and-uk-20250513/&quot;&gt;Financial Times reports that China has criticized the trade deal between the US and UK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/whats-driving-teslas-rise-20250513/&quot;&gt;What&apos;s driving Tesla&apos;s rise?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nzdusd-climbs-after-sellers-miss-their-shot-at-breakdown-20250513/&quot;&gt;NZDUSD climbs after sellers miss their shot at breakdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-wednesday-14-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250513/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Wednesday, 14 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
News
and data flow was fairly light during the session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;It
began with a surprise build in crude inventory showing in the private
(API) survey. Oil has dribbled a little lower during the session with
the large draw cited as a contributor. Official US government
inventory data will follow mid-morning on Wednesday in the US. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;From
Japan we had wholesale inflation data. The April PPI came in as
expected and down a touch from March. The slightly stronger yen
helped ease imported inflationary pressure but fuel and rice prices
remained high. Japan&apos;s government has released rice from its strategic
reserve but price decline is slow to filter through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;USD/JPY
ticked up just a little after the data but soon reversed. Highs were
around 147.65 and the trek lower took the rate to circa 147.01. The
Bank of Japan bought back 20bn yen in JGBs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
People’s Bank of China continued to mark the onshore yuan stronger,
setting it at its highest against the USD (ie the lowest for USD/CNY)
since April 3 at 7.1956, well under the psychological 7.2 level. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Trump
crossed the wires with a few comments in a Fox interview but with
nothing to move markets around. He defended accepting the free plane
from Qatar to be used as Air Force 1 in a social media post. News crossed also that a
Chinese company linked to TikTok bought US$300,000,000 of TRUMP
Coin. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;From
Australia we had Q1 wages data, the 0.9% q/q rise was above the 0.8%
consensus expectation but matched the Reserve Bank of Australia&apos;s forecast. The RBA is expected to cut its cash rate at its meeting on
May 19-20. The data today, having hit their target, is unlikely to
stop that cut.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HASSETT: WHEN TRUMP GETS BACK HE WILL ANNOUNCE NEXT DEAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922395831484690454#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922395831484690454#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HASSETT: WHEN TRUMP GETS BACK HE WILL ANNOUNCE NEXT DEAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HASSETT: GOT MORE THAN 20 TO 25 DEALS ON THE TABLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922393337639686291#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:47:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922393337639686291#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HASSETT: GOT MORE THAN 20 TO 25 DEALS ON THE TABLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US COMMERCE DEPARTMENT RESCINDS BIDEN-ERA AI DIFFUSION RULE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922357314620670240#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:24:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922357314620670240#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US COMMERCE DEPARTMENT RESCINDS BIDEN-ERA AI DIFFUSION RULE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
