<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Economic calendar in Asia Thursday, May 15, 2025 - Fed speaker, Australia jobs report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-thursday-may-15-2025-fed-speaker-australia-jobs-report-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-thursday-may-15-2025-fed-speaker-australia-jobs-report-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco President Mary Daly is speaking soon, at 2140 GMT / 1740 US Eastern time:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;participates in a fireside chat before the California Bankers Association 25th Annual Conference and Directors Forum&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later we&apos;ll get the Australian employment report for April. It feels early in the month for this, but the data is due on the third Thursday of each month and its rolled around quickly this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solid, but not spectacular, job growth is expected to continue. The jobless rate is expected to hold steady. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barring a surprise the AUD impact should be very limited. The Reserve Bank of Australia is expected to cut its cash rate by 25bp again next week. The Bank meets on May 19 and 20. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The times in the left-most column are GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The numbers in the right-most column are the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month/quarter as the case may be) result. The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade ideas thread - Thursday, 15 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-thursday-15-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:17:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-thursday-15-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Good morning, afternoon and evening all. Any charts, technical analysis, trade ideas, thoughts, views, ForexLive traders would like to share and discuss with fellow ForexLive traders, please do so:
 &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At the close: Tech leads as US stocks climb again</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/at-the-close-tech-leads-as-us-stocks-climb-again-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:06:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/at-the-close-tech-leads-as-us-stocks-climb-again-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;It was more of a battle today but the bulls came out ahead. Newsflow was quiet today -- one of the quietest days of the year -- and that allowed the momentum trade to continue to tick higher. Big winners were in megacap tech and the usual retail-driven tech stocks while some biotech stocks were hit by selling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq Comp +0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russell 2000 -0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DJIA -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you can see there some divergence is creeping in but given the magnitude of recent moves, this was small potatoes. Tomorrow we get retail sales numbers and that could get things moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is a glance at some of the winners and losers on the Nasdaq.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Einhorn: There is no effort to reduce the deficit, buy gold</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/david-einhorn-there-is-no-effort-to-reduce-the-deficit-buy-gold-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:48:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/david-einhorn-there-is-no-effort-to-reduce-the-deficit-buy-gold-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Hedge fund manager David Einhorn is on CNBC:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s not even the beginning of a plan to do anything about the deficit until it&apos;s a crisis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DOGE talked about $2 trillion in savings, it maybe found $150 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs might raise $100 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I don&apos;t understand why the trade deficit is a problem&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;ll be happy if gold goes to $3500, or $3800 but not if it goes to $30,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The administration is &apos;building a retreat&apos;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I don&apos;t see a great incentive for other countries to really negotiate with the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m pretty sure that in a few months we&apos;ll be talking about other things (than tariffs)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I don&apos;t think the USA is coming across as a reliable partner&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says he&apos;s short leveraged MSTR leveraged ETFs and hedged with a long MSTR. Explains it&apos;s a costly ETF to run because it can&apos;t use swaps and must buy high-priced options instead&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Einhorn pitcked LanXess, a German chemical company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today,
 I’m presenting a company where the management has made excellent 
strategic decisions, but the stock has suffered due to a lot of bad 
luck,” he said. “The
 opportunity today is to realize that the troubles have largely passed 
and that the company is likely to be on a successful path to realizing 
the benefits of its transformation.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The frontier: A trading algorithm that writes itself and evolves</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-frontier-a-trading-algorithm-that-writes-itself-and-evolves-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:17:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-frontier-a-trading-algorithm-that-writes-itself-and-evolves-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;For at least the past 25 years, human traders have been anxious about being replaced by machines and yet -- today -- there are more people trading than ever. I&apos;d argue that many of them shouldn&apos;t be trading and note that many of the human tasks in markets have been replaced but the future is hard to predict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a cottage industry around writing and (mostly) selling trading algos. Their success has been mixed at best and it&apos;s mostly been an avenue for grift in the retail space but Jim Simons made ungodly amounts of money quant trading and relatively simplistic methods (though we don&apos;t know the details).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In any case, could this be the next frontier in trading technology?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Google DeepMind today pulled the curtain back on AlphaEvolve,
 an artificial-intelligence agent that can invent brand-new computer 
algorithms — then put them straight to work inside the company’s vast 
computing empire.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;AlphaEvolve pairs Google’s Gemini
 large language models with an evolutionary approach that tests, 
refines, and improves algorithms automatically. The system has already 
been deployed across Google’s data centers, chip designs, and AI 
training systems — boosting efficiency and solving mathematical problems
 that have stumped researchers for decades.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;That description comes from a Venturebeat &lt;a href=&quot;https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-alphaevolve-the-google-ai-that-writes-its-own-code-and-just-saved-millions-in-computing-costs/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;report &lt;/a&gt;on the DeepMind announcement today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea is that the model combines the creativity of a large language model with algorithms 
that can scrutinize the model’s suggestions to filter and improve 
solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can almost guarantee that there are people pouring money into this idea in markets. Unfortunately, the same technology is going to be put to military use and we&apos;ll be lucky to survive it.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WE WILL DO THINGS FOR QATAR THAT THEY WILL BE HAPPY ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922730546410471632#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:07:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922730546410471632#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WE WILL DO THINGS FOR QATAR THAT THEY WILL BE HAPPY ABOUT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: WHEN BESSENT GOES ON TV, EVERYTHING GOES UP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922729313696145419#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922729313696145419#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: WHEN BESSENT GOES ON TV, EVERYTHING GOES UP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil futures settle at $63.15</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6315-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:47:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6315-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The price of crude oil futures are settling at $63.15. That is up $0.52 or 0.82%. The high-priced today rates $63.64. The low price was at $62.78.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;129&quot; data-end=&quot;529&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The price has generally remained below the 50% retracement level of the trading range from the 2020 low, which stands at $64.71. For the bullish bias to gain traction, a sustained move above this midpoint is essential. On April 23, the price briefly climbed above this level, reaching a high of $64.83, before reversing lower—highlighting the importance of this technical barrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;531&quot; data-end=&quot;900&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Geopolitical developments may influence sentiment, with Ukraine and Russia set to hold talks on Thursday. Former President Trump has indicated he may attend, though it&apos;s unclear if President Putin will be present. Trump also reiterated his willingness to strike a deal with Iran, but only on the condition that Iran abandons its nuclear weapons program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;902&quot; data-end=&quot;1346&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Fundamentally, the market is drawing support from the growing view that recession fears may have been overstated. Meanwhile, the latest U.S. crude oil inventory report showed a surprise build of 3.454 million barrels, compared to expectations for a draw of 1.078 million. Gasoline inventories, however, fell by 1.022 million barrels, larger than the expected 561,000-barrel decline—a sign of continued strong demand.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: April US retail sales likely to show frontloading boost</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-april-us-retail-sales-likely-to-show-frontloading-boost-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-april-us-retail-sales-likely-to-show-frontloading-boost-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;87&quot; data-end=&quot;323&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs expects core retail sales to rise in April as consumers frontloaded purchases ahead of impending tariffs, while headline retail sales are likely to remain flat due to weak auto sales and falling gas prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;325&quot; data-end=&quot;340&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;342&quot; data-end=&quot;729&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;342&quot; data-end=&quot;469&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;344&quot; data-end=&quot;469&quot;&gt;Core retail sales forecast: +0.4% m/m, driven by precautionary spending ahead of expected tariff-related price increases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;471&quot; data-end=&quot;586&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;473&quot; data-end=&quot;586&quot;&gt;Headline retail sales forecast: Unchanged, as lower auto sales and gasoline prices offset strength elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;588&quot; data-end=&quot;729&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;590&quot; data-end=&quot;729&quot;&gt;Tariff impact emerging: Consumer behavior appears responsive to trade policy developments, with early signs of demand shifting forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;731&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;731&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot;&gt;Goldman sees the April retail sales report as an early reflection of tariff-driven consumer behavior, supporting resilient core demand but masking it under flat headline numbers due to sector-specific drags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;731&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot;&gt;The US retail sales report is due out Thursday at 8:30 am ET.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747333787383000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw1CROAdlfLrUjx1-cj4kpSp&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747333787383000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw1CROAdlfLrUjx1-cj4kpSp&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD bounces off support target and trying to extend above and toward MA targets</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-bounces-off-support-target-and-trying-to-extend-above-and-toward-ma-targets-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:30:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-bounces-off-support-target-and-trying-to-extend-above-and-toward-ma-targets-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;115&quot; data-end=&quot;367&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCAD moved lower in early trading today but found support near a familiar swing area between 1.38917 and 1.3904. Buyers leaned against that zone, which has acted as a floor in recent sessions, and the price responded with a bounce higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;369&quot; data-end=&quot;596&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The recovery has taken the pair back above the 100-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, currently at 1.39656. That’s a constructive technical step for buyers, as it shifts short-term momentum back in their favor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;598&quot; data-end=&quot;871&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;However, the pair still trades comfortably below the 200-day moving average, which comes in at 1.40115. That longer-term trend indicator is located within a key resistance zone between 1.40097 and 1.40208, making it a critical hurdle for any further upside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;873&quot; data-end=&quot;1078&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Above that, the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement of the March 2025 high-to-low move comes in at 1.40525. That level represents a more meaningful target for buyers looking to gain firmer control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1080&quot; data-end=&quot;1404&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In summary, buyers stepped in at key support and have completed the first step by reclaiming the 100-bar MA. But to turn today’s bounce into something more substantial, they’ll need to push through the 200-day MA and break above the 1.40525 retracement level. Until then, upside confidence remains tentative.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin not interested in one-on-one meeting with Zelensky in Istanbul - report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/putin-not-interested-in-one-on-one-meeting-with-zelensky-in-istanbul-report-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:18:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/putin-not-interested-in-one-on-one-meeting-with-zelensky-in-istanbul-report-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Moscow Times reports that Putin has no intention of meeting directly with Zelensky in Istanbul.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This war has gone on for far too long but it&apos;s hard to say if we&apos;re really in the endgame.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SocGen: We don&apos;t recommend USD shorts here; prefer long AUD and short CHF exposures</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/socgen-we-dont-recommend-usd-shorts-here-prefer-long-aud-and-short-chf-exposures-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:50:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/socgen-we-dont-recommend-usd-shorts-here-prefer-long-aud-and-short-chf-exposures-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;77&quot; data-end=&quot;355&quot;&gt;Société Générale refrains from recommending explicit short USD positions for now, citing policy-driven disruption in FX markets. Instead, they favor tactical long AUD and short CHF exposure, anticipating benefits from trade thaw and reduced geopolitical tension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;357&quot; data-end=&quot;372&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;374&quot; data-end=&quot;975&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;374&quot; data-end=&quot;554&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;376&quot; data-end=&quot;554&quot;&gt;USD view neutral for now: Despite President Trump’s desire for a weaker dollar and rising US yields, SocGen expects EUR/USD and USD/JPY to stay range-bound until late summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;556&quot; data-end=&quot;732&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;558&quot; data-end=&quot;732&quot;&gt;Market uncertainty: Disconnected relationships between FX and rate differentials—similar to 2022—suggest traders are reacting more to political signals than fundamentals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;734&quot; data-end=&quot;835&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;736&quot; data-end=&quot;835&quot;&gt;AUD bullish bias: SocGen favors being long AUD amid signs of improving US-China trade dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;837&quot; data-end=&quot;975&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;839&quot; data-end=&quot;975&quot;&gt;CHF bearish bias: Recommends short CHF positioning, expecting a decline in safe-haven demand as geopolitical risk potentially eases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot;&gt;SocGen avoids a direct USD short stance but sees selective opportunities: long AUD as trade tensions ease and short CHF as geopolitical risk subsides. Broader USD weakness is more likely after the summer once clearer policy and data signals emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot;&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747331392560000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0RYlIf4wI_OcP4iut4d04j&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747331392560000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0RYlIf4wI_OcP4iut4d04j&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The market has removed 60 basis points of Fed easing in the year ahead</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/the-market-has-removed-60-basis-points-of-fed-easing-in-the-year-ahead-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:21:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/the-market-has-removed-60-basis-points-of-fed-easing-in-the-year-ahead-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fed pricing has substantially shifted since the peak of angst about growth, tariffs and inflation two weeks ago. At the time, the market was pricing in 131 bps in easing through the April 29, 2026 scheduled FOMC meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, that has dropped to 71 bps as the market cheers the sharp drop in US-China tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even in the past day, the move has continued as a Sept cut has gone from fully priced in (and a tad more) to now at 91%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think for risk assets this is ultimately a good thing as provides for a large Fed put on top of what&apos;s a seeming re-emergence of the Trump put. For the US dollar it&apos;s more complicated as any weakness in the US economy now leaves it vulnerable to a rapid repricing lower in rates.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – Price breaks below 200-bar MA on 4H as momentum shifts lower</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-price-breaks-below-200-bar-ma-as-momentum-shifts-lower-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:44:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-price-breaks-below-200-bar-ma-as-momentum-shifts-lower-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;86&quot; data-end=&quot;357&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Gold has broken below the 200-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, signaling a potential shift in momentum following its recent highs.The last few attempts of that rising MA (see green line on the chart above) found sellers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;86&quot; data-end=&quot;357&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A close - and staying below this key trend-defining level - would confirm weakening bullish control and open the door for deeper corrective movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;359&quot; data-end=&quot;393&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The next downside targets include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;394&quot; data-end=&quot;598&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;394&quot; data-end=&quot;438&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;396&quot; data-end=&quot;438&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;$3167.74 – the swing high from April 3&amp;gt; The low has reached $3173.85 so far&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;439&quot; data-end=&quot;508&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;441&quot; data-end=&quot;508&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;$3139 – the underside of the broken ascending channel trendline&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;509&quot; data-end=&quot;598&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;511&quot; data-end=&quot;598&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;$3129.26 – the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement of the rally from the November swing low&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;600&quot; data-end=&quot;843&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;These levels represent key technical checkpoints where buyers may attempt to regroup. However, failure to hold those supports could lead to an extended pullback, especially if broader risk sentiment or interest rate expectations shift further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;845&quot; data-end=&quot;976&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For bulls to regain control, a move back above the 200-bar MA near $3,249 would be needed to neutralize the immediate bearish bias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;978&quot; data-end=&quot;1003&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1004&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1004&quot; data-end=&quot;1074&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1006&quot; data-end=&quot;1074&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: $3,249 (200-bar MA), $3,306 (recent swing high zone)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1075&quot; data-end=&quot;1118&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1077&quot; data-end=&quot;1118&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: $3,167.74, $3,139, $3,129.26&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1119&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1121&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 200-bar MA; neutralizing only above $3,249&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US NOT SEEKING TO WEAKEN DOLLAR AS PART OF TRADE DEALS: SOURCE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922693791418298414#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:41:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922693791418298414#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US NOT SEEKING TO WEAKEN DOLLAR AS PART OF TRADE DEALS: SOURCE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD Technical Analysis – Sellers lean at resistance, bias bearish below support zone</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-technical-analysis-sellers-lean-at-resistance-bias-bearish-below-support-zone-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:08:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-technical-analysis-sellers-lean-at-resistance-bias-bearish-below-support-zone-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;99&quot; data-end=&quot;427&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;EURUSD failed to sustain earlier gains as price action today stalled just ahead of the 200-hour moving average (green line on the chart above) and the lower boundary of a key swing zone between 1.12657 and 1.1275. Sellers leaned into the level and have since pushed the pair back toward the 100-hour moving averages&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;429&quot; data-end=&quot;741&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The current focus is on the swing area between 1.1193 and 1.1213, which previously marked key highs from 2024 (not shown). A confirmed break below this zone - and the 100 hour MA at 1.11876 - would be technically significant and likely accelerate selling momentum. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;743&quot; data-end=&quot;1028&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, immediate targets include the 1.1145 support area followed by the weekly low near 1.10648. These levels could attract additional sellers if the current pressure persists. To shift momentum back to the upside, EURUSD would need to reclaim 1.1213 and the 200 hour MA (and stay above) at 1.12578.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1030&quot; data-end=&quot;1055&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1056&quot; data-end=&quot;1264&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1056&quot; data-end=&quot;1122&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1058&quot; data-end=&quot;1122&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.1213,  200-hour MA at 1.12578, 1.12657–1.1275 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1123&quot; data-end=&quot;1204&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1125&quot; data-end=&quot;1204&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.1193–1.1213 (swing zone), 1.11876 (100-hour MA), 1.1145, 1.10648&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1205&quot; data-end=&quot;1264&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1207&quot; data-end=&quot;1264&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 1.1213; intensifies under 1.11876&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1266&quot; data-end=&quot;1416&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The sellers remain in control as long as price stays capped below 1.1213. Watch for follow-through below key supports to confirm bearish continuation.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE BANS US AGENCIES FROM G-20 WORK IN http://S.AFRICA:WAPO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922679354821075403#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:44:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922679354821075403#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE BANS US AGENCIES FROM G-20 WORK IN &lt;a href=&quot;http://S.AFRICA&quot;&gt;S.AFRICA&lt;/a&gt;:WAPO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - TESLA SHARES EXTEND GAINS, LAST UP 4%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922678753945067597#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:41:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922678753945067597#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - TESLA SHARES EXTEND GAINS, LAST UP 4%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equity markets sag late, Spain stocks hit 16-year high</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-markets-sag-late-spain-stocks-hit-16-year-high-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:36:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-markets-sag-late-spain-stocks-hit-16-year-high-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Closing changes on the day:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stoxx 600 -0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE 100 -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.3% -- highest close since 2008&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB +0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spanish stocks have been in an impressive bull market and are making new highs after the tariff rout.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP SECURES HISTORIC $1.2 TRILLION ECONOMIC COMMITMENT IN QATAR -FACT SHEET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922676409668960446#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922676409668960446#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP SECURES HISTORIC $1.2 TRILLION ECONOMIC COMMITMENT IN QATAR -FACT SHEET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) NISSAN WEIGHS MOVING SENTRA PRODUCTION FROM MEXICO TO U.S. TO AVOID TARIFFS - AUTOMOTIVE NEWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922675711673852194#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:29:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922675711673852194#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NISSAN WEIGHS MOVING SENTRA PRODUCTION FROM MEXICO TO U.S. TO AVOID TARIFFS - AUTOMOTIVE NEWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HOTLINE CONNECTING PENTAGON AND FAA AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLERS AT WASHINGTON REAGAN AIRPORT HAS BEEN INOPERABLE SINCE 2022 -- FAA OFFICIAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922674286122164547#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:24:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922674286122164547#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HOTLINE CONNECTING PENTAGON AND FAA AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLERS AT WASHINGTON REAGAN AIRPORT HAS BEEN INOPERABLE SINCE 2022 -- FAA OFFICIAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian dollar dips to the lows of the day as S&amp;P 500 falls flat</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-dollar-dips-to-the-lows-of-the-day-as-sp-500-falls-flat-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:17:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-dollar-dips-to-the-lows-of-the-day-as-sp-500-falls-flat-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Australian dollar stalled out today at 0.6500 and is now coming under broad pressure. The dip takes place as the US dollar rebounds in a choppy market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The move looks like it was driven by profit taking in stock markets and a rise in 10-year yields to 4.50%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - ELON MUSK MEETS WITH QATAR INVESTMENT AUTHORITY CHAIRMAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922672142539165960#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:15:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922672142539165960#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - ELON MUSK MEETS WITH QATAR INVESTMENT AUTHORITY CHAIRMAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Micro Computer (SMCI) – Bullish break above 200 day MA. Key resistance targets ahead</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/super-micro-computer-smci-bullish-break-above-200-day-ma-key-resistance-targets-ahead-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:14:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/super-micro-computer-smci-bullish-break-above-200-day-ma-key-resistance-targets-ahead-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;88&quot; data-end=&quot;661&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Super Micro Computer (SMCI) shares are currently up around 17.14% at $45.57 , extending yesterday’s 16% rally. The sharp move comes on the heels of a major catalyst: a multi-year, $20 billion partnership with Saudi data-center developer DataVolt. As part of the deal, Super Micro will accelerate delivery of ultra-dense GPU platforms and rack systems for DataVolt’s hyperscale AI campuses in both Saudi Arabia and the U.S. CEO Charles Liang highlighted the partnership’s strategic value in expanding U.S. manufacturing and advancing Saudi Arabia’s ambition to become a global tech hub.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;663&quot; data-end=&quot;926&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;This agreement is embedded in a broader U.S.-Saudi commercial initiative totaling $600 billion—the largest such package ever—of which $80 billion in AI and tech infrastructure is being backed by major players including Alphabet, Oracle, Salesforce, AMD, and Uber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;928&quot; data-end=&quot;1502&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For SMCI, the rebound comes after a volatile stretch. Shares had surged to a post-split high of $122.90 in 2024 (following a 10:1 split in October), only to plunge to $17.25 in November amid concerns over accounting irregularities and a delayed earnings release that nearly cost the company its NASDAQ listing. Though the most recent earnings report on May 6 fell short—EPS of $0.31 vs. $0.41 expected, and revenue of $4.6 billion vs. $5.01 billion—the new partnership, coupled with renewed AI enthusiasm and improved transparency, has sparked a sharp reversal in sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1504&quot; data-end=&quot;1582&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;So with the worst potentially behind them, what are the technicals saying now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;91&quot; data-end=&quot;437&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Super Micro Computer (SMCI) is showing renewed bullish momentum after rebounding from a near-collapse late last year. The recent rally has pushed the stock above the 200-day moving average (green line on the chart above), now at $39.87—a level that buyers must defend to maintain control. Holding above this moving average would help solidify a base for further upside traction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;439&quot; data-end=&quot;780&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The next hurdle lies in a key swing area between $47.86 and $51.35. This zone has repeatedly acted as both support and resistance, making it a pivotal battle zone. A sustained break above this region opens the door toward trendline resistance near $53.20, followed by the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level of the 2024–2025 decline at $57.61.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;782&quot; data-end=&quot;973&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The high of the year at $66.44 came before a post-earnings collapse, but the market now appears to be regaining confidence. If buyers can keep the momentum going, there’s room to roam higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;975&quot; data-end=&quot;1106&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, failure to hold above the 200-day MA could signal a fading recovery and refocus attention on lower support levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1108&quot; data-end=&quot;1133&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1134&quot; data-end=&quot;1389&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1134&quot; data-end=&quot;1190&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1136&quot; data-end=&quot;1190&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Immediate support: $39.87 (200-day moving average)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1191&quot; data-end=&quot;1240&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1193&quot; data-end=&quot;1240&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance zone: $47.86–$51.35 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1241&quot; data-end=&quot;1318&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1243&quot; data-end=&quot;1318&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Next upside targets: $53.20 (trendline), $57.61 (38.2% Fib retracement)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1319&quot; data-end=&quot;1389&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1321&quot; data-end=&quot;1389&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bullish above $39.87 with momentum building; caution below&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another stock that was hit hard is also trying to make a comeback.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMD shares are up 5.02% after rising 5.13%,and 4.01% over the prior two days.  The price moved above the 100 aday MA on Monday at $107.48 (now a risk level for buyers looking for more upside). The 200 day MA is above at $127.30 and would need to be broken to increase the bullish bias. The 38.2% of the move down from the 2024 high is at $134.09&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares from the peak in 2024 fell -66%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the bottom is in and the tech/AI momentum reignites, staying above the 100 day MA is now the risk at $107.48.  More confidence comes on a break of the 200 day MA at $127.29. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUSSIA&apos;S LAVROV WILL NOT TAKE PART IN TALKS IN ISTANBUL - KOMMERSANT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922665257815703673#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:48:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922665257815703673#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUSSIA&apos;S LAVROV WILL NOT TAKE PART IN TALKS IN ISTANBUL - KOMMERSANT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech sector rebounds: Nvidia and Google lead market gains</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-rebounds-nvidia-and-google-lead-market-gains-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:46:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-rebounds-nvidia-and-google-lead-market-gains-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Tech sector rebounds: Nvidia and Google lead market gains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US stock market is seeing a notable uptick today, with significant contributions from the technology sector. As investors navigate an increasingly nuanced landscape, both Nvidia (NVDA) and Google (GOOG) have emerged as standout performers, driving the day&apos;s positive momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technology: The tech sector is buoying the market, highlighting a day of robust performance. Nvidia (NVDA) is up 2.02%, reflecting renewed investor confidence. Google (GOOG) adds 2.12% to its value, suggesting strong market sentiment in internet content and information services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consumer Cyclical: Despite tech gains, the consumer cyclical sector shows mixed results. Tesla (TSLA) is bucking this trend with a 1.71% increase, driven by positive developments in the auto industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consumer Defensive:Walmart (WMT) is up 1.27%, indicating some defensive play as investors hedge around economic uncertainties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healthcare: The sector is under pressure with AbbVie (ABBV) down 2.28% amid broader industry challenges.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Financial: Steady yet unspectacular, with JPMorgan Chase (JPM) gaining 0.63%, offering a small beacon of stability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s market is characterized by optimism largely rooted in tech sector performance. Investor sentiment appears bullish on tech rebounds, particularly semiconductors and internet services. However, mixed signals from consumer sectors suggest caution as market participants await further economic data that could sway trends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors should keep a close watch on technological advancements and data-driven trends in the tech sector. There&apos;s a clear opportunity to capitalize on the renewed strength seen in companies like Nvidia and Google. Meanwhile, it&apos;s prudent to maintain a balanced portfolio, given the mixed performance across other sectors such as healthcare and consumer cyclicals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the tech-led recovery, consider shifting focus towards robust performers within the sector while maintaining diversification to safeguard against potential volatility. Stay informed with up-to-date market insights and visit ForexLive.com for more detailed analysis and recommendations.📈&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KENNEDY SAYS HIS OPINIONS ABOUT VACCINES ARE IRRELEVANT, DOES NOT THINK PEOPLE SHOULD TAKE MEDICAL ADVICE FROM HIM</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922662579475714503#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:37:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922662579475714503#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KENNEDY SAYS HIS OPINIONS ABOUT VACCINES ARE IRRELEVANT, DOES NOT THINK PEOPLE SHOULD TAKE MEDICAL ADVICE FROM HIM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GBPUSD Technical Analysis – Buyers eye rebound after dip to 200-bar MA support</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gbpusd-technical-analysis-buyers-eye-rebound-after-dip-to-200-bar-ma-support-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:35:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gbpusd-technical-analysis-buyers-eye-rebound-after-dip-to-200-bar-ma-support-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;84&quot; data-end=&quot;428&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;GBPUSD&apos;s earlier rally stalled at the familiar resistance zone between 1.33619 and 1.33784, where sellers leaned in and capped upside momentum. The pullback found support earlier today at the 200-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, and the pair is now retracing lower toward that level again, presenting a potential dip-buying opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;430&quot; data-end=&quot;785&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For buyers, holding above this key moving average and reclaiming ground toward 1.33227 and beyond would signal renewed bullish intent. On the flip side, if sellers manage to push the pair below the 100-bar MA on the 4-hour chart at 1.32859 and then the 100-hour MA near the 1.32577 swing area, bearish pressure would likely build, shifting the bias lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;430&quot; data-end=&quot;785&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key support test for the GBPUSD.  Can the buyers stall the fall? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;787&quot; data-end=&quot;812&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;813&quot; data-end=&quot;1049&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;813&quot; data-end=&quot;868&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;815&quot; data-end=&quot;868&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.33619–1.33784 (swing area), 1.3423 to 1.34413 (swing highs)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;869&quot; data-end=&quot;976&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;871&quot; data-end=&quot;976&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.32859 (100-bar MA on 4H), 1.32577 (100-hour MA and swing area),&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1049&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;979&quot; data-end=&quot;1049&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Neutral-to-bullish above 1.32859; bearish bias below 1.32577&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1051&quot; data-end=&quot;1232&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Momentum will hinge on how price reacts around the moving average cluster. A bounce would reinforce bullish positioning, while a break below could open the door to further downside.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EIA weekly US crude oil inventories +3454K vs -1078K expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eia-weekly-us-crude-oil-inventories-3454k-vs-1078k-expected-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:30:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eia-weekly-us-crude-oil-inventories-3454k-vs-1078k-expected-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was -2032K&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gasoline -1022K vs -561K expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Distillates -3155K vs +129K expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refinery utilization +1.2% vs +0.8% expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Private data released late yesterday:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude +4287K&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gasoline -1374K&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Distillates -3675K&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;WTI crude oil was down 13-cents to $63.58 ahead of the data. It recovered from earlier lows after data showed Kazakhstan reduced output in April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This update is a drag for oil prices but there is strong product demand, evidently.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA SUSPENDS, SCRAPS UNRELIABLE LIST POLICIES ON SOME US COS.

*CHINA SUSPENDS EXPORTS CONTROL OVER 28 US ENTITIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922658190602219793#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:20:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922658190602219793#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA SUSPENDS, SCRAPS UNRELIABLE LIST POLICIES ON SOME US COS.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*CHINA SUSPENDS EXPORTS CONTROL OVER 28 US ENTITIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *WITKOFF SAYS HE, RUBIO TO TRAVEL TO ISTANBUL ON FRIDAY: RTRS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922657903158173812#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922657903158173812#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*WITKOFF SAYS HE, RUBIO TO TRAVEL TO ISTANBUL ON FRIDAY: RTRS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRADE-TARIFF DEALS WITH JAPAN AND SOUTH KOREA SAID TO BE “CLOSE”: SOURCES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922657301279682846#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:16:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922657301279682846#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRADE-TARIFF DEALS WITH JAPAN AND SOUTH KOREA SAID TO BE “CLOSE”: SOURCES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buyers in the NZDUSD are losing momentum. Down on the day now.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/buyers-in-the-nzdusd-are-losing-momentum-down-on-the-day-now-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:16:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/buyers-in-the-nzdusd-are-losing-momentum-down-on-the-day-now-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;89&quot; data-end=&quot;394&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;After initially breaking above the 100-bar MA on the 4-hour chart at 0.5946, NZDUSD gained upside traction, pushing to a high of 0.5968. However, the bullish momentum quickly faded, and the pair has since slipped back below both the 100-bar MA on the 4-hour chart at 0.59464, and, more recently, the 200-hour MA at 0.59378. The pair is now trading near 0.5930.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;396&quot; data-end=&quot;743&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;With upside momentum stalled, the technical bias has shifted back in favor of sellers below the aforementioned moving average levels. The next downside target lies at the 100-hour MA at 0.59063. A break below that level would strengthen the bearish outlook and open the door toward another key MA - the 200-day MA at 0.5883. That will be a critical zone that could either act as a floor or lead to further downside extension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;396&quot; data-end=&quot;743&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Earlier this week, the NZDUSD moved down to test the rising 200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart and found buyers (on Monday and Tuesday&apos;s lows).  If the selling momentum increases, that MA will be in the back of traders minds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;396&quot; data-end=&quot;743&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;If the momentum lower fades, getting back above the 100 bar MA on the 4-hour chart at 0.59464 would disappoint sellers and give the buyers more hope and control.  There is a ceiling between 0.6018 to 0.60281.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;745&quot; data-end=&quot;770&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;771&quot; data-end=&quot;979&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;771&quot; data-end=&quot;853&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;773&quot; data-end=&quot;853&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Immediate resistance: 0.5946 (broken 100-bar MA on 4H), 0.5968 (recent high from earlier today)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;854&quot; data-end=&quot;918&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;856&quot; data-end=&quot;918&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support levels: 0.59063 (100-hour MA), 0.5883 (200-day MA), 0.58579 (the rising 200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart. The lows for the week bottomed near that MA on Monday and Tuesday before racing higher).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;919&quot; data-end=&quot;979&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;921&quot; data-end=&quot;979&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 0.5946 in the short term. , intensifying below 0.59063&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;981&quot; data-end=&quot;1119&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Traders should watch whether the 100-BA MA on the 4-hour holds restance. A bounce could attract dip buyers, but failure to hold it likely deepens the pullback.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US trade deals with Japan and South Korea said to be close - report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-deals-with-japan-and-south-korea-said-to-be-close-report-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:15:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-deals-with-japan-and-south-korea-said-to-be-close-report-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Here is the scoop from Charlie Gasparino, though these deals have been rumored for a couple weeks:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Trade-tariff deals with Japan and South Korea said to be “close,” according to me Wall Street sources close to the White House. Timing unclear. India deal as well though it has been throttled by the tensions with Pakistan.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;d all love to see the details. The big question is on who is willing to swallow 10% tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) QATAR AGREES TO BUY 160 BOEING AIRCRAFT: WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922656057886642672#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:11:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922656057886642672#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;QATAR AGREES TO BUY 160 BOEING AIRCRAFT: WHITE HOUSE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA PAUSES EXPORT CONTROL MEASURES AGAINST 28 US ENTITIES FOR 90 DAYS FROM MAY 14-COMMERCE MINISTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922655347472282066#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:08:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922655347472282066#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA PAUSES EXPORT CONTROL MEASURES AGAINST 28 US ENTITIES FOR 90 DAYS FROM MAY 14-COMMERCE MINISTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA PAUSES UNRELIABLE ENTITY LIST MEASURE ON 17 US ENTITIES-COMMERCE MINISTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922655109307056431#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:07:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922655109307056431#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA PAUSES UNRELIABLE ENTITY LIST MEASURE ON 17 US ENTITIES-COMMERCE MINISTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $BA - TRUMP: BOEING AGREEMENT IS FOR OVER $200 BLN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922654805232640396#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:06:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922654805232640396#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23BA&quot;&gt;$BA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP: BOEING AGREEMENT IS FOR OVER $200 BLN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $BA - TRUMP: BOEING ORDER THE LARGEST IN HISTORY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922654755291086875#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:06:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922654755291086875#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23BA&quot;&gt;$BA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP: BOEING ORDER THE LARGEST IN HISTORY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD Technical Analysis – Buyers Defend 200-Day MA, but Momentum Wanes</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-technical-analysis-buyers-defend-200-day-ma-but-momentum-wanes-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:49:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-technical-analysis-buyers-defend-200-day-ma-but-momentum-wanes-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;78&quot; data-end=&quot;368&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The AUDUSD rally ran into resistance near the 2025 extreme area around 0.65135 earlier today and quickly reversed lower, signaling fading bullish momentum. The pullback has now brought the pair down to test a key confluence of moving average support, most notably the 200-day MA at 0.64578.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;370&quot; data-end=&quot;804&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;This level is critical. A successful defense here would provide buyers with a potential springboard to reattempt upside moves. However, failure to hold this support increases downside risk. Below the 200-day MA - but with work to do.  The 200-hour MA at 0.6440 and the dual support of the 100-bar MA on the 4-hour chart, and 100-hour MA are near the same level at 0.6418. A break below these levels would likely shift the bias back in favor of sellers and accelerate downside pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;806&quot; data-end=&quot;831&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;832&quot; data-end=&quot;1082&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;832&quot; data-end=&quot;878&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;834&quot; data-end=&quot;878&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Immediate support: 200-day MA at 0.64578&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;879&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;881&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Secondary support: 200-hour MA at 0.6440; 100-bar MA on the 4-hour chart/100-hour MA at 0.6418&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;957&quot; data-end=&quot;1007&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;959&quot; data-end=&quot;1007&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.65135 (2025 extreme high area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1008&quot; data-end=&quot;1082&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1010&quot; data-end=&quot;1082&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Neutral near term; bullish above 0.64578, bearish below 0.6418&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1084&quot; data-end=&quot;1271&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Buyers have a chance to hold the line, but if momentum continues to falter, bears may regain control. Traders should watch closely for confirmation on either side of this support cluster.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The gains continue in US equity markets, led by the Nasdaq</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-gains-continue-in-us-equity-markets-led-by-the-nasdaq-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-gains-continue-in-us-equity-markets-led-by-the-nasdaq-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The S&amp;amp;P 500 is up 0.3% in the early going while the Nasdaq is up 0.6%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There isn&apos;t much (anything?) on the calendar to derail things today so we&apos;ll wait for the usual Trump tweets and other news out of the White House. That said, what could really change things? Tariff policy is paused on various timelines and Republicans are grinding away on the tax bill. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fed is in a holding pattern for at least a month and there is no economic data to come today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That all works very well for the momentum trade.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD Technical Analysis – Resistance holds, but buyers still eye more control</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-technical-analysis-resistance-holds-but-buyers-still-eye-more-control-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:23:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-technical-analysis-resistance-holds-but-buyers-still-eye-more-control-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;80&quot; data-end=&quot;361&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCAD remains capped by key technical barriers, with Monday and Tuesday&apos;s rally stalling near the 200-day moving average at 1.40114 and the critical swing zone between 1.40097 and 1.40268. This area has proven to be a firm ceiling for now, with sellers defending their ground. The price of the USDCAD fell yesterday and again today. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;363&quot; data-end=&quot;618&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Despite this resistance near the 200 day MA, the buyers have not given up. A bounce today - after the 2 day decline - started from the swing support area between 1.38917 and 1.3904. That suggests underlying demand remains intact. The buyers are still in play - at lease in the short term.  This zone was a ceiling until broken last week and basing.   That old ceiling/now floor is helping to define the current consolidation range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;620&quot; data-end=&quot;860&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For buyers to reassert control, they will need to push decisively through nearby resistance at 1.3967 (200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart) to 1.3977 (high from April 15) . A break above that zone would open the path toward the more formidable confluence of the 200-day MA and the high of a swing area at 1.40268.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;862&quot; data-end=&quot;887&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;888&quot; data-end=&quot;1142&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;888&quot; data-end=&quot;930&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;890&quot; data-end=&quot;930&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.38917–1.3904 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;931&quot; data-end=&quot;972&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;933&quot; data-end=&quot;972&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Immediate resistance: 1.3967–1.3977&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;973&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;975&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Major resistance: 1.40097–1.40268 (swing zone) and 200-day MA at 1.40114&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1052&quot; data-end=&quot;1142&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1054&quot; data-end=&quot;1142&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Cautiously bullish above 1.3904; more bullish confirmation on break of 1.40268&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1144&quot; data-end=&quot;1261&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Momentum above 1.3977 could reignite upside pressure, but failure to clear resistance risks renewed downside probing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Jefferson: Current policy is a good place to respond to economic developments</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-jefferson-current-policy-is-a-good-place-to-respond-to-economic-developments-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:10:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-jefferson-current-policy-is-a-good-place-to-respond-to-economic-developments-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current moderately restrictive policy rate in a good place to respond to economic developments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Watching closely for signs in hard data of weaker activity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recent inflation data consistent with further progress toward 2% goal, but future path uncertainty due to tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs could lead to higher inflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Labor market still solid&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Q1 GDP data overstated deceleration in activity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whether tariffs create persistent inflation depends on implementation, response of supply chains and other factors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a remarkable unity in this thinking at the Fed.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
