<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>France April final manufacturing PMI 48.7 vs 48.2 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-487-vs-482-prelim-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:50:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-487-vs-482-prelim-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy April manufacturing PMI 49.3 vs 47.0 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-manufacturing-pmi-493-vs-470-expected-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:45:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-manufacturing-pmi-493-vs-470-expected-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 46.6&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Output nearly stabilises, having declined in the 12 months prior to April
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Softest contraction in new orders in over a year
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cost pressures cool further, but charge inflation intensifies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This appears to indicate stabilisation, despite US tariff policy. After declining almost continuously since April 2024,
production has now almost reached the 50 mark, signalling that production is roughly at the same level as in the previous
month. The turnaround also seems to be emerging in terms of new orders, where the decline is significantly milder than in
previous months. This aligns with the fact that inventories of pre-production goods were reduced only slightly.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Given the improved survey results, growth is once again within the realm of possibility. However, after the sector has been
in recession almost continuously since mid-2022, Italian industry will have to work its way out of a rather deep hole. There
will still be a number of obstacles along the way, chief among them the US tariff policy and the threat of intensified
competition from China, which will push even more products onto the European market than before.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Higher tariffs and uncertainty are weighing on Italian industry, which is reflected in the below-average optimism of
manufacturers. However, a more severe slump in sentiment could well have been expected. The fact that the PMI figures
signal stabilisation rather than a sharp deterioration may have something to do with the fact that industry is still benefiting
from some advance deals designed to circumvent higher tariffs. In addition, the defence industry is likely to see higher
demand for defence equipment, which should have a knock-on effect on the entire manufacturing sector.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland April manufacturing PMI 45.8 vs 48.6 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-manufacturing-pmi-458-vs-486-expected-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:30:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-manufacturing-pmi-458-vs-486-expected-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That&apos;s a fresh setback to the Swiss industry, with the reading seeing a steeper decline in activity compared to March. While output picked up a little, new orders slumped heavily and was a drag alongside a hit to employment conditions. The breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain April manufacturing PMI 48.1 vs 50.0 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-manufacturing-pmi-481-vs-500-expected-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:15:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-manufacturing-pmi-481-vs-500-expected-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 49.5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Steepest cut in new orders since December 2023
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Output down modestly for first time since last August
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confidence in outlook deteriorates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the PMI data, Jonas Feldhusen, Junior Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Operating conditions in Spain&apos;s Manufacturing Sector are deteriorating. The HCOB Manufacturing PMI stays in the
contraction zone for the third consecutive month and has even deteriorated compared to the previous month. This result is
underpinned by a decline in output, for the first time since August 2024, and a significant deterioration in order volumes.
Panellists report increased uncertainty and market instability, prompting customers to delay or cancel purchasing and
investment decisions. The instability of international markets is attributed to US tariff policies and the uncertainty that
accompanies it.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The decline in sentiment has not yet impacted employment levels. For four months, the employment index has signalled
little change. Given the poorer order situation and a reduction in backlogs, there is room for a deterioration in employment
levels in the coming months. Against this backdrop, business expectations of Spanish manufacturers also weakened in April.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Price dynamics in Spain&apos;s manufacturing sector have nearly come to a halt at the start of the second quarter. Input price
inflation has further weakened, as some vendors were forced to lower their prices due to weak demand. Pricing power for
customer prices was also limited, attributed to high competitive pressures and discounts to attract clients.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For the first time this year, all sub-sectors – consumer, intermediate, and investment goods – are in the contraction zone.
The decline in intermediate goods was the most pronounced. Production there was cut, orders collapsed, and consequently,
business expectations plummeted. The consumer goods sector also declined but performed relatively better. Despite
weaker operating conditions overall, employment growth in this sector continues.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan negotiators reportedly firmly opposed to US tariffs proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-negotiators-reportedly-firmly-opposed-to-us-tariffs-proposal-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:08:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-negotiators-reportedly-firmly-opposed-to-us-tariffs-proposal-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It is reported that the US proposal was a framework that included reluctance to lowering tariffs on autos, steel, and aluminum. This was what is being proposed by the US camp with it being centered on reciprocal tariffs. Considering said proposal, Japan negotiators are firmly opposed to it according to the media outlet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Adding that Japan is to take a stance that negotiations on reducing the US trade deficit will be difficult unless tariffs on autos, steel, and aluminum are on the negotiating table. No easy deals, huh? *wink* *wink*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Again, this was supposed to be one of the easier negotiations for the US administration to manage. But from the look of things, it seems far from it. And when you weigh the comments on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-min-akazawa-says-no-comment-on-specifics-of-tariff-negotiations-with-trump-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;how the talks yesterday went&lt;/a&gt;, it didn&apos;t feel like there was too much progress whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The two camps are now expected to meet again after mid-May, according to Akazawa. So, that just kicks the can down the road for at least another two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:20:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, we have the final Manufacturing PMIs for a few European economies and the Eurozone Flash CPI. The data won&apos;t change anything for the ECB so the market reaction will likely be limited. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, the focus will switch to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/april-non-farm-payrolls-preview-by-the-numbers-any-signs-of-layoffs-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US NFP&lt;/a&gt; report although I continue to think that the data doesn&apos;t matter now and the market is just waiting for the details of the first trade deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed like we could get some news on that front yesterday after &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/hassett-on-tariffs-im-sure-there-will-be-news-by-the-end-of-the-day-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Hassett&apos;s tease&lt;/a&gt;, but eventually nothing was announced and we continue to wait. As a reminder, they said that the first deal would have been announced this week of the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think everything hinges on the details of that first trade deal. The data is old news and unless we see a notable deterioration in the labour market, the central bank won&apos;t do anything. The US Jobless Claims have been stable and yesterday&apos;s data was skewed by one-off effects. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +1.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-11-in-early-european-trading-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:13:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-11-in-early-european-trading-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +1.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are up 0.6%, so that&apos;s feeding into a more positive mood going into European trading. For European stocks, it&apos;s also a catch up to the overnight gains after the Labor Day holiday yesterday. As things stand, trade headlines remain the main driver but there&apos;s also the US jobs report to be mindful of in the day ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 2 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-2-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:05:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-2-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As we look to close out the week, there isn&apos;t too much on the expiries list to take note of. There is perhaps arguably just one for USD/JPY at 146.00 but it doesn&apos;t tie to any technical significance. As such, I wouldn&apos;t expect the expiries to have much impact. The market at the moment is largely riding on trade developments and will look to the US jobs report later for some little anecdotes to work with. All that before the weekend comes along. 🎵&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The positive animal spirits stick towards the final stretch of the week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-positive-animal-spirits-stick-towards-the-final-stretch-of-the-week-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:32:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-positive-animal-spirits-stick-towards-the-final-stretch-of-the-week-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are up 0.7% on the day and that sets up the cash index to eye a potential ninth consecutive day of gains. It&apos;s been an impressive rebound in Wall Street to say the least, on what has been a lot talking the talk but nothing about walking the walk just yet. This time around, China is the one reportedly delivering some hopeful optimism &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Is that opening a slight gap in the door for Trump? We&apos;ll see. But for now, we&apos;re not at the point of picking up the phone just yet on either side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In any case, the S&amp;amp;P 500 now looks poised to recover the 61.8 Fib retracement of the fall since February as the rebound continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That is encouraging but there will be bigger technical hurdles to get through just above that. The 100 (red line) and 200-day (blue line) moving averages will present key challenges before thinking about retesting the highs near 6,000 to 6,100 again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides trade developments, we also had Amazon and Apple earnings come in. And while both delivered better than estimates, the latter does have a caveat. Greater China sales roughly met estimates with a $16.0 billion figure but that is down a little over 2% compared to a year ago. That is evident of a shift in spending mindset and perhaps the toll taken from the US-China trade rhetoric spilling over into consumer behaviour. If anything, we&apos;ll likely see this figure shrink the longer the trade war rages on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As for the day ahead, there will also be the US jobs report to look out for. Any thinking of layoffs in logistics and retail related to tariffs should be quickly dispelled here as it is still too early to see that show up in the data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It will still take a few months of hard data hitting hard before really leading to freight and trucking services to cut labour costs. But when it starts to hit, the cascading effect can be quick to catch on. So, just be wary of that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As such, the non-farm payrolls data today shouldn&apos;t be too much of a factor besides looking into the wider impact of DOGE layoffs. If you&apos;re looking for any impact from tariffs here, this isn&apos;t the time yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And that means trade headlines or should I say Trump headlines, will continue to take on more importance.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Off ramp emerging for tariffs? S&amp;P 500 futures jump</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-off-ramp-emerging-for-tariffs-sp-500-futures-jump-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-off-ramp-emerging-for-tariffs-sp-500-futures-jump-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rubio-says-ukraine-and-russia-positions-are-still-a-little-far-apart-20250502/&quot;&gt;Rubio says Ukraine and Russia positions are still a little far apart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/a-big-turn-around-for-us-equity-index-trade-higher-on-globex-on-china-comments-20250502/&quot;&gt;A big turn around for US equity index trade - higher on Globex on China comments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/&quot;&gt;China says the US has sought to begin trade talks, China says its thinking about it  ...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/its-not-just-gold-goldman-sachs-says-asian-currencies-to-benefit-from-usd-losing-status-20250502/&quot;&gt;Its not just gold - Goldman Sachs says Asian currencies to benefit from USD losing status&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-2025-non-farm-payrolls-data-the-critical-key-ranges-for-estimates-to-watch-20250502/&quot;&gt;US April 2025 non-farm payrolls data - the critical key ranges for estimates to watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-stance-of-requesting-us-cancel-tariffs-20250502/&quot;&gt;Japan PM Ishiba - no change to stance of requesting US cancel tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-retail-sales-03-mm-expected-04-20250502/&quot;&gt;Australian March retail sales +0.3% m/m (expected +0.4%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-election-this-weekend-heres-the-risk-for-the-australian-dollar-20250502/&quot;&gt;Australian election this weekend - here&apos;s the risk for the Australian dollar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-min-akazawa-says-no-comment-on-specifics-of-tariff-negotiations-with-trump-20250501/&quot;&gt;Japan eco min Akazawa says no comment on specifics of tariff negotiations with Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-eyes-rolling-back-immigration-protections-for-around-600000-venezuelan-immigrants-20250501/&quot;&gt;Trump eyes rolling back immigration protections for around 600,000 Venezuelan immigrants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-march-unemployment-rate-25-expected-24-prior-24-20250501/&quot;&gt;Japan March unemployment rate 2.5% (expected 2.4%, prior 2.4%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-april-cpi-comes-in-a-touch-higher-than-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;South Korea April CPI y/y comes in a touch higher than expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-march-building-permits-96-mm-prior-08-20250501/&quot;&gt;New Zealand March Building Permits +9.6% m/m (prior +0.8%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-vice-president-vance-russias-war-in-ukraine-is-not-going-to-end-any-time-soon-20250501/&quot;&gt;U.S. Vice President Vance: Russia’s war in Ukraine is not going to end any time soon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-for-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-20250501/&quot;&gt;&quot;Japan&apos;s US Treasury holdings among tools for trade talks, Finance Minister Kato says&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-fin-min-kato-said-had-no-discussion-at-all-with-us-of-where-yen-fx-level-should-be-20250501/&quot;&gt;Japan fin min Kato said had no discussion at all with US of where yen FX level should be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/4-reasons-the-usd-rally-will-falter-4-is-going-to-be-very-difficult-to-recover-from-20250501/&quot;&gt;4 reasons the USD rally will falter (#4 is going to be very difficult to recover from)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/apple-eps-165-versus-162-expected-revenues-9536-billion-versus-9453-billion-est-20250501/&quot;&gt;Apple EPS $1.65 versus $1.62 expected. Revenues $95.36 billion versus $94.53 billion est&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/apple-has-approved-a-new-us100bn-share-buyback-program-20250501/&quot;&gt;Apple has approved a new US$100bn share buyback program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/a-look-at-some-of-the-other-earnings-release-after-the-close-20250501/&quot;&gt;A look at some of the other earnings release after the close&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-usdjpy-soars-as-yields-turn-higher-20250501/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: USD/JPY soars as yields turn higher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/sp-closes-higher-for-the-eighth-consecutive-day-20250501/&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P closes higher for the eighth consecutive day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/amazon-revenues-1557b-vs-expectations-of-154889b-eps-159-versus-136-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;Amazon revenues $155.7B vs expectations of $154.889B. EPS $1.59 versus $1.36 expected.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-friday-2-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250501/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Friday, 2 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
Hopes
for a thaw in US-China trade tensions gained momentum Friday after
Beijing confirmed that Washington had recently conveyed, repeatedly, a desire to
start negotiations. “The US has recently sent messages to China
through relevant parties, hoping to start talks,” China’s
Commerce Ministry said, adding that “China is currently evaluating
this.” The ministry noted that the US has repeatedly expressed
interest in addressing tariff issues. Markets took the signals as a
tentative step toward dialogue, with oil prices and US equity index
futures moving higher on optimism that the world’s two largest
economies might be preparing to re-engage. In Washington, Senator
Marco Rubio echoed the sentiment, saying “the Chinese want to meet
and talk,” suggesting the ice may finally be starting to break.
Investors broadly interpreted the tone shift as a potentially
face-saving off-ramp for Trump, and a developing path forward for
China, particularly as economic cracks begin to emerge more visibly
in the recent data on both sides of the Pacific. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Still,
Beijing&apos;s tone was far from conciliatory. China’s Commerce Ministry
stressed that “if the US does not correct its unilateral tariff
measures, it has no sincerity at all” and that Washington must be
“prepared to take action in correcting erroneous practices,
including cancelling unilateral tariffs.” While China confirmed it
is open to dialogue, officials made clear that any talks would be
conditional on tangible US concessions. These statements, some
analysts argue, amount to Beijing effectively demanding a full
rollback of Trump-era tariffs as a precondition for serious
engagement — a stance that could complicate efforts to rekindle
negotiations. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Earlier
in the session, Japanese Finance Minister Katsunobu Kato made
headlines by suggesting that Japan’s substantial holdings of U.S.
Treasuries could be considered a potential bargaining chip in trade
negotiations with Washington — though he was quick to clarify that
there is no intention to deploy that option at this stage. Japan’s
lead negotiator on tariffs, Ryosei Akazawa, struck a more measured
tone, and notably indicating that the next round of talks may not take place
until after mid-May — a sign that a breakthrough is unlikely
anytime soon. Both officials confirmed that foreign exchange issues,
i.e. the yen, were not discussed. Later, Prime Minister Fumio
Ishiba reinforced Japan’s longstanding position, stating that
Tokyo, like Beijing, continues to urge the U.S. to remove its tariff
measures. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Australia
heads to the polls on Saturday, May 3, with Prime Minister Anthony
Albanese still favoured to retain government — though polling
remains tight, and the prospect of a minority government cannot be
ruled out. On the economic front, March retail sales data released today showed a modest
improvement from February but fell short of expectations, while Q1
retail sales were flat overall — a notably weak result. Meanwhile,
producer price inflation (PPI) for the quarter came in above headline
CPI, highlighting lingering cost pressures. However, none of the data
releases shifted market expectations for a 25 basis point rate cut
from the Reserve Bank of Australia when it meets on May 19–20.. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;As mentioned, oil
and equities were broadly underpinned amid easing US-China tensions,
while major currency pairs saw mixed performance. USD/JPY briefly
spiked toward 145.80 but later retraced, ending the session little
changed. Elsewhere, the US dollar weakened against most G10 peers,
with the AUD, GBP, NZD, and CAD all posting gains. EUR/USD was a
relative laggard, advancing more modestly compared to the broader
move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a gap lower to open Globex evening trade ES soared on the China news. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The above is a CFD that tracks ES. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Its not just gold - Goldman Sachs says Asian currencies to benefit from USD losing status</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/its-not-just-gold-goldman-sachs-says-asian-currencies-to-benefit-from-usd-losing-status-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/its-not-just-gold-goldman-sachs-says-asian-currencies-to-benefit-from-usd-losing-status-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;116&quot; data-end=&quot;415&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Central banks are accelerating their shift away from the US dollar, a move that has gained traction over the past decade and shows no sign of slowing. “We believe the diversification away from dollar should persist, as this trend has been well entrenched for the past decade,” the Goldman Sachs strategists wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The momentum intensified following the 2022 sanctions on Russia, when Washington froze Moscow’s dollar reserves and cut it off from the global financial system. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Those events rattled confidence in the greenback’s reliability, and concerns have only deepened amid Trump’s policies, which threaten to disrupt global trade and economic stability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; In response, central banks have also been building up gold holdings, supporting demand for the precious metal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;889&quot; data-end=&quot;1241&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Still, the dollar retains its roleas the primary reserve currency and the standard for pricing key commodities like oil&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;much of that status stems from the vast liquidity of the US Treasury market, which allows investors to transact large volumes without moving prices—an advantage no other market currently offers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;there are signs of erosion - Bloomberg’s dollar gauge has fallen more than 7% since peaking in February, as the narrative of US exceptionalism loses steam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1508&quot; data-end=&quot;1750&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;According to the strategists, the dollar is still about 17% overvalued based on Goldman’s valuation models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“We anticipate a rotation to other global assets, of which Asian assets could be a subset” &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;South Korea, Singapore and China&apos;s currencies are likely to be the biggest Asian beneficiaries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summary of a Bloomberg piece citing GS. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April 2025 non-farm payrolls data - the critical key ranges for estimates to watch</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-2025-non-farm-payrolls-data-the-critical-key-ranges-for-estimates-to-watch-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-2025-non-farm-payrolls-data-the-critical-key-ranges-for-estimates-to-watch-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The January 2025 employment report is due from the US on Friday, May 2, 2025, at 0830 US Eastern time, 1330 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;You can see the consensus estimate in the screenshot below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;The number in the right-most column is the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month) result.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look at the range of expectations compared to the median consensus (the &apos;expected&apos; in the screenshot above) for the key data points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Headline NFP number:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;25,000 to 195,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unemployment rate:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;4.1% to 4.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average hourly earnings m/m:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.2% to 0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average hourly earnings y/y:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;2.8% to 3.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is knowledge of such ranges important?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data results that fall outside of market low and high expectations tend to move markets more significantly for several reasons:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Surprise Factor: Markets often price in expectations based on forecasts and previous trends. When data significantly deviates from these expectations, it creates a surprise effect. This can lead to rapid revaluation of assets as investors and traders reassess their positions based on the new information.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Psychological Impact: Investors and traders are influenced by psychological factors. Extreme data points can evoke strong emotional reactions, leading to overreactions in the market. This can amplify market movements, especially in the short term.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Risk Reassessment: Unexpected data can lead to a reassessment of risk. If data significantly underperforms or outperforms expectations, it can change the perceived risk of certain investments. For instance, better-than-expected economic data may reduce the perceived risk of investing in equities, leading to a market rally.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Triggering of Automated Trading: In today’s markets, a significant portion of trading is done by algorithms. These automated systems often have pre-set conditions or thresholds that, when triggered by unexpected data, can lead to large-scale buying or selling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Impact on Monetary and Fiscal Policies: Data that is significantly off from expectations can influence the policies of central banks and governments. For example, in the case of the NFP due today, a weaker jobs report will fuel speculation of sooner Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) rate cuts to come. A stronger report will diminish such expectations, with the Fed on hold for longer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Liquidity and Market Depth: In some cases, extreme data points can affect market liquidity. If the data is unexpected enough, it might lead to a temporary imbalance in buyers and sellers, causing larger market moves until a new equilibrium is found.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chain Reactions and Correlations: Financial markets are interconnected. A significant move in one market or asset class due to unexpected data can lead to correlated moves in other markets, amplifying the overall market impact.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan PM Ishiba - no change to stance of requesting US cancel tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-stance-of-requesting-us-cancel-tariffs-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:07:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-stance-of-requesting-us-cancel-tariffs-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan Prime Minister Ishiba&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No change at all to our stance of requesting U.S. to cancel tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not in situation where we have found common ground yet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;But received report from Akazawa that talks were forward-looking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reaching a deal in haste is not necessarily in the best interest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier from Japan on tariffs:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-min-akazawa-says-no-comment-on-specifics-of-tariff-negotiations-with-trump-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan eco min Akazawa says no comment on specifics of tariff negotiations with Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-for-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&quot;Japan&apos;s US Treasury holdings among tools for trade talks, Finance Minister Kato says&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian March retail sales +0.3% m/m (expected +0.4%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-retail-sales-03-mm-expected-04-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-retail-sales-03-mm-expected-04-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Australian March retail sales &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;+0.3% m/m, improved from February but not by as much as was expect&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;expected +0.4%, prior +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.0% q.q in Q1 2025, no change during the quarter is a very soft reading&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior +1.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data also for PPI, Q1 2025:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;+0.9% q/q&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior +0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;+3.7% y/y&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior +3.7% also&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;PPI outrunning CPI. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD rose earlier on the China news:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China says the US has sought to begin trade talks, China says its thinking about it  ...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/a-big-turn-around-for-us-equity-index-trade-higher-on-globex-on-china-comments-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;A big turn around for US equity index trade - higher on Globex on China comments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *MARCO RUBIO SAYS CHINA IS REACHING OUT ON ECONOMIC ISSUES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918112909520933046#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:18:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918112909520933046#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*MARCO RUBIO SAYS CHINA IS REACHING OUT ON ECONOMIC ISSUES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO: THOSE TALKS WILL COME UP SOON</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918111949847748987#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918111949847748987#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO: THOSE TALKS WILL COME UP SOON&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918111652421013620#m&quot;&gt;localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918111652421013620#m&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO: CHINESE WANT TO MEET AND TALK</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918111652421013620#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:13:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918111652421013620#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO: CHINESE WANT TO MEET AND TALK&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubio says Ukraine and Russia positions are still a little far apart</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rubio-says-ukraine-and-russia-positions-are-still-a-little-far-apart-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:07:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rubio-says-ukraine-and-russia-positions-are-still-a-little-far-apart-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Rubio is US Secretary of State and will soon also be US National Security Adviser after incumbent Waltz was fired. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;says Ukraine and Russia positions are still a little far apart&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; it&apos;s going to take a breakthrough soon on Ukraine to make this possible&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump have to decide how much time to dedicate to this&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Separately:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chinese want to meet and talk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Those talks will come up soon&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There’s a broader question about how much we should buy from China going forward&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Best opportunity for Iran&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Iran should not be afraid of inspectors including Americans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is along the lines of what we heard earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-vice-president-vance-russias-war-in-ukraine-is-not-going-to-end-any-time-soon-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;U.S. Vice President Vance: Russia’s war in Ukraine is not going to end any time soon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA SAYS CURRENTLY EVALUATING POSSIBLE US TRADE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918109237453980062#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918109237453980062#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA SAYS CURRENTLY EVALUATING POSSIBLE US TRADE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A big turn around for US equity index trade - higher on Globex on China comments</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/a-big-turn-around-for-us-equity-index-trade-higher-on-globex-on-china-comments-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:50:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/a-big-turn-around-for-us-equity-index-trade-higher-on-globex-on-china-comments-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Comments from  China’s Commerce Ministry began with MofCom being couy:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“The
US has recently sent messages to China through relevant parties,
hoping to start talks with China,” &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; “China
is currently evaluating this.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;But turned confronting very quickly after:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In any possible dialogue, meeting, if US does not correct its ‘unilateral’ tariff measures, US has no sincerity at all&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US should show sincerity if it wants to talk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US should be prepared to take action in correcting ‘erroneous’ practices, cancelling unilateral tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are more here:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China says the US has sought to begin trade talks, China says its thinking about it  ...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regardless, futures have leapt higher:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While not dismissing the impact of shorts scrambling, these comments show at least some progress. China has gone from saying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;No, we haven&apos;t had any discussions at all&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;Maybe we&apos;ll think about it&quot;. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Progress of a kind. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says the US has sought to begin trade talks, China says its thinking about it  ...</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:29:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bloomberg have the info on China considering trade talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China Commerce Ministry says the US has taken the initiative to convey to China that the US is hoping to talk on trade&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China said to be conducting assessment on US trade negotiations &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Also wants the US to correct its tariff mistakes, says the US unilaterally initiated the tariff trade war&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China is urging the US to demonstrate sincerity if it wants trade talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China is evaluating possible US trade talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China says the door is open to trade talks with the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;China obviously acting coy, but at least this is some sign of tentative progress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or, perhaps not ..... more:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In any possible dialogue, meeting, if US does not correct its ‘unilateral’ tariff measures, US has no sincerity at all&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US should show sincerity if it wants to talk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US should be prepared to take action in correcting ‘erroneous’ practices, cancelling unilateral tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian election this weekend - here&apos;s the risk for the Australian dollar</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-election-this-weekend-heres-the-risk-for-the-australian-dollar-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 00:06:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-election-this-weekend-heres-the-risk-for-the-australian-dollar-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Ahead of last Monday&apos;s Canadian election Adam posted on the risk for CAD -  minority government:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/there-is-one-canadian-election-outcome-that-could-hurt-the-loonie-20250428/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;There is one Canadian election outcome that could hurt the loonie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is also a risk for this weekend&apos;s election in Australia. Polling is currently favouring the incumbent Prime Minister Albanese, but its very close. The very real risk is Albanese wins but only in minority, just like Carney this week. He will then form government with the support of Greens and/or independents and that always risks a more open wallet and a hit to fiscal irresponsibility, what little there is. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other near term risk is we won&apos;t get a clear result for many days after the election. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These could provide a setback for AUD, apart from the trade storms currently underway hitting Australia&apos;s major trading partner, China. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PM Albanese and opposition leader Dutton&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan eco min Akazawa says no comment on specifics of tariff negotiations with Trump</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-min-akazawa-says-no-comment-on-specifics-of-tariff-negotiations-with-trump-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:45:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-min-akazawa-says-no-comment-on-specifics-of-tariff-negotiations-with-trump-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan economy minister Akazawa said that FX was not discussed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Negotiation lasted for 130 minutes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Able to have thorough discussions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Again requested review of tariffs on Japan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No comment on specific negotiations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Talked how Japan can expand trade, non-tariff measures, economic security with US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Told US that tariff measures regrettable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did not discuss forex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Want to hold next meeting after mid-May&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No discussions on national security&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Asked us to review tariff measures on auto parts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Negotiation handled as a package&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;National security matters different from tariff talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did not talk about China during talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Already decided forex matters to be discussed between finance ministers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand that US wanting to reach some kind of agreements within 90-day window with various countries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I bolded that timing comment above. This is not indicative of a quick resolution to trade talks as Trump would have us believe. Not that anyone does anyway. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier from Japan:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-for-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&quot;Japan&apos;s US Treasury holdings among tools for trade talks, Finance Minister Kato says&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump eyes rolling back immigration protections for around 600,000 Venezuelan immigrants</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-eyes-rolling-back-immigration-protections-for-around-600000-venezuelan-immigrants-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:39:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-eyes-rolling-back-immigration-protections-for-around-600000-venezuelan-immigrants-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.politico.com/news/2025/05/01/trump-supreme-court-venezuela-tps-00322638&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Politico &lt;/a&gt;with the report that might have an impact on the US labour market in the weeks and months to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump&apos;s admin asked the US Supreme Court to allow rolling back immigration protections for about 600,000 Venezuelans living in the U.S.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;the latest of about a dozen expedited requests the Trump administration has brought to the high court in the past three months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;asks to lift a court order blocking Trump’s plan to curtail or end so-called temporary protected status, or TPS, for Venezuelan nationals. People who are granted TPS get protection from deportation and are issued work permits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advocates for the Venezuelan TPS recipients will have until May 8 to file a response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More at that link to the report above. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan March unemployment rate 2.5% (expected 2.4%, prior 2.4%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-march-unemployment-rate-25-expected-24-prior-24-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:30:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-march-unemployment-rate-25-expected-24-prior-24-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan March unemployment rate 2.5% &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;expected 2.4%, prior 2.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jobs to applicant ratio 1.26&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;expected 1.25, prior 1.24&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the big news  from Japan today, IMO:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-for-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&quot;Japan&apos;s US Treasury holdings among tools for trade talks, Finance Minister Kato says&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;99 problems but a job ain&apos;t one in Japan!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea April CPI y/y comes in a touch higher than expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-april-cpi-comes-in-a-touch-higher-than-expected-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 23:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-april-cpi-comes-in-a-touch-higher-than-expected-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;South Korea April CPI &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Korea April consumer price index +2.1% y/y (Reuters poll +2.0%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; +0.1% m/m is better, the slowest since November 2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core CPI +2.1% y/y vs +1.9% in March &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Copy&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand March Building Permits +9.6% m/m (prior +0.8%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-march-building-permits-96-mm-prior-08-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:48:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-march-building-permits-96-mm-prior-08-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;New Zealand March 2025 Building Permits +9.6% m/m&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;+0.8% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;and +15.9% y/y&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Vice President Vance: Russia’s war in Ukraine is not going to end any time soon</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-vice-president-vance-russias-war-in-ukraine-is-not-going-to-end-any-time-soon-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:29:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-vice-president-vance-russias-war-in-ukraine-is-not-going-to-end-any-time-soon-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;U.S. Vice President Vance: Russia’s war in Ukraine is not going to end any time soon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;up to the Russians and Ukrainians now
that each side knows what the other&apos;s terms for peace are&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;its going to be up to them to come to an agreement and stop this
brutal, brutal conflict &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;Its not going anywhere, Bret. It&apos;s not going to end any
time soon,&quot; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vance&apos;s comments came during a Fox News interview.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dialling back geopolitical tension such as ending this war, was a promise Vance and his boss made, it was always a stretch. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE: RUSSIA&apos;S WAR IN UKRAINE IS NOT GOING TO END ANY TIME SOON</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918069657187315990#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:26:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918069657187315990#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE: RUSSIA&apos;S WAR IN UKRAINE IS NOT GOING TO END ANY TIME SOON&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;Japan&apos;s US Treasury holdings among tools for trade talks, Finance Minister Kato says&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-for-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:25:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-for-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;That headline is via Reuters, recapping the bombshell remark from Kato &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-fin-min-kato-said-had-no-discussion-at-all-with-us-of-where-yen-fx-level-should-be-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;earlier&lt;/a&gt;.  Kato made the comments while appearing on a television program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;172&quot; data-end=&quot;423&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Kato is Japan’s Finance Minister. He said the country’s massive holdings of U.S. Treasuries could serve as a potential bargaining tool in trade negotiations with Washington — though he emphasized there’s no commitment to actually using that option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;noted that while Japan&apos;s main reason for holding such large reserves is to maintain sufficient liquidity for possible yen intervention, &quot;we obviously need to put all cards on the table in negotiations. It could be among such cards.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; he was quick to add a caveat: &quot;Whether we actually use that card, however, is a different question.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;817&quot; data-end=&quot;991&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Japan holds around $1.27 trillion in foreign reserves, most of which analysts believe is in U.S. Treasury debt, though the government doesn’t publicly detail the composition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;817&quot; data-end=&quot;991&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Threatening to offload some is a big step. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE: INDIA COULD BE AMONG ONE OF THE FIRST TRADE DEALS -FOX NEWS INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918067009981423984#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:16:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918067009981423984#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE: INDIA COULD BE AMONG ONE OF THE FIRST TRADE DEALS -FOX NEWS INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. VICE PRESIDENT JD VANCE SAYS WALTZ JOB CHANGE NOT THE RESULT OF SIGNAL CHAT LEAK</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918066942767702499#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918066942767702499#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. VICE PRESIDENT JD VANCE SAYS WALTZ JOB CHANGE NOT THE RESULT OF SIGNAL CHAT LEAK&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) APPLE IS &apos;VERY ENGAGED&apos; ON TARIFF DICUSSIONS - APPLE CEO TIM COOK ON CONF CALL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918056508694188374#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:34:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918056508694188374#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;APPLE IS &apos;VERY ENGAGED&apos; ON TARIFF DICUSSIONS - APPLE CEO TIM COOK ON CONF CALL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE ESTIMATES $900 MILLION IN COST INCREASES ON TARIFFS IN Q3</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918055965867332069#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918055965867332069#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE ESTIMATES $900 MILLION IN COST INCREASES ON TARIFFS IN Q3&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE: BOARD AUTHORIZED BUYBACK UP TO $100B OF COMPANY’S STOCK</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918040704015598076#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:31:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918040704015598076#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE: BOARD AUTHORIZED BUYBACK UP TO $100B OF COMPANY’S STOCK&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE 2Q IPHONE REVENUE $46.84B, EST. $45.94B</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918040638198530420#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:31:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918040638198530420#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE 2Q IPHONE REVENUE $46.84B, EST. $45.94B&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE 2Q EPS $1.65, EST. $1.62
*APPLE 2Q REV. $95.36B, EST. $94.59B
*APPLE 2Q GREATER CHINA REV. $16.00B, EST. $16.83B

$AAPL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918040470069923864#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918040470069923864#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE 2Q EPS $1.65, EST. $1.62&lt;br&gt;
*APPLE 2Q REV. $95.36B, EST. $94.59B&lt;br&gt;
*APPLE 2Q GREATER CHINA REV. $16.00B, EST. $16.83B&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AAPL&quot;&gt;$AAPL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) STRATEGY TO OFFER UP TO $21B IN CLASS A STOCK VIA ATM SALES AGREEMENT: FILING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918039722393325707#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:27:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918039722393325707#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;STRATEGY TO OFFER UP TO $21B IN CLASS A STOCK VIA ATM SALES AGREEMENT: FILING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *AMAZON SEES 2Q NET SALES $159.0B TO $164.0B, EST. $161.42B

*AMAZON SEES 2Q OPER INCOME $13.0B TO $17.5B, EST. $17.82B</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918033318462816387#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918033318462816387#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*AMAZON SEES 2Q NET SALES $159.0B TO $164.0B, EST. $161.42B&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*AMAZON SEES 2Q OPER INCOME $13.0B TO $17.5B, EST. $17.82B&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *AMAZON Q1 EPS USD 1.59 VS. IBES ESTIMATE USD 1.36
*AMAZON Q1 OPERATING INCOME USD 18,400 MILLION VS. IBES ESTIMATE USD 17,482 MILLION

$AMZN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918033146706026500#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918033146706026500#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*AMAZON Q1 EPS USD 1.59 VS. IBES ESTIMATE USD 1.36&lt;br&gt;
*AMAZON Q1 OPERATING INCOME USD 18,400 MILLION VS. IBES ESTIMATE USD 17,482 MILLION&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AMZN&quot;&gt;$AMZN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) S&amp;P 500 FINISHES HIGHER FOR 8TH STRAIGHT SESSION; LONGEST DAILY WINNING STREAK SINCE AUGUST</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918032859367186571#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:00:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918032859367186571#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 FINISHES HIGHER FOR 8TH STRAIGHT SESSION; LONGEST DAILY WINNING STREAK SINCE AUGUST&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EUROPE READY TO MAKE TRUMP A €50BN OFFER, SAYS EU NEGOTIATOR - FT

 MAROŠ ŠEFČOVIČ, EU’S TRADE COMMISSIONER: BLOC WOULD NOT ACCEPT WASHINGTON KEEPING 10% TARIFFS ON ITS GOODS AS A FAIR RESOLUTION TO TRADE TALKS - FT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918015717754191891#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:52:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918015717754191891#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EUROPE READY TO MAKE TRUMP A €50BN OFFER, SAYS EU NEGOTIATOR - FT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
 MAROŠ ŠEFČOVIČ, EU’S TRADE COMMISSIONER: BLOC WOULD NOT ACCEPT WASHINGTON KEEPING 10% TARIFFS ON ITS GOODS AS A FAIR RESOLUTION TO TRADE TALKS - FT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: ANY COUNTRY BUYING OIL FROM IRAN WILL FACE SANCTIONS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918007954181120327#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:21:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918007954181120327#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: ANY COUNTRY BUYING OIL FROM IRAN WILL FACE SANCTIONS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP PICKS RUBIO FOR INTERIM NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918007399912263861#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:19:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918007399912263861#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP PICKS RUBIO FOR INTERIM NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS WALTZ WILL BE NEXT AMBASSADOR TO U.N</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918007219812974618#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:18:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918007219812974618#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS WALTZ WILL BE NEXT AMBASSADOR TO U.N&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
