<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Japan PM Ishiba: US auto tariffs are &apos;absolutely unacceptable&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-us-auto-tariffs-are-absolutely-unacceptable-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:32:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-us-auto-tariffs-are-absolutely-unacceptable-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US auto tariffs are &apos;absolutely unacceptable&apos;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese are drawing some red lines here on auto tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had similar news earlier in the morning:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article__title&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-negotiators-reportedly-firmly-opposed-to-us-tariffs-proposal-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Japan negotiators reportedly firmly opposed to US tariffs proposal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article__title&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-kato-well-continue-to-ask-us-to-reconsider-tariffs-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Japan&apos;s Kato: We&apos;ll continue to ask US to reconsider tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 JAPAN PM ISHIBA SAYS U.S. AUTO TARIFFS ARE &apos;ABSOLUTELY UNACCEPTABLE&apos; IN FNN INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918251880158740894#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 10:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918251880158740894#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 JAPAN PM ISHIBA SAYS U.S. AUTO TARIFFS ARE &apos;ABSOLUTELY UNACCEPTABLE&apos; IN FNN INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the distribution of forecasts for the US NFP?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-is-the-distribution-of-forecasts-for-the-us-nfp-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:59:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-is-the-distribution-of-forecasts-for-the-us-nfp-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Why it&apos;s important?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ranges of estimates are 
important in terms of market reaction because when the actual data deviates from the 
expectations, it creates a surprise effect. Another
 important input in market&apos;s reaction is the distribution of forecasts. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, although we can have a range of 
estimates, most forecasts might be clustered on the upper bound of the 
range, so even if the data comes out inside the range of estimates but 
on the lower bound of the range, it can still create a surprise effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-Farm Payrolls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;25K-195K range of estimates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;120K-160K range most clustered&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;130K consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unemployment Rate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;4.3% (9%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;4.2% (79%) - consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;4.1% (12%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average Hourly Earnings Y/Y&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;3.9% (70%) - consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3.8% (27%) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.8% (3%) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average Hourly Earnings M/M&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.4% (2%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.3% (80%) - consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.2% (18%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average Weekly Hours &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;34.2 (79%) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;34.1 (18%) - consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;34.0 (3%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I&apos;ve been saying from April 2, I don&apos;t think the data matters now as the focus remains on trade negotiations. The same way the data was influenced by the uncertainty about tariffs and then the fear of recession following the April 2 announcement, it will also be influenced by the first trade deals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, say we get positive outcomes on the trade deals, the market will start to price in an improvement in the economy and even though the data might still show weakness in the first months, the market will likely just fade the negative reaction and keep going up on positive future expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the only outcome in the data that would trigger a market reaction is a notable weakening in the labour market as it would give the Fed a reason to cut rates. The US jobless claims, which is the most timely labour market data, continues to show a stable environment despite some volatility in the data caused by one-off factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, you get less hiring given the economic uncertainty, but we haven&apos;t seen layoffs picking up yet. It&apos;s just a frozen labour market as businesses await more info on the tariffs front. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSFT Stock After Earnings</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/msft-stock-after-earnings-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:37:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/msft-stock-after-earnings-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Microsoft’s AI Leap: Why Investors Should Pay Attention&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft&apos;s recent earnings report has turned heads in the investing community, as shares surged dramatically by 7.63% yesterday, breaking decisively above the significant psychological threshold of $400 and currently trading around $425 in pre-market. But what specifically is fueling this bullish response, and what does it mean for investors?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the heart of Microsoft&apos;s impressive earnings momentum lies a focused and strategic bet on artificial intelligence (AI), particularly through its Azure cloud platform. Microsoft&apos;s substantial investments in AI have shown clear and tangible returns, especially through its integration with OpenAI’s GPT technology. This integration has positioned Azure as a formidable competitor in the rapidly growing AI and cloud computing markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors have reason to be optimistic about Microsoft&apos;s AI strategy due to several key factors:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immediate Revenue Impact: Microsoft&apos;s aggressive move into AI has directly boosted its cloud revenue. Azure’s AI-driven services have attracted significant enterprise clients, bolstering recurring revenue streams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Competitive Advantage: By integrating AI deeply into its products, Microsoft creates stronger value propositions, boosting customer retention and increasing pricing power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scalable Growth: AI investments tend to scale effectively once infrastructure costs are absorbed, suggesting potential margin expansions and sustainable earnings growth in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learning from an Example:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider Microsoft&apos;s recent implementation of AI-powered features in its Office 365 productivity suite, particularly &quot;Copilot.&quot; Initial customer responses indicate a willingness to pay premium prices for enhanced productivity features, reflecting the immediate financial upside of strategic AI integration. This is a tangible demonstration of how Microsoft&apos;s AI focus translates directly into higher revenue and profitability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors should closely monitor Microsoft&apos;s stock performance over the next several quarters. Sustaining prices comfortably above the $400 level will validate continued investor confidence and signal that Microsoft&apos;s AI strategy is robust and well-executed. Conversely, a sharp reversal below this threshold would warrant caution and reevaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, Microsoft&apos;s AI-driven earnings leap is not just impressive—it&apos;s instructive. It offers traders and investors a clear case study of how targeted AI investments can rapidly translate into shareholder value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This article is intended for market commentary purposes only and does not constitute financial advice. Investors should always perform independent research and make investment decisions at their own risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For additional insights and ongoing market analysis, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt;, which will soon become &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investinglive.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;investingLive.com&lt;/a&gt;, offering enhanced coverage of stocks, commodities, and investing insights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join our free InvestingLive Stocks Telegram channel, where we regularly share actionable trade ideas and long-term investment insights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/investinglivestocks&quot;&gt;InvestingLive Stocks Telegram Channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earnings Reports of Big Tech: CapEx Surge in AI</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/earnings-reports-of-big-tech-capex-surge-in-ai-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:29:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/earnings-reports-of-big-tech-capex-surge-in-ai-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;CapEx Surge in AI: Smart Investment or Investor Trap?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest earnings reports from tech giants Microsoft, Meta, Apple, and Amazon spotlight a substantial rise in capital expenditures (CapEx), primarily driven by significant investments in artificial intelligence infrastructure. But traders and investors alike are now grappling with a key question: Will this massive spending spree pay off, or is it potentially trapping investors in a costly, overextended bet?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft&apos;s recent earnings report was particularly impressive, with the stock surging 7.63% yesterday and maintaining strength in pre-market trading today. Microsoft shares decisively broke above the critical psychological level of $400, currently trading around $425, underscoring investor confidence in its AI strategy, particularly Azure’s deep integration with OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, Meta&apos;s earnings report showed robust results, with shares jumping about 4.25% yesterday and adding an additional 0.9% in pre-market today, indicating sustained investor enthusiasm. Meta&apos;s results suggest strong momentum driven by AI-enhanced user engagement and significantly improved margins, pointing to AI expenditures translating into immediate and tangible benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, Apple has seen more cautious investor reactions. Despite reporting solid revenue growth of 5% and service revenue up 12%, Apple shares dropped approximately 3% in pre-market trading today, primarily due to uncertainty surrounding future quarters and tariff implications cited by CEO Tim Cook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon is also facing investor scrutiny despite continued investments in AI, with shares currently down around 2.5% pre-market. Amazon’s AWS unit is under particular pressure, raising questions about profitability despite the ongoing surge in AI-related CapEx.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mixed reactions to earnings reports highlight the broader uncertainty about whether substantial AI-related CapEx will yield long-term returns:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft &amp;amp; Meta: Clearly leading in translating AI investments into immediate growth and margin expansion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple &amp;amp; Amazon: Exhibiting caution and facing market skepticism amid slower returns and macroeconomic challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors should closely monitor upcoming quarters to validate whether these extensive CapEx investments in AI infrastructure lead to sustainable earnings growth or instead create substantial cost burdens, especially if macroeconomic conditions worsen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, traders should rely on price action as their primary indicator—no matter how compelling an earnings report or optimistic a corporate forecast appears. Sustained share-price strength or weakness over the coming weeks will deliver the market’s final verdict on these ambitious AI expenditures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This article provides market commentary and is not financial advice. Investors should perform their own research and make investment decisions at their own risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For additional analysis and real-time market insights, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt;, later this year evolving into &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investinglive.com&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;investingLive.com&lt;/a&gt;, offering expanded coverage of stocks, commodities, and investing insights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join our free InvestingLive Stocks Telegram channel, where we regularly share compelling trade ideas and long-term investment insights for stocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/investinglivestocks&quot;&gt;InvestingLive Stocks Telegram Channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan&apos;s Kato: We&apos;ll continue to ask US to reconsider tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-kato-well-continue-to-ask-us-to-reconsider-tariffs-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:11:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-kato-well-continue-to-ask-us-to-reconsider-tariffs-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We&apos;ll continue to ask US to reconsider tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tokyo ready to respond to Chinese import surge.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tokyo&apos;s principle is FX rates should be determined by the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Plaza accord 2.0 hasn&apos;t come up for discussion with the US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Katsunobu Kato is Japan&apos;s Finance Minister. There&apos;s nothing new here as the Japanese continue to push for a rollback of the reciprocal tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just earlier we got the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-negotiators-reportedly-firmly-opposed-to-us-tariffs-proposal-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;news&lt;/a&gt; that the Japanese negotiators firmly opposed the US tariffs proposal as it included reluctance to lowering tariffs on autos, steel, and aluminum. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone March unemployment rate 6.2% vs 6.1% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-march-unemployment-rate-62-vs-61-expected-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:00:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-march-unemployment-rate-62-vs-61-expected-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 6.1%; revised to 6.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone April preliminary CPI +2.2% vs +2.1% y/y expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-preliminary-cpi-22-vs-21-yy-expected-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-preliminary-cpi-22-vs-21-yy-expected-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI +2.7% vs +2.5% y/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The core reading is the standout here and that will add some challenge for the ECB in trying to communicate a rate cut for next month. Traders are pricing in ~86% odds of that currently, largely due to a softening economic backdrop. But with core inflation still yet to actually move towards the brink of 2%, the ECB might find it tough to oversell their narrative at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&apos;Buy Gold, Ask Questions Later&apos;. Octa Broker Comments on Trump&apos;s First 100 Days in Office</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/buy-gold-ask-questions-later-octa-broker-comments-on-trumps-first-100-days-in-office-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:29:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/buy-gold-ask-questions-later-octa-broker-comments-on-trumps-first-100-days-in-office-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Donald Trump&apos;s rise to the U.S. presidency was marked by a series
of bold and unconventional policy proposals that many pundits deemed radical at
the time. Given the length of the campaign and the public nature of his
platform, one would think that the market had plenty of time to prepare and
price in the potential policy shifts well in advance. However, it turned out
that investors were caught off guard by the extent of the upheaval that ensued.
Indeed, the first 100 days of Donald Trump&apos;s presidency were characterised by
extreme volatility and uncertainty for the global financial markets. In this
article, Octa broker reviews Trump&apos;s policies and analyses their consequences
for the global financial markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Introduction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump assumed office on 20 January 2025, and market
volatility has been rising ever since. Some of Trump&apos;s initiatives,
particularly his aggressive trade policies, have sent shockwaves through
equities, currencies, and commodities, leaving retail forex traders scrambling
to adjust. Meanwhile, larger investors struggled to adapt to the rapid pace of
proposed reforms and their far-reaching consequences. Overall, the first 100
days of President Trump saw heightened risk aversion and widespread uncertainty,
which resulted in sharp fluctuations in asset prices and currency exchange
rates as traders reacted to every policy announcement, tweet, and speech from
President Trump and his new administration.Below is a list of just a few of the notable days that shook the markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major market-moving events&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●20 January. The U.S. Dollar Index (DXY)
dropped by more than 1.20% after news surfaced that the new administration will
not immediately impose trade tariffs, prompting a rally in the currencies of
some U.S. trading partners: notably, the Mexican peso (MXN), the Euro (EUR) and
the Canadian dollar (CAD). It should be noted that prior to the sharp decline,
the greenback had been rising almost uninterruptedly since September 2024,
almost reaching a three-year high ahead of Trump&apos;s inauguration as the market
assumed that higher tariffs would spur inflation, prompting the Federal Reserve
(Fed) to pursue a more hawkish monetary policy. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●1–3 February. In the future, historians may
label 1 February as the official start of a global trade war. On this day,
Donald Trump imposed a 25% tariff on imports from Canada and Mexico, along with
an additional 10% tariff on China. The market&apos;s reaction was highly negative.
U.S. stock futures slumped in early Asian trading on Monday, 3 February, with
Nasdaq futures down 2.35% and S&amp;amp;P 500 futures 1.8% lower. U.S. oil prices
jumped more than $2, while gasoline futures jumped more than 3%. Meanwhile, the
Canadian dollar and Mexican peso weakened substantially, with USDCAD surging
past the 1.47900 mark, a 22-year high, and USDMXN touching a 3-year high as
economists warned that both countries were at risk of recession once the
tariffs kick in. Later that day, Trump agreed to delay 25% tariffs on Canada
and Mexico for a month after both countries agreed to take tougher measures to
combat migration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●3–5 March. This is when the market began to
seriously worry about the health of the global economy and a risk-off sentiment
became evident. As fresh 25% tariffs on most imports from Mexico and Canada,
along with the 20% tariffs on Chinese goods, were scheduled to take effect on 4
March, investors started to sell-off the greenback and flock into gold (XAUUSD)
as well as into alternative safe-haven currencies, such as the Swiss franc
(CHF) and the Japanese yen (JPY). In just three trading sessions (from 3–5
March), DXY plunged by more than 3% while the gold price gained more than 2%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●6 March. Donald
Trump signed an executive order establishing a U.S. cryptocurrency reserve.
However, it was unclear how exactly this reserve would work and just how much
it would differ from Bitcoin holdings already in place. Many crypto enthusiasts
were disappointed, which triggered a five-day downturn in BTCUSD, culminating
in Bitcoin briefly dipping below the crucial $80,000 level on 10 March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●2 April. The trade war entered the next
stage when Trump unveiled his long-promised &apos;reciprocal&apos; tariffs strategy,
essentially imposing import duties on more than a hundred countries. The market
route began with equity markets losing billions of dollars in valuation.
S&amp;amp;P 500 lost more than 11% in just two days, while DXY dropped to a fresh
six-month low. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●9–11 April. Trade war drama continued to
unfold. Financial markets were stunned by President Trump&apos;s abrupt reversal on
tariffs. Duties on trading partners, which had taken effect less than 24 hours
prior, were largely rolled back as the President announced a 90-day freeze on
the reciprocal tariffs. However, a 10% blanket tariff was still applied to most
nations. In contrast, the trade conflict with China escalated sharply.
Following China&apos;s 84% retaliatory tariff on U.S. goods, the U.S. increased
tariffs on Chinese imports to 125%. This, combined with existing duties,
brought the total U.S. tariff burden on Chinese imports to 145%. Kar Yong Ang,
a financial market analyst at Octa broker, comments: &apos;I will remember that day for a long
time. Traders were stunned by Trump&apos;s sudden U-turn on trade policy and really
struggled to make sense of it all. A knee-jerk reaction was to simply buy gold
and ask questions later.&apos;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apart from country-based tariffs, Trump also introduced additional
import tariffs on aluminium and steel and ordered a probe into duties on copper
imports. Overall, his aggressive trade policies have fueled speculation about
the global recession, which explains why gold has been one of the
best-performing assets since Trump took office. Kar Yong Ang comments: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&apos;We are
dealing with a rather unusual situation. Even a global depression is not out of
the question as tariffs may disrupt supply chains, hurting global output while
also contributing to stronger inflationary pressure. This will certainly
complicate monetary policy decisions. If I were to describe Trump&apos;s first 100
days in just two words, it would be &quot;run
for safety&quot;.&apos; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Trump&apos;s recent public criticism of Jerome Powell, the Fed&apos;s
Chairman, added more fuel to the fire of nervous investor sentiment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the full effect of Trump&apos;s policies is yet to materialise,
but the potential impact on global trade and the macroeconomy is substantial.
The IMF, citing escalating trade tensions, downgraded its 2025 global growth
forecast to 2.8% and warned of potential stock market crashes and a 7%
contraction in the world economy should trade wars persist. Although Scott
Bessent, the U.S. Treasury Secretary, hinted at de-escalating U.S.-China trade
tensions, it is clear that investors should still get used to living in a
period of heightened volatility and uncertainty. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kar Yong Ang has this advice for an average retail trader: &apos;Focus more
on short-term trades with tight stop-losses as opposed to long-term
position-trading, cut exposure to U.S. equities, diversify into gold and other
safe-haven currencies like Swiss franc and most importantly, keep your mind
clear and be ready to quickly switch from one position to another&apos;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compliance reminder:
trading Contracts for Difference (CFDs)
carries a high level of risk and may not be suitable for all investors.
Emotional trading can increase this risk. Always trade within your means and
understand the risks involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About Octa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.octafx.com?utm_source=media&amp;amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;amp;utm_campaign=TrumpsFirst100Days&amp;amp;utm_content=ww_fx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Octa&lt;/a&gt; is an international broker that has
been providing online trading services worldwide since 2011. It offers
commission-free access to financial markets and various services used by
clients from 180 countries who have opened more than 52 million trading accounts.
To help its clients reach their investment goals, Octa offers free educational
webinars, articles, and analytical tools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company is involved in a
comprehensive network of charitable and humanitarian initiatives, including the
improvement of educational infrastructure and short-notice relief projects
supporting local communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its foundation, Octa has won
more than 100 awards, including the &apos;Most Reliable Broker Global 2024&apos; award
from Global Forex Awards and the &apos;Best Mobile Trading Platform 2024&apos; award from
Global Brand Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDJPY Technical Analysis – Dollar shorts unwind as de-escalation gathers steam</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-dollar-shorts-unwind-as-de-escalation-gathers-steam-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:24:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-dollar-shorts-unwind-as-de-escalation-gathers-steam-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD continues to be
supported amid the ongoing de-escalation in trade wars. This has most likely to
do with positioning rather than fundamentals. The short dollar trade got very
overstretched so positive news on the tariffs front is providing a pullback. In
the medium term, the US Dollar should keep on depreciating as the path of least
resistance for the Fed remains to cut rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the JPY side, the
currency has been driven mainly by global events rather than domestic
fundamentals. Alongside the Swiss Franc, it’s been the favoured safe haven in
the currencies space amid the swings in risk sentiment. On the monetary policy
front, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;BoJ&lt;/a&gt; kept interest rates unchanged as expected and
delivered a dovish message. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was then echoed by BoJ
Governor Ueda which placed a great deal on trade war developments. In summary,
the central bank is likely to go faster on rate hikes in case we get a good
trade deal and delay rate adjustments in case the trade deal disappoints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that USDJPY continues to pull back from the key 140.00 handle. From a risk
management perspective, the sellers will have a better risk to reward setup
around the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt; to position for further
downside, while the buyers will look for a break higher to increase the bullish
bets into the 151.00 handle next. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see that we have an upward minor trendline defining the bullish momentum. If we
get a pullback, the buyers will likely lean on the trendline to position for a
rally into the major trendline, while the sellers will look for a break lower
to increase the bearish bets into the 140.00 handle next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, there’s
not much else we can add here as chasing the rally at these levels doesn’t look
good. We have also the US NFP report today which could provide a pullback in
case the data is weaker than expected. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we conclude the week with the US NFP report but
watch out for tariff related news as that’s what really matters for the market
now. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone April final manufacturing PMI 49.0 vs 48.7 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-490-vs-487-prelim-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-490-vs-487-prelim-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.6&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The headline reading is a 32-month high while the output index also improved to 51.5, up from 50.5 in March, and that&apos;s a 37-month high. It&apos;s a positive sign to start Q2 as the euro area industry looks to stabilise, helped by meaningful improvements in France and Germany in particular. That said, the path ahead remains uncertain; not least with US tariffs still clouding the outlook. HCOB notes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“A fourth consecutive increase in the HCOB PMI can be seen as a sign that the situation in the manufacturing sector is
stabilising. This comes as a surprise given the many uncertainties and shocks of recent months. However, the situation
remains fragile, as evidenced by the fact that the headline index remains below the threshold value of 50. Industrial activity
remains highly exposed to US tariff policy, but the planned sharp increase in defence spending in the EU could help stabilise
the situation in the long term. This is confirmed by the survey’s optimism gauge, which is relatively elevated when compared
with the trend over the past three years.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“The near stabilisation of the industrial economy was helped by a production pick-up in both Germany and France in April,
and Italy is fighting its way back into expansion territory. This may have been spurred by the fall in oil and gas prices in April,
and this was underscored by a decline in input prices, which had risen in each of the three months prior. Interest rate cuts by
the ECB and the prospect of further monetary easing are also likely to have been welcome news for companies.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“Manufacturers were clearly able to expand their profit margins in April, as purchasing prices fell while selling prices rose at
their fastest pace in two years. This is unlikely to continue, however, as US tariff policy is likely to see Chinese goods being
offered more widely in the EU, intensifying competition.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany April final manufacturing PMI 48.4 vs 48.0 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-484-vs-480-prelim-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-484-vs-480-prelim-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 48.3&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Germany Manufacturing PMI at 32-month high.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Germany Manufacturing PMI Output Index at 37-month high.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business expectations ease to weakest in four months.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“With the headline PMI moving closer to the neutral 50 mark, one might think that German industry is gradually emerging
from a downturn that has lasted almost three years. After all, manufacturers have expanded production for the second
month in a row. It doesn&apos;t take a crystal ball to see that the road ahead will be bumpy, though. US tariffs and the associated
uncertainty are going to weigh on German exporters. And it is quite possible that the expansion in production over the past
two months is due to pull-forward effects in connection with the impending US tariff increases, which means that there might
be a backlash in the coming months.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Despite global headwinds, German manufacturers recorded a marginal increase in export orders for the first time in over
three years. This supported a second straight monthly rise in overall order intakes. Orders from the German Bundeswehr are
probably not yet playing a decisive role here, but many companies – defence contractors, but also vehicle and drone
manufacturers and producers of optical equipment, for example – are likely to benefit from the planned additional defence
spending in the future.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Falling energy prices are helping German industry. The drop in oil and gas prices due to increased fears of recession in the
US is reflected in lower purchase prices and is helping manufacturers to expand their profit margins. This is even more the
case as sales prices rose slightly in April for the first time in nearly two years.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France April final manufacturing PMI 48.7 vs 48.2 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-487-vs-482-prelim-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:50:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-487-vs-482-prelim-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That&apos;s a modest revision higher with output rising for the first time in nearly three years. Overall, industry activity is still seen contracting but there is some underlying improvement at least. That said, there are softness in the data with employment, purchasing, and stocks all declining on the month. HCOB notes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;Since the beginning of 2025, the French manufacturing PMI has shown tentative signs of recovery, with the headline index
nearing the growth level and output increasing for the first time in almost three years in April. This upswing comes as a bit of
a surprise, given the turbulence over the past few weeks and the darkened outlook for global trade.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;Orders from both domestic and foreign clients remain in contraction, albeit at a significantly reduced rate. This suggests
potential improvements in underlying business conditions within the manufacturing sector. While US tariffs are expected to
negatively impact French manufacturing and heighten uncertainty, lower interest rates from the ECB and credible EU efforts
to reduce bureaucratic hurdles and massively increase defence spending could stimulate manufacturing activity. On that
note, future business expectations have risen to their highest level in nearly a year. Despite this, French manufacturers
continue to reduce staffing levels, although the reduction was relatively moderate. Anecdotal evidence indicates that
workforce capacity was streamlined by not replacing departing employees and opting against renewing fixed-term contracts.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;Price dynamics are not a major concern. Input prices have only seen a slight increase, likely benefiting from the decline in
energy prices, particularly oil and gas, driven by recession fears. Factory gate charges have decreased for the second
consecutive month due to competitive pressures.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;A sub-sectoral analysis revealed no significant changes from the previous month across the consumer, intermediate, and
investment goods segments. Consumer goods producers experienced a slight improvement in conditions once again, while
the intermediate and investment goods sectors remained marginally below the growth threshold.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy April manufacturing PMI 49.3 vs 47.0 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-manufacturing-pmi-493-vs-470-expected-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:45:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-manufacturing-pmi-493-vs-470-expected-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 46.6&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Output nearly stabilises, having declined in the 12 months prior to April
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Softest contraction in new orders in over a year
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cost pressures cool further, but charge inflation intensifies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This appears to indicate stabilisation, despite US tariff policy. After declining almost continuously since April 2024,
production has now almost reached the 50 mark, signalling that production is roughly at the same level as in the previous
month. The turnaround also seems to be emerging in terms of new orders, where the decline is significantly milder than in
previous months. This aligns with the fact that inventories of pre-production goods were reduced only slightly.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Given the improved survey results, growth is once again within the realm of possibility. However, after the sector has been
in recession almost continuously since mid-2022, Italian industry will have to work its way out of a rather deep hole. There
will still be a number of obstacles along the way, chief among them the US tariff policy and the threat of intensified
competition from China, which will push even more products onto the European market than before.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Higher tariffs and uncertainty are weighing on Italian industry, which is reflected in the below-average optimism of
manufacturers. However, a more severe slump in sentiment could well have been expected. The fact that the PMI figures
signal stabilisation rather than a sharp deterioration may have something to do with the fact that industry is still benefiting
from some advance deals designed to circumvent higher tariffs. In addition, the defence industry is likely to see higher
demand for defence equipment, which should have a knock-on effect on the entire manufacturing sector.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland April manufacturing PMI 45.8 vs 48.6 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-manufacturing-pmi-458-vs-486-expected-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:30:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-manufacturing-pmi-458-vs-486-expected-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That&apos;s a fresh setback to the Swiss industry, with the reading seeing a steeper decline in activity compared to March. While output picked up a little, new orders slumped heavily and was a drag alongside a hit to employment conditions. The breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain April manufacturing PMI 48.1 vs 50.0 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-manufacturing-pmi-481-vs-500-expected-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:15:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-manufacturing-pmi-481-vs-500-expected-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 49.5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Steepest cut in new orders since December 2023
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Output down modestly for first time since last August
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confidence in outlook deteriorates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the PMI data, Jonas Feldhusen, Junior Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Operating conditions in Spain&apos;s Manufacturing Sector are deteriorating. The HCOB Manufacturing PMI stays in the
contraction zone for the third consecutive month and has even deteriorated compared to the previous month. This result is
underpinned by a decline in output, for the first time since August 2024, and a significant deterioration in order volumes.
Panellists report increased uncertainty and market instability, prompting customers to delay or cancel purchasing and
investment decisions. The instability of international markets is attributed to US tariff policies and the uncertainty that
accompanies it.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The decline in sentiment has not yet impacted employment levels. For four months, the employment index has signalled
little change. Given the poorer order situation and a reduction in backlogs, there is room for a deterioration in employment
levels in the coming months. Against this backdrop, business expectations of Spanish manufacturers also weakened in April.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Price dynamics in Spain&apos;s manufacturing sector have nearly come to a halt at the start of the second quarter. Input price
inflation has further weakened, as some vendors were forced to lower their prices due to weak demand. Pricing power for
customer prices was also limited, attributed to high competitive pressures and discounts to attract clients.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For the first time this year, all sub-sectors – consumer, intermediate, and investment goods – are in the contraction zone.
The decline in intermediate goods was the most pronounced. Production there was cut, orders collapsed, and consequently,
business expectations plummeted. The consumer goods sector also declined but performed relatively better. Despite
weaker operating conditions overall, employment growth in this sector continues.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan negotiators reportedly firmly opposed to US tariffs proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-negotiators-reportedly-firmly-opposed-to-us-tariffs-proposal-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:08:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-negotiators-reportedly-firmly-opposed-to-us-tariffs-proposal-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It is reported that the US proposal was a framework that included reluctance to lowering tariffs on autos, steel, and aluminum. This was what is being proposed by the US camp with it being centered on reciprocal tariffs. Considering said proposal, Japan negotiators are firmly opposed to it according to the media outlet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Adding that Japan is to take a stance that negotiations on reducing the US trade deficit will be difficult unless tariffs on autos, steel, and aluminum are on the negotiating table. No easy deals, huh? *wink* *wink*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Again, this was supposed to be one of the easier negotiations for the US administration to manage. But from the look of things, it seems far from it. And when you weigh the comments on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-min-akazawa-says-no-comment-on-specifics-of-tariff-negotiations-with-trump-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;how the talks yesterday went&lt;/a&gt;, it didn&apos;t feel like there was too much progress whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The two camps are now expected to meet again after mid-May, according to Akazawa. So, that just kicks the can down the road for at least another two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:20:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, we have the final Manufacturing PMIs for a few European economies and the Eurozone Flash CPI. The data won&apos;t change anything for the ECB so the market reaction will likely be limited. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, the focus will switch to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/april-non-farm-payrolls-preview-by-the-numbers-any-signs-of-layoffs-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US NFP&lt;/a&gt; report although I continue to think that the data doesn&apos;t matter now and the market is just waiting for the details of the first trade deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed like we could get some news on that front yesterday after &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/hassett-on-tariffs-im-sure-there-will-be-news-by-the-end-of-the-day-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Hassett&apos;s tease&lt;/a&gt;, but eventually nothing was announced and we continue to wait. As a reminder, they said that the first deal would have been announced this week of the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think everything hinges on the details of that first trade deal. The data is old news and unless we see a notable deterioration in the labour market, the central bank won&apos;t do anything. The US Jobless Claims have been stable and yesterday&apos;s data was skewed by one-off effects. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +1.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-11-in-early-european-trading-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:13:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-11-in-early-european-trading-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +1.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are up 0.6%, so that&apos;s feeding into a more positive mood going into European trading. For European stocks, it&apos;s also a catch up to the overnight gains after the Labor Day holiday yesterday. As things stand, trade headlines remain the main driver but there&apos;s also the US jobs report to be mindful of in the day ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 2 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-2-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 05:05:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-2-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As we look to close out the week, there isn&apos;t too much on the expiries list to take note of. There is perhaps arguably just one for USD/JPY at 146.00 but it doesn&apos;t tie to any technical significance. As such, I wouldn&apos;t expect the expiries to have much impact. The market at the moment is largely riding on trade developments and will look to the US jobs report later for some little anecdotes to work with. All that before the weekend comes along. 🎵&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The positive animal spirits stick towards the final stretch of the week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-positive-animal-spirits-stick-towards-the-final-stretch-of-the-week-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 04:32:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-positive-animal-spirits-stick-towards-the-final-stretch-of-the-week-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are up 0.7% on the day and that sets up the cash index to eye a potential ninth consecutive day of gains. It&apos;s been an impressive rebound in Wall Street to say the least, on what has been a lot talking the talk but nothing about walking the walk just yet. This time around, China is the one reportedly delivering some hopeful optimism &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Is that opening a slight gap in the door for Trump? We&apos;ll see. But for now, we&apos;re not at the point of picking up the phone just yet on either side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In any case, the S&amp;amp;P 500 now looks poised to recover the 61.8 Fib retracement of the fall since February as the rebound continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That is encouraging but there will be bigger technical hurdles to get through just above that. The 100 (red line) and 200-day (blue line) moving averages will present key challenges before thinking about retesting the highs near 6,000 to 6,100 again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides trade developments, we also had Amazon and Apple earnings come in. And while both delivered better than estimates, the latter does have a caveat. Greater China sales roughly met estimates with a $16.0 billion figure but that is down a little over 2% compared to a year ago. That is evident of a shift in spending mindset and perhaps the toll taken from the US-China trade rhetoric spilling over into consumer behaviour. If anything, we&apos;ll likely see this figure shrink the longer the trade war rages on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As for the day ahead, there will also be the US jobs report to look out for. Any thinking of layoffs in logistics and retail related to tariffs should be quickly dispelled here as it is still too early to see that show up in the data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It will still take a few months of hard data hitting hard before really leading to freight and trucking services to cut labour costs. But when it starts to hit, the cascading effect can be quick to catch on. So, just be wary of that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As such, the non-farm payrolls data today shouldn&apos;t be too much of a factor besides looking into the wider impact of DOGE layoffs. If you&apos;re looking for any impact from tariffs here, this isn&apos;t the time yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And that means trade headlines or should I say Trump headlines, will continue to take on more importance.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Off ramp emerging for tariffs? S&amp;P 500 futures jump</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-off-ramp-emerging-for-tariffs-sp-500-futures-jump-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-off-ramp-emerging-for-tariffs-sp-500-futures-jump-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rubio-says-ukraine-and-russia-positions-are-still-a-little-far-apart-20250502/&quot;&gt;Rubio says Ukraine and Russia positions are still a little far apart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/a-big-turn-around-for-us-equity-index-trade-higher-on-globex-on-china-comments-20250502/&quot;&gt;A big turn around for US equity index trade - higher on Globex on China comments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/&quot;&gt;China says the US has sought to begin trade talks, China says its thinking about it  ...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/its-not-just-gold-goldman-sachs-says-asian-currencies-to-benefit-from-usd-losing-status-20250502/&quot;&gt;Its not just gold - Goldman Sachs says Asian currencies to benefit from USD losing status&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-2025-non-farm-payrolls-data-the-critical-key-ranges-for-estimates-to-watch-20250502/&quot;&gt;US April 2025 non-farm payrolls data - the critical key ranges for estimates to watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-stance-of-requesting-us-cancel-tariffs-20250502/&quot;&gt;Japan PM Ishiba - no change to stance of requesting US cancel tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-retail-sales-03-mm-expected-04-20250502/&quot;&gt;Australian March retail sales +0.3% m/m (expected +0.4%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-election-this-weekend-heres-the-risk-for-the-australian-dollar-20250502/&quot;&gt;Australian election this weekend - here&apos;s the risk for the Australian dollar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-min-akazawa-says-no-comment-on-specifics-of-tariff-negotiations-with-trump-20250501/&quot;&gt;Japan eco min Akazawa says no comment on specifics of tariff negotiations with Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-eyes-rolling-back-immigration-protections-for-around-600000-venezuelan-immigrants-20250501/&quot;&gt;Trump eyes rolling back immigration protections for around 600,000 Venezuelan immigrants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-march-unemployment-rate-25-expected-24-prior-24-20250501/&quot;&gt;Japan March unemployment rate 2.5% (expected 2.4%, prior 2.4%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-april-cpi-comes-in-a-touch-higher-than-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;South Korea April CPI y/y comes in a touch higher than expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-march-building-permits-96-mm-prior-08-20250501/&quot;&gt;New Zealand March Building Permits +9.6% m/m (prior +0.8%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-vice-president-vance-russias-war-in-ukraine-is-not-going-to-end-any-time-soon-20250501/&quot;&gt;U.S. Vice President Vance: Russia’s war in Ukraine is not going to end any time soon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-for-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-20250501/&quot;&gt;&quot;Japan&apos;s US Treasury holdings among tools for trade talks, Finance Minister Kato says&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-fin-min-kato-said-had-no-discussion-at-all-with-us-of-where-yen-fx-level-should-be-20250501/&quot;&gt;Japan fin min Kato said had no discussion at all with US of where yen FX level should be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/4-reasons-the-usd-rally-will-falter-4-is-going-to-be-very-difficult-to-recover-from-20250501/&quot;&gt;4 reasons the USD rally will falter (#4 is going to be very difficult to recover from)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/apple-eps-165-versus-162-expected-revenues-9536-billion-versus-9453-billion-est-20250501/&quot;&gt;Apple EPS $1.65 versus $1.62 expected. Revenues $95.36 billion versus $94.53 billion est&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/apple-has-approved-a-new-us100bn-share-buyback-program-20250501/&quot;&gt;Apple has approved a new US$100bn share buyback program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/a-look-at-some-of-the-other-earnings-release-after-the-close-20250501/&quot;&gt;A look at some of the other earnings release after the close&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-usdjpy-soars-as-yields-turn-higher-20250501/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: USD/JPY soars as yields turn higher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/sp-closes-higher-for-the-eighth-consecutive-day-20250501/&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P closes higher for the eighth consecutive day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/amazon-revenues-1557b-vs-expectations-of-154889b-eps-159-versus-136-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;Amazon revenues $155.7B vs expectations of $154.889B. EPS $1.59 versus $1.36 expected.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-friday-2-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250501/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Friday, 2 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
Hopes
for a thaw in US-China trade tensions gained momentum Friday after
Beijing confirmed that Washington had recently conveyed, repeatedly, a desire to
start negotiations. “The US has recently sent messages to China
through relevant parties, hoping to start talks,” China’s
Commerce Ministry said, adding that “China is currently evaluating
this.” The ministry noted that the US has repeatedly expressed
interest in addressing tariff issues. Markets took the signals as a
tentative step toward dialogue, with oil prices and US equity index
futures moving higher on optimism that the world’s two largest
economies might be preparing to re-engage. In Washington, Senator
Marco Rubio echoed the sentiment, saying “the Chinese want to meet
and talk,” suggesting the ice may finally be starting to break.
Investors broadly interpreted the tone shift as a potentially
face-saving off-ramp for Trump, and a developing path forward for
China, particularly as economic cracks begin to emerge more visibly
in the recent data on both sides of the Pacific. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Still,
Beijing&apos;s tone was far from conciliatory. China’s Commerce Ministry
stressed that “if the US does not correct its unilateral tariff
measures, it has no sincerity at all” and that Washington must be
“prepared to take action in correcting erroneous practices,
including cancelling unilateral tariffs.” While China confirmed it
is open to dialogue, officials made clear that any talks would be
conditional on tangible US concessions. These statements, some
analysts argue, amount to Beijing effectively demanding a full
rollback of Trump-era tariffs as a precondition for serious
engagement — a stance that could complicate efforts to rekindle
negotiations. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Earlier
in the session, Japanese Finance Minister Katsunobu Kato made
headlines by suggesting that Japan’s substantial holdings of U.S.
Treasuries could be considered a potential bargaining chip in trade
negotiations with Washington — though he was quick to clarify that
there is no intention to deploy that option at this stage. Japan’s
lead negotiator on tariffs, Ryosei Akazawa, struck a more measured
tone, and notably indicating that the next round of talks may not take place
until after mid-May — a sign that a breakthrough is unlikely
anytime soon. Both officials confirmed that foreign exchange issues,
i.e. the yen, were not discussed. Later, Prime Minister Fumio
Ishiba reinforced Japan’s longstanding position, stating that
Tokyo, like Beijing, continues to urge the U.S. to remove its tariff
measures. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Australia
heads to the polls on Saturday, May 3, with Prime Minister Anthony
Albanese still favoured to retain government — though polling
remains tight, and the prospect of a minority government cannot be
ruled out. On the economic front, March retail sales data released today showed a modest
improvement from February but fell short of expectations, while Q1
retail sales were flat overall — a notably weak result. Meanwhile,
producer price inflation (PPI) for the quarter came in above headline
CPI, highlighting lingering cost pressures. However, none of the data
releases shifted market expectations for a 25 basis point rate cut
from the Reserve Bank of Australia when it meets on May 19–20.. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;As mentioned, oil
and equities were broadly underpinned amid easing US-China tensions,
while major currency pairs saw mixed performance. USD/JPY briefly
spiked toward 145.80 but later retraced, ending the session little
changed. Elsewhere, the US dollar weakened against most G10 peers,
with the AUD, GBP, NZD, and CAD all posting gains. EUR/USD was a
relative laggard, advancing more modestly compared to the broader
move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a gap lower to open Globex evening trade ES soared on the China news. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The above is a CFD that tracks ES. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Its not just gold - Goldman Sachs says Asian currencies to benefit from USD losing status</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/its-not-just-gold-goldman-sachs-says-asian-currencies-to-benefit-from-usd-losing-status-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 03:02:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/its-not-just-gold-goldman-sachs-says-asian-currencies-to-benefit-from-usd-losing-status-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;116&quot; data-end=&quot;415&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Central banks are accelerating their shift away from the US dollar, a move that has gained traction over the past decade and shows no sign of slowing. “We believe the diversification away from dollar should persist, as this trend has been well entrenched for the past decade,” the Goldman Sachs strategists wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The momentum intensified following the 2022 sanctions on Russia, when Washington froze Moscow’s dollar reserves and cut it off from the global financial system. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Those events rattled confidence in the greenback’s reliability, and concerns have only deepened amid Trump’s policies, which threaten to disrupt global trade and economic stability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; In response, central banks have also been building up gold holdings, supporting demand for the precious metal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;889&quot; data-end=&quot;1241&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Still, the dollar retains its roleas the primary reserve currency and the standard for pricing key commodities like oil&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;much of that status stems from the vast liquidity of the US Treasury market, which allows investors to transact large volumes without moving prices—an advantage no other market currently offers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;there are signs of erosion - Bloomberg’s dollar gauge has fallen more than 7% since peaking in February, as the narrative of US exceptionalism loses steam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1508&quot; data-end=&quot;1750&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;According to the strategists, the dollar is still about 17% overvalued based on Goldman’s valuation models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“We anticipate a rotation to other global assets, of which Asian assets could be a subset” &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;South Korea, Singapore and China&apos;s currencies are likely to be the biggest Asian beneficiaries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summary of a Bloomberg piece citing GS. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April 2025 non-farm payrolls data - the critical key ranges for estimates to watch</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-2025-non-farm-payrolls-data-the-critical-key-ranges-for-estimates-to-watch-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-2025-non-farm-payrolls-data-the-critical-key-ranges-for-estimates-to-watch-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The January 2025 employment report is due from the US on Friday, May 2, 2025, at 0830 US Eastern time, 1330 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;You can see the consensus estimate in the screenshot below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;The number in the right-most column is the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month) result.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look at the range of expectations compared to the median consensus (the &apos;expected&apos; in the screenshot above) for the key data points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Headline NFP number:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;25,000 to 195,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unemployment rate:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;4.1% to 4.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average hourly earnings m/m:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.2% to 0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average hourly earnings y/y:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;2.8% to 3.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is knowledge of such ranges important?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data results that fall outside of market low and high expectations tend to move markets more significantly for several reasons:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Surprise Factor: Markets often price in expectations based on forecasts and previous trends. When data significantly deviates from these expectations, it creates a surprise effect. This can lead to rapid revaluation of assets as investors and traders reassess their positions based on the new information.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Psychological Impact: Investors and traders are influenced by psychological factors. Extreme data points can evoke strong emotional reactions, leading to overreactions in the market. This can amplify market movements, especially in the short term.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Risk Reassessment: Unexpected data can lead to a reassessment of risk. If data significantly underperforms or outperforms expectations, it can change the perceived risk of certain investments. For instance, better-than-expected economic data may reduce the perceived risk of investing in equities, leading to a market rally.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Triggering of Automated Trading: In today’s markets, a significant portion of trading is done by algorithms. These automated systems often have pre-set conditions or thresholds that, when triggered by unexpected data, can lead to large-scale buying or selling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Impact on Monetary and Fiscal Policies: Data that is significantly off from expectations can influence the policies of central banks and governments. For example, in the case of the NFP due today, a weaker jobs report will fuel speculation of sooner Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) rate cuts to come. A stronger report will diminish such expectations, with the Fed on hold for longer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Liquidity and Market Depth: In some cases, extreme data points can affect market liquidity. If the data is unexpected enough, it might lead to a temporary imbalance in buyers and sellers, causing larger market moves until a new equilibrium is found.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chain Reactions and Correlations: Financial markets are interconnected. A significant move in one market or asset class due to unexpected data can lead to correlated moves in other markets, amplifying the overall market impact.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan PM Ishiba - no change to stance of requesting US cancel tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-stance-of-requesting-us-cancel-tariffs-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 02:07:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-no-change-to-stance-of-requesting-us-cancel-tariffs-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan Prime Minister Ishiba&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No change at all to our stance of requesting U.S. to cancel tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not in situation where we have found common ground yet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;But received report from Akazawa that talks were forward-looking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reaching a deal in haste is not necessarily in the best interest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier from Japan on tariffs:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-min-akazawa-says-no-comment-on-specifics-of-tariff-negotiations-with-trump-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan eco min Akazawa says no comment on specifics of tariff negotiations with Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-us-treasury-holdings-among-tools-for-trade-talks-finance-minister-kato-says-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&quot;Japan&apos;s US Treasury holdings among tools for trade talks, Finance Minister Kato says&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian March retail sales +0.3% m/m (expected +0.4%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-retail-sales-03-mm-expected-04-20250502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-retail-sales-03-mm-expected-04-20250502/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Australian March retail sales &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;+0.3% m/m, improved from February but not by as much as was expect&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;expected +0.4%, prior +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;0.0% q.q in Q1 2025, no change during the quarter is a very soft reading&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior +1.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data also for PPI, Q1 2025:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;+0.9% q/q&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior +0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;+3.7% y/y&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior +3.7% also&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;PPI outrunning CPI. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD rose earlier on the China news:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-the-us-has-sought-to-begin-trade-talks-china-says-its-thinking-about-it-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China says the US has sought to begin trade talks, China says its thinking about it  ...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/a-big-turn-around-for-us-equity-index-trade-higher-on-globex-on-china-comments-20250502/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;A big turn around for US equity index trade - higher on Globex on China comments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *MARCO RUBIO SAYS CHINA IS REACHING OUT ON ECONOMIC ISSUES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918112909520933046#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:18:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918112909520933046#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*MARCO RUBIO SAYS CHINA IS REACHING OUT ON ECONOMIC ISSUES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO: THOSE TALKS WILL COME UP SOON</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918111949847748987#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918111949847748987#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO: THOSE TALKS WILL COME UP SOON&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918111652421013620#m&quot;&gt;localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918111652421013620#m&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO: CHINESE WANT TO MEET AND TALK</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918111652421013620#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:13:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918111652421013620#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO: CHINESE WANT TO MEET AND TALK&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA SAYS CURRENTLY EVALUATING POSSIBLE US TRADE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918109237453980062#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918109237453980062#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA SAYS CURRENTLY EVALUATING POSSIBLE US TRADE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE: RUSSIA&apos;S WAR IN UKRAINE IS NOT GOING TO END ANY TIME SOON</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918069657187315990#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:26:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918069657187315990#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE: RUSSIA&apos;S WAR IN UKRAINE IS NOT GOING TO END ANY TIME SOON&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE: INDIA COULD BE AMONG ONE OF THE FIRST TRADE DEALS -FOX NEWS INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918067009981423984#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:16:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918067009981423984#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE: INDIA COULD BE AMONG ONE OF THE FIRST TRADE DEALS -FOX NEWS INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. VICE PRESIDENT JD VANCE SAYS WALTZ JOB CHANGE NOT THE RESULT OF SIGNAL CHAT LEAK</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918066942767702499#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:16:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918066942767702499#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. VICE PRESIDENT JD VANCE SAYS WALTZ JOB CHANGE NOT THE RESULT OF SIGNAL CHAT LEAK&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) APPLE IS &apos;VERY ENGAGED&apos; ON TARIFF DICUSSIONS - APPLE CEO TIM COOK ON CONF CALL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918056508694188374#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:34:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918056508694188374#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;APPLE IS &apos;VERY ENGAGED&apos; ON TARIFF DICUSSIONS - APPLE CEO TIM COOK ON CONF CALL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE ESTIMATES $900 MILLION IN COST INCREASES ON TARIFFS IN Q3</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918055965867332069#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 21:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918055965867332069#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE ESTIMATES $900 MILLION IN COST INCREASES ON TARIFFS IN Q3&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE: BOARD AUTHORIZED BUYBACK UP TO $100B OF COMPANY’S STOCK</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918040704015598076#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:31:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918040704015598076#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE: BOARD AUTHORIZED BUYBACK UP TO $100B OF COMPANY’S STOCK&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE 2Q IPHONE REVENUE $46.84B, EST. $45.94B</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918040638198530420#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:31:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918040638198530420#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE 2Q IPHONE REVENUE $46.84B, EST. $45.94B&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE 2Q EPS $1.65, EST. $1.62
*APPLE 2Q REV. $95.36B, EST. $94.59B
*APPLE 2Q GREATER CHINA REV. $16.00B, EST. $16.83B

$AAPL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918040470069923864#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918040470069923864#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE 2Q EPS $1.65, EST. $1.62&lt;br&gt;
*APPLE 2Q REV. $95.36B, EST. $94.59B&lt;br&gt;
*APPLE 2Q GREATER CHINA REV. $16.00B, EST. $16.83B&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AAPL&quot;&gt;$AAPL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) STRATEGY TO OFFER UP TO $21B IN CLASS A STOCK VIA ATM SALES AGREEMENT: FILING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918039722393325707#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:27:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918039722393325707#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;STRATEGY TO OFFER UP TO $21B IN CLASS A STOCK VIA ATM SALES AGREEMENT: FILING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *AMAZON SEES 2Q NET SALES $159.0B TO $164.0B, EST. $161.42B

*AMAZON SEES 2Q OPER INCOME $13.0B TO $17.5B, EST. $17.82B</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918033318462816387#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918033318462816387#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*AMAZON SEES 2Q NET SALES $159.0B TO $164.0B, EST. $161.42B&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*AMAZON SEES 2Q OPER INCOME $13.0B TO $17.5B, EST. $17.82B&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *AMAZON Q1 EPS USD 1.59 VS. IBES ESTIMATE USD 1.36
*AMAZON Q1 OPERATING INCOME USD 18,400 MILLION VS. IBES ESTIMATE USD 17,482 MILLION

$AMZN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918033146706026500#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:01:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918033146706026500#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*AMAZON Q1 EPS USD 1.59 VS. IBES ESTIMATE USD 1.36&lt;br&gt;
*AMAZON Q1 OPERATING INCOME USD 18,400 MILLION VS. IBES ESTIMATE USD 17,482 MILLION&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AMZN&quot;&gt;$AMZN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) S&amp;P 500 FINISHES HIGHER FOR 8TH STRAIGHT SESSION; LONGEST DAILY WINNING STREAK SINCE AUGUST</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918032859367186571#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 20:00:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918032859367186571#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 FINISHES HIGHER FOR 8TH STRAIGHT SESSION; LONGEST DAILY WINNING STREAK SINCE AUGUST&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EUROPE READY TO MAKE TRUMP A €50BN OFFER, SAYS EU NEGOTIATOR - FT

 MAROŠ ŠEFČOVIČ, EU’S TRADE COMMISSIONER: BLOC WOULD NOT ACCEPT WASHINGTON KEEPING 10% TARIFFS ON ITS GOODS AS A FAIR RESOLUTION TO TRADE TALKS - FT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918015717754191891#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:52:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918015717754191891#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EUROPE READY TO MAKE TRUMP A €50BN OFFER, SAYS EU NEGOTIATOR - FT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
 MAROŠ ŠEFČOVIČ, EU’S TRADE COMMISSIONER: BLOC WOULD NOT ACCEPT WASHINGTON KEEPING 10% TARIFFS ON ITS GOODS AS A FAIR RESOLUTION TO TRADE TALKS - FT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: ANY COUNTRY BUYING OIL FROM IRAN WILL FACE SANCTIONS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918007954181120327#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:21:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918007954181120327#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: ANY COUNTRY BUYING OIL FROM IRAN WILL FACE SANCTIONS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP PICKS RUBIO FOR INTERIM NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1918007399912263861#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:19:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1918007399912263861#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP PICKS RUBIO FOR INTERIM NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
