<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>The dip buying in bonds seems to have run out of gas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-dip-buying-in-bonds-seems-to-have-run-out-of-gas-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:31:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-dip-buying-in-bonds-seems-to-have-run-out-of-gas-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The opportunity to buy 30-year Treasuries yielding 5% briefly presented itself this week for the fourth time this year. All the other attempts were quickly beaten back and that same knee-jerk unfolded this time, driving yields to as low as 4.86% today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UMich report though seemed to underline ongoing angst about inflation and led to a bounce to 4.90%. If it holds, that will be the second-highest weekly close since October 2023 (the Liz Truss fiasco). Beyond that you need to go to before the financial crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, the opportunity to buy bonds at these kinds of rates is rare and the market hasn&apos;t forgotten that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was probably some good news on the fiscal front for bonds today as some Republicans pushed back on the huge deficit increase that&apos;s coming in Trump&apos;s budget. That said, he&apos;s right to be highlighting that they&apos;re just grandstanding and will ultimately support it.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Hughes US oil rig count -1</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/baker-hughes-us-oil-rig-count-1-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 17:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/baker-hughes-us-oil-rig-count-1-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Total rigs down 2 to 576. It&apos;s the third consecutive weekly drop in rigs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The oil market is in flux at the moment as OPEC brings back more barrels than anticipated and Trump zig-zags on trade policy. Natural gas is looking healthier though with days of US supply down about 18% y/y.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve said to plan cuts of 10% of workforce over next several years</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/federal-reserve-said-to-plan-cuts-of-10-of-workforce-over-next-several-years-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/federal-reserve-said-to-plan-cuts-of-10-of-workforce-over-next-several-years-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Someone the Federal Reserve system employs 26,000 people. That seems like an awful lot of people to manager currency, process checks and supervise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think they&apos;ll be fine with a 10% haircut.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *FED SAID TO SHRINK WORKFORCE ABOUT 10% OVER NEXT SEVERAL YEARS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923417636827812318#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:37:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923417636827812318#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*FED SAID TO SHRINK WORKFORCE ABOUT 10% OVER NEXT SEVERAL YEARS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tax bill fails in House panel</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-tax-bill-fails-in-house-panel-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:04:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-tax-bill-fails-in-house-panel-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The vote failed in the Budget Committee, 16-21.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a strong belief in markets that they will twist the right arms in order to get it through when it matters. As it stands, this is putting the US on the path to another 1 or 1.5 percentage point increase in the deficit, or above 7% of GDP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The votes against it want to cut Medicaid, which looks like the battle ground at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looks like there won&apos;t be another vote today.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HARDLINE CONSERVATIVES OPPOSE BILL, SEEKING MORE MEDICAID CUTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923409000495804906#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:03:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923409000495804906#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HARDLINE CONSERVATIVES OPPOSE BILL, SEEKING MORE MEDICAID CUTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP TAX BILL FAILS IN HOUSE PANEL AS GOP SPLITS ON COST</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923408393902919764#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:01:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923408393902919764#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP TAX BILL FAILS IN HOUSE PANEL AS GOP SPLITS ON COST&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equity close: Solid finish to a fifth-straight week of gains</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-close-solid-finish-to-a-fifth-straight-week-of-gains-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-close-solid-finish-to-a-fifth-straight-week-of-gains-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Closing changes on the day:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX, +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK&apos;s FTSE 100 +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex +0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the week:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX, +1.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC +1.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK&apos;s FTSE 100 +1.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex +3.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB +3.1%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Liberation Day declines have been nearly erased everywhere and Italy, Spain and Germany finished with record closing highs. I think this masks the extent of the battle that will unfold between the EU and US on trade, as I don&apos;t see any easy path to a compromise there.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. WILL START DISCUSSIONS LATER THIS YEAR ON TROOP REDUCTION IN EUROPE, US NATO AMBASSADOR SAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923403134916771906#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:40:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923403134916771906#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. WILL START DISCUSSIONS LATER THIS YEAR ON TROOP REDUCTION IN EUROPE, US NATO AMBASSADOR SAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $AAPL - APPLE: DID NOT TAKE ACTION TO REMOVE FORTNITE FROM THE EU

APPLE: ASKED EPIC TO RESUBMIT UPDATE WITHOUT INCLUDING THE US</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923401597809213705#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:34:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923401597809213705#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AAPL&quot;&gt;$AAPL&lt;/a&gt; - APPLE: DID NOT TAKE ACTION TO REMOVE FORTNITE FROM THE EU&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
APPLE: ASKED EPIC TO RESUBMIT UPDATE WITHOUT INCLUDING THE US&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) UKRAINIAN FOREIGN MINISTRY SPOKESMAN SAYS: ZELENSKIY IS READY FOR DIRECT NEGOTIATIONS WITH PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923401011076464758#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:31:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923401011076464758#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UKRAINIAN FOREIGN MINISTRY SPOKESMAN SAYS: ZELENSKIY IS READY FOR DIRECT NEGOTIATIONS WITH PUTIN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BofA: 6 reasons to stay bearish on the USD despite the US-China truce</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-6-reasons-to-stay-bearish-on-the-usd-despite-the-us-china-truce-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:27:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-6-reasons-to-stay-bearish-on-the-usd-despite-the-us-china-truce-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;75&quot; data-end=&quot;322&quot;&gt;While a temporary truce between the U.S. and China has offered some relief to markets, BofA maintains a bearish outlook on the dollar. The recent bounce is seen as tactical rather than structural, with longer-term headwinds intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;324&quot; data-end=&quot;339&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-start=&quot;341&quot; data-end=&quot;1438&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;341&quot; data-end=&quot;551&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;344&quot; data-end=&quot;551&quot;&gt;Policy uncertainty persists:The pause in trade tensions is temporary. Policy direction remains erratic and could reintroduce volatility later this summer as deadlines and tariff suspensions expire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;553&quot; data-end=&quot;741&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;556&quot; data-end=&quot;741&quot;&gt;Lingering economic drag:Even with de-escalation, the U.S. economy is now on a slower growth path than pre-trade war due to delayed investment and weakened business confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;743&quot; data-end=&quot;897&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;746&quot; data-end=&quot;897&quot;&gt;Current account deterioration:A narrowing U.S. current account surplus is reducing investment inflows and undermining support for the dollar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;899&quot; data-end=&quot;1074&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;902&quot; data-end=&quot;1074&quot;&gt;Foreign asset reallocation:Institutional real money investors are reassessing exposure to U.S. assets and the dollar, contributing to persistent capital outflows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1076&quot; data-end=&quot;1262&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1079&quot; data-end=&quot;1262&quot;&gt;Fiscal uncertainty:An unpredictable fiscal trajectory adds risk, with potential implications for long-term Treasury issuance, inflation expectations, and investor sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1264&quot; data-end=&quot;1438&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1267&quot; data-end=&quot;1438&quot;&gt;Weaker-dollar bias from policymakers:The Trump administration continues to favor lower rates and a softer dollar, which adds to long-term depreciation pressures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1440&quot; data-end=&quot;1723&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1440&quot; data-end=&quot;1723&quot;&gt;BofA remains bearish on the USD, despite tactical reprieves. Structural forces—ranging from weaker capital inflows to policy unpredictability—are seen as increasingly difficult to reverse, suggesting a lower dollar over the medium term with a choppier path forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1440&quot; data-end=&quot;1723&quot;&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747495616851000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0FnVseEYgOaFgBrAnSWNdk&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747495616851000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0FnVseEYgOaFgBrAnSWNdk&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech sees volatility: A closer look at today&apos;s market movements</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sees-volatility-a-closer-look-at-todays-market-movements-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:46:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sees-volatility-a-closer-look-at-todays-market-movements-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s stock market presents a mixed bag of performances across various sectors. Let&apos;s delve into each area to understand the driving forces behind the numbers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;📈 Communication Services: Google (GOOG) surged by 1.98%, highlighting a strong performance in this sector. However, Meta (META) faced a decline of 1.69%, indicating divergent investor sentiments within digital platforms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;📉 Semiconductors: The sector showed mixed signals with Nvidia (NVDA) inching up by 0.18% while Broadcom (AVGO) dropped by 1.99%. Concerns remain prevalent about overvaluations and potential supply chain disruptions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🚀 Healthcare: A bright spot today, with Eli Lilly (LLY) leading the pack, gaining 2.40%. Robust drug pipeline news and strong earnings continue to fuel this sector&apos;s growth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🏦 Financials: A somewhat neutral day with Visa (V) increasing by 0.32% contrasted against JPMorgan Chase (JPM) slipping by 0.40%. Economic data and interest rate expectations are key factors.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🏗️ Industrials and Energy: Both sectors faced challenges, with Exxon (XOM) and Chevron (CVX) down by nearly 1%. This reflects broader concerns over energy demand fluctuations and geopolitical tensions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market sentiment today seems cautiously optimistic, with investors balancing growth opportunities against potential risks. Lingering inflationary pressures and evolving global economic indicators add complexity to investment strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tech stocks reveal volatility, illustrating a rotation in investor focus towards more stable and defensive areas like utilities and healthcare. Meanwhile, communication services display resilience, as shown by Google&apos;s robust performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consider Diversification: With today&apos;s volatility, diversifying portfolios could be beneficial. Focus on balanced exposure across defensive sectors such as healthcare and emerging market technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Watch Market Indicators: Keep a close eye on economic data releases that might impact interest rates and sector movements.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Explore Growth Opportunities: Strong performers in the healthcare sector, particularly biotech, could offer attractive entry points for growth-oriented investors.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In these uncertain times, staying informed with real-time market updates and analysis is crucial. Whether you&apos;re a seasoned investor or a market novice, continued vigilance and strategic adjustments will be key to navigating today&apos;s dynamic market landscape. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://forexlive.com&quot;&gt;Forexlive.com&lt;/a&gt; for continuous insights and updates.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euro sags as US yields climb off the floor</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/euro-sags-as-us-yields-climb-off-the-floor-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:45:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/euro-sags-as-us-yields-climb-off-the-floor-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US dollar is bid across the board at the moment as yields rebound from earlier lows. US 2-year yields were at 3.92% earlier today but have ticked up to 3.96%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market has grown more-hesitant about pricing in rate cuts after the UMich consumer sentiment &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/umich-may-prelim-consumer-sentiment-508-vs-534-expected-20250516/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;report &lt;/a&gt;showed a surge in inflation expectations. One-year inflation rose to 7.3% from 6.5%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s notable that this was mostly before Trump backtracked on China tariffs so these numbers will assuredly come down in the final report or next month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We could also be seeing some flows ahead of the 4 pm London fix, so keep an eye out for a USD reversal after that.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $BA - BOEING REACHES TENTATIVE U.S. NON-PROSECUTION AGREEMENT IN FATAL CRASHES CASE, SOURCES SAY

BOEING NO LONGER AGREES TO PLEAD GUILTY IN FATAL CRASHES CASE, SOURCES SAY

U.S. DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE WEIGHING NON-PROSECUTION AGREEMENT WITH BOEING IN FATAL CRASHES CASE VERSUS TAKING COMPANY TO TRIAL, SOURCES SAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923385255634817373#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:29:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923385255634817373#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23BA&quot;&gt;$BA&lt;/a&gt; - BOEING REACHES TENTATIVE U.S. NON-PROSECUTION AGREEMENT IN FATAL CRASHES CASE, SOURCES SAY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
BOEING NO LONGER AGREES TO PLEAD GUILTY IN FATAL CRASHES CASE, SOURCES SAY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE WEIGHING NON-PROSECUTION AGREEMENT WITH BOEING IN FATAL CRASHES CASE VERSUS TAKING COMPANY TO TRIAL, SOURCES SAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $NVDA - NVIDIA SAYS NOT SENDING ANY GPU DESIGNS TO CHINA TO BE MODIFIED TO COMPLY WITH EXPORT CONTROLS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923380794594119960#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:11:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923380794594119960#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt; - NVIDIA SAYS NOT SENDING ANY GPU DESIGNS TO CHINA TO BE MODIFIED TO COMPLY WITH EXPORT CONTROLS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: STOP TALKING AND GET IT DONE!</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923380171463073933#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:09:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923380171463073933#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: STOP TALKING AND GET IT DONE!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: DON&apos;T NEED &quot;GRANDSTANDERS&quot; IN REPUBLICAN PARTY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923380028433145969#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:08:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923380028433145969#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: DON&apos;T NEED &quot;GRANDSTANDERS&quot; IN REPUBLICAN PARTY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: COUNTRY WILL SUFFER GREATLY WITHOUT THIS LEGISLATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923379974557376852#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:08:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923379974557376852#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: COUNTRY WILL SUFFER GREATLY WITHOUT THIS LEGISLATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: REPUBLICANS MUST UNITE BEHIND, BIG BEAUTIFUL BILL!</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923379931376959795#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:08:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923379931376959795#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: REPUBLICANS MUST UNITE BEHIND, BIG BEAUTIFUL BILL!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US factory orders data throttled lower in revisions</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-factory-orders-data-throttled-lower-in-revisions-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-factory-orders-data-throttled-lower-in-revisions-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;March factory orders revised to +3.4% from +4.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ex transport to -0.4% from -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nondefense capital goods orders ex air -0.2% vs +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The amount of times this report is revised is dizzying but this will be a drag on Q1 GDP when it&apos;s revised.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $NVDA - NVIDIA SAYS IT IS NOT SENDING GPU DESIGNS TO CHINA AFTER REPORTS OF NEW SHANGHAI OPERATION - CNBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923378207136383286#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923378207136383286#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt; - NVIDIA SAYS IT IS NOT SENDING GPU DESIGNS TO CHINA AFTER REPORTS OF NEW SHANGHAI OPERATION - CNBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *UMICH YR-AHEAD EXPECTED INFLATION AT 7.3%, HIGHEST SINCE 1981</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923378072738267377#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:00:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923378072738267377#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*UMICH YR-AHEAD EXPECTED INFLATION AT 7.3%, HIGHEST SINCE 1981&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *MICHIGAN CONSUMER SENTIMENT AT 50.8, SECOND LOWEST ON RECORD

*UMICH PRELIM MAY CONSUMER SENTIMENT FALLS TO 50.8; EST 53.4</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923378061786943574#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:00:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923378061786943574#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*MICHIGAN CONSUMER SENTIMENT AT 50.8, SECOND LOWEST ON RECORD&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*UMICH PRELIM MAY CONSUMER SENTIMENT FALLS TO 50.8; EST 53.4&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMich May prelim consumer sentiment 50.8 vs 53.4 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/umich-may-prelim-consumer-sentiment-508-vs-534-expected-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/umich-may-prelim-consumer-sentiment-508-vs-534-expected-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 52.2&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current conditions 57.6    vs 59.6 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expectations 46.5   vs 48.0 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1-year inflation 7.3% vs 6.5% prior &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year inflation 4.6% vs 4.4% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a poor reading. I would have expected to see some recovery after Trump reversed the Liberation Day tariffs but that didn&apos;t show up in this round. The pause in China tariffs should be a tailwind in the month ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan not keep for compromise in US trade talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-not-keep-for-compromise-in-us-trade-talks-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:52:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-not-keep-for-compromise-in-us-trade-talks-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;This was out earlier but it&apos;s an important development:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The FT &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/45d52534-00a1-42d5-be46-486cf34fcfb8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;reports &lt;/a&gt;that Japan is holding out for a better deal with the US, including a full removal of 25% auto tariffs. It says a deal is now unlikely to be reached before elections due in late July, which is beyond the 90-day delay the US imposed (expiration is July 8).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There had been reports this week that Japanese and South Korean deals would be soon announced, though there is a meeting still planned for next week and the G7 in Canada will be closely watched.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP TO ATTEND BILL SIGNING CEREMONY MONDAY AT 3PM ET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923375800260100121#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:51:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923375800260100121#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP TO ATTEND BILL SIGNING CEREMONY MONDAY AT 3PM ET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ZELENSKIY AFTER CALL WITH TRUMP: UKRAINE IS READY FOR QUICK STEPS FOR PEACE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923374792083660835#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:47:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923374792083660835#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ZELENSKIY AFTER CALL WITH TRUMP: UKRAINE IS READY FOR QUICK STEPS FOR PEACE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian delegration: We will continue talks, we&apos;re satisfied with talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russian-delegration-we-will-continue-talks-were-satisfied-with-talks-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:36:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russian-delegration-we-will-continue-talks-were-satisfied-with-talks-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Each side will set out its vision for a future ceasefire, in detail&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;From what I understand, Russia asked for Ukraine unconquered territory so the question is whether Ukraine wants to keep talking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is from Axios:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;The Russian delegation demanded the complete withdrawal of the Ukrainian Armed Forces from 4 regions, and when the Ukrainians refused, ours stood up and declared that next time they would have to leave 5 (including Dnipropetrovsk)&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doesn&apos;t sound promising.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUSSIAN DELEGATION: WE WILL CONTINUE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923371624222294109#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:35:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923371624222294109#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUSSIAN DELEGATION: WE WILL CONTINUE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUSSIAN DELEGATION: SATISFIED WITH RESULTS OF TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923371571701240125#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:34:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923371571701240125#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUSSIAN DELEGATION: SATISFIED WITH RESULTS OF TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) UMEROV SAYS CEASEFIRE WAS DISCUSSED AT TALKS IN ISTANBUL

UMEROV SAYS DELEGATION DISCUSSED CONTACTS BETWEEN ZELENSKIY AND PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923370783314698712#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:31:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923370783314698712#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UMEROV SAYS CEASEFIRE WAS DISCUSSED AT TALKS IN ISTANBUL&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
UMEROV SAYS DELEGATION DISCUSSED CONTACTS BETWEEN ZELENSKIY AND PUTIN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There has only been one negative day in the S&amp;P 500 since April 21</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/there-has-only-been-one-negative-day-in-the-sp-500-since-april-21-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:09:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/there-has-only-been-one-negative-day-in-the-sp-500-since-april-21-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are up 0.2% today as today is the monthly equity and single-stock options expiration. Those who bought on April 7 are certainly feeling good about those calls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yields are coming down and that&apos;s taking away one risk from stock markets in what&apos;s been an incredible run. Trump&apos;s trip to the Middle East has also made it pleasantly quiet on the domestic front.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A gain today would be the 5th in a row and that comes on the heels of a nine-day rally that was only broken up by a small loss on May 9. There has only been one negative day since April 21.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April housing starts 1.361m vs 1.365m expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-housing-starts-1361m-vs-1365m-expected-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:30:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-housing-starts-1361m-vs-1365m-expected-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-march-housing-starts-1324m-vs-1420m-expected-20250417/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior &lt;/a&gt;month 1.324M&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style=&quot;&quot;&gt;Building permits 1.412M vs 1.450M expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li style=&quot;&quot;&gt;Prior permits 1.467M&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday&apos;s NAHB home builder sentiment &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-may-nahb-housing-market-index-34-vs-40-expected-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;reading &lt;/a&gt;matched the worst since 2022 and this week, US 30-year yields hit 5%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t see how the housing market provides any strength this year to the economy but that sector may be near a bottom.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April import prices +0.1% vs -0.4% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-import-prices-01-vs-04-expected-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-import-prices-01-vs-04-expected-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-march-import-prices-01-vs-00-expected-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior&lt;/a&gt; was -0.1% (revised to -0.4%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Export prices m/m +0.1%% vs -0.5% expected &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 0.0% (revised to +0.1%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Import prices y/y +0.1% vs +0.9% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Export prices y/y +2.0% vs +2.4% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;Higher prices for nonfuel imports more than offset lower prices for fuel imports in April.
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Trading: The Rise of Novice to Pro Traders</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/the-future-of-trading-the-rise-of-novice-to-pro-traders-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:24:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/the-future-of-trading-the-rise-of-novice-to-pro-traders-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Funded trading has become a
ubiquitous offering in the retail space, helping empower traders of all levels
of expertise. With more opportunities than ever before, many traders are opting
to join funded trading programs, necessitating the need for reliable providers.
Finance Magnates checked in with &lt;a href=&quot;https://tinyurl.com/2ucxmfja&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Axi Select&lt;/a&gt; for their take on its growing free
funded trader program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Axi group through the Axi
Select program provides funding and a structured pathway for traders to reach
their trading potential, while giving skilled traders a genuine platform to
become professional traders and forge careers. Greg Rubin- Head of Axi Select outlined
the group’s goals and program structure in an interview below. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks for taking the time to
speak with us, let’s dive right in. I think we can all agree there is no
one-size-fits-all-approach to a trading journey. What advice do you have for
novice traders just looking to enter the retail space?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consistency always trumps over big wins. Its best for new
traders to use a demo or low-risk live account to understand their edge. Nobody
needs to stop learning ever and we can all continue to do so for the rest of
our lives. We always encourage traders to treat this as a long-term
professional journey — not a get-rich-quick scheme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To this point, are there any
pitfalls or traps newer traders should be cognizant of when embarking on this
experience?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Absolutely. Some basic things stick out as recurring
tendencies and should be avoided. This includes overleveraging, chasing the
market, and ignoring risk management. Each of which can be classified as the
most common traps. Unfortunately, many new traders also fall for expensive “get
funded quick” prop schemes with unrealistic expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Axi , with the Select program, our goal is to guide
traders with structure and transparency. We also provide tools like the Edge
Score — a proprietary system that helps traders understand their strengths and
weaknesses. The better the score, the more consistent and potentially
profitable the trader becomes. It’s a long-term framework built to help traders
grow sustainably.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Empowering traders has
certainly been one of Axi Select’s core mandates. In what ways is the company
democratizing the route to becoming a professional trader?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Axi Select removes the usual barriers and engenders every
trader with the power to succeed. There are no upfront costs, no evaluation
phases, and traders keep up to 90% of their profits. We offer real capital to
real traders to trade live markets, not simulations. If you show consistency,
we back you with funding — simple as that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How does Axi Select help
mitigate or avoid inherent risks in traditional prop trading?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike many traditional prop firms, &lt;a href=&quot;https://tinyurl.com/2ucxmfja&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Axi Select&lt;/a&gt; is a capital
allocation program, backed by a regulated broker.  Traders can be assured of fund allocation and
profit payout once the program conditions are met. We don’t charge sign-up
fees, and traders trade their own strategies in live market conditions with
full transparency. It’s about alignment and sustainability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What gap does prop trading fill compared to traditional
retail trading? In what ways is Axi Select a better option for traders compared
to other firms out there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Access to capital has been the bane of retail traders. Prop
firms or capital allocation programs have since stepped in to fill that void
albeit not effectively. Axi Select gives retail traders the best of both
worlds. The benefit of a brokerage platform with access to scale funding up to
$1M and up to 90% profit payouts . All this without registration fees or
restrictive market conditions. We focus on growth , trading skill development
and support — not quick churn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what impact has Axi Select made since its launch?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’ve seen incredible momentum with thousands of traders on
the program. We have paid out over $5.6M+ since launch as profit to our
traders. Three traders have already reached the Pro-M stage — managing capital
allocations of $1 million US dollars each. And we’re just getting started!
We’ve also got a 22-yr old trader who recently made it as the 3rd
trader since launch to access up to $1M in funding. We continue to support
thousands of traders to develop real skills to harness the opportunity in the
market. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks between Ukraine and Russia in Turkey finish</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/talks-between-ukraine-and-russia-in-turkey-finish-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:23:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/talks-between-ukraine-and-russia-in-turkey-finish-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Maybe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talks seemed to wrap up too quickly for anything substantive though. We&apos;ll wait to hear more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Update: This doesn&apos;t sound promising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;A Ukrainian diplomatic source said the Russian side demanded during the meeting that the Ukrainian army withdraws from several areas inside Ukraine in return for a ceasefire.&quot;Russian demands are detached from reality and go far beyond anything that was previously discussed&quot;, the source said&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Trading Glossary: Terms Every Beginner Must Know</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/the-essential-trading-glossary-terms-every-beginner-must-know-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:19:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/the-essential-trading-glossary-terms-every-beginner-must-know-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Your Go-To
Trading Dictionary: The 2025 Edition&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether
you interpret price charts or read through market commentary, fluency in key
terms is essential for new traders as it enables them to build a robust
foundation of knowledge for sustained success in trading. Octa broker presents
this 2025-ready glossary that unites classic concepts and trending terms for
today’s markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foundational Concepts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ask / Bid PriceThe ask
price is the lowest price a seller will accept; the bid price is the highest
price a buyer is willing to pay. If you buy a financial instrument (for
example, a forex pair), you buy it at an ask price (and pay it to the seller).
If you then decide to sell it, you sell it at a bid price, which is paid by the
buyer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spread&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A spread is
the difference between the ask and bid price.A deep and liquid market (for example, EURUSD) would usually have
a narrow, or ‘tight’, spread. Conversely, markets with fewer sellers and buyers
would normally have a relatively wide, or 
‘loose,’ spread. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pip&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pip
measures a small movement in exchange rates, usually 0.0001. Example: a move
from 1.2040 to 1.2045 is five pips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leverage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leverage
lets traders control big positions with less capital. Depending on the broker’s
rules, leverage can multiply gains as well as losses.
Example: With 1:100 leverage, an account with £1,000 would be able to control a
position worth  £100,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long / Short Position&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going long means buying an asset, anticipating
that its price will rise. Going short
means selling an asset, anticipating that its price will fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lot Size&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forex trades
use standardised units called lots.
One standard lot equals 100,000 units of currency. There are also mini lots and micro lots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stop-Loss / Take-Profit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These
normally refer to pending orders on open positions to automatically close them
at pre-set levels. This is vital for risk control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CFD (Contract for Difference)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CFD is a
financial instrument that lets traders speculate on the price moves of an asset
without actually owning it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish / Bearish&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refer to
investors&apos; and/or traders’ expectations. ‘Bullish’ describes positive market
outlook and expectations for higher prices, while ‘bearish’ indicates a
negative perception and anticipation for lower prices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical Terms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Support / Resistance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A support
level is where a lot of buyers are expected to enter the market, thus
supporting the price and preventing it from falling further. Likewise, a
resistance level is where sellers are anticipated, preventing the price from
rising higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trend / Trendline&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A trend
shows overall price direction. The trend is bullish
if an asset’s price is rising, with each consecutive peak and trough higher
than the previous one. A trend is bearish
if the price is falling and each successive peak and trough is lower than the
previous one. A trend can also be sideways
or range-bound when the price is
moving within a specific trading range. Traders would normally draw trendlines to identify a trend. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moving Average (MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A moving
average calculates the average price of an asset over a specific timeframe, usually measured in candles.
Example: A 50-day MA calculates the average price over the last 50 trading
sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Candles (Candlesticks)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Visual
representations of price movements over a specific timeframe. Each candle shows
the opening, closing, high, and low prices within that period, helping traders
interpret market sentiment at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refers
to the length of time each candlestick or bar represents on a chart. It defines
how much market data is condensed into a single price unit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Example:
On a 1-hour timeframe, each candlestick
shows the price movement during one hour of trading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volatility&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measures the
extent and the speed of price moves. More volatility usually means higher risk
and greater potential reward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breakout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A breakout
happens when price smashes through support or resistance, often precipitating a
new trend in the direction of a breakout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volume&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number
of contracts, shares, or lots traded during a specific timeframe. Surging volume usually confirms strong moves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market-Related Vocabulary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liquidity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How easily
something can be bought or sold. High liquidity equals faster execution and
tighter spreads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slippage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a trade
fills at a worse price than expected or planned. This is common during
high-impact events, when the price moves very fast and ‘slips through’ the
desired price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Correction / Reversal / Retracement /
Pullback&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All describe
a pause or change in trend. Often used interchangeably, though with subtle
differences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consolidation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A phase of
sideways movement—markets catch their breath before choosing direction.
Example: Gold consolidated in August-November 2022, before turning bullish in
Q1 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trading Slang / Jargon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOMO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stands for ‘fear of missing out&apos;—a common feeling
of anxiety stemming from the fear of missing out on pleasant or rewarding
experiences. In trading, FOMO frequently refers to a trader&apos;s apprehension
about not participating in a significant upward or downward price movement,
thereby missing potential gains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HODL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Born from a
typo, now gospel in crypto circles. Means “hold on through the chaos.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pump and Dump&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An asset’s
price is deliberately pushed up, only to be quickly sold off for profit—often
seen in new, thinly traded cryptocurrencies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whipsaw&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapid price
reversals that hurt both buyers and sellers, making it difficult to spot a
sustainable trend&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bagholder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stuck
holding a crashing asset, hoping for a comeback.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rekt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trader-speak
for taking a major loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dead Cat Bounce&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A brief
recovery during a strong downtrend—often misleading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trending Terms in 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DePIN (Decentralised Physical
Infrastructure Network)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A
blockchain-based system that manages real-world infrastructure—such as wireless
networks, sensors, or energy grids—by allowing users to contribute hardware and
earn rewards for supporting the network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI Agent Trading&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI bots that
trade autonomously based on market signals, news, and historical data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gas Fees&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fees paid to
process blockchain transactions—can spike during congestion, especially on
Ethereum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learning
these terms is just the beginning of facilitating market understanding. The
more fluent traders are in the language of the markets, the quicker they adapt.
For those just starting out, it’s advised to study educational resources and
webinars from market experts—similar to those offered by global brokers like
Octa. In markets that never sleep, knowledge really is power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: Trading involves risks and may not be
suitable for all investors. Use your expertise wisely and evaluate all
associated risks before making an investment decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About Octa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.octafx.com?utm_source=media&amp;amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;amp;utm_campaign=TradingDictionary&amp;amp;utm_content=ww_fx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Octa&lt;/a&gt; is an
international broker that has been providing online trading services worldwide
since 2011. It offers commission-free access to financial markets and various
services used by clients from 180 countries who have opened more than 52
million trading accounts. To help its clients reach their investment goals,
Octa offers free educational webinars, articles, and analytical tools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company is involved in a
comprehensive network of charitable and humanitarian initiatives, including the
improvement of educational infrastructure and short-notice relief projects
supporting local communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its foundation, Octa has won
more than 100 awards, including the &apos;Most Reliable Broker Global 2024&apos; award
from Global Forex Awards and the &apos;Best Mobile Trading Platform 2024&apos; award from
Global Brand Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation expectations in the UMich report later in the day will be interesting</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/inflation-expectations-in-the-umich-report-later-in-the-day-will-be-interesting-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:02:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/inflation-expectations-in-the-umich-report-later-in-the-day-will-be-interesting-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Today we get the May&apos;s University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment report. You would expect inflation expectations to ease given the recent positive developments on the trade front right? I think that&apos;s the consensus even though we don&apos;t have consensus numbers for the inflation expectations data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What if they increase further though? That would be a surprise for me, and I think the risk of expectations having de-anchored would be high and make the Fed even more uncomfortable. The Fed has been placing a great deal on inflation expectations lately and if you expect growth to pick up in the next months, then you would also expect the central bank to be very cautious on rate cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cutting now could exacerbate higher inflation expectations and contrary to Trump&apos;s belief, long term Treasury yields would rise further. The problem for the Fed is that they haven&apos;t reached the target yet and they will now face better growth expectations, a potential surge in economic activity (the Philly Fed yesterday could have been a signal), tax cuts, deregulation and let&apos;s not forget that we still end up with 10% tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To sum up, there&apos;s a risk that an increase in inflation expectations could trigger a hawkish repricing in interest rates expectations and that will have a repercussion on different asset classes. The more straightforward reaction to a hawkish repricing would be long USD and short long term Treasuries. But I can see also a pullback in the stock market as the positioning is getting overstretched. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive European FX news wrap: Major currencies little changed, gold falls back</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-major-currencies-little-changed-gold-falls-back-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:45:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-major-currencies-little-changed-gold-falls-back-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Headlines:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-us-officials-will-send-letters-out-soon-to-countries-for-trade-deals-20250516/&quot;&gt;Trump says US officials will send letters out soon to countries for trade deals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-trade-truce-should-be-extended-says-global-times-20250516/&quot;&gt;US-China trade truce should be extended, says Global Times&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-delegation-to-visit-us-next-week-for-further-tariff-negotiations-20250516/&quot;&gt;South Korea delegation to visit US next week for further tariff negotiations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-says-there-is-possibility-trade-deal-might-come-after-8-july-deadline-20250516/&quot;&gt;South Korea says there is possibility trade deal might come after 8 July deadline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-interest-rates-expectations-after-this-weeks-events-and-data-20250516/&quot;&gt;What are the interest rates expectations after this week&apos;s events and data?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-bostic-sees-just-one-rate-cuts-this-year-amid-uncertainty-20250516/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Bostic sees just one rate cut this year amid uncertainty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-villeroy-we-are-not-currently-in-a-currency-war-but-rather-a-trade-war-situation-20250516/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Villeroy: We are not currently in a currency war but rather a trade war situation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-kazks-meeting-by-meeting-approach-is-right-20250516/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Kazāks: Meeting-by-meeting approach is right&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/snbs-schlegel-switzerland-is-not-a-currency-manipulator-20250516/&quot;&gt;SNB&apos;s Schlegel: Switzerland is not a currency manipulator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bojs-nakamura-us-tariffs-policy-pose-greater-uncertainties-serious-challenges-for-japan-20250516/&quot;&gt;BOJ&apos;s Nakamura: US tariffs policy pose greater uncertainties, serious challenges for Japan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-final-cpi-19-vs-20-yy-prelim-20250516/&quot;&gt;Italy April final CPI +1.9% vs +2.0% y/y prelim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-march-trade-balance-368-billion-vs-240-billion-prior-20250516/&quot;&gt;Eurozone March trade balance €36.8 billion vs €24.0 billion prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/barclays-no-longer-expects-a-us-recession-in-the-second-half-of-the-year-20250516/&quot;&gt;Barclays no longer expects a US recession in the second half of the year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;NZD leads, CHF lags on the day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;European equities higher; S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up 0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields down 5.7 bps to 4.398%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold down 2.0% to $3,175.20&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude up 0.3% to $61.80&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin up 0.2% to $103,712&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It was a quiet session for the most part as markets continue to digest the reprieve on the trade front, with Trump wrapping up his visit to the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There weren&apos;t much meaningful headlines, at least not major ones, and so that is seeing broader markets stick to the theme for much of the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar is trading more sideways for once at least, keeping little changed against the likes of the euro and the yen. EUR/USD is sticking closer to the 1.1200 mark, with large option expiries at the figure level creating a magnet for price action. Meanwhile, USD/JPY did ease to test the 145.00 mark but is now holding little changed near 145.60 on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Elsewhere, the dollar isn&apos;t doing too much as well. USD/CHF is up 0.1% to 0.8368 and USD/CAD nearly flat at 1.3961 on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This comes despite equities holding some light gains during the session. US futures were flattish initially but are now slightly higher as investors look to end a good week on a positive note. The same goes for European indices, which are holding modest gains on the session thus far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides that, we are seeing bond yields come off a little on the day with 10-year yields easing back to around 4.40% and 30-year yields back under 4.90% to 4.86% currently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the commodities space, gold is running into another round of selling after a minor bounce yesterday. The precious metal is down 2% to $3,175 with the drop now erasing the advance from the day before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I&apos;m gonna be off for a little break next week. I wish everyone a wonderful weekend and I&apos;ll catch you guys again in just over a week. Stay safe and have a good one.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNB&apos;s Schlegel: Switzerland is not a currency manipulator</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snbs-schlegel-switzerland-is-not-a-currency-manipulator-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snbs-schlegel-switzerland-is-not-a-currency-manipulator-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Switzerland is not a currency manipulator.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have only acted to dampen the overvaluation of the Franc which threatened price stability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Currency market interventions are not about gaining a competitive advantage for Switzerland.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technical experts in the US understand the Swiss position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;More:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cannot rule out that negative rates could be a necessary instrument in the future.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;National bank does not like negative rates.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a couple of remarks on currency intervention. The SNB and the BoJ are the two most active ones among the major central banks in currency interventions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A currency manipulator though is a country that deliberately influences the exchange rate of its currency to gain unfair advantages in international trade. That&apos;s not the case for the SNB and the BoJ. They care about the impact on price stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The part on negative rates is not new. We&apos;ve heard those same comments for months.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYCServers Expands London Infrastructure with LD4 Launch, Enhancing Forex VPS</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/nycservers-expands-london-infrastructure-with-ld4-launch-enhancing-forex-vps-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:45:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/nycservers-expands-london-infrastructure-with-ld4-launch-enhancing-forex-vps-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;NewYorkCityServers, a leading provider of
performance-optimized &lt;a href=&quot;https://newyorkcityservers.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Forex VPS&lt;/a&gt; hosting,
has announced the expansion of its global infrastructure with the deployment of
new hardware inside the LD4 datacenter in London. This move marks a significant
step forward in providing ultra-low latency connectivity for traders operating
across Europe and global markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The LD4 facility, located just outside London, is
considered one of the most important financial data centers in the world —
hosting infrastructure for top-tier liquidity providers, brokers, and
exchanges. By launching a dedicated presence within LD4, NYCServers is now able
to offer direct cross-connect proximity to many of the largest forex brokers,
reducing latency to less than single-digit milliseconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“London remains a critical hub for the FX ecosystem,” said
Nick Esposito, founder of NYCServers. “With LD4, we’re putting our clients
right where the action happens — next to the execution engines of their
brokers. It’s a game-changer for traders who care about speed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Built for Serious Traders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new London infrastructure is powered by the same
high-performance infrastructure NYCServers is known for: AMD Ryzen 7950X CPUs,
fast NVMe storage, and virtualized environments tuned specifically for trading
platforms like MetaTrader 4 and MetaTrader 5. Combined with optimized routing
and premium bandwidth providers, clients can expect robust performance and
minimal latency regardless of market volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the company&apos;s New York location (located in NY4)
continues to serve North American traders with outstanding connectivity, the
LD4 deployment ensures that European clients — or those trading with brokers
hosted in London — can now benefit from an equally optimized experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This expansion is especially relevant for clients trading
with brokers such as Tickmill, Blueberry Markets, KeyToMarkets, FTMO, and other
firms that maintain infrastructure within LD4. With direct peering and no
unnecessary network hops, the time between order submission and execution is
reduced to its bare minimum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is a Forex VPS?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Forex VPS (Virtual Private Server) is a dedicated virtual
environment specifically optimized to run trading platforms 24/7 with
consistent uptime, fast execution, and minimal delays. It allows traders to
deploy Expert Advisors (EAs), custom indicators, and automated strategies
without relying on their local internet connection or hardware.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For serious retail traders, especially those who trade with
automation or during volatile news events, hosting MetaTrader platforms on a
Forex VPS can provide a significant edge. Reduced latency means better order
fills, lower slippage, and faster reaction times to market movements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NYCServers’ Forex VPS offerings are particularly suited for
this purpose. With years of experience and thousands of active clients, the
company continues to refine its infrastructure to meet the demands of modern
traders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why LD4 Matters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latency — the time it takes for an order to travel from the
trader’s platform to the broker’s server — can have a measurable impact on
execution quality. In high-speed forex environments, even a few milliseconds
can determine whether an order is filled at the expected price or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LD4 is home to many of the world’s most active brokers and
liquidity providers. Hosting your trading platform in the same facility as your
broker removes unnecessary geographic distance and improves the speed of
execution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With this launch, NYCServers clients now have the ability
to deploy VPS instances in either LD4 or NY4 — depending on their broker’s
location and trading needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Broker-Focused Integration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of NYCServers’ key advantages is its broker-focused
approach. The company partners with multiple forex brokerages to offer
sponsored or discounted VPS plans to eligible clients. These partnerships often
allow traders to receive free or reduced-cost hosting when they meet minimum
trading volume requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This LD4 expansion is expected to deepen those
relationships, enabling brokers in London to offer their clients faster, more
stable VPS services without needing to build their own infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Many of our broker partners want to ensure their clients
have access to fast, reliable VPS hosting — especially those using EAs or
scalping strategies,” said Esposito. “Our LD4 expansion gives them a reliable
solution right where they need it most.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Client-Controlled,
Broker-Ready&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NYCServers offers a streamlined deployment experience
tailored for forex traders. Clients can launch their VPS with MetaTrader 4 or 5
pre-installed — already configured with their preferred broker — dramatically
reducing setup time and allowing them to start trading in minutes. With support
for over 100 brokers available for instant deployment, the process is designed
for speed, simplicity, and compatibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each VPS includes full administrator access, a dedicated
public IP address, and flexible server locations — including New York (NY4) and
London (LD4) — so traders can choose the datacenter closest to their broker for
optimal latency. A built-in latency checker is also available on the NYCServers
website to help clients identify the fastest connection for their trading
setup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Built for the Future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As algorithmic strategies, prop firm challenges, and
time-sensitive trading models become more widespread, low-latency
infrastructure is no longer optional — it’s essential. NYCServers is meeting
that demand head-on by continuing to invest in enterprise-grade hardware,
optimized routing, and strategic datacenter placement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With LD4 now live alongside its established NY4 presence,
NYCServers is focused on delivering best-in-class performance where traders
need it most — and is actively exploring new opportunities to bring its
infrastructure even closer to the global trading community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our mission is to give traders a competitive edge —
wherever they’re located,” said Nick Esposito. “This isn’t just about servers.
It’s about giving our clients the speed, reliability, and proximity they need
to perform at the highest level.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About NYCServers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2012, NYCServers specializes in premium hosting
for traders. Its Forex VPS infrastructure is trusted by thousands of clients
around the world, including retail traders, prop firms, and institutional
partners. With a focus on performance, uptime, and support, the company
continues to be a go-to provider for those seeking execution speed without
compromise.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Ukraine talks in Istanbul set to begin shortly</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-ukraine-talks-in-istanbul-set-to-begin-shortly-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:30:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-ukraine-talks-in-istanbul-set-to-begin-shortly-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, that&apos;s a long enough delay. The talks were supposed to begin at around 0900 GMT. But earlier, Russia&apos;s Medinsky had talks on the side with the US before this. There were also some alleged pushback as seen &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-demands-that-talks-with-ukraine-take-place-without-us-turkish-representatives-20250516/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but at least now we&apos;re starting to get this over and done with.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the interest rates expectations after this week&apos;s events and data?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-interest-rates-expectations-after-this-weeks-events-and-data-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-interest-rates-expectations-after-this-weeks-events-and-data-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 56 bps (92% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 52 bps (91% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 47 bps (89% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 47 bps (64% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 77 bps (98% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 60 bps (76% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 44 bps (83% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;*for the SNB, the rest of the probability is for a 50 bps cut&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 16 bps (98% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia demands that talks with Ukraine take place without US, Turkish representatives</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-demands-that-talks-with-ukraine-take-place-without-us-turkish-representatives-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-demands-that-talks-with-ukraine-take-place-without-us-turkish-representatives-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Ukraine is meanwhile not too happy about said demand, saying that it is a sign that Russia is undermining peace efforts by putting forward demands and conditions. It&apos;s all falling apart before it even begins, which is not surprising after Putin&apos;s no-show. The talks were supposedly to have started at 0900 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
