<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>India Launches Missile Strikes on Alleged Terror Camps in Pakistan</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-launches-missile-strikes-on-alleged-terror-camps-in-pakistan-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:58:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-launches-missile-strikes-on-alleged-terror-camps-in-pakistan-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;72&quot; data-end=&quot;401&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;India has confirmed carrying out missile strikes on what it described as terrorist camps across the border in Pakistan, including areas in Pakistan-occupied Jammu and Kashmir. According to the Indian government, the operation targeted nine sites and was executed with &quot;considerable restraint&quot; in both target selection and method.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;403&quot; data-end=&quot;665&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Pakistani security officials reported that missiles were fired into three locations along the border. The strikes mark a significant escalation in cross-border tensions, though India has framed the operation as a limited and precise response to security threats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;403&quot; data-end=&quot;665&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;403&quot; data-end=&quot;665&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The missile strikes carried out by India, were a response to a deadly terrorist attack that occurred two weeks earlier in the town of Pahalgam, located in Indian-administered Kashmir. On April 22, gunmen opened fire on a group of Hindu tourists, resulting in the deaths of 26 individuals and injuring several others. The Resistance Front, a militant group believed to be linked to Pakistan-based Lashkar-e-Taiba, claimed responsibility for the attack. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;403&quot; data-end=&quot;665&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;India accused Pakistan&apos;s military and intelligence services of orchestrating the massacre, an allegation that Islamabad has vehemently denied. In the aftermath, India undertook a series of retaliatory measures, including suspending the Indus Waters Treaty, expelling Pakistani diplomats, halting bilateral trade, and closing the Attari-Wagah border crossing. These actions significantly escalated tensions between the two nuclear-armed neighbors and set the stage for the subsequent missile strikes.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIA GOVT ON PRECISION STRIKE: INDIA HAS DEMONSTRATED CONSIDERABLE RESTRAINT IN SELECTION OF TARGETS AND METHOD OF EXECUTION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919856130756399349#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919856130756399349#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIA GOVT ON PRECISION STRIKE: INDIA HAS DEMONSTRATED CONSIDERABLE RESTRAINT IN SELECTION OF TARGETS AND METHOD OF EXECUTION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: US dollar slumps as trade deals remain stuck</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-us-dollar-slumps-as-trade-deals-remain-stuck-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:41:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-us-dollar-slumps-as-trade-deals-remain-stuck-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/merz-confirmed-in-second-parliamentary-vote-20250506/&quot;&gt;Merz confirmed in second parliamentary vote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-and-carney-talk-to-the-press-canada-chose-a-talented-person-20250506/&quot;&gt;Trump and Carney talk to the press: We will possibly start to renegotiate USMCA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-takes-the-first-trump-carney-meeting-in-stride-discussions-were-constructive-20250506/&quot;&gt;USD/CAD takes the first Trump-Carney meeting in stride. Discussions were &apos;constructive&apos;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-the-only-question-for-carney-is-why-the-us-is-subsidizing-canada-20250506/&quot;&gt;Trump: The only question for Carney is why the US is subsidizing Canada&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-march-international-trade-balance-1405b-vs-1370b-expected-20250506/&quot;&gt;US March international trade balance -140.5B vs -137.0B expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-auctions-off-42-billion-of-tenure-notes-at-a-high-yield-of-4342-20250506/&quot;&gt;US treasury auctions off $42 billion of 10 year notes at a high yield of 4.342%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-22-versus-11-previously-20250506/&quot;&gt;Atlanta Fed GDPNow 2.2% versus 1.1% previously&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-touts-very-good-offers-on-trade-again-market-yawns-and-sells-the-us-dollar-20250506/&quot;&gt;Bessent touts &apos;very good offers&apos; on trade again, market yawns and sells the US dollar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-announces-a-big-trade-deal-but-not-with-the-country-expected-20250506/&quot;&gt;India announces a big trade deal... but not with the country expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-trade-balance-canada-trade-balance-for-march-c-051b-vs-156b-estimate-20250506/&quot;&gt;Canada trade balance Canada trade balance for March (C$) -0.51B vs -1.56B estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/april-canada-ivey-pmi-479-vs-513-prior-20250506/&quot;&gt;April Canada Ivey PMI 47.9 vs 51.3 prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold up $89 to $3423&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude oil up $1.98 to $59.12&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields down 3.7 bps to 4.31%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 down 0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;JPY leads, USD lags&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market is getting increasingly anxious about the lack of US trade deals or even any real parameters about what&apos;s coming. We did get a fresh leak today about the UK but it appears to be limited to autos and steel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I would highlight two comments that add to the apprehension about the path of the trade war:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bessent said they weren&apos;t talking with China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump in his meeting with Carney indicated that the US will dictate trade deals to others&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;To balance that, Trump talked about the importance of a friendly relationship with Canada so it all wasn&apos;t bad news. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In any case, the US dollar was steadily sold and there was a massive bid in gold, both highlighting mounting worries about the trade war. Some of the dollar weakness could be position squaring ahead of the Fed tomorrow but I don&apos;t see much of a scope for a big dovish shift.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late in the day, we&apos;re getting some Indian strikes on Pakistan and with one nuclear-armed country shooting at another, that could further add to gold and yen bids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of market moves, AUD/USD is flirting with 0.6500 for the first time this year as its sharp comeback from the Liberation Day lows continues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The euro got some bids as Merz made it though on the second vote but it was a fleeting pop, as it as widely expected. The euro did manage to string together a nice gain but it was largely in line with GBP and the overall USD move.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: LOOKING AT A LOT OF COUNTRIES FOR TRADE DEALS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919854324131287198#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:38:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919854324131287198#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: LOOKING AT A LOT OF COUNTRIES FOR TRADE DEALS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PAKISTAN SECURITY SOURCE SAYS AT LEAST ONE CHILD KILLED IN ATTACK AND TWO INJURED NEAR BAHAWALPUR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919854187698913765#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:38:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919854187698913765#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAKISTAN SECURITY SOURCE SAYS AT LEAST ONE CHILD KILLED IN ATTACK AND TWO INJURED NEAR BAHAWALPUR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: HAVEN&apos;T CALLED CARNEY GOVERNOR YET AND MAYBE I WON&apos;T; HAD A LOT OF FUN WITH TRUDEAU</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919854093704552946#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:37:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919854093704552946#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: HAVEN&apos;T CALLED CARNEY GOVERNOR YET AND MAYBE I WON&apos;T; HAD A LOT OF FUN WITH TRUDEAU&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil: private survey of inventory shows headline crude oil draw larger than expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-private-survey-of-inventory-shows-headline-crude-oil-draw-larger-than-expected-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:36:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-private-survey-of-inventory-shows-headline-crude-oil-draw-larger-than-expected-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Via twitter:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expectations I had seen centred on:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;Headline crude -2.5mn barrels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;Distillates -2.7mn bbls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;Gasoline -1.5 mn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;This data point is from a privately-conducted survey by the American Petroleum Institute (API).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s a survey of oil storage facilities and companies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The official report is due Wednesday morning US time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two reports are quite different.The official government data comes from the US Energy Information Administration (EIA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Its based on data from the Department of Energy and other government agencies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;Whereas information on total crude oil storage levels and variations from the previous week&apos;s levels are both provided by the API report, the EIA report also provides statistics on inputs and outputs from refineries, as well as other significant indicators of the status of the oil market, and storage levels for various grades of crude oil, such as light, medium, and heavy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;the EIA report is held to be more accurate and comprehensive than the survey from the API&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIAN ARMY SAYS IN POST ON X &quot; JUSTICE IS SERVED&quot; AFTER INDIA LAUNCHES ATTACK ON SITES IN PAKISTAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919852885946286455#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:32:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919852885946286455#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIAN ARMY SAYS IN POST ON X &quot; JUSTICE IS SERVED&quot; AFTER INDIA LAUNCHES ATTACK ON SITES IN PAKISTAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: HAD GREAT MEETING WITH CARNEY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919852263796867494#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:30:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919852263796867494#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: HAD GREAT MEETING WITH CARNEY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI - China press conference Wednesday - PBOC, securities regulator, financial regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-china-press-conference-wednesday-pboc-securities-regulator-financial-regulator-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:26:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-china-press-conference-wednesday-pboc-securities-regulator-financial-regulator-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;ForexLive had the news of the China government notice issued Tuesday post earlier. A reminder or an ICYMI:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Officials from the People’s Bank of China, the National Financial Regulatory Administration and the China Securities Regulatory Commission will speak at 9 am local time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; about “a financial policy package to stabilize market and expectations&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;9 am China time is 0100 GMT and 2100 US Eastern time (Tuesday evening).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep your expectations low and avoid disappointment. Announcements like this have been of piecemeal stimulus efforts for more than a year. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INTENSE SHELLING, LOUD EXPLOSIONS HEARD IN TWO BORDER AREAS OF INDIAN KASHMIR - POLICE OFFICER, WITNESSES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919850667205624037#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:24:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919850667205624037#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INTENSE SHELLING, LOUD EXPLOSIONS HEARD IN TWO BORDER AREAS OF INDIAN KASHMIR - POLICE OFFICER, WITNESSES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIA GOVT: NINE SITES TARGETED AS PART OF ‘OPERATION SINDOOR’

INDIA GOVT: &quot;OUR ACTIONS HAVE BEEN FOCUSED, MEASURED AND NON-ESCALATORY IN NATURE&quot;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919850038068424707#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:21:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919850038068424707#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIA GOVT: NINE SITES TARGETED AS PART OF ‘OPERATION SINDOOR’&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
INDIA GOVT: &quot;OUR ACTIONS HAVE BEEN FOCUSED, MEASURED AND NON-ESCALATORY IN NATURE&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) THE INDIAN ARMED FORCES LAUNCHED ‘OPERATION SINDOOR’, HITTING TERRORIST INFRASTRUCTURE IN PAKISTAN AND PAKISTAN-OCCUPIED JAMMU AND KASHMIR -STATEMENT

NO PAKISTANI MILITARY FACILITIES HAVE BEEN TARGETED-STATEMENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919849363095818591#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:18:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919849363095818591#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE INDIAN ARMED FORCES LAUNCHED ‘OPERATION SINDOOR’, HITTING TERRORIST INFRASTRUCTURE IN PAKISTAN AND PAKISTAN-OCCUPIED JAMMU AND KASHMIR -STATEMENT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
NO PAKISTANI MILITARY FACILITIES HAVE BEEN TARGETED-STATEMENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PAKISTAN INTERNATIONAL AIRLINES SPOKESPERSON SAYS FLIGHTS ALREADY AIRBORNE HAVE BEEN DIVERTED TO KARACHI</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919848968600646071#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:17:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919848968600646071#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAKISTAN INTERNATIONAL AIRLINES SPOKESPERSON SAYS FLIGHTS ALREADY AIRBORNE HAVE BEEN DIVERTED TO KARACHI&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PAKISTAN WILL RESPOND TO ATTACKS BY INDIA - PAKISTAN MILITARY SPOKESMAN TELLS ARY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919848772533620815#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:16:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919848772533620815#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAKISTAN WILL RESPOND TO ATTACKS BY INDIA - PAKISTAN MILITARY SPOKESMAN TELLS ARY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919847556755951709#m&quot;&gt;localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919847556755951709#m&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SOME TIME AGO, INDIA ATTACKED PAKISTAN IN THREE LOCATIONS WITH MISSILES - PAKISTAN MILITARY SPOKESMAN TELLS ARY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919847556755951709#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:11:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919847556755951709#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SOME TIME AGO, INDIA ATTACKED PAKISTAN IN THREE LOCATIONS WITH MISSILES - PAKISTAN MILITARY SPOKESMAN TELLS ARY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P closes lower for the second consecutive day</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-closes-lower-for-the-second-consecutive-day-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:03:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-closes-lower-for-the-second-consecutive-day-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The S&amp;amp;P index is closing lower for the second consecutive day. That comes after nine straight days of gains. The NASDAQ and Dow industrial average also fell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A snapshot of the closing levels shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average -390.83 or -0.95% at 40829.00.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index -43.52 points or -0.77% at 5606.86&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index -154.58 points or -0.87% at 17689.66.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The small-cap Russell 2000 fell -21.07 points or -1.05% at 1983.18.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic calendar in Asia Wednesday, May 7, 2025 - New Zealand jobs report for Q1</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/economic-calendar-in-asia-wednesday-may-7-2025-new-zealand-jobs-report-for-q1-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:00:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/economic-calendar-in-asia-wednesday-may-7-2025-new-zealand-jobs-report-for-q1-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The employment data from New Zealand is for the January - March quarter. The unemployment rate is expected to have risen. The Reserve Bank of New Zealand is on a likely continued rate cut course. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior to the data the Reserve Bank of New Zealand will publish its Financial Stabilty Report - there will be a media conference related to this, I&apos;ll post headline comments of relevance to traders. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The times in the left-most column are GMT.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The numbers in the right-most column are the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month/quarter as the case may be) result. The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I’ve noted data for New Zealand and Australia with text as the similarity of the little flags can sometimes be confusing.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade ideas thread - Wednesday, 7 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-wednesday-7-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:00:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-wednesday-7-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Good morning, afternoon and evening all. Any charts, technical analysis, trade ideas, thoughts, views, ForexLive traders would like to share and discuss with fellow ForexLive traders, please do so:
 &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CANADA PM CARNEY: THERE WERE NO DECISIONS ON TARIFFS TODAY

*CARNEY: US, CANADA BOTH WANT TO MOVE FORWARD WITH TRADE TALKS

*CARNEY:   IT’S A VERY COMPLEX SITUATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919838595902308811#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:36:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919838595902308811#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CANADA PM CARNEY: THERE WERE NO DECISIONS ON TARIFFS TODAY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*CARNEY: US, CANADA BOTH WANT TO MOVE FORWARD WITH TRADE TALKS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*CARNEY:   IT’S A VERY COMPLEX SITUATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD/CAD takes the first Trump-Carney meeting in stride. Discussions were &apos;constructive&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-takes-the-first-trump-carney-meeting-in-stride-discussions-were-constructive-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:33:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-takes-the-first-trump-carney-meeting-in-stride-discussions-were-constructive-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Carney didn&apos;t get &quot;Zelensky&apos;d&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That bar for today&apos;s meeting between the North American leaders was to avoid a meltdown and as the picture above shows, it went well enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Canadian PM is out with a readout now and said discussions were &apos;constructive&apos; and &apos;wide ranging&apos; and agreed to discuss more and have a meeting at the G7. Those are mostly coded words and not exactly great ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are a CAD bull, you would have hoped for some positive talk about a reset and a North American bloc but that wasn&apos;t really the case. If you are a CAD bear, you would have hoped for a damaging breakdown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither of those things happened so it looks like the status quo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I think we established a good basis today,&quot; Carney said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the bigger picture today, the US dollar is selling off broadly and that has USD/CAD down 56 pips to 1.3769. The broader market is starting to worry about the lack of progress on trade deals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I fear that a nine-day stock market rally has emboldened Trump to push harder on tariffs and that&apos;s going to make trade deals with allies a very tough proposition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More from Carney:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There were no decisions on tariffs today&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It is a very complex situation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I was clear with Trump that Canada will never be for sale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We made progress, had very comprehensive, tangible exchanges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There will be meetings between ministers and officials&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Progress would not necessarily be evident during negotiations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is the point at which serious discussion begins&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Asked Trump to stop calling Canada the 51st state today&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD knocking on the 0.6500 target level.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-knocking-on-06500-level-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:33:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-knocking-on-06500-level-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The AUDUSD found support today at 0.6437, holding within a key swing area between 0.6427 and 0.6442. The rebound during the early U.S. session lifted the pair back above its 200-day moving average at 0.64608. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The price is now testing the psychologically important and natural resistance target at the 0.6500 level, with additional resistance at an early December 2024 swing high of 0.6504. A sustained move above this zone would distance the pair from its 200-day moving average and could trigger further upside momentum. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next targets come between 0.65357 and 0.65537. The 61.8% retracement of the move down from the September 2024 high is at 0.65486 which is within that swing area.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earnings after the close include Super Microcomputers, AMD, Rivian</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/earnings-after-the-close-include-super-microcomputers-amd-rivian-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:08:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/earnings-after-the-close-include-super-microcomputers-amd-rivian-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The major US indices remain in negative territory for the second consecutive day. The S&amp;amp;P snapped its nine day win streak yesterday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A snapshot of the market currently shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average -296.55 points or -0.72% at 40922.98.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index -25.78 points or -0.46% at 5624.64.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index -92.57 points or -0.52% at 17752.38.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both the S&amp;amp;P and the NASDAQ indices have been able to stay above their 50-hour moving average. The current rising 50 hour moving average for the S&amp;amp;P is at 5592.28 and for the NASDAQ index, 17607.38. Staying above those levels keeps the buyers and firm control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earnings after the close include supermicro computer. Recall from last week they lowered their estimates for EPS and revenue. AMD and Ruby and will also report after the close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow morning, Uber, Walt Disney, Unity Software will be announcing before the open:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the rest of the week:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;267&quot; data-end=&quot;287&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Wednesday (May 8)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;267&quot; data-end=&quot;287&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;After the Close:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;288&quot; data-end=&quot;436&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;288&quot; data-end=&quot;298&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;290&quot; data-end=&quot;298&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Applovin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;299&quot; data-end=&quot;308&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;301&quot; data-end=&quot;308&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Carvana&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;309&quot; data-end=&quot;323&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;311&quot; data-end=&quot;323&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Arm Holdings&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;324&quot; data-end=&quot;342&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;326&quot; data-end=&quot;342&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Cleveland-Cliffs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;350&quot; data-end=&quot;360&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;352&quot; data-end=&quot;360&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;DoorDash&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;361&quot; data-end=&quot;373&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;363&quot; data-end=&quot;373&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dutch Bros&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;443&quot; data-end=&quot;467&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Thursday (May 9)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;468&quot; data-end=&quot;488&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Before the Open:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;489&quot; data-end=&quot;630&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;489&quot; data-end=&quot;498&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;491&quot; data-end=&quot;498&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Peloton&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;499&quot; data-end=&quot;508&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;501&quot; data-end=&quot;508&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Shopify&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;509&quot; data-end=&quot;525&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;511&quot; data-end=&quot;525&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;ConocoPhillips&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;526&quot; data-end=&quot;534&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;528&quot; data-end=&quot;534&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Warner Bros. Discovery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;605&quot; data-end=&quot;612&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;607&quot; data-end=&quot;612&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Crocs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;632&quot; data-end=&quot;652&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;After the Close:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;653&quot; data-end=&quot;785&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;653&quot; data-end=&quot;669&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;655&quot; data-end=&quot;669&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Trade Desk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;670&quot; data-end=&quot;680&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;672&quot; data-end=&quot;680&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Coinbase&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SENIOR CANADIAN GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL: TRUMP ASKED CARNEY’S OPINION ON CHINA, UKRAINE AND RUSSIA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919831554743775580#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:08:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919831554743775580#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SENIOR CANADIAN GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL: TRUMP ASKED CARNEY’S OPINION ON CHINA, UKRAINE AND RUSSIA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SENIOR CANADIAN GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL: CARNEY&apos;S LUNCH WITH TRUMP WAS CONSTRUCTIVE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919831445150773335#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:07:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919831445150773335#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SENIOR CANADIAN GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL: CARNEY&apos;S LUNCH WITH TRUMP WAS CONSTRUCTIVE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US CALLS FOR INDIA, PAKISTAN TO REACH &apos;RESPONSIBLE RESOLUTION&apos;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919829136345899137#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:58:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919829136345899137#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US CALLS FOR INDIA, PAKISTAN TO REACH &apos;RESPONSIBLE RESOLUTION&apos;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil futures settles at $59.09</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-futures-cell-at-5909-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:43:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-futures-cell-at-5909-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Crude oil futures are settling at $59.09. That&apos;s up $1.96 or 3.43%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;75&quot; data-end=&quot;327&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the hourly chart, today’s rally stalled at $59.79—just shy of the falling 200-hour moving average at $60.01 and the 50% retracement of the April 23 to May 4 decline at $60.08. A break above both those levels is needed to strengthen the bullish bias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;329&quot; data-end=&quot;566&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, the price is hovering near the broken 38.2% retracement at $58.96. A move back below that level would open the door for further downside probing, with the 100-hour moving average at $58.06 as the next target for sellers.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US and UK close to trade agreement - report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-and-uk-close-to-trade-agreement-report-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-and-uk-close-to-trade-agreement-report-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The FT &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ft.com/content/ca3837bb-34e3-4e15-b4e6-f4c927a3af5a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;reports &lt;/a&gt;that the US and UK are close to a trade agreement that would lower UK quotas on cars and steel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The agreement would include lower-tariff quotas for UK steel and car exports to the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; The UK is hoping to secure reductions in the sector specific 25% tariffs that Trump has levied on steel and autos&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The UK&apos;s concessions include changes to digital services tax, cuts on US auto export tariffs, and reduced tariffs on US agricultural products&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The UK refuses to accept US food production standards like chlorine-washed chicken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK industries, especially luxury car brands like Bentley and Jaguar Land Rover, are facing &quot;severe&quot; impacts from the current tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This report is short on the critical question: What tariffs will the US continue to charge the UK? The UK overall is facing a 10% rate but also 25% of autos and steel. This appears to deal with only the latter two but it&apos;s short on details. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looked last week like a deal with India was coming but now it looks like the UK could be first out of the gate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, the market reaction here has been very muted, even in GBP/USD.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US-UK DEAL SET TO BE SIGNED THIS WEEK: FT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919815230978154965#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919815230978154965#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US-UK DEAL SET TO BE SIGNED THIS WEEK: FT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919815019954401707#m&quot;&gt;localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919815019954401707#m&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *UK AND US CLOSE TO TRADE PACT WITH LOWER TARIFFS: FT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919815019954401707#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919815019954401707#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*UK AND US CLOSE TO TRADE PACT WITH LOWER TARIFFS: FT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *SUPREME COURT LETS TRUMP DISCHARGE TRANSGENDER SERVICEMEMBERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919814867671728539#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919814867671728539#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*SUPREME COURT LETS TRUMP DISCHARGE TRANSGENDER SERVICEMEMBERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PAKISTAN WILL DESTROY IF INDIA BUILDS ANYTHING TO STOP WATER 

PAKISTAN, INDIA CLASH IS “IMMINENT&apos; SAYS PAKISTAN DEFENSE MINISTER KHAWAJA ASIF</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919809337398079556#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:39:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919809337398079556#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAKISTAN WILL DESTROY IF INDIA BUILDS ANYTHING TO STOP WATER &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
PAKISTAN, INDIA CLASH IS “IMMINENT&apos; SAYS PAKISTAN DEFENSE MINISTER KHAWAJA ASIF&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold surges for the second day as it climbs $80. What&apos;s driving the move</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-surges-for-the-second-day-as-it-climbs-80-whats-driving-the-move-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:26:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-surges-for-the-second-day-as-it-climbs-80-whats-driving-the-move-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The gold buyers are back in a big way following the holiday in China and other parts of Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold surged yesterday and traced out an outside bullish reversal. That pattern extended today in a powerful signal for gold buyers. If we close here it will be the second-best closing level ever and just $10 from the closing record on April 21.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big level though is $3500, which is where gold stalled on April 22. That was followed by a heavy round of profit taking that coincided with optimism about US trade deals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lately though, progress appears to have stalled. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent today confirmed that the US and China aren&apos;t talking. He continued to tease other trade deals but the market is at the point where it wants to see less talk and more signed papers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump today said he&apos;s tired of questions about when deals would be struck and &quot;we&apos;re going to put down the price the people are going to have to pay to shop in the United States.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;whitespace-pre-wrap break-words&quot;&gt;&quot;We&apos;re going to put very fair numbers down, and we&apos;re going to say, here&apos;s – what this country, what we want. And congratulations, we have a deal. And they&apos;ll either say &apos;great,&apos; and they&apos;ll start shopping, or they&apos;ll say, not good,&apos;&quot; Trump said alongside Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;whitespace-pre-wrap break-words&quot;&gt;&quot;It&apos;s going to be a very fair number, it&apos;ll be a low number. We&apos;re not looking to hurt countries,&quot; he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;whitespace-pre-wrap break-words&quot;&gt;This all sounds like improvisation and Trump has likely been emboldened by the bounce back in stock markets.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US treasury auctions off $42 billion of 10 year notes at a high yield of 4.342%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-auctions-off-42-billion-of-tenure-notes-at-a-high-yield-of-4342-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:03:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-auctions-off-42-billion-of-tenure-notes-at-a-high-yield-of-4342-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High yield 4.342%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;WI yield before the auction 4.354%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tail -1.2 basis points vs six-month average of 0.7 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bid to cover 2.60x versus the six-month average of 2.59X&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Direct 19.88% vs the six-month average of 16.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Indirects 71.2% vs six-month average of 70.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dealers 8.93% versus the six-month average of 13.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUCTION GRADE: A&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Domestic buyers were higher than the average. International buyers are also higher than the average. The dealers therefore were saddled with less than average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US 10 year yield is now trading near loss for the day at 4.321% down 2.1 basis points&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed GDPNow 2.2% versus 1.1% previously</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-22-versus-11-previously-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:58:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-22-versus-11-previously-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The GDPNow growht estimate for the Q2 rose to 2.2% from 1.1% prior. In their own words:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;The GDPNow model estimate for real GDP growth (seasonally adjusted annual rate) in the second quarter of 2025 is 2.2 percent on May 6, up from 1.1 percent on May 1. After recent releases from the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, the US Census Bureau, and the US Bureau of Economic Analysis, the nowcasts of second-quarter real personal consumption expenditures growth and real private fixed investment growth increased from 1.9 percent and 1.3 percent, respectively, to 3.3 percent and 3.6 percent.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next GDPNow update is Thursday, May 8. Please see the &quot;Release Dates&quot; tab below for a list of upcoming releases.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Carney talk to the press: We will possibly start to renegotiate USMCA</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-and-carney-talk-to-the-press-canada-chose-a-talented-person-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:10:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-and-carney-talk-to-the-press-canada-chose-a-talented-person-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Canada chose a talented person&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oval office improved with the help of gold   ; ) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Houthis don&apos;t want to fight anymore&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will stop bombing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will discuss Ukraine&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will have a very big announcement before middle east trip&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Announcement will be made Thursday, Friday or Monday before we leave.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;USMCA is still very effective. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;USMCA was a transitional step &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We&apos;ll possibly start to renegotiate USMCA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will be friends with Canada&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Being 51st state would be a massive tax cut, free military. I do feel it will be much better for Canada&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Want to protect auto industry business&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have tremendous amounts of energy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On sale of Canada to US, &quot;Time will tell&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China wants to negotiate and we will meet at the right time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Massive amount of companies are moving into the United States&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Could have  $9 trillion of investment in the United States&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The announcement over next few days not necessarily on trade&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On trade deals, were not chaotic, we are flexible.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On India, not going to put up with high tariffs from India&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Think of US as a super luxury store.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;USMCA is fine. It&apos;s there. It&apos;s good.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some things of USMCA will have to change.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We won&apos;t do much business with Canada&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dealing more with concepts right now&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;They are paying tariffs and steel right now&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We dont really want cars from Canada&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At some point it won&apos;t make economic sense for Canada to build these cars&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is no reason for us to subsidize Canada&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We subsidize Canada $200B a year.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carney: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are a transformational leader&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I have been elected to transform Canada with focus on the economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;History is Canada – US stronger when we work together&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Canada is not for sale and would never be for sale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;My government is commited for a step change in providing international security&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some things on USMCA will have to change.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is a bigger discussion which will take time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For what it is worth, Trump ended by saying US subsidizes Canada by $200B per year which is a little high. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US/Canada goods deficit is more like $63.3 billion in 2024 with a trader surplus of $31.7 billion for a net deficit of about $32B. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For NATO, it is calculated that Canada owes around $20B more per year.  So overall, the $200B is exaggerated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USDCAD has moved lower and trades to a new low for the year and looks to the 61.8% of the move up from the 2023 low. That level comes in at 1.37415.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD/CAD touches the lows of the day as Carney arrives at the White House</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-touches-the-lows-of-the-day-as-carney-arrives-at-the-white-house-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:57:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-touches-the-lows-of-the-day-as-carney-arrives-at-the-white-house-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;USD/CAD has been in a 150-pip range since April 15 but it&apos;s near the low end of that range at the moment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I expect the loonie to move on the tone and comments from today&apos;s Trump-Carney meeting but at the end of the day, it&apos;s just one meeting in what will be a long relationship between two newly-elected leaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s not clear when they will address reporters but that&apos;s the usual protocol.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NZDUSD tests key swing area resistance as buyers push higher after holding MA support</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nzdusd-tests-key-swing-area-resistance-as-buyers-push-higher-after-ma-support-at-lows-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:29:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nzdusd-tests-key-swing-area-resistance-as-buyers-push-higher-after-ma-support-at-lows-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;178&quot; data-end=&quot;443&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The NZDUSD is pushing toward the top of a key swing area, testing resistance near 0.6000, which sits just below the 2024 high. This marks the 11th test of this zone, and the pair continues to find sellers on approaches, keeping the ceiling well-defined. Nevertheless, a break above would target the high from 2025 at 0.60281.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;445&quot; data-end=&quot;789&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The move to the upside was helped over the last few days by support holding. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last Thursday, buyers leaned against a rising trend line, which held support and helped set the stage for the current bullish move.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On Friday, and at the start of trading on Monday, the price corrected down to the 100-hour moving average and found support buyers. Bullish&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Today, the low price held above both the 100-hour moving average and the 100-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart—a dual technical confirmation that invited fresh upside interest. Bullish&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;791&quot; data-end=&quot;1034&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;While momentum has carried the pair back to recent highs, the area between 0.5994 and 0.6000 remains a stubborn barrier. A break above this zone would likely trigger stops and open the door toward a retest of the 2024 high near 0.6028.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1036&quot; data-end=&quot;1074&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, watch for support at:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1075&quot; data-end=&quot;1202&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1075&quot; data-end=&quot;1124&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1077&quot; data-end=&quot;1124&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;0.5960–0.5950 (near short-term swing lows),&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1125&quot; data-end=&quot;1202&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1127&quot; data-end=&quot;1202&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Followed by the 100-hour MA and trend line support near 0.5920.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1209&quot; data-end=&quot;1234&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1235&quot; data-end=&quot;1476&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1235&quot; data-end=&quot;1299&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1237&quot; data-end=&quot;1299&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.6000 (high of swing area), 0.6028 (2024 high)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1300&quot; data-end=&quot;1368&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1302&quot; data-end=&quot;1368&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 0.5979 (low of swing area) then 0.5949 – 0.5953 (cluster of moving averages including 100 hour, 100 bar on the 4 hour chart, and 200 hour moving averages)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1369&quot; data-end=&quot;1476&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1371&quot; data-end=&quot;1476&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bullish above moving averages a breakout above 0.6000 and the high for the year strengthens the upside case&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: The only question for Carney is why the US is subsidizing Canada</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-the-only-question-for-carney-is-why-the-us-is-subsidizing-canada-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:28:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-the-only-question-for-carney-is-why-the-us-is-subsidizing-canada-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;This isn&apos;t a promising start but it&apos;s the same thing he&apos;s said forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don&apos;t need Canada&apos;s cars, energy or lumber&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I look forward to meeting Carney&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carney is due to arrive at the White House any minute.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The S&amp;P and Nasdaq indice bounce near 50-hour MAs. Buyers still holding short-term control</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-sp-and-nasdaq-indice-bounce-near-50-hour-mas-buyers-still-holding-short-term-control-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:03:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-sp-and-nasdaq-indice-bounce-near-50-hour-mas-buyers-still-holding-short-term-control-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;236&quot; data-end=&quot;402&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Both the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Nasdaq indices came under modest selling pressure today, but buyers stepped in near key technical support, helping to stabilize the declines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;404&quot; data-end=&quot;425&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 Index&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;426&quot; data-end=&quot;755&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;426&quot; data-end=&quot;533&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;428&quot; data-end=&quot;533&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The index dipped to an intraday low of 5586.04, just above the 50-hour moving average at 5583.09&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;534&quot; data-end=&quot;607&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;536&quot; data-end=&quot;607&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The MA held as support, keeping the short-term bullish bias intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;608&quot; data-end=&quot;755&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;610&quot; data-end=&quot;755&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A break below this level would expose the 50% retracement of the March-April decline near 5491.24, and could invite further selling momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;757&quot; data-end=&quot;787&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Nasdaq Composite Index&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;788&quot; data-end=&quot;1098&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;788&quot; data-end=&quot;862&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;790&quot; data-end=&quot;862&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Nasdaq also softened intraday, reaching a session low of 17,592.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;863&quot; data-end=&quot;971&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;865&quot; data-end=&quot;971&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;However, the 50-hour moving average at 17,573 provided a technical floor, as buyers leaned against it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;972&quot; data-end=&quot;1098&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;974&quot; data-end=&quot;1098&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A move below the MA would be more bearish and could lead to a deeper pullback, with the next support 50% midpoint of the move down from the mid-December high. Pamela comes in at 17494131&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1100&quot; data-end=&quot;1377&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Despite today&apos;s pullback, the bounce off these key hourly moving averages shows that dip buyers remain active. The 50-hour MAs now serve as key short-term risk levels for both indices. A sustained break below would shift near-term momentum more clearly to the downside.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech faces turbulence as energy stocks surge: A detailed market analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-faces-turbulence-as-energy-stocks-surge-a-detailed-market-analysis-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:46:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-faces-turbulence-as-energy-stocks-surge-a-detailed-market-analysis-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tech sector is navigating choppy waters today, with major players showing mixed results. Microsoft (MSFT) slipped slightly at -0.34%, while Nvidia (NVDA), a significant semiconductor stock, declined by 1.01%. The semiconductor segment overall continues to struggle, with Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) dropping 1.64%. The technology sector’s volatility suggests cautious investor sentiment towards impending tech earnings and regulatory scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In stark contrast, the energy sector is seeing a wave of green. ExxonMobil (XOM) soared by 1.55%, demonstrating robust investor confidence, likely fueled by climbing oil prices. Chevron (CVX) also appreciated by 0.59%, highlighting energy&apos;s current market momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s market sentiment reflects a shift towards defensive investments. The technology sector&apos;s persistent volatility indicates underlying investor anxiety, possibly linked to recent tech earnings forecasts and broader market uncertainties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The healthcare sector faced significant pressure, with Eli Lilly (LLY) tumbling 2.79% and Vertex Pharmaceuticals (VRTX) plunging 11.64%. This downturn may be driven by recent regulatory developments affecting drug pricing or recent clinical trial outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For cautious investors: Consider reallocating portfolio weights towards stable energy stocks like XOM or CVX, which are positioned to benefit from current commodity price movements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For risk-tolerant investors: Monitor tech stocks closely. Select undervalued opportunities post-earnings season may arise, specifically in semiconductor stocks like NVDA and AMD, once market sentiment stabilizes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, while health sector volatility is pronounced, investors with a long-term horizon might explore companies engaged in critical research that are temporarily facing headwinds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the market is a patchwork of reds and greens today, with significant sectoral divergences underscoring the complexity of current investment landscapes. Investors should stay vigilant and informed, adapting to emerging trends and maintaining diversified portfolios to navigate the ongoing market shifts. 📊 For real-time market insights, stay connected with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD holds support above 100-hour MA as bulls eye December highs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-holds-support-above-100-hour-ma-as-bulls-eye-december-highs-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:36:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-holds-support-above-100-hour-ma-as-bulls-eye-december-highs-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;81&quot; data-end=&quot;356&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The AUDUSD continues to exhibit a bullish bias after climbing to its highest level since early December 2024. Buyers have kept the pair supported above the key swing area between 0.6429 and 0.6444 as well as the 100-hour moving average, currently near 0.6430.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;358&quot; data-end=&quot;762&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;That swing area, which previously acted as strong resistance (see green numbered circles), has now flipped to support. Price action above this zone reflects a positive shift in sentiment. Just above, the pair has been fluctuating around the 200-day moving average at 0.6461, suggesting some buyer hesitation. Still, the recent move back above this level leans the bias more firmly in favor of buyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;764&quot; data-end=&quot;982&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Holding above both the 200-day MA and the swing area keeps the bullish structure intact. A break above the recent high near 0.6493 would clear the path for a push toward additional resistance levels from late 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;984&quot; data-end=&quot;1161&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, a move back below the 200-day MA, followed by a drop through 0.6429–0.6444, would weaken the bullish outlook and likely invite further selling pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;93&quot; data-end=&quot;120&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;121&quot; data-end=&quot;326&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;121&quot; data-end=&quot;183&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;123&quot; data-end=&quot;183&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;0.6461 – 200-day moving average (currently being broken)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;184&quot; data-end=&quot;249&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;186&quot; data-end=&quot;249&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;0.6493 – High from yesterday / highest level since Dec 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;250&quot; data-end=&quot;326&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;252&quot; data-end=&quot;326&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;0.6500+ – Opens the door even further above the natural resistance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;328&quot; data-end=&quot;352&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;353&quot; data-end=&quot;536&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;353&quot; data-end=&quot;413&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;355&quot; data-end=&quot;413&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;0.6444–0.6429 – Key swing area (now acting as support)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;414&quot; data-end=&quot;452&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;416&quot; data-end=&quot;452&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;0.6430 – 100-hour moving average&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;453&quot; data-end=&quot;536&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;455&quot; data-end=&quot;536&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Below 0.6429 – Bias shifts bearish; opens risk toward broader downside levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent touts &apos;very good offers&apos; on trade again, market yawns and sells the US dollar</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-touts-very-good-offers-on-trade-again-market-yawns-and-sells-the-us-dollar-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:30:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-touts-very-good-offers-on-trade-again-market-yawns-and-sells-the-us-dollar-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Beyonce is on tour but no one seems to care. The tickets are going for $25 and there are plenty of empty seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At some point, people don&apos;t want to see the same old song and dance anymore. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s increasingly the case with Trump&apos;s trade team talking up trade deals that never seem to materialize. Hassett &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/hassett-on-tariffs-im-sure-there-will-be-news-by-the-end-of-the-day-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;said &lt;/a&gt;on Thursday that a deal was coming later that day and we&apos;re still waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now Bessent is playing the classics again:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Many trading partners have approached us with very good offers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US negotiating with 17 trading partners&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have not engaged with China yet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;I would think that perhaps as early as this week, we will be announcing trade deals with some of our largest trading partners,&quot; he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market rallied for 9 days in a row on the hope/expectation that Trump would start to announce trade deals but the clock keeps ticking and yesterday we &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-focus-is-back-on-trade-today-in-more-ways-than-one-20250506/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;learned &lt;/a&gt;that the US isn&apos;t going to offer zero tariffs, at least to Japan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar is sagging today and gold is up $51 in a troubling potential return of the early-April paradigm. That said, US equities seem to be trying to rally on it once again.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merz confirmed in second parliamentary vote</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/merz-confirmed-in-second-parliamentary-vote-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:29:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/merz-confirmed-in-second-parliamentary-vote-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The German political drama of the day is over as Merz was confirmed as Chancellor in the second anonymous vote.  His coalition held a 12-seat majority in the first vote but a dozen parliamentarians decided to cast protest votes before falling in line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The euro touched the highs of the day but it was fleeting as this was expected.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the third time a charm? EURUSD buyers take the price above the 200 hour MA</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/is-the-third-time-a-charm-eurusd-buyers-take-the-price-above-the-200-hour-ma-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:05:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/is-the-third-time-a-charm-eurusd-buyers-take-the-price-above-the-200-hour-ma-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;167&quot; data-end=&quot;465&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The EURUSD is trading above its 200-hour moving average (currently at 1.1347) for the third consecutive day. In the previous two attempts, the pair posted modest gains before retreating, so a sustained move above this level would be a more convincing bullish signal from a technical standpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;467&quot; data-end=&quot;682&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;If the pair fails to hold above the 200-hour MA, focus shifts back to the 100-hour moving average at 1.13296. Conservative traders may use a break below this level as confirmation that upside momentum has faded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;735&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the topside, key resistance levels to watch are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;736&quot; data-end=&quot;796&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;736&quot; data-end=&quot;767&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;738&quot; data-end=&quot;767&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1364 – Yesterday’s high&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;768&quot; data-end=&quot;796&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;770&quot; data-end=&quot;796&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1380 – Friday’s high&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;798&quot; data-end=&quot;896&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A break above these levels would strengthen the bullish bias and open the door for further upside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;798&quot; data-end=&quot;896&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Is the third time a charm? Will the buyers make a more concerted effort and move higher, or is this just another failed break with focus still on the downside (at least in the short term)?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
