<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>UK April final services PMI 49.0 vs 48.9 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-final-services-pmi-490-vs-489-prelim-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-final-services-pmi-490-vs-489-prelim-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Final Services PMI 49.0 vs 48.9 preliminary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 52.5 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Final Composite PMI 48.5 vs 48.2 preliminary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 51.5 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Renewed downturn in new work weighs on service
sector output
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fastest decline in export sales since February 2021
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business activity expectations slump to a two-and-
a-half year low&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Moore, Economics Director at S&amp;amp;P Global Market
Intelligence, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;UK service sector output slipped into contraction for
the first time in one-and-a-half years as heightened
business uncertainty weighed on order books during
April. Export conditions were particularly weak, with new
business from abroad falling to the greatest extent since
February 2021.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Survey respondents often commented on the impact
of global financial market turbulence in the wake of US
tariff announcements. Businesses in the technology and
financial service sectors noted rising risk aversion and
delayed spending decisions among clients, especially in
relation to major investment plans. Consumer service
providers meanwhile cited subdued domestic economic
conditions and challenges with passing on rising payroll
costs, especially those in the hospitality and leisure
sectors.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Input prices increased at the steepest pace since the
summer of 2023 as higher National Living Wage rates and
National Insurance contributions added to payroll costs
in April. Prices charged inflation was also the strongest
for nearly two years as service providers sought to pass
on additional costs to clients despite fragile demand.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Business expectations for the year ahead fell sharply
as service sector firms braced for an extended period of
global economic turbulence and heightened recession
risks. Some 22% of the survey panel predict an outright
decline in business activity during the next 12 months, up
from 14% in March and well above the post-election low
of 6% in July 2024.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China&apos;s Xi: China and EU should oppose unilateral bullying</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-xi-china-and-eu-should-oppose-unilateral-bullying-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:21:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-xi-china-and-eu-should-oppose-unilateral-bullying-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; China and EU should oppose unilateral bullying.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ready to work with EU leaders to expand mutual openness, properly handle frictions and differences.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Calls for China, EU to safeguard fairness and justice.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stands ready to work with European Council, European commission to deepen strategic communication, enhance understanding and mutual trust.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are not new comments. We&apos;ve been getting such comments since April 2. Of course, the lack of real progress in trade talks could unnerve the market at some point.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German stocks fall as political uncertainty creeps in</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/german-stocks-fall-as-political-uncertainty-creeps-in-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:20:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/german-stocks-fall-as-political-uncertainty-creeps-in-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It was supposed to be a straightforward appointment for Friedrich Merz to be German chancellor today. But when push comes to shove, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/merz-falls-short-of-majority-needed-to-become-german-chancellor-in-first-voting-round-20250506/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;it turned out to be anything but that&lt;/a&gt;. It&apos;s a big and embarrassing setback for Merz and his coalition, who by the way commands 328 votes in the Bundestag, yet he only managed to secure 310 votes today. He needed 316 votes to secure a majority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;We&apos;re now in a bit of an unprecedented situation in German politics. No candidate for chancellor has ever failed in the first round of voting. However, the constitution does allow up to 14 days for a new round of voting. But will we see another vote today? Or tomorrow? Nobody knows for sure. But the worry here is that the CDU/CSU/SPD coalition may already be damaged before it even begins governing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merz falls short of majority needed to become German chancellor in first voting round</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/merz-falls-short-of-majority-needed-to-become-german-chancellor-in-first-voting-round-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:08:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/merz-falls-short-of-majority-needed-to-become-german-chancellor-in-first-voting-round-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, that didn&apos;t go according to plan. The expectation was that Merz would&apos;ve been elected upon the first round of voting and then the Bundestag session will be adjourned as he travels to meet with the German president to formalise his appointment. Now, all of that is put on hold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;He needed 316 votes to win a majority but didn&apos;t manage to reach that (only got 310 votes) even though the CDU/CSU/SPD coalition has 328 MPs. There can be a second or third round of voting but it&apos;s still unclear if that will take place today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Update: The session is now adjourned as the political parties regroup to try and seek a resolution on this.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone April final services PMI 50.1 vs 49.7 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-services-pmi-501-vs-497-prelim-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 08:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-services-pmi-501-vs-497-prelim-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 51.0&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 50.4 vs 50.1 prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 50.9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The reading reaffirms stagnation in the euro area economy to start Q2, with the services sector experiencing a stall. Demand conditions continue to suffer and that&apos;s not a good look amid a more challenging economic backdrop in the months ahead. The good news at least is that price pressures have eased a touch further on the month. HCOB notes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;Eurozone economic growth slowed at the start of the second quarter, following a pick-up in the first three months of the
year. The services sector, which is a major player, practically stagnated in April. Even though manufacturing output saw a
surprising uptick, it wasn&apos;t enough to prevent the overall slowdown in growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;In the services sector, cost pressures are still relatively high, though they have eased a bit over the past couple of months.
Inflation is down for sales prices and continued to trend lower. Many members of the European Central Bank (ECB) have
been hinting at another interest rate cut in June, and these latest figures seem to support their stance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;Euro area employment has seen a slight stabilization. The drop in headcounts among manufacturers has been more-thancounterbalanced by an increase in jobs within the service sector. Overall, there&apos;s still a noticeable hesitation to hire new staff,
which isn&apos;t too surprising given the current uncertainties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;Spain is leading the pack in terms of growth, followed by Italy, then Germany with marginal growth, and France trailing
behind. This is reflected in the Composite PMI data for the first four months of 2025 and aligns with Eurostat&apos;s GDP data for
the first quarter. We expect Germany to soon outpace Italy thanks to a generous fiscal package, while France is likely to
remain at the bottom for now due to its uncertain political climate.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNB&apos;s Schlegel: We haven&apos;t ruled out negative interest rates</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/snbs-schlegel-we-havent-ruled-out-negative-interest-rates-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:55:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/snbs-schlegel-we-havent-ruled-out-negative-interest-rates-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No one likes negative rates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But if we have to, we are prepared to do it again&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We expected Swiss inflation to come down&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And there we go. From yesterday: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/a-return-to-negative-rates-look-to-be-a-given-now-for-the-snb-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;A return to negative rates looks to be a given now for the SNB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany April final services PMI 49.0 vs 48.8 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-final-services-pmi-490-vs-488-prelim-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-final-services-pmi-490-vs-488-prelim-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Final Services PMI 49.0 vs. 48.8 preliminary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 50.9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Final Composite PMI 50.1 vs. 49.7 preliminary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 51.3 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany Services PMI Business Activity Index at 14-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany Composite PMI Output Index at 4-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Optimism towards year-ahead outlook wanes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The German service sector has hit the brakes. Business activity dipped a bit in April, ending a four-month streak of growth.
The composite PMI didn&apos;t slip into recession territory, thanks to manufacturing companies ramping up production, just like
they did in March after a slump that lasted nearly two years.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Service providers probably felt the squeeze on profit margins in April. Costs went up more than last month, but they had to
dial back on price hikes. With this in mind, confidence about future business took a hit, with the index dropping further below
its long-term average.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At first glance, the future doesn&apos;t look too bright. New business has shrunk for the eighth month in a row, order book
backlogs have been sliding downhill for most of the past two years, and there&apos;s no sign of a solid recovery in exports. But,
companies are still hiring, and job growth has even picked up for the second month straight. Clearly, businesses aren&apos;t ready
to throw in the towel just yet. And for good reason, as the new government, expected to start this week, could well give the
economy a boost with its fiscal stimulus program in infrastructure and defence, plus more social spending. All of this should
also spread to the services sector.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France April final services PMI 47.3 vs 46.8 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-april-final-services-pmi-473-vs-468-prelim-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:50:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-april-final-services-pmi-473-vs-468-prelim-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 47.9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 47.8 vs 47.3 prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.0&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The slight revision higher doesn&apos;t take away from the fact that French business activity has now contracted for eight straight months. Demand conditions remain subdued and that&apos;s troubling amid a more challenging outlook in the months ahead. HCOB notes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;April marked another month of declining activity in the French private sector. The HCOB Composite PMI signals a
continued downturn in economic activity in France, driven by weakness in the services sector. However, the manufacturing
sector has managed to increase production for the first time in nearly three years.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;The French services sector remains on a downward trajectory. Business activity declined again in April, attributed to lower
customer demand and generally poorer market conditions. The rapid decline in new orders is particularly concerning this
month. Surveyed companies report that weak market conditions make it very difficult to attract new business, and existing
customers are also hesitant to engage in new transactions. High trade policy uncertainty seems to be causing
postponements to investment and consumption decisions.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;Current developments – weak demand amid high uncertainty – do not bode well for the profit margins of French service
providers. Additionally, our survey results indicate that operating costs, appear to be rising faster than end prices, which
have virtually stagnated due to competitive pressures.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;Future business expectations remain in the growth zone, but significantly below the historical average. Employees find
themselves in a concerning situation, as they are increasingly at risk of job loss as workloads decrease due to the order
slump and simultaneous reduction of backlogs.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy April services PMI 52.9 vs 51.5 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-services-pmi-529-vs-515-expected-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:45:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-services-pmi-529-vs-515-expected-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Services PMI 52.9 vs. 51.5 expected &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 52.0 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 52.1 vs. 50.5 prior.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Output and new orders up at sharper rates in April
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cost pressures at their lowest in 2025 so far
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business confidence drops to weakest level in four-and-a-half years&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The growth trend appears to be consolidating. The Italian private sector has grown for three months in a row, led by the
service sector, while manufacturing output has practically stopped shrinking after a year. According to the Bank of Italy,
tourism and hospitality have supported growth in the service sector during the first months of the year, which suggests a
certain degree of sustainability. In the manufacturing sector, the question remains as to whether this sector could soon be hit
harder by US tariffs and EU countermeasures. For the year as a whole, we expect economic growth of around half a
percent.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The service sector is showing relatively robust growth, which has accelerated slightly compared with the previous month.
Accordingly, service providers have once again hired more people, especially as they were also able to expand new
business more strongly than in March. It’s encouraging that most people were hired on a permanent basis, as panellists
said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Tariff uncertainty could also indirectly weigh on the service sector, with the challenging economic and geopolitical
climate mentioned by panellists as having weighed on expectations regarding future activity, with the index already well
below its long-term average. However, especially in these times, the service sector is likely to maintain its role as a stabiliser
of the Italian economy, which it has held for around two years.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is some slight relief on the cost side for service companies. Operating costs have not risen quite as sharply as in
previous months. However, companies were also unable to increase sales prices at the same pace as before and had to
settle for significantly lower increases, meaning that profit margins were unlikely to benefit.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic: Proposed 0 for 0 tariffs on industrial goods</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-trade-commissioner-sefcovic-proposed-0-for-0-tariffs-on-industrial-goods-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:41:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-trade-commissioner-sefcovic-proposed-0-for-0-tariffs-on-industrial-goods-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proposed 0 for 0 tariffs on industrial goods.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accelerating trade talks with India among others.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Another €170B US-exports may be impacted by tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ready to use all available tools in trade defence.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s nothing new here as we&apos;ve been aware of the 0 for 0 offer for weeks. The problem is that we still haven&apos;t got any breakthrough. Last week, French Finance Minister Lombard said that he discussed the idea of reciprocal 
zero tariffs with Scott Bessent, and Bessent told him that it was not 
unrealistic. So, this will keep the hopes alive.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNB&apos;s Schlegel: We remain committed to our mandate of price stability</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/snbs-schlegel-we-remain-committed-to-our-mandate-of-price-stability-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/snbs-schlegel-we-remain-committed-to-our-mandate-of-price-stability-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Swiss franc has really appreciated a lot&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have said we are ready to intervene in the FX market as necessary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;After the latest inflation numbers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-cpi-00-vs-02-yy-expected-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, the pressure is on for the SNB to go big. 50 bps rate cut incoming next?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – Focus on the FOMC decision</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-focus-on-the-fomc-decision-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:17:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-focus-on-the-fomc-decision-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold erased last week’s losses
in just a couple of days. It’s unclear what was the catalyst though. I can cite
the usual “dollar weakness, safe haven demand” reasons but those don’t help
with market timing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most plausible explanation
could be the recent volatility in some Asian currencies which would explain the
timing and the safe haven demand. Authorities are now intervening so we could
see an ease in the safe haven demand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have also the FOMC
decision tomorrow and that could be a risk for the bulls as the Fed is likely
to push back against the aggressively dovish market pricing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the bigger picture, gold
remains in an uptrend as real yields will likely continue to fall amid Fed
easing. But in the short-term more positive news on the tariffs front and a
hawkish Fed could trigger more downside for gold as the market readjusts to new
conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that gold bounced around the 3200 level and pulled all the way back to the key
swing level at 3370. From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a
better risk to reward setup around the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt;,
while the sellers will look for a break lower to increase the bearish bets into
the 2957 level next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see the price recently broke below the 3258 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-support-and-resistance-20220405/&quot;&gt;support&lt;/a&gt;
but eventually climbed back above it and extended the rally into the key swing point
around the 3370 level. This is where we can expect the sellers to step in with
a defined risk above the high to position for a drop into the major trendline.
The buyers, on the other hand, will want to see the price breaking into a new
high to increase the bullish bets into a new all-time high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor upward trendline defining the bullish momentum. The
buyers will likely continue to lean on the trendline to keep pushing into new
highs, while the sellers will look for a break lower to target a drop back into
the 3258 level. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we have the Trump-Carney meeting. Tomorrow, we have
the FOMC Rate Decision, while on Thursday, we get the latest US Jobless Claims
figures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain April services PMI 53.4 vs 54.0 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-services-pmi-534-vs-540-expected-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:15:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-services-pmi-534-vs-540-expected-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 54.7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 52.5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 54.0&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That&apos;s a slightly softer reading than estimated, with softer gains in new work recorded on the month. Meanwhile, confidence in the outlook has also fallen to its lowest since November. HCOB notes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“In April, business activity growth in Spain&apos;s private sector slightly slowed according to the HCOB Composite PMI. While
growth in the services sector weakened, production in the manufacturing sector declined. This trend is also reflected in the
order situation: service providers recorded slower order growth, while orders in the manufacturing sector decreased.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“Service providers report a more challenging work environment. This is not surprising, given the increasing tensions in
international markets – keywords: trade frictions – which led to postponed or cancelled consumption and investment
decisions. Despite the slight slowdown, business activity and order levels remain in the growth zone.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“Operating costs for Spanish service providers remain high, despite the current slight slowdown. Anecdotal evidence
suggests that trade tariffs have already had initial impacts on supply chains, leading to input price increases. Additionally,
wage increases continue to be a significant driver of prices. As a result of rising input costs, companies are passing these
costs on to their customers.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“Spanish service providers remain optimistic about the future, even though the corresponding index recorded a decline this
month, falling to the lowest level of the year. This is mainly due to the uncertainty arising from US tariffs and their effects on
the international trade network. However, this has no immediate impact on Spanish workers. Given the continued growth in
orders and increasing backlogs, service providers added to their workforces.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says would welcome EU leaders to visit in a timely manner to hold new round of talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-would-welcome-eu-leaders-to-visit-in-a-timely-manner-to-hold-new-round-of-talks-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-would-welcome-eu-leaders-to-visit-in-a-timely-manner-to-hold-new-round-of-talks-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The Chinese foreign ministry is out saying that they would welcome a visit to China from António Costa and/or Ursula von der Leyen &quot;in a timely manner to hold a new round of China-EU leaders&apos; meeting&quot;. As things stand, both sides are finding some common ground in pushing back against the US and Trump&apos;s tariffs. China has also confirmed that they have lifted all restrictions on mutual exchanges with the EU for now as both sides look to find some solution to the trade war.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices little changed to kick start the day</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-little-changed-to-kick-start-the-day-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 07:08:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-little-changed-to-kick-start-the-day-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s a slower start to proceedings as broader markets are mainly waiting on further trade developments for the most part. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down 0.3% after the overnight drop but again as a reminder, it came after nine straight days of gains. We&apos;re pretty much taking a breather until the next meaningful headline hits on tariffs/trade. But the longer that drags on, the more apprehension there will be filling up in the air.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 06:16:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Today we don&apos;t have much on the agenda other than a few low tier data releases. In the European session, we get the final PMI readings for the UK and Eurozone economy, while in the American session we don&apos;t have anything excepts the 10 year auction for those following it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main event will be the Trump-Carney meeting at 11:45 ET/15:45 GMT where the focus will of course be on tariff related headlines. Also, watch out for trade deals as that&apos;s what the market is eagerly waiting to see. US officials repeated once again that the first one could be announced this week.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures -0.2% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-02-in-early-european-trading-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 06:07:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-02-in-early-european-trading-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;UK stocks will have to balance out the mood after the long weekend but overall risk sentiment is a little on the softer side today. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down 0.35% following the drop yesterday, with investors still waiting on more concrete trade developments to work with. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-rejects-japan-request-for-full-exemption-from-reciprocal-tariffs-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;This one&lt;/a&gt; from overnight involving Japan isn&apos;t too bright to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland April seasonally adjusted unemployment rate 2.8% vs 2.8% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-seasonally-adjusted-unemployment-rate-28-vs-28-expected-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 05:45:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-seasonally-adjusted-unemployment-rate-28-vs-28-expected-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 2.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The Swiss jobless rate holds steady with the number of registered unemployed persons falling slightly in April to 130,101 - down from 132,569 in March.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold keeps the push higher after another round of bids in Asia</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-keeps-the-push-higher-after-another-round-of-bids-in-asia-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 05:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-keeps-the-push-higher-after-another-round-of-bids-in-asia-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It has been a bit of a recurring theme in the past few weeks, as noted before &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-runs-into-some-near-term-consolidation-after-backing-away-from-3500-20250425/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. And today, we are once again seeing gold push up after another round of bids earlier in Asia trading. On the week itself, the precious metal is finding itself in a good position as price climbs back above the $3,000 mark as well as its key hourly moving averages. That puts the near-term bias in a more bullish spot once again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the bigger picture, it&apos;s still hard to pin down gold considering the broader market and economic landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Trump tariffs continue to threaten financial dislocations with regards to the dollar, and recent revaluation talk among Asian currencies are only fueling the fire here. Then, you have heightened uncertainty with regards to the global economy and inflation. So, all of that together is continuing to make a case for gold to stay underpinned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That is not to mention &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-stays-relentless-in-its-push-higher-eyes-3500-next-20250422/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;ETFs having to play catch up&lt;/a&gt; and also central banks still buying up supply too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For today, there is some short-term resistance around $3,367-70 to get through before potentially talking about a return towards $3,500.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 6 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-6-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 04:38:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-6-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There is just one to take note of on the board for today, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That being for EUR/USD at the 1.1325 level. The expiries match up with the 100-hour moving average, which alongside the 200-hour moving average at 1.1347 might help to keep a lid on price action in the session ahead. The dollar is in a calmer mood after having falling slightly yesterday before a bit of a recovery late on and earlier today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The price action to start the week is not indicative of much, as traders continue to wait on trade developments for the most part. There&apos;s also the prospect of the Fed coming up later in the week. And by that, I mean Trump&apos;s reaction to when the central bank leaves interest rates unchanged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs expects USD/CNY to decline further</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-expects-usdcny-to-decline-further-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-expects-usdcny-to-decline-further-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs expects USD/CNY to decline further, citing &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;growing optimism around U.S.-China trade talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;shift from short to long CNY positions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The move lower could be swift and event-driven in the near term, while the PBOC may guide a more gradual adjustment over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China will welcome back yuan strength. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Some give back for Asian currencies</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-some-give-back-for-asian-currencies-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:40:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-some-give-back-for-asian-currencies-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-lawmaker-targets-nvidia-chip-smuggling-to-china-with-new-bill-20250506/&quot;&gt;U.S. lawmaker targets Nvidia chip smuggling to China with new bill&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-dollar-has-dropped-some-of-its-gains-today-after-friday-and-mondays-surge-20250506/&quot;&gt;Taiwan dollar has dropped some of its gains today after Friday and Monday&apos;s surge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/41-of-hong-kongs-container-shipments-to-north-america-cancelled-for-the-week-of-may-12-20250506/&quot;&gt;41% of Hong Kong’s container shipments to North America cancelled for the week of May 12&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/coinbase-slams-the-federal-reserve-in-its-new-tv-ad-for-bitcoin-20250506/&quot;&gt;Coinbase slams the Federal Reserve in its new TV ad for Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/fomc-preview-fed-confronts-lose-lose-scenario-amid-haphazard-tariff-rollout-20250506/&quot;&gt;FOMC preview - &quot;Fed confronts lose-lose scenario amid haphazard tariff rollout&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-and-canadian-prime-minister-carney-to-meet-at-1145-am-us-eastern-time-tuesday-20250506/&quot;&gt;Trump and Canadian Prime Minister Carney to meet at 11.45 am US Eastern time Tuesday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-caixin-services-pmi-for-april-2025-is-507-expected-517-20250506/&quot;&gt;China Caixin Services PMI for April 2025 is 50.7 (expected 51.7)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-314-million-domestic-trips-made-during-may-holiday-64-yy-20250506/&quot;&gt;China says 314 million domestic trips made during May holiday, +6.4% y/y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-building-permits-88-mm-expected-06-20250506/&quot;&gt;Australian March building permits -8.8% m/m (expected -0.6%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdjpy-back-above-14420-20250506/&quot;&gt;USD/JPY back above 144.20&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72008-vs-estimate-at-72518-20250506/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.2008 (vs. estimate at 7.2518)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-data-april-anz-world-commodity-price-index-0-mm-prior-04-20250506/&quot;&gt;New Zealand data - April ANZ World Commodity Price Index 0% m/m (prior -0.4%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/usd-pops-a-little-higher-in-asia-morning-trade-20250506/&quot;&gt;USD pops a little higher in Asia morning trade&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/ubs-sees-sp-500-hitting-5800-by-year-end-citing-easing-tariffs-and-fed-cuts-20250506/&quot;&gt;UBS sees S&amp;amp;P 500 hitting 5,800 by year-end, citing easing tariffs and Fed cuts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-westpac-ceo-says-the-worst-is-behind-us-across-consumer-and-business-stress-20250505/&quot;&gt;Australia - Westpac CEO says the ‘Worst is behind us’ across consumer and business stress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-national-australia-bank-nab-revised-its-year-end-audusd-forecast-higher-to-070-20250505/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - National Australia Bank (NAB) revised its year-end AUD/USD forecast higher to 0.70&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/mentions-of-recession-on-sp-500-earnings-calls-have-surged-to-highest-level-since-2023-20250505/&quot;&gt;Mentions of “recession” on S&amp;amp;P 500 earnings calls have surged to highest level since 2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-equities-retail-investors-pile-in-but-can-retail-alone-ignite-a-bull-market-20250505/&quot;&gt;US equities - Retail investors pile in, but can retail alone ignite a bull market?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-goldman-sachs-reiterated-its-structural-bullish-gold-view-sees-as-high-as-4000-20250505/&quot;&gt;ICYMI: Goldman Sachs reiterated its structural bullish gold view, sees as high as $4,000&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-vitesse-energy-says-itll-cut-capex-by-32-20250505/&quot;&gt;US Vitesse Energy says it&apos;ll cut capex by 32%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/hong-kong-central-bank-intervenes-in-the-hong-kong-dollar-20250505/&quot;&gt;Hong Kong central bank intervenes in the Hong Kong dollar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-pledges-half-bn-eur-to-lure-scientists-from-trump-cuts-if-you-love-freedom-come-20250505/&quot;&gt;EU pledges half bn EUR to lure scientists from Trump cuts - &quot;If you love freedom, come&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-5-may-usd-moves-lower-in-up-down-trading-sp-falls-20250505/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 5 May: USD moves lower in up &amp;amp; down trading. S&amp;amp;P falls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-hell-announce-pharmaceutical-tariffs-over-the-next-two-weeks-20250505/&quot;&gt;Trump says he&apos;ll announce pharmaceutical tariffs over the next two weeks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/financial-times-reports-eu-set-to-make-it-easier-for-uk-professionals-to-work-in-the-bloc-20250505/&quot;&gt;Financial Times reports EU set to make it easier for UK professionals to work in the bloc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-signs-order-to-reduce-regulatory-barriers-to-domestic-pharmaceutical-manufacturing-20250505/&quot;&gt;Trump signs order to reduce regulatory barriers to domestic pharmaceutical manufacturing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/lutnick-says-a-trade-deal-with-canada-is-possible-but-its-very-complex-20250505/&quot;&gt;Lutnick says a trade deal with Canada is possible, but its &apos;really complex&apos;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-tuesday-6-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250505/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Tuesday, 6 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
It
was a volatile day for Asian currencies, with some losses against the
USD. The Taiwan dollar retraced a little after its epic surge higher
on Friday and Monday. Comments from Central Bank Governor Yang
Chin-Long sought to calm markets and have had some success. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Hong
Kong’s central bank, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority, intervened to
sell HKD at the top end of its band. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;USD/JPY
rose from early lows under 143.60 to above 144.25 before giving almost
all back. Its circa 143.80 as I update.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
pattern of movement was similar across much of major FX. EUR, GBP,
AUD, NZD, CAD all lost ground in early Asia trade against the US
dollar but have retraced those losses. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;There
were a few items of interest for US equities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump says he&apos;ll announce pharmaceutical tariffs over the next two weeks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;a
U.S. lawmaker will be introducing legislation in coming weeks to
verify the location of artificial-intelligence chips like those made
by Nvidia (NVDA) after they are sold, aiming to  address reports of
widespread smuggling of  chips into China in violation of U.S. export
control laws&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The
U.S. Justice Department has asked a judge to require Google to sell
two of its businesses that help websites buy, sell and serve online
advertising after a judge found the company illegally monopolized
those markets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;US
stock futures fell,
S&amp;amp;P 500 e-minis down 0.3%, Nasdaq futures down 0.56% as
I update.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;On
the data front:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China
Caixin Services PMI for April 2025 remained in expansion at 50.7, but
at its slowest since September 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chinese
markets reopened after holidays on Thursday, Friday and Monday. The
People’s Bank of China set the reference rate at it strongest (for
CNY) since April 7. 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Australian
building permits and household spending, both for March, were weak.
Household Spending was its slowest in 6 months.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;As
a heads up, Trump and Canadian Prime Minister Carney will meet at 11.45
am US Eastern time on Tuesday. US Commerce Secretary Lutnick said that
while a trade deal with Canada is possible, its really complex. Keep
your expectations low seems to be the (not very quiet) subtext of
this. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brent oil rose a little after its four year low yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/TWD&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. lawmaker targets Nvidia chip smuggling to China with new bill</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-lawmaker-targets-nvidia-chip-smuggling-to-china-with-new-bill-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:07:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-lawmaker-targets-nvidia-chip-smuggling-to-china-with-new-bill-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;U.S. Representative Bill Foster, a Democrat from Illinois, once worked as a particle physicist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He  plans to introduce legislation in coming weeks to verify the location of artificial-intelligence chips like those made by Nvidia (NVDA) after they are sold. The aim is to address reports of widespread smuggling of Nvidia&apos;s chips into China in violation of U.S. export control laws.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-lawmaker-targets-nvidia-chip-smuggling-china-with-new-bill-2025-05-05/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Info via Reuters &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan dollar has dropped some of its gains today after Friday and Monday&apos;s surge</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-dollar-has-dropped-some-of-its-gains-today-after-friday-and-mondays-surge-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:01:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/taiwan-dollar-has-dropped-some-of-its-gains-today-after-friday-and-mondays-surge-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Taiwan dollar weakened against the U.S. dollar after Central Bank Governor Yang Chin-Long sought to calm markets following a sharp two-day rally in the local currency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yang urged restraint from market commentators and warned manufacturers not to be swayed by exaggerated or misleading exchange rate analyses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to DBS strategist Philip Wee, the currency’s pullback reflects official efforts to rein in speculation. These include the central bank’s confirmation that it had intervened to counter what it viewed as overly aggressive expectations for Taiwan dollar appreciation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWD update, not a big retracement!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I posted on the TWD surge:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/mufg-on-the-taiwan-dollar-move-a-19-standard-deviation-event-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;MUFG on the Taiwan dollar move a &quot;19-standard-deviation event&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/surging-twd-fuelling-revaluation-talk-20250505/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;Surging TWD fuelling revaluation talk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>41% of Hong Kong’s container shipments to North America cancelled for the week of May 12</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/41-of-hong-kongs-container-shipments-to-north-america-cancelled-for-the-week-of-may-12-20250506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 03:01:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/41-of-hong-kongs-container-shipments-to-north-america-cancelled-for-the-week-of-may-12-20250506/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;164&quot; data-end=&quot;487&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Hong Kong’s shipping sector is reeling from the fallout of the intensifying U.S.-China trade war, with 41% of container capacity to North America’s west coast scrapped for mid-May. The surge in tariffs and disruption to global supply chains are delivering a heavy blow to the city’s re-export-driven economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;489&quot; data-end=&quot;1053&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
•  41% of Hong Kong’s container shipments to North America cancelled for the week of May 12.
•  Data from Freightos and Sea-Intelligence point to widespread sailing cancellations, reflecting escalating trade tensions.
•  Soaring tariffs—145% from the U.S. and 125% in Chinese retaliation—are choking cross-Pacific trade volumes.
•  Hong Kong’s role as a re-export hub makes it especially exposed to shocks in global trade flows.
•  Analysts warn tariffs above 35% wipe out margins, rendering many export routes economically unviable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;489&quot; data-end=&quot;1053&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Info via Reuters &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) LUTNICK, ASKED IF A DEAL WITH CANADA IS POSSIBLE, SAYS IT IS &apos;VERY COMPLEX&apos; -FOX BUSINESS INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919497276122153181#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:59:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919497276122153181#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LUTNICK, ASKED IF A DEAL WITH CANADA IS POSSIBLE, SAYS IT IS &apos;VERY COMPLEX&apos; -FOX BUSINESS INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. COMMERCE SECRETARY LUTNICK SAYS FIRST TRADE DEAL GOT TO BE WITH A &apos;TOP TEN&apos; ECONOMY -FOX BUSINESS INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919497231079493932#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:59:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919497231079493932#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. COMMERCE SECRETARY LUTNICK SAYS FIRST TRADE DEAL GOT TO BE WITH A &apos;TOP TEN&apos; ECONOMY -FOX BUSINESS INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SIGNS EXECUTIVE ORDER ON GAIN OF FUNCTION RESEARCH</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919497078641668298#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919497078641668298#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SIGNS EXECUTIVE ORDER ON GAIN OF FUNCTION RESEARCH&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS HE&apos;LL HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT NEXT WEEK RELATED TO THE COSTS OF MEDICINE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919497005635678651#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:58:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919497005635678651#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS HE&apos;LL HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT NEXT WEEK RELATED TO THE COSTS OF MEDICINE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *LUTNICK: DON&apos;T SEE HOW TRUMP-CARNEY MEETING WORKS OUT PERFECT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919496934215045459#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:58:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919496934215045459#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*LUTNICK: DON&apos;T SEE HOW TRUMP-CARNEY MEETING WORKS OUT PERFECT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SPOT GOLD RISES NEARLY 3% TO $3,336.19/OZ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919475604333695037#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:33:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919475604333695037#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPOT GOLD RISES NEARLY 3% TO $3,336.19/OZ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP TO SIGN ORDER TO ENCOURAGE DOMESTIC DRUG MANUFACTURING - WAPO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919472570975371705#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:21:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919472570975371705#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP TO SIGN ORDER TO ENCOURAGE DOMESTIC DRUG MANUFACTURING - WAPO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *OPENAI ABANDONS PLANNED FOR-PROFIT CONVERSION -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919469056551211225#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:07:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919469056551211225#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*OPENAI ABANDONS PLANNED FOR-PROFIT CONVERSION -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COMMUNICATION APP USED BY TRUMP ADVISER SAYS IT IS TEMPORARILY SUSPENDING SERVICES FOLLOWING REPORTED HACK</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919460740336893992#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919460740336893992#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COMMUNICATION APP USED BY TRUMP ADVISER SAYS IT IS TEMPORARILY SUSPENDING SERVICES FOLLOWING REPORTED HACK&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: CHINA WANTS TO MAKE DEAL &apos;VERY BADLY&apos;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919452891825283429#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919452891825283429#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: CHINA WANTS TO MAKE DEAL &apos;VERY BADLY&apos;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS HE BETS CANADA&apos;S CARNEY WANTS TO MAKE A DEAL DURING VISIT TUESDAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919452481542607153#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:01:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919452481542607153#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS HE BETS CANADA&apos;S CARNEY WANTS TO MAKE A DEAL DURING VISIT TUESDAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ON NORDSTREAM: A LOT OF PEOPLE KNOW WHO BLEW IT UP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919451721815761241#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:58:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919451721815761241#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ON NORDSTREAM: A LOT OF PEOPLE KNOW WHO BLEW IT UP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS HE KNOWS NOTHING ABOUT IMAGE OF HIM AS POPE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919451169916653788#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:56:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919451169916653788#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS HE KNOWS NOTHING ABOUT IMAGE OF HIM AS POPE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS REFERRING TO RUSSIA, `THEY WANT TO SETTLE, UKRAINE WANTS TO SETTLE&apos;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919450987292393924#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:55:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919450987292393924#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS REFERRING TO RUSSIA, `THEY WANT TO SETTLE, UKRAINE WANTS TO SETTLE&apos;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS WANTS TO MAKE SURE INDUSTRY IS HAPPY WITH TARIFF IDEA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919450522626519537#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919450522626519537#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS WANTS TO MAKE SURE INDUSTRY IS HAPPY WITH TARIFF IDEA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS WILL MEET WITH SOME FILM INDUSTRY OFFICIALS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919450462102720836#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:53:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919450462102720836#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS WILL MEET WITH SOME FILM INDUSTRY OFFICIALS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *NEWARK AIR TRAFFIC RADAR CUT OUT FOR 90 SECONDS ON APRIL 28</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919450397543961014#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:53:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919450397543961014#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*NEWARK AIR TRAFFIC RADAR CUT OUT FOR 90 SECONDS ON APRIL 28&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SAYS WASHINGTON WILL HOST 2027 NFL DRAFT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919447509652455569#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919447509652455569#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SAYS WASHINGTON WILL HOST 2027 NFL DRAFT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) IMF&apos;S GEORGIEVA: U.S. TO FACE INFLATION, CHINA TO FACE DEFLATION FROM TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919439669835546744#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:10:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919439669835546744#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IMF&apos;S GEORGIEVA: U.S. TO FACE INFLATION, CHINA TO FACE DEFLATION FROM TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. ARMY PAUSING HELICOPTER FLIGHTS AROUND PENTAGON PENDING INVESTIGATION INTO THURSDAY FLIGHT THAT DISRUPTED TWO CIVILIAN FLIGHTS -- U.S. OFFICIAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919431647365062793#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919431647365062793#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. ARMY PAUSING HELICOPTER FLIGHTS AROUND PENTAGON PENDING INVESTIGATION INTO THURSDAY FLIGHT THAT DISRUPTED TWO CIVILIAN FLIGHTS -- U.S. OFFICIAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
