<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>IEA sees more supply flowing through oil market for the year</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/iea-sees-more-supply-flowing-through-oil-market-for-the-year-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:21:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/iea-sees-more-supply-flowing-through-oil-market-for-the-year-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2025 global supply growth forecast seen at 1.6 mil bpd (up by 380k bpd)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;2025 global demand growth forecast seen at 650k bpd for remainder of 2025 (down from 990k bpd in Q1)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;2025 average oil demand growth forecast seen at 740k bpd (up by 20k bpd)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;2026 average oil demand growth forecast seen at 760k bpd (previously 690k bpd)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The agency sees a further slowdown in oil demand growth, largely due to ongoing economic headwinds and rising EV sales. Adding to that is a further increase in supply as OPEC+ steps up production further. Not quite the positive outlook for the oil market as such. But at least looking to next year, IEA sees some better prospects compared to the month before.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Commerce Ministry: China always open to resolving economic, trade relations offline</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-commerce-ministry-china-always-open-to-resolving-economic-trade-relations-offline-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 08:15:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-commerce-ministry-china-always-open-to-resolving-economic-trade-relations-offline-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China always open to resolving economic, trade relations offline.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will release more information in due course.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It starts looking more and more like Trump wasn&apos;t lying about US and China having private conversations about trade, and the Chinese were just denying that because they want to keep things private (which is something Trump couldn&apos;t do).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyway, this is not new information, so it won&apos;t affect the market, but it&apos;s nice to see that things continue to look better and better.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDJPY Technical Analysis – We filled the Monday gap</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-we-filled-the-monday-gap-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:40:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-we-filled-the-monday-gap-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD got a boost across
the board on Monday as the US-China tariff relief was a much better than
expected news. The market started to look at the more hawkish scenario where we
get an average 10% global tariff rate and economic activity picks up on an
easing in growth fears and general uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That led to a hawkish
repricing in interest rates expectations with the market now seeing 50 bps of
easing for the Fed by year-end compared to like 120 bps at the peak of the
fears in April. The short dollar trade was pretty overcrowded so the unwinding
in positioning gave the greenback even more strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we repriced the interest
rates expectations, the USD started to lose ground against the major currencies
once again. We will likely need the market to price in an even less dovish path
for interest rates to give the greenback another boost. That could come from
economic data or hawkish Fed comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the JPY side, the
currency has been driven mainly by global events rather than domestic
fundamentals. Alongside the Swiss Franc, it’s been the favoured safe haven in
the currencies space amid the swings in risk sentiment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent positive mood in
the markets weighed on the Japanese Yen which lost ground against all the major
currencies despite the market increasing the expectations for another rate hike
this year. We got a rally in the JPY yesterday although there was no clear
catalyst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that USDJPY fell back below the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt; in what could end up being a
fakeout. From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a better risk
to reward setup around the upward trendline to position for a rally into the
151.00 handle, while the sellers will look for a break lower to increase the
bearish bets into the 140.00 handle next. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see that the price is now filling the Monday gap which could act as support.
This is where we can expect the buyers to step in with a defined risk below the
gap to position for a rally into new highs. The sellers, on the other hand,
will look for a break lower to extend the pullback into the upward trendline
next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a downward trendline defining the bearish momentum on this
timeframe. The sellers will likely continue to lean on the trendline to push
into new lows, while the buyers will look for a break higher to increase the
bullish bets into the 151.00 handle next. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we get the latest US Jobless Claims figures, the US
PPI and the US Retail Sales data. We will also hear from Fed Chair Powell, so
it’s worth to keep an eye on that in case he delivers some market moving
comments. Tomorrow, we conclude the week with the Japanese Q1 GDP report and
the University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment survey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU trade commissioner Šefčovič says will meet with Lutnick at OECD meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-trade-commissioner-efovi-says-will-meet-with-lutnick-at-oecd-meeting-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:38:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-trade-commissioner-efovi-says-will-meet-with-lutnick-at-oecd-meeting-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;EU, US have agreed to intensify contact on trade talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, time&apos;s a wasting. The meeting will only come around in the next three weeks and by then, there will only be five more weeks before the reciprocal tariffs pause times out.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU must respond to US tariffs with unity and determination, says German finance minister</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-must-respond-to-us-tariffs-with-unity-and-determination-says-german-finance-minister-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:29:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-must-respond-to-us-tariffs-with-unity-and-determination-says-german-finance-minister-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We expect that the negotiations will lead to a good result&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But would like to make it clear that we are prepared to act if talks do not succeed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So far, it&apos;s been very slow-going in terms of any progress between the EU and US. Well, to be fair the only countries that are making real progress are the US&apos; closer allies i.e. UK, Japan, India, South Korea. If you think about it, it is a slap in the face to everyone else that China also got the same 10% baseline treatment after all the retaliation by only deciding to sit down and talk. Meanwhile, everyone else had no choice but to get that shoved down their throat even by trying to reconcile instead of retaliating.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Bessent: We are going into a series of negotiations with China</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-bessent-we-are-going-into-a-series-of-negotiations-with-china-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:20:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-bessent-we-are-going-into-a-series-of-negotiations-with-china-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are going into a series of negotiations with China to prevent escalation again.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We now have a mechanism with China counterparts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s nothing new here.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices hold more sluggish at the open today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-hold-more-sluggish-at-the-open-today-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:18:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-hold-more-sluggish-at-the-open-today-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 -0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE -0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This comes as US futures are also holding lower so far on the day. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down 0.5%, with Nasdaq futures down 0.5% and Dow futures down 0.6% currently. It&apos;s a bit of a check back for US stocks after the surging gains all through the week, mainly for tech shares.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: India offered the US a deal, one with zero tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-india-offered-the-us-a-deal-one-with-zero-tariffs-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 07:04:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-india-offered-the-us-a-deal-one-with-zero-tariffs-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That&apos;s a much stronger promise than what was initially reported &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-reportedly-offers-to-cut-tariffs-gap-by-two-thirds-to-seal-trade-deal-with-the-us-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. It will be interesting to see what Trump is offering back in return though. Will India be able to buy an exemption? Or is there still going to be the 10% baseline?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: I think we are getting very close to getting a deal with Iran</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-i-think-we-are-getting-very-close-to-getting-a-deal-with-iran-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:58:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-i-think-we-are-getting-very-close-to-getting-a-deal-with-iran-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With his visit to the Middle East, Trump is turning his attention to other geopolitical matters this week. For markets in general, all of this at least buys further reprieve on the trade front after the US and China settled on a 90-day de-escalation since the weekend. As for the topic itself, Iran continues to defend their stance and not give in though. However, they did at least outline clear terms for accepting a deal but it remains to be seen if Ali Khamenei will be on board if the US can deliver as needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The comments are putting a drag on oil though, with WTI crude down over 3% on the day now to $60.62.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: We&apos;re getting close to doing a deal with Iran</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-were-getting-close-to-doing-a-deal-with-iran-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-were-getting-close-to-doing-a-deal-with-iran-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We&apos;re getting close to doing a deal with Iran.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Iran has agreed to terms; we want them to succeed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We were losing Middle East due to past administration.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had reports overnight suggesting that a deal was coming, so this is not something fresh.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France April final CPI +0.8% vs +0.8% y/y prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-april-final-cpi-08-vs-08-yy-prelim-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:46:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-april-final-cpi-08-vs-08-yy-prelim-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HICP +0.9% vs +0.8% y/y prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Core annual inflation continues to hold steady at 1.3%, the same as in March and February.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:34:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;We have a very busy day ahead on the data front. In the European session, there won&apos;t be that much as we just get the Eurozone Q1 GDP (2nd estimate) and the Eurozone Employment Change data. Both of them are old news and rarely market moving releases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we have lots of data but the main highlights include the US PPI, US Jobless Claims and US Retail Sales. The Core PPI Y/Y is expected at 3.1% vs. 3.3% prior, while the M/M reading is seen at 0.3% vs. -0.1% prior. I think the focus switched back to inflation so watch out for surprises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Initial Claims are expected at 229K vs. 228K prior, while Continuing Claims are seen at 1890K vs. 1879K prior. The US Jobless
Claims continue to be one of the most important releases to follow every week
as it’s a timelier indicator on the state of the labour market.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They haven&apos;t been market moving for several months because the data never surprised. Initial Claims remain below the cycle high at 260K. We will likely need a spike above that level to trigger a market reaction. Some analysts are suggesting we could see higher readings due to some seasonal patterns in the next weeks but as long as we stay below that 260K level, it should be fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Retail Sales M/M is expected at 0.0% vs. 1.5% prior, while the ex-Autos measure is seen at 0.3% vs. 0.6% prior. The Control Group is seen at 0.3% vs. 0.4% prior. I don&apos;t really care about retail sales data myself because it&apos;s a volatile data set. Goldman Sachs expects core retail sales to rise in April as consumers frontloaded purchases ahead of impending tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;06:00 GMT - ECB&apos;s Cipollone (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;06:50 GMT - ECB&apos;s Elderson (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:40 GMT/08:40 ET - Fed Chair Powell (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;14:00 GMT/10:00 ET - BoE&apos;s Dhingra (uber dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;18:05 GMT/14:05 ET - Fed&apos;s Barr (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland April producer and import prices +0.1% vs +0.1% m/m prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-producer-and-import-prices-01-vs-01-mm-prior-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:30:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/switzerland-april-producer-and-import-prices-01-vs-01-mm-prior-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The breakdown shows producer prices rising by 0.2% on the month while import prices were flat in April. Compared to the same month a year ago, the overall index is down 0.5% with the chunk of that owing to a decline in import prices (-1.8%).&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures -0.3% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-03-in-early-european-trading-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:08:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-03-in-early-european-trading-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures -0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;European indices closed lower yesterday and look to follow up on that with another sluggish showing today. This comes as US futures are also running into some exhaustion after the strong surge earlier in the week. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are marked down by 0.3% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany April wholesale price index -0.1% vs -0.2% m/m prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-wholesale-price-index-01-vs-02-mm-prior-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-wholesale-price-index-01-vs-02-mm-prior-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s a marginal decline in wholesale prices on the month but the overall reading remains elevated. Compared to the same month last year, German wholesale prices are seen up 0.8% still.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK March monthly GDP +0.2% vs 0.0% m/m expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-monthly-gdp-02-vs-00-mm-expected-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:00:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-monthly-gdp-02-vs-00-mm-expected-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Services +0.4% vs +0.1% m/m expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Industrial output -0.7% vs -0.5% m/m expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +1.5%; revised to +1.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing output -0.8% vs -0.5% m/m expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.2%; revised to +2.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Construction output +0.5% vs +0.1% m/m expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.4%; revised to +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The focus today is on the quarterly report but the beat on estimates in the March report here is helping to give the former a boost as well. It reaffirms a solid showing in the UK economy in the first quarter of the year at least.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Q1 preliminary GDP +0.7% vs +0.6% q/q expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-q1-preliminary-gdp-07-vs-06-qq-expected-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 06:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-q1-preliminary-gdp-07-vs-06-qq-expected-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The beat comes amid a stronger March monthly report &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-monthly-gdp-02-vs-00-mm-expected-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, hinting at a more solid showing by the UK economy in Q1. The jump in the first quarter is largely led by the services sector, which also expanded by 0.7% on the quarter in terms of output.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, China said to have bilateral engagement on sidelines of APEC conference</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-said-to-have-had-bilateral-engagement-on-sidelines-of-apec-conference-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:45:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-said-to-have-had-bilateral-engagement-on-sidelines-of-apec-conference-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The meeting on the sidelines here is said to involve US trade representative, Jamieson Greer, and China&apos;s trade envoy, Li Chenggang. This as both parties were in attendance of the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) conference. No further details are given on the engagement yet. But considering that it is just a pull aside conversation, there shouldn&apos;t be too much in it.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 15 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-15-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:38:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-15-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There are a couple to take note of on the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The first one is for EUR/USD at the 1.1200 level. That might act as a bit of a magnet in trapping price action in between its key hourly moving averages in the session ahead at least. That especially after the upside run yesterday stalled at the 200-hour moving average. The key technical level is seen at 1.1249 currently with the 100-hour moving average seen at 1.1180.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Then, there is one for AUD/USD at the 0.6475 level. It isn&apos;t one that ties to any technical significance with the pair struggling to get above 0.6500 in the bigger picture for the time being. So, the figure level takes on more importance in terms of limiting upside for the pair at this current point in time. The expiries should have negligible impact but could offer to hold upside during the session at best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And lastly, there is one for NZD/USD at the 0.5880 level. That rests nearby the 200-day moving average of 0.5880 and might offer to keep price action stickier in the session ahead. The lows earlier in the week around 0.5850 will act as a secondary layer of short-term support. But trading sentiment will continue to be largely dictated by risk flows and dollar sentiment still.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJ expected to pause rate hikes through September amid tariffs uncertainty - poll</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-expected-to-pause-rate-hikes-through-september-amid-tariffs-uncertainty-poll-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 04:16:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-expected-to-pause-rate-hikes-through-september-amid-tariffs-uncertainty-poll-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;59 of 62 economists (95%) see no change to interest rates in June meeting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;39 of 58 economists (67%) see interest rates staying unchanged in Q3 (previously 36%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;30 of 58 economists (52%) see at least one more rate hike by year-end&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The median prediction for end-September rate is now 0.50% (previously 0.75%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The median prediction for year-end rate is 0.75% (unchanged)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;16 of 29 economists (55%) either strongly or somewhat approve of the Japanese government&apos;s approach to tariff negotiations with the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In terms of market pricing, traders are seeing ~98% odds of no change in the upcoming meeting in June. As for the year itself, there&apos;s only ~17 bps priced in currently by the final meeting in December. So, that fits with the above view somewhat - at least through Q3.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Oil lower on Iran wanting a deal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-oil-lower-on-iran-wanting-a-deal-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:37:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-oil-lower-on-iran-wanting-a-deal-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-chair-powell-is-speaking-on-thursday-20250515/&quot;&gt;Federal Reserve Chair Powell is speaking on Thursday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-china-will-take-over-taiwan-without-firing-a-shot-20250515/&quot;&gt;How China will take over Taiwan. Without firing a shot.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/apec-sees-trade-policy-volatility-in-april-9-times-greater-than-average-of-20152024-20250515/&quot;&gt;APEC sees trade policy volatility in April 9 times greater than average of 2015–2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/audusd-popped-higher-on-the-huge-beat-in-the-april-jobs-report-20250515/&quot;&gt;AUD/USD popped higher on the huge beat in the April jobs report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-april-2025-unemployment-rate-41-vs-41-expected-employment-change-890k-20250515/&quot;&gt;Australia April 2025 unemployment rate 4.1% (vs. 4.1% expected) &amp;amp; Employment Change +89.0K&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71963-vs-estimate-at-72217-20250515/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1963 (vs. estimate at 7.2217)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-inflation-expectations-survey-for-may-2025-41-prior-42-20250515/&quot;&gt;Australia Inflation Expectations survey for May 2025: 4.1% (prior 4.2%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/chinese-financial-media-reports-again-that-there-is-room-for-cuts-to-the-rrr-this-year-20250515/&quot;&gt;Chinese financial media reports, again, that there is room for cuts to the RRR  this year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-10-year-yield-rises-to-its-highest-in-a-month-at-455-20250515/&quot;&gt;US Treasury 10-year yield rises to its highest in a month at 4.55%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/ubs-sees-sees-further-upside-for-technology-stocks-but-note-4-risks-20250514/&quot;&gt;UBS sees sees further upside for technology stocks but note 4 risks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-food-price-index-for-april-08-mm-prior-05-20250514/&quot;&gt;New Zealand Food Price Index for April +0.8% m/m (prior +0.5%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil, Iran:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-on-iran-is-ready-to-sign-a-nuclear-deal-if-sanctions-lifted-20250514/&quot;&gt;More on &quot;Iran is ready to sign a nuclear deal&quot; if sanctions lifted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/media-reports-that-iran-is-ready-to-sign-an-agreement-for-relief-from-sanctions-20250514/&quot;&gt;Media reports that Iran is ready to sign an agreement for relief from sanctions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/more-from-feds-daly-cant-give-forward-guidance-now-due-to-uncertainty-20250514/&quot;&gt;More from Fed&apos;s Daly - can&apos;t give forward guidance now due to uncertainty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/point72s-steve-cohen-says-the-us-is-not-in-recession-yet-fed-will-be-slow-to-cut-20250514/&quot;&gt;Point72&apos;s Steve Cohen says the US is not in recession ... yet. Fed will be slow to cut.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-daly-business-is-cautious-amidst-the-economic-uncertainty-but-not-stalling-out-20250514/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Daly: Business is cautious amidst the economic uncertainty, but not &quot;stalling out&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/citi-edge-their-0-3-month-brent-crude-forecast-slightly-higher-20250514/&quot;&gt;Citi edge their 0 - 3 month Brent crude forecast slightly higher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/foot-locker-shares-jump-higher-dicks-sporting-goods-is-close-to-acquiring-20250514/&quot;&gt;Foot Locker shares jump higher -  Dick’s Sporting Goods is close to acquiring&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/deutsche-bank-says-us-equities-to-maintain-short-term-outperformance-amid-tariff-pause-20250514/&quot;&gt;Deutsche Bank says U.S. equities to maintain short-term outperformance amid tariff pause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-14-may-the-usd-rebounds-from-earlier-declines-gold-lower-20250514/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 14 May: The USD rebounds from earlier declines. Gold lower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymichina-tightens-full-chain-control-on-strategic-minerals-to-bolster-national-security-20250514/&quot;&gt;ICYMI:China tightens full-chain control on strategic minerals to bolster national security&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-thursday-15-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250514/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Thursday, 15 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
Oil
prices dropped quickly in early Asia after significant comments from
a top
adviser to Iran’s Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei. He
said that Iran
would agree
to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;never
making nuclear weapons&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;getting
rid of its stockpiles of highly-enriched uranium&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;allow
international inspectors to supervise the process&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;in
exchange for the immediate lifting of all economic sanctions on Iran. He said Iran was ready to sign such an agreement today. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;After
the drop price falls extended lower, an oil chart is posted below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;News
flow was light otherwise. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;From
Australia we had a the latest employment report, for April. 89,000
jobs were added, the biggest monthly increase in 14 months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;59,500
of those full-time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
unemployment rate held steady at 4.1%, not too far off 5-decade lows.
The participation rate rose to a record high 67.1%, meaning more
entrants into the labour market keeping the jobless rate unchanged on
the month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
Reserve Bank of Australia meet next week, May 19 and 20, and despite
this solid jobs report are still expected to cut their cash rate by
25bp. The
Australian dollar popped a few points after the data release but
there has been no extentison higher as yet. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;EUR,
GBP, NZD, CAD are all a little higher on the session. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;USD/JPY
lost some ground on no news or data flow. As I post its testing its session lows around 146.00.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Gold
lost further ground on the session. China has been a reliable buyer
during the timezone but supportive flows from there have diminished. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;US
Treasury yields rose higher. Markets are questioning whether the rise
in yield reflects expectations of better growth ahead, or
expectations of some sort of reckoning to come with US debt
continuing to skyrocket. Trump’s plan had been to replace income
taxes with tariff revenue, to control the US debt/GDP ratio, but,
while tax cuts are still being planned, the tariff revenue dream is
looking lost. 
&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve Chair Powell is speaking on Thursday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-chair-powell-is-speaking-on-thursday-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 03:02:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-chair-powell-is-speaking-on-thursday-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;At 0840 US Eastern time (1240 GMT) Powell speaks on the Bank&apos;s &quot;Framework Review&quot; (the Fed does this review every 5 years):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;it analyses the Bank&apos;s approach to monetary policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;We are open to new ideas and critical feedback and will take onboard lessons from the last five years and adapt our approach where appropriate to best serve the American people, to whom we are accountable,&quot; Fed Chair Jerome Powell said in a statement when the review was announced last year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;the Fed&apos;s 2% inflation goal &quot;will not be a focus of the review&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How China will take over Taiwan. Without firing a shot.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-china-will-take-over-taiwan-without-firing-a-shot-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:48:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-china-will-take-over-taiwan-without-firing-a-shot-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;This is not directly about financial markets, but it might be of interest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of the current discourse on Taiwan centres around one scenario: war. The prevailing imagery involves amphibious landings, missile strikes, and an Indo-Pacific showdown with global ramifications. Yet the most plausible outcome may be the one least discussed: China could secure Taiwan without firing a shot.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;... victory can be achieved not through kinetic escalation but through the slow erosion of political cohesion, economic independence, and societal confidence, all without triggering a Western military response. The signs are already visible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goal is not to convince Taiwan that reunification is just. It is to persuade it that reunification is unavoidable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is the link if you want to read it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lowyinstitute.org/the-interpreter/beiping-model-how-china-could-absorb-taiwan-without-war&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The Beiping model: How China
could absorb Taiwan without a war&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APEC sees trade policy volatility in April 9 times greater than average of 2015–2024</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/apec-sees-trade-policy-volatility-in-april-9-times-greater-than-average-of-20152024-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 02:23:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/apec-sees-trade-policy-volatility-in-april-9-times-greater-than-average-of-20152024-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Trade representatives of APEC member economies are meeting today and tomorrow. To discuss multilateral trade and other cooperation agendas, including reforms of the World Trade Organization. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Headlines via Reuters: APEC sees regional GDP growth for 2025 at 2.6% down from 3.3% earlier&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sees export growth for 2025 at 0.4% versus 5.7% in 2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sees unprecedented rise in trade policy uncertainty fueled by frictions amplifies risks to growth for trade-dependent economies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sees trade policy volatility in April is 9 times greater than average of 2015–2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Export outlook downgrade due largely to US tariffs &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;APEC stands for Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
It is a regional economic forum established in 1989 to promote free trade and economic cooperation throughout the Asia-Pacific region. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;APEC has 21 member economies, including the United States, China, Japan, Australia, and most major economies bordering the Pacific Ocean.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUD/USD popped higher on the huge beat in the April jobs report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/audusd-popped-higher-on-the-huge-beat-in-the-april-jobs-report-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 01:49:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/audusd-popped-higher-on-the-huge-beat-in-the-april-jobs-report-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Australian April 2025 jobs data is here:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-april-2025-unemployment-rate-41-vs-41-expected-employment-change-890k-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Australia April 2025 unemployment rate 4.1% (vs. 4.1% expected) &amp;amp; Employment Change +89.0K&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;89,000 jobs were added, thebiggest monthly increase in 14 months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;59,500 of those full-time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s a strong, strong result. The consensus analyst expectation was for 20,000 jobs to be added, so the result was more than 4 times that. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking some shine off the result is the unemployment rate steady at 4.1%, so no inroads into the jobless rate. Still 4.1% is not too far off 5 decade lows. The participation rate rose to a record high 67.1%. More entrants into the l;about market has held the jobless rate steady. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I said in the data post, this report ushers in the prospect of no rate cut from the Reserve Bank of Australia next week. the Bank meets on May 19 and 20 and expectations have been wide for a 25bp rate cut. Those expectations will wobble a little on this report. Add in a calming in markets after the US-China ceasefire in Trump&apos;s trade tariff war and its not difficult seeing the RBA holding steady. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this stage I&apos;m still in the 25bp rate cut camp. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Australian dollar popped a few points higher on the report, but so far with no follow-through. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S DALY: MONETARY POLICY WELL-POSITIONED, MODERATELY RESTRICTIVE

DALY: BUSINESSES ARE CAUTIOUS AMID UNCERTAINTY, BUT NOT STALLING OUT

DALY: SOLID GROWTH, SOLID LABOR MARKET, DECLINING INFLATION

DALY: THAT&apos;S WHERE WE WANT TO BE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922771734987514101#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922771734987514101#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S DALY: MONETARY POLICY WELL-POSITIONED, MODERATELY RESTRICTIVE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
DALY: BUSINESSES ARE CAUTIOUS AMID UNCERTAINTY, BUT NOT STALLING OUT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
DALY: SOLID GROWTH, SOLID LABOR MARKET, DECLINING INFLATION&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
DALY: THAT&apos;S WHERE WE WANT TO BE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WE WILL DO THINGS FOR QATAR THAT THEY WILL BE HAPPY ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922730546410471632#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:07:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922730546410471632#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WE WILL DO THINGS FOR QATAR THAT THEY WILL BE HAPPY ABOUT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: WHEN BESSENT GOES ON TV, EVERYTHING GOES UP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922729313696145419#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922729313696145419#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: WHEN BESSENT GOES ON TV, EVERYTHING GOES UP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 📊 MARKETS NOW EXPECT 2 RATE CUTS IN 2025

Kalshi’s latest forecast shows 2 rate cuts priced in for 2025, a sharp reset from the 4–5 cuts expected earlier this year. Sticky inflation, tight labor markets, and cautious Fed guidance are forcing traders to rethink the easing cycle.

Is the market underestimating recession risks — or is the Fed done cutting?
https://kalshi.com/markets/kxratecutcount/number-of-rate-cuts</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922697283037970660#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:55:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922697283037970660#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;📊 MARKETS NOW EXPECT 2 RATE CUTS IN 2025&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Kalshi’s latest forecast shows 2 rate cuts priced in for 2025, a sharp reset from the 4–5 cuts expected earlier this year. Sticky inflation, tight labor markets, and cautious Fed guidance are forcing traders to rethink the easing cycle.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Is the market underestimating recession risks — or is the Fed done cutting?&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://kalshi.com/markets/kxratecutcount/number-of-rate-cuts&quot;&gt;kalshi.com/markets/kxratecut…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:8080/pic/media%2FGq7K-FSWUAARJ5T.png&quot; style=&quot;max-width:250px;&quot; /&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US NOT SEEKING TO WEAKEN DOLLAR AS PART OF TRADE DEALS: SOURCE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922693791418298414#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:41:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922693791418298414#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US NOT SEEKING TO WEAKEN DOLLAR AS PART OF TRADE DEALS: SOURCE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE BANS US AGENCIES FROM G-20 WORK IN http://S.AFRICA:WAPO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922679354821075403#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:44:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922679354821075403#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE BANS US AGENCIES FROM G-20 WORK IN &lt;a href=&quot;http://S.AFRICA&quot;&gt;S.AFRICA&lt;/a&gt;:WAPO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - TESLA SHARES EXTEND GAINS, LAST UP 4%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922678753945067597#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:41:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922678753945067597#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - TESLA SHARES EXTEND GAINS, LAST UP 4%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP SECURES HISTORIC $1.2 TRILLION ECONOMIC COMMITMENT IN QATAR -FACT SHEET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922676409668960446#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922676409668960446#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP SECURES HISTORIC $1.2 TRILLION ECONOMIC COMMITMENT IN QATAR -FACT SHEET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) NISSAN WEIGHS MOVING SENTRA PRODUCTION FROM MEXICO TO U.S. TO AVOID TARIFFS - AUTOMOTIVE NEWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922675711673852194#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:29:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922675711673852194#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NISSAN WEIGHS MOVING SENTRA PRODUCTION FROM MEXICO TO U.S. TO AVOID TARIFFS - AUTOMOTIVE NEWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HOTLINE CONNECTING PENTAGON AND FAA AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLERS AT WASHINGTON REAGAN AIRPORT HAS BEEN INOPERABLE SINCE 2022 -- FAA OFFICIAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922674286122164547#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:24:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922674286122164547#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HOTLINE CONNECTING PENTAGON AND FAA AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLERS AT WASHINGTON REAGAN AIRPORT HAS BEEN INOPERABLE SINCE 2022 -- FAA OFFICIAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - ELON MUSK MEETS WITH QATAR INVESTMENT AUTHORITY CHAIRMAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922672142539165960#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:15:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922672142539165960#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - ELON MUSK MEETS WITH QATAR INVESTMENT AUTHORITY CHAIRMAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUSSIA&apos;S LAVROV WILL NOT TAKE PART IN TALKS IN ISTANBUL - KOMMERSANT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922665257815703673#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:48:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922665257815703673#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUSSIA&apos;S LAVROV WILL NOT TAKE PART IN TALKS IN ISTANBUL - KOMMERSANT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KENNEDY SAYS HIS OPINIONS ABOUT VACCINES ARE IRRELEVANT, DOES NOT THINK PEOPLE SHOULD TAKE MEDICAL ADVICE FROM HIM</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922662579475714503#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:37:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922662579475714503#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KENNEDY SAYS HIS OPINIONS ABOUT VACCINES ARE IRRELEVANT, DOES NOT THINK PEOPLE SHOULD TAKE MEDICAL ADVICE FROM HIM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA SUSPENDS, SCRAPS UNRELIABLE LIST POLICIES ON SOME US COS.

*CHINA SUSPENDS EXPORTS CONTROL OVER 28 US ENTITIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922658190602219793#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:20:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922658190602219793#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA SUSPENDS, SCRAPS UNRELIABLE LIST POLICIES ON SOME US COS.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*CHINA SUSPENDS EXPORTS CONTROL OVER 28 US ENTITIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *WITKOFF SAYS HE, RUBIO TO TRAVEL TO ISTANBUL ON FRIDAY: RTRS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922657903158173812#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922657903158173812#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*WITKOFF SAYS HE, RUBIO TO TRAVEL TO ISTANBUL ON FRIDAY: RTRS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRADE-TARIFF DEALS WITH JAPAN AND SOUTH KOREA SAID TO BE “CLOSE”: SOURCES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922657301279682846#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:16:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922657301279682846#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRADE-TARIFF DEALS WITH JAPAN AND SOUTH KOREA SAID TO BE “CLOSE”: SOURCES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) QATAR AGREES TO BUY 160 BOEING AIRCRAFT: WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922656057886642672#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:11:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922656057886642672#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;QATAR AGREES TO BUY 160 BOEING AIRCRAFT: WHITE HOUSE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA PAUSES EXPORT CONTROL MEASURES AGAINST 28 US ENTITIES FOR 90 DAYS FROM MAY 14-COMMERCE MINISTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922655347472282066#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:08:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922655347472282066#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA PAUSES EXPORT CONTROL MEASURES AGAINST 28 US ENTITIES FOR 90 DAYS FROM MAY 14-COMMERCE MINISTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA PAUSES UNRELIABLE ENTITY LIST MEASURE ON 17 US ENTITIES-COMMERCE MINISTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922655109307056431#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:07:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922655109307056431#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA PAUSES UNRELIABLE ENTITY LIST MEASURE ON 17 US ENTITIES-COMMERCE MINISTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $BA - TRUMP: BOEING AGREEMENT IS FOR OVER $200 BLN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922654805232640396#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:06:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922654805232640396#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23BA&quot;&gt;$BA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP: BOEING AGREEMENT IS FOR OVER $200 BLN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
