<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Nippon Steel says position on planned acquisition of US Steel remains unchanged</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/nippon-steel-says-position-on-planned-acquisition-of-us-steel-remains-unchanged-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:49:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/nippon-steel-says-position-on-planned-acquisition-of-us-steel-remains-unchanged-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Taking all stake continues to be the starting point for negotiations with the US government&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;We are presenting a range of proposals in talks with the US government&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;CFIUS expected to make a recommendation to US Steel deal to Trump by 21 May&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;A decision by Trump is expected by 5 June&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;At least now we have some key dates to attach to how things are playing out on this matter. As a reminder, Biden blocked the deal as one of his final acts as president. And in his most recent comments last month, Trump said that &quot;we don&apos;t want to see it go to Japan&quot;. So, there&apos;s that.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We might have reached the peak in the de-escalation trade</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/we-might-have-reached-the-peak-in-the-de-escalation-trade-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:33:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/we-might-have-reached-the-peak-in-the-de-escalation-trade-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;If this trade deal with the UK was announced two or three weeks ago, I would have said that it&apos;s really good for the markets and would have been very upbeat on risk sentiment. The context is a bit different now, in my opinion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recall back in the middle of April, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/federal-reserve-governor-wallers-strategy-for-dealing-with-tariffs-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Waller&lt;/a&gt; outlined his strategy to deal with tariffs. He had two scenarios in mind: tariffs around 25% on average and tariffs around 10%. The second scenario is the one that is playing out and it involves the Fed being less inclined to cut rates faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the market is taking this first trade deal as the more hawkish scenario for the Fed and the pricing is converging towards the original Fed&apos;s baseline of two rate cuts in 2025 (the pricing is now showing 68 bps by year-end compared to 80 bps at the start of the week). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem here is that with new information throughout the weeks, the 10% has become a &quot;meh&quot; outcome. After April 9 pause, the market rallied on expectations that eventually the US would have gone for 10% reciprocal tariffs and would have lowered the tariffs on China back to the original 50-60% rate. This is what the whole &quot;de-escalation trade&quot; was based on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have now reached the peak in this trade because the US said that the 10% will be the floor for all other deals and we got a report from New York Post yesterday saying that the US is considering lowering the tariffs on China to 50-54%. Recall, the market was expecting 10% global tariffs and 50% on China before the April 2 surprise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this should now be priced in and the market&apos;s reaction to the news of the US lowering tariffs on China could be a hint. In fact, you would have expected a strong rally, but the market actually went in the opposite way. Nonetheless, this has opened up for a weekend risk scenario in which the market opens up with a positive gap next week, so the selling pressure into the weekend could be limited (I mean it doesn&apos;t look good from a risk management perspective for the bears).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what makes this first trade deal a &quot;meh&quot; outcome is that not only we have some overstretched positioning but we also have the risk of retaliation now. The EU has been repeating that they won&apos;t accept the 10% tariff rate and has been threatening a retaliation in case negotiations fail. But the US is saying that 10% is the best anyone can get and tariffs could be even higher. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next week will be the tell. If we open up with a positive gap and the stock market then performs badly throughout the week, then it could be a signal that we have indeed reached the peak (at least in the short term). I would expect the bears to seize the opportunity and start selling at the start of the week. You either catch the top or you get it wrong, but from a risk/reward perspective it doesn&apos;t look bad at all. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equities open higher to start the final day of the week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-open-higher-to-start-the-final-day-of-the-week-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:10:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-open-higher-to-start-the-final-day-of-the-week-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;US futures are also keeping steadier, with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures seen up 0.1%. The US-UK trade deal agreement yesterday helped to steady the ship but it was mostly comments from Trump that caused markets to rally. His mentions of &quot;better go out and buy stocks now&quot; and &quot;the stock market will really rally now&quot; were what got the animal spirits pumped up.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDJPY Technical Analysis – Waller’s scenario #2 is playing out. Now what?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-wallers-scenario-2-is-playing-out-now-what-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 07:00:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-wallers-scenario-2-is-playing-out-now-what-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD got a boost across
the board yesterday on positive expectations about the first trade deal that
eventually was revealed to be with the UK. Trump &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-reached-breakthrough-deal-with-uk-20250508/&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt;
that tariffs on cars and steel will be lowered but the most important part was
that the 10% “global tariff” will remain in place. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US officials
highlighted that the 10% is going to be the floor and the trade deal with the
UK is going to be the baseline for all other deals. There’s a risk now that we
reached the peak in de-escalation and other countries might not like the 10%
floor, especially the EU. For now, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/federal-reserve-governor-wallers-strategy-for-dealing-with-tariffs-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Federal Reserve Governor Waller’s scenario&lt;/a&gt;
#2 is playing out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recall, that he said 10% or
lower tariffs would make him less inclined to cut rates faster. This is now triggering
a repricing in interest rates as the market scaled back the easing expectations
to 68 bps by year-end. We were at more than 80 bps at the start of the week. It
gave also the greenback a boost as the market unwound the crowded dollar
shorts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the JPY side, the
currency has been driven mainly by global events rather than domestic
fundamentals. Alongside the Swiss Franc, it’s been the favoured safe haven in
the currencies space amid the swings in risk sentiment. On the monetary policy
front, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;BoJ&lt;/a&gt; kept interest rates unchanged as expected and
delivered a dovish message. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was then echoed by BoJ
Governor Ueda which placed a great deal on trade developments. In summary, the
central bank is likely to go faster on rate hikes in case we get a good trade
deal and delay rate adjustments in case the trade deal disappoints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that USDJPY continues to erase the April losses and it’s now approaching
the major trendline. The sellers will likely lean on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt; with a defined risk above it to
position for a drop back into the 140.00 handle, while the buyers will look for
a break higher to increase the bullish bets into the 151.00 handle next. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see that we have now an upward trendline defining the bullish structure on this
timeframe. From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a better
risk to reward setup around the trendline, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into new lows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor upward trendline defining the bullish momentum on this
timeframe. The buyers will likely continue to lean on the trendline to keep pushing
into new highs, while the sellers will look for a break lower to extend the
pullback into the next trendline. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Rehn: Disinflation is on track and the growth outlook is weakening</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-rehn-disinflation-is-on-track-and-the-growth-outlook-is-weakening-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-rehn-disinflation-is-on-track-and-the-growth-outlook-is-weakening-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The usual commentary is continuing by the ECB for the time being. Traders are pricing in a ~90% probability of a rate cut for their next policy decision in June. So, there&apos;s not much change to the rhetoric and narrative for now.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China foreign ministry reaffirms that US should respect international trade rules</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-foreign-ministry-reaffirms-that-us-should-respect-international-trade-rules-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:48:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-foreign-ministry-reaffirms-that-us-should-respect-international-trade-rules-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This is as what you&apos;d expect from China ahead of the talks tomorrow. The question now is, are we going to see the US drop its tariff levels before both sides sit down at the table over the weekend? It&apos;s certainly a consideration, particularly after this report &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/white-house-weighing-plan-to-slash-china-tariffs-to-as-low-as-50-report-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That will help to at least try and build a starting point for trade discussions. But knowing China, they won&apos;t accept anything less than going back to where things were before. So, we&apos;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:21:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, we have a pretty empty agenda with just a couple of low tier data releases that won&apos;t be market-moving. In the American session, we get the Canadian Employment report which is expected to show 2.5K jobs added in April and the Unemployment Rate to tick higher to 6.8% vs. 6.7% prior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s the day after the outline of the first trade deal and we have expectations for the US lowering the tariffs on China over the weekend so that&apos;s gonna be the main theme going into the weekend. As always, watch out for tariff related news throughout the day, especially potential retaliatory threats from other countries (EU) as the US stated that the 10% rate is going to be the floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:40 GMT/04:40 ET - BoE&apos;s Bailey (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;09:55 GMT/05:55 ET - Fed&apos;s Barr (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10:45 GMT/06:45 ET - Fed&apos;s Kugler (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:30 GMT/08:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Barkin (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:30 GMT/08:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Williams (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;14:00 GMT/10:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Goolsbee (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;15:30 GMT/11:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Waller (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;23:45 GMT/19:45 ET - Fed&apos;s Cook (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;23:45 GMT/19:45 ET - ECB&apos;s Schnabel (neutral - voter)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +0.3% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-03-in-early-european-trading-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 06:09:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-03-in-early-european-trading-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are seen up 0.1% following the gains yesterday, though the run higher in Wall Street was rather middling in the end. Looking to the day ahead, all eyes will be on any headlines in the build up to US-China talks over the weekend. You can surely expect Trump to say something before we wrap things up on the week.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 9 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-9-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 05:31:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-9-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There are a couple to take note of on the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The first one is for EUR/USD at the 1.1200 mark. Amid a firmer dollar, the expiries here could help to act as a bit of a floor for price action before we get to US trading. That is considering the likely quieter period in European trading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Then, there is one for USD/JPY at the 145.00 level but it isn&apos;t one that ties to any technical significance. But the expiries could also keep a floor on price action, amid some extension of the range in play during the session ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;However, dollar and broader risk sentiment remains the bigger driver at the moment. So if we do see risk pick up, expect that to underpin the greenback as well with the expiries taking a backseat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All eyes today though will be on any follow up trade headlines ahead of US-China talks over the weekend. That overrides everything else before we look to close out the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan March leading indicator index 107.7 vs 108.2 prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/japan-march-leading-indicator-index-1077-vs-1082-prior-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 05:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/japan-march-leading-indicator-index-1077-vs-1082-prior-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coincident index 116.0&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 117.3&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The assessment of the coincident index remains the same as before, seen as &quot;halting to fall&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did US tariffs impact China&apos;s latest trade numbers?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-did-us-tariffs-impact-chinas-latest-trade-numbers-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 04:21:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-did-us-tariffs-impact-chinas-latest-trade-numbers-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In overall terms, the numbers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-january-april-yuan-denominated-exports-75-yy-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; were much better than expected as China exports in particular held up. However, the devil is always in the details. China&apos;s exports to the US actually fell by nearly 18% on the month from March to April. So, what gives?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It is basically this: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-china-has-been-preparing-itself-ahead-of-this-tariffs-eventuality-with-the-us-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;How China has been preparing itself ahead of this tariffs eventuality with the US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;China is pretty much just rerouting goods by origin washing as exports to Vietnam especially surged on the month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The good news for the US is that perhaps this might even just be a temporary thing. After speaking to US retailers last week, Trump looks to have given some assurance of sorts as we&apos;re starting to even see a pick up in China container ships leaving for the US now:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Is this a start of a return to some form of new normality? If so, it&apos;s possibly a hint that the US will lower China tariffs as we look to talks over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: China April exports not as bad as feared</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-china-april-exports-not-as-bad-as-feared-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 03:55:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-china-april-exports-not-as-bad-as-feared-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/aud-popped-above-06400-after-better-than-expected-china-exports-data-be-careful-folks-20250509/&quot;&gt;AUD popped above 0.6400 after better than expected China exports data ... be careful folks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article-slot__title title top&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-january-april-yuan-denominated-exports-75-yy-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China January - April yuan denominated exports +7.5% y/y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expects-bank-of-england-hold-at-the-june-meeting-20250509/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs expects Bank of England hold at the June meeting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-vice-foreign-minister-hua-on-us-trade-talks-come-on-we-have-no-fear-20250509/&quot;&gt;China Vice Foreign Minister Hua: On US trade talks ... ‘come on. We have no fear.’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-to-establish-a-fast-track-program-for-foreign-investors-20250509/&quot;&gt;US Treasury to establish a fast track program for foreign investors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/fed-speakers-friday-williams-barr-kugler-barking-goolsbee-cook-hammack-musalem-20250509/&quot;&gt;Fed speakers Friday: Williams, Barr, Kugler, Barkin, Goolsbee, Cook, Hammack, Musalem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-smic-warns-of-weak-q2-amid-trade-uncertainty-projects-revenue-decline-20250509/&quot;&gt;China&apos;s SMIC warns of weak Q2 amid trade uncertainty, projects revenue decline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-schnabel-is-speaking-after-market-close-on-friday-20250509/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Schnabel is speaking after market close on Friday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72095-vs-estimate-at-72581-20250509/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.2095 (vs. estimate at 7.2581)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-england-governor-andrew-bailey-is-speaking-on-friday-20250509/&quot;&gt;Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey is speaking on Friday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-weighs-nationwide-ban-on-home-pre-sales-to-stabilise-property-market-20250509/&quot;&gt;China weighs nationwide ban on home pre-sales to stabilise property market&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-not-appropriate-to-lower-consumption-tax-20250508/&quot;&gt;Japan finance minister Kato: Not appropriate to lower consumption tax&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/westpac-forecast-rbnz-rate-cut-of-25bp-in-may-and-25bp-cut-in-july-20250508/&quot;&gt;Westpac forecast RBNZ rate cut of 25bp in May and 25bp cut in July&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-data-march-household-spending-21-yy-expected-02-prior-05-20250508/&quot;&gt;Japan data - March household spending +2.1% y/y (expected +0.2%, prior -0.5%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-data-march-labor-cash-earnings-21-yy-expected-23-prior-31-20250508/&quot;&gt;Japan data - March Labor Cash Earnings +2.1% y/y (expected +2.3%, prior +3.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tesla-has-scrapped-the-range-extender-accessory-it-was-making-for-cybertrucks-20250508/&quot;&gt;Tesla has scrapped the range extender accessory it was making for Cybertrucks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/standard-chartered-say-they-were-wrong-on-us120k-btc-q2-forecast-too-low-20250508/&quot;&gt;Standard Chartered say they were wrong on US$120K BTC Q2 forecast - too low!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/preview-china-export-growth-likely-slowed-sharply-to-19-yy-in-april-124-in-march-20250508/&quot;&gt;Preview: China export growth likely slowed sharply to +1.9% y/y in April (+12.4% in March)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-hits-a-high-circa-us104k-20250508/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin hits a high circa US$104K&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-intends-to-buy-around-us900-million-of-soybeans-corn-vegetable-oil-from-argentina-20250508/&quot;&gt;China intends to buy around US$900 million of soybeans, corn, vegetable oil from Argentina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-8-mayuk-in-the-news-boe-cuts-uk-makes-trade-deal-w-us-20250508/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 8 May:UK in the news. BOE cuts. UK makes trade deal w/ US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/lutnick-says-the-uk-deal-helps-wants-a-trade-deal-with-a-big-country-from-asia-20250508/&quot;&gt;Lutnick says the UK deal helps, wants a trade deal with a big country from Asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/lutnick-says-the-best-any-country-can-do-is-a-10-us-tariff-20250508/&quot;&gt;Lutnick says the best any country can do is a 10% US tariff&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/major-us-indices-close-higher-for-the-second-consecutive-day-20250508/&quot;&gt;Major US indices close higher for the second consecutive day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-friday-9-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250508/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Friday, 9 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;252&quot; data-end=&quot;464&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trade policy developments, weak Japanese wage data, and surprisingly strong Chinese exports were key themes in Asia today, ahead of a high-stakes weekend meeting between U.S. and Chinese officials in Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;468&quot; data-end=&quot;805&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;U.S. Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick said new trade deals with Japan and South Korea may take significantly longer to conclude than the recently announced UK framework agreement. The comments signal a slower path ahead for deepening trade ties in Asia. Lutnick also said that 10% tariffs were the lowest countries could hope for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;809&quot; data-end=&quot;1134&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Japan’s real wages fell 2.1% year-on-year in March, marking the third straight monthly decline and the steepest drop in two years. The data underscores continued pressure on household purchasing power and complicates the Bank of Japan’s case for normalising policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1138&quot; data-end=&quot;1555&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Chinese Vice Foreign Minister Hua Chunying struck a defiant tone ahead of trade talks, saying Beijing has “no fear” in the face of U.S. tariffs and calling Washington’s current policy unsustainable. Her remarks come as China and the U.S. prepare for their first high-level talks aimed at easing tensions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1557&quot; data-end=&quot;1895&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China’s latest trade data showed exports jumped 8.1% y/y in April, well above expectations (Reuters poll consensus was 1.9%) and continuing from a strong March when exporters moved swiftly ahead of tariff hikes. Imports fell a modest 0.2%, a smaller decline than forecast and an improvement from March, though underlying domestic demand remains weak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1897&quot; data-end=&quot;2067&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China&apos;s goods trade totalled 14.14 trillion yuan ($1.96 trillion) in the first four months, up 2.4% year-on-year, with the pace of growth picking up slightly from Q1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2071&quot; data-end=&quot;2249&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin climbed toward USD 104,000 amid reports that El Salvador had resumed government purchases. The move spilled into other cryptocurrencies as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2071&quot; data-end=&quot;2249&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2071&quot; data-end=&quot;2249&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Major FX rates traded in a subdued fashion after a hectic week. Gold bounced from under $3280. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2071&quot; data-end=&quot;2249&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin update:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUD popped above 0.6400 after better than expected China exports data ... be careful folks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/aud-popped-above-06400-after-better-than-expected-china-exports-data-be-careful-folks-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 03:30:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/aud-popped-above-06400-after-better-than-expected-china-exports-data-be-careful-folks-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The numbers are here, exports did not plunge as feared. They were lower than in March, but the pipelines were jammed full in March ahead of more Trump tariffs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-january-april-yuan-denominated-exports-75-yy-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;April figures, in US dollar terms: exports +8.1% y/y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Putting on my sceptical hat for a minute .... &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are sometimes questions about the veracity of Chinese data. This has been ramped a little higher in the present environment, especially going into the weekend when the US and China begin tentative trade talks. Neither side wants to display weakness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the US its been bluster about a stack of deals coming in in the weeks ahead (yeah, right), supported by a lack lustre &apos;framework&apos; of an agreement&apos; with the UK. From China we had tough talk just today:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-vice-foreign-minister-hua-on-us-trade-talks-come-on-we-have-no-fear-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China Vice Foreign Minister Hua: On US trade talks ... ‘come on. We have no fear.’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;And now we get decent export numbers? And ... the data came out as scheduled whereas normally we are kept waiting and waiting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyway, make up your own mind, but I&apos;m sceptical. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD off its low:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China January  - April yuan denominated exports +7.5% y/y</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-january-april-yuan-denominated-exports-75-yy-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 03:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-january-april-yuan-denominated-exports-75-yy-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China January  - April yuan-denominated exports +7.5% y/y, imports -4.2% y/y&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For April alone, yuan-denominated&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;exports +9.3% (prior +13.5%) ... this is a good result given the tariff impact, if the data is correct&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;imports +0.8% y/y (prior -3.5%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jan–Apr dollar-denominated exports +6.4% y/y&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jan–Apr dollar-denominated imports -5.2% y/y-customs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Jan–Apr trade balance $ +368.76 bln&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jan - April trade surplus with the US is $97.07bn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;April figures, in US dollar terms:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;exports +8.1% y/y&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;imports -0.2% y/y &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;trade balance is a surplus of 96.18bn USD&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;trade surplus with the US is 20.46bn USD&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs expects Bank of England hold at the June meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expects-bank-of-england-hold-at-the-june-meeting-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 02:55:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expects-bank-of-england-hold-at-the-june-meeting-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs now expects BoE to hold interest rates at the June meeting (Thursday, 19 June) vs prior forecast of a 25 bp cut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expects BoE to cut rates at every meeting from August 2025 and reach 2.75% terminal rate in March 2026&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Bank cut yesterday:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-cuts-bank-rate-by-25-bps-to-425-as-expected-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;BOE cuts bank rate by 25 bps to 4.25%, as expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-governor-bailey-interest-rates-are-not-on-auto-pilot-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;BOE governor Bailey: Interest rates are not on auto-pilot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-governor-bailey-dont-know-what-to-expect-from-uk-us-trade-deal-for-now-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;BOE governor Bailey: Don&apos;t know what to expect from UK-US trade deal for now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Vice Foreign Minister Hua: On US trade talks ... ‘come on. We have no fear.’</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-vice-foreign-minister-hua-on-us-trade-talks-come-on-we-have-no-fear-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 02:49:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-vice-foreign-minister-hua-on-us-trade-talks-come-on-we-have-no-fear-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China Vice Foreign Minister Hua:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;United States cannot ‘sustain what it is doing’ in trade policy
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China has ‘full confidence’ in its ability to manage US trade issues
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China does not want a ‘war of any kind with any other country’
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China has ‘full capability to overcome difficulties’ amid trade war
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;‘Ordinary people’ in China do not want trade war but are confident
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On US trade talks, ‘if we have to face up to reality, come on. We have no fear.’&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;China and the US meet in Geneva this weekend to take the first steps, tentative I imagine, on trade talks. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Treasury to establish a fast track program for foreign investors</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-to-establish-a-fast-track-program-for-foreign-investors-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 02:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-to-establish-a-fast-track-program-for-foreign-investors-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;ICYMI, on Thursday the U.S. Treasury announced it will launch a fast track process to encourage investment from allied and partner nations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;162&quot; data-end=&quot;301&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;164&quot; data-end=&quot;301&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A &quot;Known Investor&quot; portal will be introduced to allow foreign investors to submit information to CFIUS in advance of a formal filing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;302&quot; data-end=&quot;374&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;304&quot; data-end=&quot;374&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The initiative will begin as a pilot program and expand over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;375&quot; data-end=&quot;519&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;377&quot; data-end=&quot;519&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The effort aligns with the America First Investment Policy, aimed at boosting investment from trusted sources while screening out threats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;520&quot; data-end=&quot;630&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;522&quot; data-end=&quot;630&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Treasury seeks to improve efficiency in the CFIUS review process without compromising national security.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;631&quot; data-end=&quot;790&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;633&quot; data-end=&quot;790&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent emphasized the importance of stable, secure investments from allies and maintaining an open investment environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed speakers Friday: Williams, Barr, Kugler, Barkin, Goolsbee, Cook, Hammack, Musalem</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/fed-speakers-friday-williams-barr-kugler-barking-goolsbee-cook-hammack-musalem-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 02:26:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/fed-speakers-friday-williams-barr-kugler-barking-goolsbee-cook-hammack-musalem-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The times listed below are in GMT/US Eastern time format&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;0955/0555 Federal Reserve Board Governor Michael Barr speaks on &quot;Artificial Intelligence and the Labor Market&quot; before the Reykjavik Economic Conference organized by the Central Bank of Iceland&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1045/0645  Federal Reserve Board Governor Adriana Kugler speaks on &quot;Maximum Employment&quot; before the Reykjavik Economic Conference&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1230/0830 Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond President Thomas Barkin participates in a fireside chat before the Loudon County Chamber of Commerce &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1230/0830 Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams speaks before the Reykjavik Economic Conference &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1400/1000 Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago President Austen Goolsbee gives welcome and opening remarks before the &quot;Fed Listens: Perspectives from the Midwest&quot; event &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1530/1130 (via pre-recorded video) Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams speaks on &quot;Taylor Rules in Policy before the Hoover Monetary Policy Conference &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2345/1945 Federal Reserve Board Governor Lisa Cook, Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Beth Hammack, Federal Reserve Bank of St Louis President Alberto Musalem participate in monetary policy panel before the Hoover Monetary Policy Conference &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I highlighted the two speaking engagements for Williams. As head of the New York Fed Williams is Vice-Chair of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) (Powell is Chair) and a permanent voter. As governors, Barr, Kugler, and Cook also have permanent votes,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Willaims and Powell&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China&apos;s SMIC warns of weak Q2 amid trade uncertainty, projects revenue decline</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-smic-warns-of-weak-q2-amid-trade-uncertainty-projects-revenue-decline-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 02:08:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-smic-warns-of-weak-q2-amid-trade-uncertainty-projects-revenue-decline-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China&apos;s semiconductor foundry, Semiconductor Manufacturing International Corporation (SMIC), will closely monitor the impact of tariffs on demand&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;warned of uncertain demand and trade-related risks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;projecting a potential Q2 revenue decline of up to 6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;While U.S. tariffs provided a modest lift in orders, Co-CEO Zhao Haijun noted the overall effect was limited. The company remains vulnerable to U.S.-China trade tensions and global supply chain shifts, with demand visibility for the current quarter still unclear. Investors are watching for broader implications for China’s semiconductor sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Info comes via Reuters.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Schnabel is speaking after market close on Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-schnabel-is-speaking-after-market-close-on-friday-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 01:40:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-schnabel-is-speaking-after-market-close-on-friday-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;2345 GMT / 1945 US Eastern time:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Participation by ECB Board member Isabel Schnabel in panel discussion at Hoover Monetary Policy Conference - Finishing the Job and New Challenges&apos; at Harvard University&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.2095 (vs. estimate at 7.2581)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72095-vs-estimate-at-72581-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 01:18:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72095-vs-estimate-at-72581-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous close was 7.2450 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD/CNY fix has been ticking lower (ie a stronger CNY). I guess this will be something the China side will atn acknowledged in the talks this weekend in Switzerland. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC injects 77bn yuan via 7-day RR, sets rate at 1.4%&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey is speaking on Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-england-governor-andrew-bailey-is-speaking-on-friday-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 01:03:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-england-governor-andrew-bailey-is-speaking-on-friday-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;On Thursday:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-cuts-bank-rate-by-25-bps-to-425-as-expected-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;BOE cuts bank rate by 25 bps to 4.25%, as expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-governor-bailey-interest-rates-are-not-on-auto-pilot-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;BOE governor Bailey: Interest rates are not on auto-pilot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-governor-bailey-dont-know-what-to-expect-from-uk-us-trade-deal-for-now-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;BOE governor Bailey: Don&apos;t know what to expect from UK-US trade deal for now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coming up at 0840 GMT / 0440 US Eastern time on Fridat #dat:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bank of England Governor Andrew Bailey delivers keynote address at the Reykjavik economic conference 2025, hosted by Northwestern University and the Central Bank of Iceland, Reykjavik&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China weighs nationwide ban on home pre-sales to stabilise property market</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-weighs-nationwide-ban-on-home-pre-sales-to-stabilise-property-market-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:24:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-weighs-nationwide-ban-on-home-pre-sales-to-stabilise-property-market-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;57&quot; data-end=&quot;214&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China is considering banning pre-sales of homes, requiring developers to sell only completed properties to reduce risks and stabilise the housing market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;215&quot; data-end=&quot;378&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;217&quot; data-end=&quot;378&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The proposed reform is part of a “new model” of real estate development being formulated by the central government, though details are still being finalised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;379&quot; data-end=&quot;521&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;381&quot; data-end=&quot;521&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The rule would apply only to future land sales, excluding public housing, with local governments allowed implementation flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;522&quot; data-end=&quot;675&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;524&quot; data-end=&quot;675&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The move aims to limit new housing supply and prevent further price declines, especially in smaller cities where the downturn has been more severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;676&quot; data-end=&quot;804&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;678&quot; data-end=&quot;804&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China’s pre-sales system fueled excessive supply and developer debt, leading to unfinished projects and mortgage boycotts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;805&quot; data-end=&quot;942&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;807&quot; data-end=&quot;942&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Around 90% of homes were pre-sold in 2021, falling to 74% in 2023, but developers remain reliant on advance payments for cash flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;943&quot; data-end=&quot;1069&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;945&quot; data-end=&quot;1069&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Analysts warn the ban may exacerbate funding strains, slow land purchases, and curb new construction and investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1070&quot; data-end=&quot;1198&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1072&quot; data-end=&quot;1198&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The government has pledged to accelerate supportive financing mechanisms for this new model, though details remain sparse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1199&quot; data-end=&quot;1339&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1201&quot; data-end=&quot;1339&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;April data showed new-home sales from top developers fell 8.7% y/y, adding urgency for reform amid weak demand and fresh U.S. tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1340&quot; data-end=&quot;1479&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1342&quot; data-end=&quot;1479&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Over 30 cities have already piloted finished-home sales, and the central government signaled it will promote this nationwide in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The info was out Thursday ICYMI. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC is expected to set the USD/CNY reference rate at 7.2581 – Reuters estimate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72581-reuters-estimate-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:13:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72581-reuters-estimate-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China USD/CNY reference rate is due around 0115 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How the process works:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type=&quot;disc&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily midpoint setting: Each morning, the PBOC sets a midpoint for the yuan against a basket of currencies, primarily the US dollar. The central bank takes into account factors such as market supply and demand, economic indicators, and international currency market fluctuations. The midpoint serves as a reference point for that day&apos;s trading.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The trading band: The PBOC allows the yuan to move within a specified range around the midpoint. The trading band is set at +/- 2%, meaning the yuan could appreciate or depreciate by a maximum of 2% from the midpoint during a single trading day. This range is subject to change by the PBOC based on economic conditions and policy objectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intervention: If the yuan&apos;s value approaches the limit of the trading band or experiences excessive volatility, the PBOC may intervene in the foreign exchange market by buying or selling the yuan to stabilize its value. This helps maintain a controlled and gradual adjustment of the currency&apos;s value.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan finance minister Kato: Not appropriate to lower consumption tax</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-not-appropriate-to-lower-consumption-tax-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 23:48:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-not-appropriate-to-lower-consumption-tax-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan finance minister Kato headline crossing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not appropriate to lower consumption tax&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *EL SALVADOR BUYS MORE BITCOIN: THE BITCOIN OFFICE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920595591895175500#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 21:44:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920595591895175500#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*EL SALVADOR BUYS MORE BITCOIN: THE BITCOIN OFFICE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *LUTNICK: IF COUNTRIES OPEN MARKET, BEST THEY CAN DO IS 10%

*LUTNICK: DE-ESCALATION, BRINGING RATES DOWN IS GOAL FOR CHINA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920574832124559833#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:21:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920574832124559833#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*LUTNICK: IF COUNTRIES OPEN MARKET, BEST THEY CAN DO IS 10%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*LUTNICK: DE-ESCALATION, BRINGING RATES DOWN IS GOAL FOR CHINA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) LUTNICK ON TARIFFS: AS YOU GET TO BIGGER ECONOMIES, MORE WORK, TAKES TIME</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920574546169475078#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:20:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920574546169475078#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LUTNICK ON TARIFFS: AS YOU GET TO BIGGER ECONOMIES, MORE WORK, TAKES TIME&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *LUTNICK ON TRADE DEALS: THINK WE&apos;LL GET THERE BY JULY 8</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920574498685723085#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:20:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920574498685723085#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*LUTNICK ON TRADE DEALS: THINK WE&apos;LL GET THERE BY JULY 8&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *VANCE: MUSK IS NOT DISAPPEARING, MORE WASTE CAN BE FOUND</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920565913989833106#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:46:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920565913989833106#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*VANCE: MUSK IS NOT DISAPPEARING, MORE WASTE CAN BE FOUND&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP SEEKS TAX HIKE ON WEALTHY WHO EARN $2.5 MILLION OR MORE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920565006715748663#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:42:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920565006715748663#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP SEEKS TAX HIKE ON WEALTHY WHO EARN $2.5 MILLION OR MORE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) VANCE: TRUMP IS RIGHT ABOUT JEROME POWELL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920564923832139945#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:42:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920564923832139945#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;VANCE: TRUMP IS RIGHT ABOUT JEROME POWELL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) VANCE SAYS U.S. WOULD WALK AWAY FROM RUSSIA, UKRAINE TALKS IF IT CONCLUDES RUSSIA IS NOT ENGAGING &apos;IN GOOD FAITH&apos; -FOX NEWS INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920564815732392387#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:41:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920564815732392387#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;VANCE SAYS U.S. WOULD WALK AWAY FROM RUSSIA, UKRAINE TALKS IF IT CONCLUDES RUSSIA IS NOT ENGAGING &apos;IN GOOD FAITH&apos; -FOX NEWS INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) S&amp;P: TARIFF UNCERTAINTY COULD PUSH BACK FED RATE MOVES TO LATE 2025</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920564721989656715#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:41:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920564721989656715#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P: TARIFF UNCERTAINTY COULD PUSH BACK FED RATE MOVES TO LATE 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP ADMIN WEIGHS CHINA TARIFF CUTS AHEAD OF SWISS TALKS: NYP

 *CHINA TARIFFS COULD BE SLASHED TO 50%-54% NEXT WEEK: NYP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920559663889695073#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:21:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920559663889695073#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP ADMIN WEIGHS CHINA TARIFF CUTS AHEAD OF SWISS TALKS: NYP&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
 *CHINA TARIFFS COULD BE SLASHED TO 50%-54% NEXT WEEK: NYP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CELSIUS FOUNDER ALEX MASHINSKY GETS 12 YEARS FOR CRYPTO FRAUD</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920559436432650426#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:20:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920559436432650426#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CELSIUS FOUNDER ALEX MASHINSKY GETS 12 YEARS FOR CRYPTO FRAUD&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) META IN TALKS TO DEPLOY STABLECOINS AFTER ABANDONING LANDMARK CRYPTO PROJECT: FORTUNE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920556210136240232#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:07:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920556210136240232#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;META IN TALKS TO DEPLOY STABLECOINS AFTER ABANDONING LANDMARK CRYPTO PROJECT: FORTUNE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *NAVARRO: WE&apos;RE GOING TO TAKE GOOD CARE OF BOEING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920550851849937363#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:46:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920550851849937363#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*NAVARRO: WE&apos;RE GOING TO TAKE GOOD CARE OF BOEING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: I DON&apos;T THINK I WILL TALK TO PUTIN IN SAUDI ARABIA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920544857258406075#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:22:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920544857258406075#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: I DON&apos;T THINK I WILL TALK TO PUTIN IN SAUDI ARABIA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ON ELECTION OF AMERICAN POPE:  LOOK FORWARD TO MEETING POPE LEO XIV. IT WILL BE A VERY MEANINGFUL MOMENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920530899080249782#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:27:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920530899080249782#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ON ELECTION OF AMERICAN POPE:  LOOK FORWARD TO MEETING POPE LEO XIV. IT WILL BE A VERY MEANINGFUL MOMENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ON ELECTION OF AMERICAN POPE:  IT IS SUCH AN HONOR TO REALIZE THAT HE IS THE FIRST AMERICAN POPE.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920530837537231048#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:26:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920530837537231048#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ON ELECTION OF AMERICAN POPE:  IT IS SUCH AN HONOR TO REALIZE THAT HE IS THE FIRST AMERICAN POPE.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) NEW POPE HAS TAKEN NAME LEO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920527939436704053#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:15:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920527939436704053#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NEW POPE HAS TAKEN NAME LEO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) USA CARDINAL PREVOST ELECTED POPE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920527733244702769#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:14:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920527733244702769#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;USA CARDINAL PREVOST ELECTED POPE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SPOT GOLD  FALLS NEARLY 2% TO $3,298.48/OZ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920527065947742404#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:11:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920527065947742404#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPOT GOLD  FALLS NEARLY 2% TO $3,298.48/OZ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP PRIVATELY URGED SPEAKER MIKE JOHNSON ON A PHONE CALL WEDNESDAY TO RAISE THE TOP TAX RATE AND CLOSE THE CARRIED INTEREST LOOPHOLE -PUNCHBOWL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920525345096102355#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:04:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920525345096102355#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP PRIVATELY URGED SPEAKER MIKE JOHNSON ON A PHONE CALL WEDNESDAY TO RAISE THE TOP TAX RATE AND CLOSE THE CARRIED INTEREST LOOPHOLE -PUNCHBOWL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
