<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GERMANY&apos;S MERZ: ANYONE WHO CHALLENGES NATO MUST KNOW THAT WE ARE PREPARED, WILL JOINTLY DEFEND EVERY INCH OF TERRITORY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925513099974427004#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:24:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925513099974427004#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GERMANY&apos;S MERZ: ANYONE WHO CHALLENGES NATO MUST KNOW THAT WE ARE PREPARED, WILL JOINTLY DEFEND EVERY INCH OF TERRITORY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JOHNSON: THE TAX BILL WILL BE DONE BY JULY 4</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925510293976678473#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:13:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925510293976678473#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JOHNSON: THE TAX BILL WILL BE DONE BY JULY 4&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 30-YR U.S. TREASURY YIELD  RISES TO SESSION HIGH, LAST UP 2.5 BASIS POINTS AT 5.116%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925510206974271694#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:13:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925510206974271694#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;30-YR U.S. TREASURY YIELD  RISES TO SESSION HIGH, LAST UP 2.5 BASIS POINTS AT 5.116%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. S&amp;P 500 E-MINI FUTURES UP 0.2%, NASDAQ 100 FUTURES UP 0.4%, DOW FUTURES UP 0.1%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925509708107878519#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:11:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925509708107878519#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. S&amp;amp;P 500 E-MINI FUTURES UP 0.2%, NASDAQ 100 FUTURES UP 0.4%, DOW FUTURES UP 0.1%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BITCOIN POISED TO RISE FURTHER AFTER RECORD HIGH

Bitcoin may continue to climb after hitting a record high, says Standard Chartered’s Geoff Kendrick. A high U.S. Treasury term premium is boosting bitcoin, which tends to follow it. Inflows into U.S. spot bitcoin ETFs are growing, and both institutional and government interest are increasing. A new U.S. stablecoin regulation bill also supports the market. Standard Chartered expects bitcoin to reach $120,000 by the end of Q2, $200,000 by late 2025, and $500,000 by 2028. Bitcoin is currently up 2.3% at $110,768 after reaching $111,862.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925509317895028778#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925509317895028778#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BITCOIN POISED TO RISE FURTHER AFTER RECORD HIGH&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Bitcoin may continue to climb after hitting a record high, says Standard Chartered’s Geoff Kendrick. A high U.S. Treasury term premium is boosting bitcoin, which tends to follow it. Inflows into U.S. spot bitcoin ETFs are growing, and both institutional and government interest are increasing. A new U.S. stablecoin regulation bill also supports the market. Standard Chartered expects bitcoin to reach $120,000 by the end of Q2, $200,000 by late 2025, and $500,000 by 2028. Bitcoin is currently up 2.3% at $110,768 after reaching $111,862.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Eco Minister: No change to Japan&apos;s stance of demanding elimination of US tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-minister-no-change-to-japans-stance-of-demanding-elimination-of-us-tariffs-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:06:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-eco-minister-no-change-to-japans-stance-of-demanding-elimination-of-us-tariffs-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan&apos;s Economy Minister Akazawa is scheduled to visit the US from Friday-Sunday for tariff negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JAPAN ECON MINISTER AKAZAWA: NO CHANGE TO JAPAN&apos;S STANCE OF DEMANDING AN ELIMINATION OF U.S. TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925507757647470708#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925507757647470708#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JAPAN ECON MINISTER AKAZAWA: NO CHANGE TO JAPAN&apos;S STANCE OF DEMANDING AN ELIMINATION OF U.S. TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) S&amp;P 500 E-MINI FUTURES MOVE SLIGHTLY LOWER AFTER TRUMP TAX-CUT BILL PASSES US HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925506789467902198#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:59:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925506789467902198#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 E-MINI FUTURES MOVE SLIGHTLY LOWER AFTER TRUMP TAX-CUT BILL PASSES US HOUSE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JAPAN ECON MINISTER AKAZAWA: TO VISIT U.S. ON FROM FRIDAY-SUNDAY FOR TARIFF NEGOTIATIONS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925506738423312839#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:59:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925506738423312839#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JAPAN ECON MINISTER AKAZAWA: TO VISIT U.S. ON FROM FRIDAY-SUNDAY FOR TARIFF NEGOTIATIONS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US House passes the Trump tax bill and sends it to the Senate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-passes-the-trump-tax-bill-and-sends-it-to-the-senate-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:57:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-passes-the-trump-tax-bill-and-sends-it-to-the-senate-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US House passes the Trump tax bill and sends it to the Senate. That&apos;s a win for Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HOUSE PASSES REVISED TRUMP TAX BILL, SENDS IT TO SENATE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925506042089054616#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:56:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925506042089054616#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HOUSE PASSES REVISED TRUMP TAX BILL, SENDS IT TO SENATE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion to recommit failed, now the House is voting on the tax bill</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/motion-to-recommit-failed-now-the-house-is-voting-on-the-tax-bill-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:51:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/motion-to-recommit-failed-now-the-house-is-voting-on-the-tax-bill-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Motion to recommit failed, now the House is voting on the tax bill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow live &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mXUsahxtDJI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US House is voting</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-is-voting-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:29:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-house-is-voting-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US House is voting...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First the motion to recommit, then comes passage of the reconciliation package.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;h/t &lt;a href=&quot;https://x.com/JakeSherman/status/1925497874097356962&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Jake Sherman&lt;/a&gt; on X&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can follow live &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mXUsahxtDJI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House to vote on the &quot;big, beautiful bill&quot; shortly</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-to-vote-on-the-big-beautiful-bill-shortly-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:10:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-to-vote-on-the-big-beautiful-bill-shortly-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Schedule per Haley Talbot (CNN) post on X (ET time):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Approx 5:30 – 6:00 am, vote on the following:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1) Motion to Recommit
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2) Passage of H.R. 1 - One Big Beautiful Bill Act
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3) H.R. 1701 - Strategic Ports Reporting Act 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walk off the floor: 6:00 – 6:30am 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recess begins, members return June 3rd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can follow live&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mXUsahxtDJI&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt; here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Holzmann: The Euro&apos;s importance as a global currency is set to increase</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-holzmann-the-euros-importance-as-a-global-currency-is-set-to-increase-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:46:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-holzmann-the-euros-importance-as-a-global-currency-is-set-to-increase-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Euro&apos;s importance as a global currency is set to increase.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Frequent shifts in trade policy have fuelled economic uncertainty, undermining stability and resulting in tangible losses for all parties involved.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It makes economic forecasts more complex and policy decision more challenging in an already uncertain environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These policies certainly lead to volatility in the short term.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful Reversal Pattern: Mastering the Head &amp; Shoulders Pattern- Trusted by FBS Analysts</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/powerful-reversal-pattern-mastering-the-head-shoulders-pattern-trusted-by-fbs-analysts-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:42:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/powerful-reversal-pattern-mastering-the-head-shoulders-pattern-trusted-by-fbs-analysts-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The
Head and Shoulders pattern is an important pattern that is frequently used in
technical analysis and signals a potential trend change in the market. The head
and shoulders pattern appears at the end of an uptrend. This pattern consists
of three peaks that form in sequence. The first and third peaks are called the
‘shoulders’, while the highest peak in the middle is called the ‘head’. The
formation appears at the end of an uptrend and gives us signals that the price
may reverse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How is the Head and Shoulders Pattern
formed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Head and Shoulders pattern consists of the left shoulder, head and right
shoulder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
First Shoulder (Left Shoulder): Prices initially continue a historical uptrend,
reach a peak, and then experience a slight pullback. This is not a scary drop
at first, but a minor correction.

Head: After the correction is over, prices rise again and form a new high that
exceeds the first shoulder. This high forms the head of the formation and is
usually the highest point. Up until this stage, there is no indication that the
price will turn down.

Second Shoulder (Right): Prices start to fall again after the head and then
turn back up from the previous low to form a second peak. This peak is usually
near the level of the first shoulder and does NOT break through the highest
peak formed by the head.

Neckline: The line connecting the lowest points between the two shoulders is
called the neckline. Breaking this line indicates that the Head and Shoulders
formation is complete and a downtrend may begin.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to trade this pattern?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Step 1 - Identify the Pattern Formation: One of the trickiest parts of
trading a head and shoulders pattern is identifying the pattern as it forms.
The shoulders may not be symmetrical, making it more difficult to spot the
pattern. There are two things to keep in mind when looking for a head and
shoulders pattern. First, these patterns require an existing uptrend. Without a
strong uptrend, there can be no head and shoulders pattern. Second, traders
should keep an eye on trading volume. In an ideal head and shoulders pattern,
volume will be highest as the left shoulder forms, lower as the head forms, and
lowest as the right shoulder forms. In addition, the volume should increase as
the left shoulder declines to the first trough and as the head declines to the
second trough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Step 2 - Wait for the Breakdown: The breakdown at the end of a head and
shoulders pattern occurs when the neckline is broken. This breakdown should be
convincing, occurring on strong volume and coinciding with momentum indicators
pointing towards strong bearish momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Step 3 - Enter a Trade: Once a breakdown is confirmed, traders can enter a
trade. Since a head and shoulders pattern predicts a bearish move, most traders
will short the target stock to profit from the breakdown. The expected size of
the breakdown can be estimated by measuring the distance from the top of the
head to the neckline directly below the head.

Step 4 - Take Profit: To determine the target price in the Head and Shoulders
pattern, the distance between the top of the head and the neckline is calculated
and this distance is added below the neckline. Thus, if the price triggers the
Head and Shoulders, the likely target is found.

Step 5- Stop Loss: It is also important to consider the possibility that the
formation may break down and remain a trap. You can minimize your losses by
placing the stop loss just above the neckline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How can we confirm the pattern?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several
different methods can be used to confirm the formation. One of them is volume
analysis - an increase in volume as the neckline is broken increases the
reliability of the formation. Or we can use technical indicators - indicators
such as the support of moving averages, the candle formation formed on the
neckline, and the rapid completion of the right shoulder can help confirm the
formation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inverse Head and Shoulders Pattern&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It
is symmetrical to the head and shoulder formation. It appears at the end of a
downtrend.The first component of an
inverse head and shoulders pattern is a lead-in downtrend, which is a clear
downward trend in the price of the asset. This downtrend is typically
characterized by a series of lower lows and lower highs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to trade an inverse Head and
Shoulders Pattern&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The
first step in trading an inverse head and shoulders pattern is to identify the
pattern. This involves looking for the lead-in downtrend, the inverse head and
shoulders formation, and the potential reversal breakout above the neckline
resistance.  Candlestick patterns are
rarely as uniform as pictures often suggest, but formations should still be
visible to a practiced eye. If you see a low followed by a lower low (the left
shoulder and head), be on the lookout for that higher low (right shoulder) to
potentially catch the break out before it gets away from you. Waiting for the
breakout to confirm the bullish reversal can be the safer trade, but sometimes
entering while the right shoulder is forming offers the best risk-to-reward.
However, traders should always be cautious trading off of still-forming
patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to manage risk management on Head
and Shoulders?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first and most important risk management step is to set the right
stop-loss level. The ideal stop-loss point in the pattern is above the neckline.
If the price goes back above the neckline after the formation is broken, it
means the formation is unsuccessful. In this case, closing your position is the
best approach to prevent further losses.

Setting a target price and taking profit when this target is reached is part of
disciplined risk management. In the formation, the target price is calculated
by measuring the distance between the head and neckline below the neckline
breakout. However, the exact target price may not always be reached. Therefore,
gradually reducing your position as you approach the target or using a trailing
stop can help you protect your profit.

And, it is important to get confirmation with other technical indicators to
increase the reliability of the pattern. By using additional tools such as
volume analysis, momentum indicators or trend indicators, you can increase the
chances of the pattern being successful and better manage your risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is the Head and Shoulders pattern safe?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the Head and Shoulders formation is one of the most recognized and
used formations in technical analysis, it does not have absolute reliability,
as with every formation. The reliability of the formation may vary depending on
market conditions, time frame and other factors. The most powerful aspect of
the formation is that it is formed after a long uptrend and clearly signals a
trend change. Especially when supported by high trading volume, the formation&apos;s
chance of success increases. However, not every formation in the market is
successful and in some cases it can produce false signals. One important point
to note is the mistake of entering the trade before the formation is fully
completed. Taking a position before the neckline is definitely broken means
acting prematurely, which usually results in a loss. It is important to be
patient and wait for confirmation signals for the formation to be completed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The
Head and Shoulders pattern is one of the most reliable and widely recognized
reversal patterns in technical analysis. It signals a potential change in trend
direction, typically from bullish to bearish in its standard form, and from
bearish to bullish in its inverse variation. It consists of three peaks: a
higher central peak (head) flanked by two lower peaks (shoulders).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The
pattern is confirmed when the price breaks below the neckline (or above, in the
inverse case) with increased volume. Often used to anticipate reversals and
identify entry and exit points. Used correctly, the Head and Shoulders pattern
helps traders spot major turning points and improve their decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Price Forecast - Also Using Liquidation Levels</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-price-forecast-also-using-liquidation-levels-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 09:01:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-price-forecast-also-using-liquidation-levels-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Price Forecast &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, I am watching $117k - $119k on the Bitcoin futures. Now I apologize for the next video not having audio due to a technical issue being looked into, but I am sure most of you with a will, will find a way, and see why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now you will note in the chart within the video, also shown below, that we have that little grey line for an expected price level of liquadation at $115,500. I explain what this means further below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;&gt;Understanding Liquidation Levels and How They Influence Bitcoin Price Forecast&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Bitcoin traders and investors, understanding liquidation levels—especially those linked to large positions—is crucial. Liquidations can dramatically influence short-term price movements, triggering swift and often volatile market reactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;&gt;What Does &apos;Liquidation&apos; Actually Mean?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In cryptocurrency futures trading, liquidation occurs when a trader&apos;s leveraged position is closed automatically by the exchange because the position&apos;s margin is no longer sufficient to cover potential losses. Traders holding leveraged long positions (expecting price to rise) will face liquidation if the price moves significantly lower. Conversely, leveraged short positions (expecting prices to drop) face liquidation if prices rise significantly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;&gt;What Is &apos;Cumulative Short Liquidation Leverage&apos;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &quot;cumulative short liquidation leverage&quot; refers to the total amount of short positions that could be forcibly closed if Bitcoin&apos;s price hits a certain level. When the price approaches these liquidation points, shorts become at risk of being liquidated, forcing these traders to buy Bitcoin at market prices to cover their positions. This forced buying adds upward pressure on prices, often triggering even higher spikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why Bitcoin Traders (and Investors) Should Care&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These liquidation levels act as magnets or significant pivot points in price action. Let&apos;s consider two critical liquidation zones for Bitcoin based on recent data:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-spread=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Above Current Price: At around $115,549, approximately 3.75k BTC worth of short positions could be liquidated. This forced buying could push prices rapidly higher, creating momentum that attracts additional buyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below Current Price: A notable zone between approximately $96,000 and $97,335 shows significant potential liquidations of leveraged long positions. If Bitcoin prices drop into this range, substantial selling could be triggered, rapidly pushing prices lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;How Liquidations Can Propel BTC Futures Price Further&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a large liquidation occurs (let&apos;s say short liquidation at a higher price), traders holding shorts must rapidly buy Bitcoin at the market price to cover their positions. This buying activity creates immediate upward pressure, potentially triggering additional liquidations of other short sellers, causing prices to spike even higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, these rapid price movements attract momentum traders, scalpers, and short-term speculators who ride the trend further upwards. However, caution is necessary: significant liquidation points often become attractive levels for larger, savvy traders to take profits. Thus, it&apos;s common to witness price spiking above critical liquidation levels, followed by a reversal or at least a retest of previously broken resistance or support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Trading Guidance for Bitcoin Traders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-spread=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do Not Treat Liquidation Levels as Precise Reversal Points: Instead, anticipate potential overshoots. Price often moves beyond these levels due to the aggressive market orders and new entrants drawn by the momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expect Potential Reversals Post-Liquidation Spikes: Often, sharp moves above resistance (or below support) are temporary, leading to a reversal as profit-takers seek new buyers or sellers entering at extreme prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay Alert to Retests: After a liquidation-driven breakout, watch carefully if prices return to test the previously significant level—often a key indicator of the next market direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why Track Whales Specifically?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While standard liquidation maps provide helpful insights, focusing on whale or large institutional positions offers enhanced predictive value. Large traders typically hold sizable positions with significant market impact. Their liquidation points, therefore, are more likely to trigger noticeable price movements, setting off cascades of secondary liquidations and momentum-driven trades. By tracking these larger positions, traders gain clearer insights into potentially explosive market dynamics and critical price thresholds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In summary, understanding liquidation dynamics, especially those involving significant &quot;whale&quot; positions, gives Bitcoin traders a vital edge. Remain vigilant around key liquidation zones, anticipate temporary volatility spikes, and prepare for potential reversals and retests. Trade wisely, understanding that these are guides—not guarantees—of price action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;3:1-3:24&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Price Outlook&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;5:1-5:92&quot;&gt;My current analysis indicates a target range of $117,000 - $119,000 for Bitcoin futures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;7:1-7:217&quot;&gt;Please note that the above video contains visual information only, as a technical issue is currently being addressed which impacts the audio. Viewers are encouraged to observe the presented charts for key insights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;7:1-7:217&quot;&gt;You can also check out &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article__title&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/eth-analysis-for-today-with-tradecompass-20250522/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;ETH Analysis for Today with tradeCompass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;9:1-9:224&quot;&gt;Back to BTC, as highlighted in the video&apos;s chart (and shown above ), a significant expected liquidation price level is identified at $115,500. The implications of this level will be further elaborated upon in the text below the video.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;11:1-11:551&quot;&gt;Important Disclaimer: This content reflects my personal technical analysis and is provided for informational purposes only. It does not constitute financial advice, investment recommendation, or an offer to buy or sell any financial instrument. The cryptocurrency market is highly volatile and speculative. Past performance is not indicative of future results. All investment decisions carry inherent risks, and you should conduct your own thorough due diligence and consult with a qualified financial advisor before making any investment choices.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Vujcic: Eurozone growth positive but low</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-vujcic-eurozone-growth-positive-but-low-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-vujcic-eurozone-growth-positive-but-low-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurozone growth positive but low.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I expect to get close to 2% target at the end of 2025.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I expect to reach the target in early 2026.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same old stuff from the ECB as they keep their conviction on hitting the target soon and therefore continue with rate cuts.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Rate Cut Countdown: How Low Will the Fed Go?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/2025-rate-cut-countdown-how-low-will-the-fed-go-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:37:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/2025-rate-cut-countdown-how-low-will-the-fed-go-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The latest numbers on American inflation
have left the global financial community wondering. How many times will the
Federal Reserve cut interest rates this year? With inflation at a four-year
low, markets are tracking every hint and putting their probabilities together
with rising confidence. The April 2025 Consumer Price Index (CPI) figure,
released on May 13 by the Bureau of Labor Statistics, was a stark departure
from the inflation forecast and had the potential to determine the Fed&apos;s action
plan for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disinflation gathers pace&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The April headline CPI rose just 0.2%, a
recovery from the 0.1% fall in March. Far more significant, the year-on-year
inflation rate slowed to 2.3%, the lowest since February 2021. The reading
records not just the fading away of pandemic-driven temporary price shocks but
also the growing potency of the Fed&apos;s two-year effort at aggressive monetary
tightening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core CPI, stripping out volatile food and
energy prices, also held steady at 2.8% year-over-year. While still above the
Fed&apos;s 2% benchmark, the slowdown is the first sign that the most stubborn
causes of inflation — services, housing, and wage-sensitive sectors — are no
longer accelerating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Highlight April activity is a sharp 12.7%
decline in egg prices and a 0.4% decline in &quot;food at home&quot; as both
capture relief in pantry goods. Shelter costs, which make up more than
one-third of the CPI basket, however, rose 0.3%. This ongoing rise in housing
costs remains frustrating to the Fed as core inflation continues to be sticky
even as headline numbers ease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reading between the lines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At its May 7 session, the Federal Reserve
decided to leave its target rate of 4.25%-4.50% in place, citing
&quot;cross-economic trends&quot; and the still uncertain rate of core
inflation. Fed Chairman Jerome Powell made cautious but honest comments at his
press conference, casting aside any reservations when he stated that a rate cut
is within reach, but not necessarily a given.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;We notice encouraging signs, but
too soon to declare victory,&quot; Powell stated. &quot;We need more confidence
that inflation is on track to a sustainable path to 2%.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fed release also mentioned new
geopolitical tensions, decelerating capital expenditures, and the emerging
effects of recent trade measures. Market participants interpret the Fed&apos;s words
as &quot;dovish&quot;, since futures prices signal one or two rate cuts through
2025, and some speculative bets signal three.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The irony is not lost on veteran
investors: whereas the Fed assures it uses data, markets increasingly depend on
the Fed. Each drop in the consumer price index, each report on labor markets,
and each trade news headline are now used in figuring out the rate cut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade tensions and tariffs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;April also saw the introduction of a 10%
across-the-board tariff applied to all US imports, as well as targeted
increases on Chinese consumer electronics, EV batteries, and foreign-made
autos. These protectionist measures, although geared toward reshoring critical
supply chains and energizing domestic production, pose a complex inflationary
risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, these tariffs have not much
impacted consumer prices — perhaps due to long-term contracts, delayed
pass-through effects, or offsetting cuts elsewhere. But experts expect
inflation to return in the summer once businesses begin to raise their prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Substantial progress is the initial
US-China trade agreement in early May to reduce trade tensions. Under this
agreement, both nations agreed to roll back selected tariffs during Q3 2025. If
it succeeds, the agreement will solve some of the tariff-sustained inflation
and soften pressure on the Fed to be higher for longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forex markets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key rate cut could significantly affect
the market as a whole. Let&apos;s examine a few instruments closely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDollar fell to the critical support
area of 61.8 Fibonacci, and rebounded. However, the price is ready to retest
this area again. At the same time, Parabolic SAR indicates the possibility of
growth, and CCI came out of the oversold zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
A break of the 99.000 support area
will drop the price to 95.500;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
A rebound from the support will
bring USDollar back to 101.500 and further to 104.000;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;XAUUSD continues to update historical
highs, and the price is consolidating near 261.8 Fibonacci. The price crossed
the upper Bollinger line, indicating overbought. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
Consolidation above 3300 will open
the way to 4200;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
A rebound from resistance will
drop Gold to 2750 and on further decline to 2500;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is currency traders&apos; top worry whether
the European Central Bank and the Bank of England will follow suit. If the Fed
cuts spending but its counterparts do not, the dollar could fall further. But
if inflation stabilizes and the Fed procrastinates, the dollar&apos;s appreciation
could persist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the Japanese yen and Swiss
franc, the safe-haven currencies, also increased modestly as expectations of
falling interest rates cause the re-evaluation of risks. Volatility in the
foreign exchange market is expected to increase during the summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How many cuts are coming?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the April CPI numbers in hand and
inflation seemingly front and center, everyone is waiting for the Federal
Reserve to act. It&apos;s no longer a question of whether the Fed will cut rates,
but how often. The existing futures markets are already pricing in a 70% chance
of the first cut being in September, followed by a second in December, which is
increasingly likely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is uncertainty. Sticky core
inflation, geopolitical uncertainty, the wild card path of tariffs, and a
still-resilient labor market complicate the projection. The Fed&apos;s dual mandate
— maximum employment and price stability — remains a tightrope. If hiring slows
while inflation keeps falling, the Fed could move more aggressively. If
inflation re-accelerates, cuts could be delayed into never-never land.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The April consumer price index report may
be the most significant reading of the year. He puts the US economy at a fork
in the road: low inflation, steady jobs, and a central bank faced with patience
or preventive measures. The next couple of months will be a test of the Fed&apos;s
mettle, market imagination, and the strength of international trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the currency markets, volatility will
be an opportunity as well as a risk. As the Fed balances down the inflation
rate and the dollar serves as a barometer of the world&apos;s economy, volatility
will make both investors and policy makers prepare for a data-driven,
diplomatically influenced, and decisions-yet-to-be-made second half of 2025&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBA&apos;s Hauser: Australian exporters upbeat about resilience of China demand</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rbas-hauser-australian-exporters-upbeat-about-resilience-of-china-demand-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:37:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rbas-hauser-australian-exporters-upbeat-about-resilience-of-china-demand-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Australian exporters upbeat about resilience of China demand.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On recent China trip, found confidence Beijing would do what was needed to sustain growth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Found striking confidence that China going into trade war with strong hand.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China organizations expected large share of economic costs of tariffs would fall on US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China contacts expressed a determination not to cushion those costs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Found little expectations that yuan would be devalued to insulate US from tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Possible could see more intense competition at home from Chinese firms discounting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Unclear how big an impact given limited overlap between Chinese and Australian output.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s nothing on monetary policy here.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK May flash services PMI 50.2 vs 50.0 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-may-flash-services-pmi-502-vs-500-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-may-flash-services-pmi-502-vs-500-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 49.0&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing PMI 45.1 vs 46.0 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 45.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 49.4 vs 49.3 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are mostly in line figures and nothing to be afraid or cheer about. The agency notes that confidence rebounded and price pressures have moderated after spiking higher. The sentiment about prospects in the year ahead remains subdued and job cutting remains worryingly aggressive, especially in manufacturing. The agency sees the BoE continuing with rate cuts.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where ESG Meets Smart Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/where-esg-meets-smart-trading-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:11:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/where-esg-meets-smart-trading-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Award-winning online trading platform&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ironfx.com/en/?utm_source=publishers&amp;amp;utm_medium=media&amp;amp;utm_content=homepage&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt; IronFX&lt;/a&gt; is known for its long list of headlining sports sponsorships, from freediving championships in Korea to world-famous football clubs. Rising to the challenge is clearly a hallmark of this forex trading broker’s ethos. To this end, it also helps vulnerable groups in communities to make their lives better through charitable and Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;What do child welfare in Cyprus, earthquake victims in the Yunnan Province, and flood victims in Hungary have in common? IronFX Foundation has contributed to their relief with charity concerts, team contributions and donations as part of its corporate social responsibility (CSR) programme. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;In 2025, those who want to trade online - particularly those with significant experience and financial knowledge - expect a lot more than competitive pricing and advanced technology. They are also looking for higher standards of conduct from their brokers. An IronFX review from any of the 180 countries where it accepts clients shows this MT4 trading broker has a reputation as a trusted platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;This mindset shift is fundamentally changing what it means to be the best forex broker in the financial markets, and ESG factors have moved to the centre of investor and trader decision-making. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;IronFX has woven these principles into its DNA. The foundation has contributed to causes in countries around the world. Community support projects include donations for children with special needs, flood relief efforts in Malaysia, and assistance for students with financial difficulties amongst others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Through these ongoing activities, IronFX has set an example of what is possible, demonstrating that responsible trading can bring together market conduct and a positive role in society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Investor trends: standards drive broker choice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Recent feedback from the company’s clients underscores a clear trend: the trading competition has changed, and traders are increasingly seeking brokers who reflect their own values. Many, including those trading with an Islamic forex account, are choosing to partner with firms that prioritise fairness, social responsibility, and transparency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;From the new to the seasoned, traders are aligning their broker relationships with their professional and personal benchmarks. As a result, ESG practices are now a core advantage for brokers aiming to attract and retain discerning clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Aligning with sustainability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;As ESG considerations become more prominent, IronFX has taken practical steps to ensure its offerings and operations are aligned with the expectations of sustainability-minded clients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The company has gone digital-first, slashing paper waste and unnecessary travel to shrink its carbon footprint. It has also moved much of its client engagement, documentation, and educational content online. These changes have reduced paper usage and lowered the company’s environmental impact. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;In the spirit of showing that sustainability is more than just a buzzword, the company is rolling out eco-friendly office practices and exploring carbon-offset partnerships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Solid governance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;For experienced traders searching for a high-leverage forex broker, trust is built on robust governance. The broker places a strong emphasis on risk management and its platform is designed to be accessible, fair and secure, so that clients have confidence that the platform operates with integrity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Clear communication and a commitment to best practices underpin the firm’s approach, ensuring that the expectations of conscientious traders are consistently met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Education and empowerment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The company recognises that informed traders are empowered traders, and has expanded its educational resources to include ESG-focused content through its academy and blog. These materials will help clients understand the impact of ESG trends on global markets and trading behaviour, providing practical insights without promoting specific products. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;By encouraging a deeper understanding of trustworthy practices, IronFX aims to support its clients with the knowledge needed to master an increasingly complex financial landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The next steps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;This shift towards ESG is becoming a wider industry trend. Brokers are evaluated not just on their product offerings, but on their reliability and commitment to ethical conduct. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;From being awarded “Best Education Tools APAC” (UF Awards 2024) to its ongoing efforts to be recognised as the best forex broker for informed traders, IronFX continues to expand its educational content to include ESG-focused materials. A series of blog articles and IronFX Academy webinars are in the works which will discuss the implications of these trends on global markets and trader behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;As such principles become integral to investor expectations, the broker’s forward-thinking approach positions it as a platform of choice for those seeking both financial performance and ethical alignment. The company’s ongoing commitment to CSR, environmental responsibility, and transparent governance positions it as a leader in an evolving industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;For those who want their investments to mean more, ESG isn’t on the sidelines - it’s the new standard. The commitment to fairness and making a positive difference shows IronFX is resolute in its approach so that traders do not have to choose between performance and purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Start trading with this ESG-active broker &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ironfx.com/en/?utm_source=publishers&amp;amp;utm_medium=media&amp;amp;utm_content=homepage&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;by following this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany May Ifo business climate index 87.5 vs 87.4 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-ifo-business-climate-index-875-vs-874-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-ifo-business-climate-index-875-vs-874-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 86.9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current assessment 86.1 vs. 86.8 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 86.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expectations 88.9 vs. 88.0 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 87.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s getting tentatively better as we go forward. As seen in the German PMI report, fiscal boost and ECB rate cuts are helping the economy.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone May flash services PMI 48.9 vs 50.3 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-flash-services-pmi-489-vs-503-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-flash-services-pmi-489-vs-503-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 50.1&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing PMI 49.4 vs 49.3 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 49.0&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 49.5 vs 50.7 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 50.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Eurozone Composite PMI Output Index at 6-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Eurozone Services PMI Business Activity Index at 16-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Eurozone Manufacturing PMI Output Index at Unchanged pace of growth.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Eurozone Manufacturing PMI at 33-month high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the flash PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The eurozone economy just cannot seem to find its footing. Since January, the overall PMI has shown only the slightest hint
of growth and in May, the private sector actually slipped into contraction. Do not blame US tariffs for this one. In fact, efforts
to get ahead of those tariffs might partly explain why manufacturing has held up a bit better lately. Manufacturers have now
increased production for the third straight month, and for the first time since April 2022, new orders did not decline. On the
flip side, service providers, who are generally less exposed to US trade policy, except in areas like international logistics, are
seeing business activity shrink for the first time since November 2024. While foreign demand for services is softening, it is
the sluggish domestic demand that seems to be dragging the sector down.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“May’s snapshot is not pretty. Looking ahead, companies are only cautiously optimistic. The expectations index is still well
below its long-term average. However, there are reasons for confidence in the longer term. The recovery in manufacturing is
broad-based, with encouraging signs coming out of both Germany and France. Further interest rate cuts could provide a
boost, and lower oil prices compared to last year are also helping. Germany, in particular, might be gearing up to reclaim its
role as the eurozone’s economic engine, thanks to a potentially very expansionary fiscal policy. That is backed up by a
notable jump in Germany’s future production index, which has climbed to an above-average level.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For the European Central Bank, these numbers are likely to leave it with mixed feelings. Inflation in service sector sales
prices has ticked down slightly from an already low level, but input costs are still rising and even picking up speed. With
energy prices falling, higher wages are probably the main driver here. Still, the ECB seems inclined to continue with cautious
rate cuts, especially with purchase prices in manufacturing on the decline.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany May flash manufacturing PMI 48.8 vs 48.9 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-flash-manufacturing-pmi-488-vs-489-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 07:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-flash-manufacturing-pmi-488-vs-489-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Services PMI 47.2 vs 49.5 expected
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 49.0 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 48.6 vs 50.4 expected
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 50.1 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Germany Composite PMI Output Index at 5-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Germany Services PMI Business Activity Index at 30-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Germany Manufacturing PMI Output Index at 3-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Germany Manufacturing PMI at 33-month high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the flash PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These numbers paint a mixed picture - there are both positives and negatives here. On the bright side, manufacturing is
doing better, as output has been climbing for three months in a row, and new orders are following suit. In the service sector,
by contrast, activity has taken a sharper tumble. And since services make up a big chunk of the economy, that drop has
pulled overall activity into contraction. Considering the modest growth we saw in Q1, this latest data lines up with what the
German Council of Economic Experts are forecasting, namely that the economy might just be treading water this year.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In manufacturing things are looking up. While the headline PMI is still in recessionary territory, it’s been inching higher for
five straight months. That upward trend likely reflects a mix of short-term factors - like companies rushing orders ahead of
US tariffs - and broader cyclical improvements supported by ECB rate cuts. Looking ahead, increased defence spending and
a more defined infrastructure package could give the sector an extra push. Plus, falling input costs, which are driven by
cheaper energy, should offer manufacturers some breathing room.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Service providers are struggling a bit. Activity has been sliding for two months now, with new business drying up and pricing
power fading. Meanwhile, costs are still climbing fast, which could squeeze profit margins. On a more positive note, service
providers are still hiring, bucking the broader trend. And future expectations have ticked up a bit, though the level of
optimism is still well below the long-term average. Overall, our nowcast model, which considers the PMI among other
factors, calculates that activity of service providers will barely expand in the second quarter.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France May flash services PMI 47.4 vs 47.5 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-flash-services-pmi-474-vs-475-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 07:15:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-flash-services-pmi-474-vs-475-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 47.3&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing PMI 49.5 vs 48.9 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 48.0 vs 48.0 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 47.8&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash France Composite PMI Output Index at 2-month high.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash France Services PMI Business Activity Index at 2-month high.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash France Manufacturing PMI Output Index at 37-month high.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash France Manufacturing PMI at 28-month high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the flash PMI data, Jonas Feldhusen, Junior Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“France’s private sector remained subdued in May. The Flash Composite PMI continues to signal contraction, reflecting the
economic challenges France is facing amid domestic political instability and a fragile macroeconomic environment.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Diverging trends emerged across sectors. The services sector deteriorated, with business activity still weak. Looking ahead,
prospects are equally dim. The index measuring the order situation—an indicator of future business—remains well below the
long-term average and inside contraction territory. In contrast, the manufacturing sector showed signs of recovery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The
Manufacturing PMI improved for the fifth straight month, supported by increased factory output. Despite ongoing uncertainty
and trade-related headwinds, several factors may explain this upward trend, such as the ECB’s easing of credit conditions,
EU efforts to reduce regulatory burdens, and the push to increase defense spending. These developments could, despite
prevailing risks, pave the way for a cyclical rebound following the prolonged downturn in the sector.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Price dynamics raise new concerns for French businesses. While output prices slipped into deflationary territory in May,
input cost inflation accelerated, signalling a squeeze on profit margins, particularly in the services sector. This raises the
question of how trade frictions will influence European price levels in the coming months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;On one hand, supply chain
disruptions and frontloading could drive prices up. On the other hand, goods facing increased competition as a result of
supply being redirected to the European market away from the US might exert downward pressure on prices. Nevertheless,
HCOB Economics still expects three additional ECB rate cuts this year, as the subdued growth and inflation environment
leaves scope for further easing.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Despite improvements in manufacturing and President Macron’s recent efforts to position France as an attractive
destination for investment, research and development, the overall outlook for the private sector remains bleak, as seen by
the business outlook falling sharply in May, especially in the service sector.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France May business confidence 97 vs 99 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-business-confidence-97-vs-99-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:45:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-business-confidence-97-vs-99-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 99 (revised to 100)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not a market moving indicator but it&apos;s a bit of a disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House votes to advance revised tax plan in procedural vote</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-votes-to-advance-revised-tax-plan-in-procedural-vote-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:43:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-votes-to-advance-revised-tax-plan-in-procedural-vote-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US House votes to advance revised tax plan in procedural vote.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US House votes to open debate on Trump tax bill with vote on passage to follow.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here&apos;s the plan shared by Haley Talbot (CNN) on her X account (ET time):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;At approx 12:45 – 1:45 a.m., vote on the adoption of the rule
 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Next, the House will debate H.R. 1 - One Big Beautiful Bill Act
 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Following debate, at approx 4:30 – 5:30 a.m., vote on PASSAGE
 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Walk off the floor: 5:30 – 6:00 a.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are trying to do it as soon as possible before the long weekend as we have Memorial Day on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEC+ discusses another 411K B/D output hike in July</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/opec-discusses-another-411k-bd-output-hike-in-july-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:32:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/opec-discusses-another-411k-bd-output-hike-in-july-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;OPEC+ discusses another 411K B/D output hike in July.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crude oil is down on the headline as higher supply expectations continue to keep a lid on further gains.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoJ Noguchi: Recent rise in long-term rates likely won&apos;t have impact on bond taper plan</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boj-noguchi-recent-rise-in-long-term-rates-likely-wont-have-impact-on-bond-taper-plan-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boj-noguchi-recent-rise-in-long-term-rates-likely-wont-have-impact-on-bond-taper-plan-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recent rise in long-term rates likely won&apos;t have an impact on our new bond taper plan to be decided in June.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most important thing is that things are different now than during period when we had YCC.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don&apos;t look at the size of our JGB buying from standpoint of monetary policy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In tapering bond buying, giving market predictability, while maintaining flexibility, is most important.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whether to maintain current pace of bond taper beyond April 2026 will be something to be discussed leading up to the next policy meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recent rise in super-long bond yields likely driven by global trend in yields, they are rapid but not necessarily abnormal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Don&apos;t think it&apos;s appropriate to recklessly intervene to correct bond yield moves.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud of uncertainty clearing somewhat in US-China trade tension.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets restoring some calm, though uncertainty surrounding US tariff policy and impact on Japan&apos;s economy high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ shouldn&apos;t move on rates when there is lack of clarity on economic outlook.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shouldn&apos;t move on rates now, better to scrutinise developments for time being.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Focus on bond taper plan for next fiscal year onward should be to avoid disrupting markets, BoJ doesn&apos;t need to rush in trimming its huge bond holdings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ doesn&apos;t need to maintain its huge balance sheet at current levels, natural to shrink its size.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Long-term interest rates, at times, make volatile moves reflecting various views on outlook.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At times, central banks must take action to stabilise markets but don&apos;t think we are facing such conditions now.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Noguchi has talked a lot today but the core message is that he doesn&apos;t see any reason to intervene in the JGBs market or tweak the tapering because of the surge in long term yields. He&apos;s also in a wait and see mode regarding further rate hikes as he&apos;s waiting for more clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market is currently pricing 17 bps of tightening in 2025 which is basically a 50% chance of another hike by year-end.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 22 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-22-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:31:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-22-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;EUR/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1400 (EUR 751mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1315
(EUR 1.00bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1300 (EUR 624mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1175 (EUR 2.13bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
143.50
(US$ 601mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;GBP/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3500 (GBP 347mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3395 (GBP 456mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3260 (GBP 778mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CHF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8525 (CHF 598mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.4050
(US$ 1.41bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3700 (US$ 659mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6700 (AUD 286mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6100 (AUD 204mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH Analysis for Today with TradeCompass</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/eth-analysis-for-today-with-tradecompass-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 04:59:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/eth-analysis-for-today-with-tradecompass-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Ethereum Futures Analysis Today – TradeCompass Methodology in Action&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello traders and crypto investors,
Today we bring you a fresh Ethereum futures analysis using the TradeCompass methodology—a professional-grade approach that incorporates volume profile, VWAPs, liquidity zones, and key historical levels to help you make more informed decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethereum (ETH) remains the second-largest crypto asset by market cap, with the most active developer community in the blockchain world. And while Bitcoin has already surged past its all-time high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethereum has not reached its all time high yet —which makes this market particularly interesting from both a technical and strategic standpoint (including having more historic levels and references to consider... more to work with).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why Ethereum Futures and Not Spot ETH?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We analyze ETH futures (not spot prices) because futures markets offer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More transparent volume and liquidity data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Institutional order flow visibility&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consistent structure across timeframes for analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time of writing, ETH futures are trading in the $2,624–$2,628 range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;tradeCompass Methodology: How It Works&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TradeCompass system combines several professional tools:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Volume Profile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shows where the majority of trading volume has taken place at specific price levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Highlights Point of Control (POC), Value Area High (VAH), and Value Area Low (VAL)—critical levels where price is likely to react.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. VWAP (Volume-Weighted Average Price)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP calculates the average price of Ethereum based on both price and volume during a session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Standard deviations of VWAP help define trend boundaries, breakout zones, and support/resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. Liquidity Zones &amp;amp; Round Numbers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Round numbers like $2,600, $2,500, and $2,700 attract heavy trading and stop orders. They act as magnets or reversal zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market makers often use these levels to create fakeouts and stop hunts, so we adjust our strategy accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. Partial Profit Framework&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;TradeCompass emphasizes taking profits in stages, reducing risk and protecting gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goal is not just accuracy, but sustainable profitability by managing trades dynamically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Ethereum Futures Levels Right Now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish Bias Above $2,600&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$2,600 is a round number and a major pivot level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aligned with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 16 VWAP: $2,600&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 16 POC: $2,602&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 22 (Today’s) POC: $2,604&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holding above this zone confirms buyer control. Dips to this region and rebounds can be viewed as long opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another CLOSE and RELEVANT Bullish Support Zone: $2,580–$2,586&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 13 VWAP: $2,580&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today’s VWAP: $2,586.4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If ETH futures dip here, it&apos;s a technical buy zone with clearly defined risk (stop just below) and strong reward potential&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;ETH Futures - Bearish If Below $2,538&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Ethereum futures break below $2,538, it could trigger a shift to bearish sentiment. This level will be updated further as we analyze liquidity clusters, lower VWAP deviations, and developing volume profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What to Do as a Crypto Trader or Investor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t chase long breakouts blindly.
Wait for retracements into support zones near VWAP or POC clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t short blindly.
Shorting into bullish support zones or near VAHs without confirmation often leads to losses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partial profits are key.
Whether you are long from $2,580 or $2,600, don’t wait for a fantasy top. Take profits along the way at pre-planned levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Comments Below as ETH Price Updates May Come In&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will possibly add the profit-taking prices on both sides of the trade, so traders can plan their exits with discipline and structure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ETH Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethereum remains in a bullish zone for now. The best strategy today may be to buy retracements into support and avoid late-stage shorts. TradeCompass continues to guide decisions using proven institutional tools like volume profile and VWAP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade at your own risk. This is not financial advice, but a data-driven decision support framework.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;investingLive Crypto – sharp trades, news gems that matters, unique education &amp;amp; important updates, zero noise!  

Get important alerts, tradeCompass insights, and more decision support - without the spam. Join now for free!

🔗 &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/investingLiveCrypto&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;t.me/investingLiveCrypto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 04:26:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, the focus will be on the Flash PMIs where the market will want to see how business confidence changed since the new developments on the trade front and what&apos;s the sentiment going forward. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we have the US Jobless Claims and the US Flash PMIs. The Jobless Claims data will likely be ignored as usual as the labour market remains stable and therefore not a source of concerns. Only a spike above the 260K level for Initial Claims could trigger a repricing in expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Flash PMIs, on the other hand, will be important to see if there&apos;s a strong bounce back in activity (or expectations of that in the months ahead) and the picture around inflation. The market is currently pricing 51 bps of easing for the Fed in 2025 with the first cut in September. The data from now on could change those expectations and therefore move the markets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, the US House could also vote on the &quot;big, beautiful bill&quot; and if successful could add to inflationary concerns and therefore push long term yields higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;07:15 GMT/03:15 ET - BoE&apos;s Breeden (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:30 GMT/04:30 ET - RBA&apos;s Hauser (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:00 GMT/08:00 ET - BoE&apos;s Dhingra (uber dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:30 GMT/08:30 ET - BoE&apos;s Pill (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;18:00 GMT/14:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Williams (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan&apos;s Mimura says Japan, US did not discuss FX levels at finance ministers&apos; meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-mimura-says-japan-us-did-not-discuss-fx-levels-at-finance-ministers-meeting-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 03:47:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-mimura-says-japan-us-did-not-discuss-fx-levels-at-finance-ministers-meeting-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan&apos;s Mimura says Japan, US did not discuss FX levels at finance ministers&apos; meeting &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;reaffirmed that forex should be determined by the market &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not believe that there is any gap in understanding with the U.S.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Finance Minister Kato agreed with Bessent that FX rates should be set by markets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did not discuss current rates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did not discuss future rates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mimura is repeating what US Treasury told us much earlier, triggering a yen sell off:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-confirm-that-sec-bessent-met-with-japan-finance-minister-kato-20250521/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;US Treasury confirm that Sec. Bessent met with Japan finance minister Kato&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Atsushi Mimura is Japan&apos;s vice finance minister for international affairs, AKA &apos;top currency diplomat&apos;. Japan&apos;s finance ministry is the relevant authority in Japan for ordering intervention in the JPY. Mimura would be directing Bank of Japan intervention, should it come to that. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: GIVING VERY SERIOUS CONSIDERATION TO BRINGING FANNIE MAE AND FREDDIE MAC PUBLIC.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925327060253159558#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 23:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925327060253159558#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: GIVING VERY SERIOUS CONSIDERATION TO BRINGING FANNIE MAE AND FREDDIE MAC PUBLIC.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, DOW JONES DOWN 2.00 PCT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925268317859622995#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:11:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925268317859622995#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, DOW JONES DOWN 2.00 PCT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) Kennedy Jr.&apos;s &apos;MAHA&apos; Report Expected to Criticize Chemicals in Food, Lobbyists and Vaccines, Sources Say -- WSJ

Report Goes Easier on Pesticides in Farming, People Briefed on Draft of Report Say -- WSJ

Final MAHA Report May Be Released as Soon as Thursday, Sources Say -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925254291582816315#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:16:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925254291582816315#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kennedy Jr.&apos;s &apos;MAHA&apos; Report Expected to Criticize Chemicals in Food, Lobbyists and Vaccines, Sources Say -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Report Goes Easier on Pesticides in Farming, People Briefed on Draft of Report Say -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Final MAHA Report May Be Released as Soon as Thursday, Sources Say -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TEXAS HOUSE APPROVES BILL TO CREATE BITCOIN RESERVE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925243245526708503#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:32:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925243245526708503#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TEXAS HOUSE APPROVES BILL TO CREATE BITCOIN RESERVE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, NASDAQ DOWN 1.00 PCT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925241804296777870#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:26:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925241804296777870#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, NASDAQ DOWN 1.00 PCT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 20-YEAR U.S. TREASURY YIELD CLIMBS TO 5.104%, HIGHEST SINCE NOV 2023; LAST UP 11.3 BASIS POINTS AT 5.103%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925241316511773006#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:24:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925241316511773006#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;20-YEAR U.S. TREASURY YIELD CLIMBS TO 5.104%, HIGHEST SINCE NOV 2023; LAST UP 11.3 BASIS POINTS AT 5.103%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) NASDAQ TURNS NEGATIVE, LAST DOWN 0.5%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925240572517744781#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:21:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925240572517744781#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NASDAQ TURNS NEGATIVE, LAST DOWN 0.5%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 ISRAEL PM NETANYAHU SAYS ISRAEL PROBABLY KILLED HAMAS LEADER MOHAMMED SINWAR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925239849562349959#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:18:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925239849562349959#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 ISRAEL PM NETANYAHU SAYS ISRAEL PROBABLY KILLED HAMAS LEADER MOHAMMED SINWAR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US REP. LAWLER: MADE GREAT PROCESS ON TAX BILL, WAITING FOR DETAILS

US REP. LAWLER: FEELING MUCH BETTER ABOUT TAX BILL NOW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925239768301879639#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:18:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925239768301879639#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US REP. LAWLER: MADE GREAT PROCESS ON TAX BILL, WAITING FOR DETAILS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
US REP. LAWLER: FEELING MUCH BETTER ABOUT TAX BILL NOW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SOUTH AFRICA&apos;S JOHANN RUPERT AT WHITE HOUSE: NEED STARLINK AT EVERY POLICE STATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925237345474773123#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:08:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925237345474773123#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SOUTH AFRICA&apos;S JOHANN RUPERT AT WHITE HOUSE: NEED STARLINK AT EVERY POLICE STATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US 20Y BONDS DRAW 5.047% VS 5.035% PRE-SALE WHEN-ISSUED YIELD</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925235856127696978#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925235856127696978#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US 20Y BONDS DRAW 5.047% VS 5.035% PRE-SALE WHEN-ISSUED YIELD&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
