<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq Analysis for Today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/nasdaq-analysis-for-today-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:30:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/nasdaq-analysis-for-today-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;&gt;Nasdaq Analysis for Today: Bulls Take Charge Post US-China Trade Talks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current Nasdaq Futures Price: $20,558 (+2.1% from Friday&apos;s close)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Context After US-China Trade Talks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasdaq futures are bullishly positioned today following moderately positive news from the weekend’s US-China trade talks. The optimistic sentiment has investors seeking opportunities to &quot;buy the dip&quot; rather than anticipating a bearish reversal. With a favorable geopolitical backdrop, the tradeCompass today underscores strategic entry points leveraging volume profile and VWAP indicators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Educational Insight: Volume Profile and VWAP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volume Profile:
Volume Profile visually represents trading activity at specific price levels, revealing where significant trading volume occurred. The Point of Control (POC) highlights the price level with the highest traded volume, often serving as strong support or resistance. The Value Area (VA), comprising approximately 70% of trading activity, indicates prices viewed as fair value by market participants. Traders use these zones to identify high-probability trade entries and exits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP (Volume Weighted Average Price):
VWAP shows the average price at which transactions occur throughout the trading day, adjusted by volume. Acting as a benchmark, prices above the VWAP signal bullish strength, while those below suggest bearish pressure. Traders often look to join bullish trends on pullbacks toward the VWAP or its standard deviation bands, as it reflects a fair market valuation supported by volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Bullish Entry Points for Nasdaq Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering today&apos;s bullish bias, traders could target the following support levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,495 - Today&apos;s Developing VWAP: Ideal for initial pullback entry, representing fair intraday pricing supported by volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,450 - Today&apos;s POC &amp;amp; Semi-Round Number: Offers even stronger support due to high accumulated volume and psychological significance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,425 - Today&apos;s Value Area Low: Represents the lower bound of fair value, providing attractive risk-reward potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,327 - May 8th Value Area High: Deep pullback level providing excellent bullish re-entry potential if reached.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intraday Bullish Targets for Nasdaq Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should bullish momentum continue, traders may aim for these price levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,572 &amp;amp; $20,613: Immediate upside targets at today&apos;s 2nd and 3rd upper VWAP standard deviations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$20,725: Further bullish target corresponding to the January 13 pivot low, achievable with sustained buying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Longer-term traders can also monitor the psychological $21,000 target, potentially within reach this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearish Reversal Scenario (Lower Probability)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While currently less likely, prudent traders must remain prepared for potential reversals. Watch for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decisive bearish signal would be two consecutive 30-minute candle closes below $20,300. Such a move would invalidate today&apos;s bullish scenario.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key bearish targets in this scenario: $20,270, $20,215 (May 2 POC), $20,167 (Friday&apos;s VWAP), and ultimately $19,855–$19,800 in a deeper bearish move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;tradeCompass Summary&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bias: Bullish after positive US-China trade discussions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Entries: Look to buy dips around volume-supported key levels ($20,495, $20,450, and $20,425).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Targets: Immediate bullish targets at VWAP upper deviations ($20,572 &amp;amp; $20,613), and potential higher swing target at $20,725.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caution Point: Monitor the critical $20,300 level closely as a bullish-bearish pivot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trader Education Recap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Utilize Volume Profile to pinpoint market-validated fair value zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use VWAP to confirm intraday price strength and optimize your entry points around its dynamic bands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Always remain adaptive, setting stop-losses and adjusting positions if the market narrative changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: Use this analysis as orientation. Always trade at your own risk, using a disciplined strategy tailored to your risk tolerance and trading style.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-China tariff reductions reportedly will exceed 100%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-tariff-reductions-reportedly-will-exceed-100-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:28:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-tariff-reductions-reportedly-will-exceed-100-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Phoenix TV is out with the headline, citing a source familiar with the matter. This is also being aired across Twitter/X now but there&apos;s yet to be a more credible source echoing the headline yet. Just be wary of that in case. But if true, that&apos;s a significant reduction as there was some expectation that tariffs will be reduced to around 50-60% - which is still a relative disruption. So if the tariff levels are to be below that, it will be a much welcome stance in facilitating negotiations between the two sides.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:11:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Today, the calendar is empty on the data front as we will just hear from some central bank members. It would have been a boring day if it wasn&apos;t for the US-China trade talks statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 07:00 GMT/03:00 ET, we have the US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent briefing on the US-China trade talks held in Switzerland over the weekend. This is going to be the main event of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sentiment is positive going into the event as both sides delivered upbeat remarks. Nonetheless, we might have reached the peak in the &quot;de-escalation trade&quot;, so we will likely need very good news to keep the party going. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:00 GMT/04:00 ET - BoE&apos;s Lombardelli (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10:30 GMT/06:30 ET - BoE&apos;s Greene (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:50 GMT/08:50 ET - BoE&apos;s Mann (hawkish - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;16:00 GMT/12:00 ET - BoE&apos;s Taylor (dovish - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +1.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-11-in-early-european-trading-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:09:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-11-in-early-european-trading-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +1.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are also up 1.5% on the day, largely holding gains much compared to the dollar from earlier in the day. All eyes will be on Bessent&apos;s brief later at the top of the hour as we also await the joint statement from both US and China after the talks over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heads up: Bessent to speak on China talks at 0700 GMT</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-bessent-to-speak-on-china-talks-at-0700-gmt-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:33:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-bessent-to-speak-on-china-talks-at-0700-gmt-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just a heads up as there will be headline risk to watch out for soon enough. Coincidentally, the timing also matches up with when China will normally comment on international affairs. So, do be on the lookout for that as well. This was Bessent&apos;s remarks yesterday on the matter:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;“I’m happy to report that we made substantial progress between the United States and China in the very important trade talks. First, I want to thank our Swiss host. The Swiss government has been very kind in providing us this wonderful venue, and I think that led to a great deal of productivity we’ve seen. We will be giving details tomorrow, but I can tell you that the talks were productive. We had the vice premier, two vice ministers, who were integrally involved, Ambassador Jamieson, and myself. And I spoke to President Trump, as did Ambassador Jamieson, last night, and he is fully informed of what is going on. So, there will be a complete briefing tomorrow morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Outlook for the week of 12th - 16th May</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-12th-16th-may-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:24:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-12th-16th-may-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Monday will be a light day in terms of scheduled economic events. On Tuesday, Japan will release the BoJ summary of opinions; in the U.K., we’ll get the claimant count change, the average earnings index 3m/y, and the unemployment rate. In the U.S., the main focus will be on the inflation data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, Australia will release the wage price index q/q and on Thursday the employment change and the unemployment rate. Also on Thursday, in the U.K. we&apos;ll get the GDP m/m and the preliminary GDP q/q figures and in the U.S., the PPI m/m, retail sales m/m and unemployment claims. Fed Chair Powell will speak at the Second Thomas Laubach Research Conference in Washington, D.C. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, on Friday, we’ll get the preliminary UoM consumer sentiment and inflation expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the U.S., the consensus for the core CPI m/m is 0.3% vs. the prior 0.1%; for the CPI m/m, it is 0.3% vs. the prior -0.1%; and the CPI y/y is expected to remain unchanged at 2.4%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month’s decline in the monthly reading was due to softness in volatile categories such as energy, travel, and lodging, which are areas affected by economic uncertainty, government austerity, and anticipation of tariff changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While similar headwinds persisted into April, seasonal patterns and the early effects of tariffs, particularly on auto prices, may begin to push core goods inflation higher, according to analysts from Wells Fargo. However, the full impact of the tariff policies will not yet be visible in inflation this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Australia, the consensus for the wage price index q/q is 0.8% vs. the prior 0.7%. In the December quarter, wage growth came in below analyst forecasts and the market consensus.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, annual wage inflation declined from 3.6% to 3.2% in the previous quarter. This week’s data is not expected to show improvement, and the outlook remains subdued; however, the annual rate is expected to hold steady at 3.2%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consensus for the employment change in Australia is 20.9K vs. the prior 32.2K, while the unemployment rate is expected to remain unchanged at 4.1%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; In March, employment rose by 32.2K, but was flat in Q1 2025 overall. According to Westpac analysts, the uneven monthly prints likely reflect softer population growth, which has also contributed to a decline in labour force participation from recent highs. Given the ongoing moderation in population growth, a modest employment increase in April is likely to keep the employment-to-population ratio steady. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent labour force data has shown a notable shift in participation, with the rate falling from a peak of 67.2% in January to a more stable 66.7–66.8% range in recent months. This emerging downtrend appears cyclical, likely reflecting reduced pressure on households to seek additional work as inflation eases and cost-of-living concerns begin to subside. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The expectation for participation to remain at 66.8%, along with an unchanged unemployment rate at 4.1%, reflects the resilience of the labour market amid softer population and employment growth, according to Westpac. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of monetary policy, the RBA will continue monitoring labour market data alongside inflation, which has been softening. The bank is expected to proceed with gradual rate cuts of likely one per quarter, with analysts forecasting additional 25 bps cuts at the August and November meetings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the U.S., the consensus for core retail sales m/m is 0.3% vs. the prior 0.5%, while retail sales m/m are expected to be flat at 0.0% vs. the prior 1.4%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent rise in retail sales was largely driven by households accelerating big-ticket purchases, especially autos, in anticipation of upcoming tariffs, evidenced by a 5.3% surge in vehicle sales. However, strength extended beyond tariff-sensitive categories: restaurant spending rose 1.8%, and the control group (which feeds directly into GDP) posted a solid 0.4% gain, suggesting underlying consumer momentum remains strong, according to Wells Fargo analysts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, the sustainability of consumer spending will depend on whether March’s strength was primarily due to front-loaded demand. If purchases for big-ticket items like vehicles were pulled forward, it could lead to softer spending in the coming months as households scale back. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, early reports indicate that auto sales remained robust in April, likely delaying any major slowdown. As a result, retail sales for April are expected to post a modest overall gain, with non-auto categories rising a steady 0.3%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Gina Constantin at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One good reason to be optimistic of US-China talks over the weekend</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/one-good-reason-to-be-optimistic-of-us-china-talks-over-the-weekend-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:13:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/one-good-reason-to-be-optimistic-of-us-china-talks-over-the-weekend-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;When Trump talks something up, you can bet that there&apos;s always going to be exaggeration to the story. Not least with talks with China, we&apos;ve already gotten a precedent for that back in 2019. This time around is no different of course as he said that both sides &quot;had a very good meeting&quot; over the weekend. However, the big difference this time is actually the response from the Chinese camp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;More often than not, you&apos;ll see China refute claims by the US on how talks are progressing. Or even denying the fact that any talks were taking place, as they did in the weeks prior to this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But now, both sides are expected to produce a joint statement - which is a rarity on its own - after talks in Switzerland. And China is sounding rather upbeat about the situation as well, which supports Trump&apos;s narrative too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The timing of the statement remains unclear but China is saying that: &quot;If the dish is delicious, then the timing is not a matter.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Adding that: &quot;No matter when this statement is released, it&apos;s going to be big news and good news for the world.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With headlines like that, it is little wonder to see why risk trades are looking more exuberant to start the new week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All that being said, the devil will still be in the details. Most reports are indicating that there is some form of agreement of sorts, but the Chinese state media has said that both sides have agreed to &quot;establish an economic and trade consultation mechanism&quot;. And that this will be the main platform as the US and China now move towards negotiating their positions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In other words, the positive thing now is that both sides are showing keen interest to engage in further talks. However, there&apos;s still some ways to go before expecting any grand deal or the likes of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the meantime, we&apos;ll have to see what this means on the existing 145% tariffs. Trump touted &quot;a total reset&quot; but it&apos;s still not clear if that means in both sides&apos; intentions to negotiate or whether that applies to existing tariff levels as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;My guess would be the joint statement should allude to some form of easing on tariffs as both sides seek to negotiate progress by a certain timeline. But again, whether or not there will be actual progress, remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Come what may, we might just get a repeat of the Phase One trade deal from Trump&apos;s first term. And that was a complete failure to say the least. Six years down the road, and we&apos;re still talking about further decoupling between both countries. Nothing&apos;s changed.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Analysis for Today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-analysis-for-today-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 05:10:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-analysis-for-today-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Analysis for Today: tradeCompass Highlights Critical Levels Near $104,265&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s Bitcoin Futures (BTC) are trading at approximately $104,265, slightly below today&apos;s Volume Weighted Average Price (VWAP) at $104,530, signaling mild intraday bearish momentum. However, since the trading session is still developing, this early bearish signal remains tentative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;tradeCompass Levels for May 12, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish Above: $104,735&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Positioned above today&apos;s developing Value Area High (VAH) at $104,630.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More importantly, above the third upper standard deviation of Friday’s VWAP, indicating significant bullish momentum if crossed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$105,200 - Below today&apos;s second VWAP deviation, providing a cautious first profit-taking zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$105,540 - Just under today&apos;s third VWAP deviation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$108,200 - A more ambitious target assuming bullish continuation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearish Below: $103,920&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Located below the first upper deviation of Friday&apos;s VWAP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below today&apos;s Value Area Low (VAL) at $104,070, signaling potential bearish sentiment if breached.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearish Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$103,590 - Near Friday&apos;s VWAP, suggesting a moderate initial downside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$103,140 - Just above Friday&apos;s VAL.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$102,360 - Above Thursday&apos;s VAH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$101,850 - Near Thursday&apos;s Point of Control (POC), where high volume indicates strong historical trading interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$100,450 - Just above Thursday&apos;s VWAP, crucially close to the psychologically significant $100,000 level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding Volume Profile and VWAP in tradeCompass Analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volume Profile:
Volume profile analysis helps traders visualize areas of significant buying and selling activity at specific price levels. Levels with high traded volume, known as &quot;Points of Control&quot; or &quot;Value Areas,&quot; often act as strong support or resistance due to the accumulated market interest. Traders monitor these areas carefully to predict price reversals or continuations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP (Volume Weighted Average Price):
VWAP represents the average price weighted by volume throughout the trading session. It&apos;s a critical benchmark for institutional traders and is often used as a dynamic support or resistance level. Standard deviation bands around VWAP indicate normal trading ranges, providing actionable insights into potential price extremes. Crossing these bands can signal robust momentum and trend shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Context: Revisiting the $100K Level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin recently surpassed the major psychological level of $100,000. Historically, price tends to revisit significant milestones before confirming directional moves. Market makers utilize these levels to trigger stop orders, thereby increasing trading volatility. Consequently, despite the recent bullish breakout, a retest around $100K remains highly probable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium-term sentiment is slightly bearish, suggesting possible consolidation or pullback before any sustained upward movement. However, the longer-term perspective still favors an eventual revisit of the all-time high near $110,150.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Practical Application of tradeCompass&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use the provided bullish and bearish thresholds strategically:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch how price action unfolds near these key levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider partial profit-taking at designated targets to manage risk effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintain flexibility in trading strategies, adapting to real-time market signals and volume indications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Always manage your risk prudently, using tradeCompass as a directional guide complemented by your personalized trading tactics and timeframes.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 12 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-12-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 04:53:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-12-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There are a couple to take note of on the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The first being for EUR/USD at the 1.1250 level. It isn&apos;t one that ties to any technical significance but the expiries do sit nearby the gap closure level after the pair opened with a gap down today. The dollar is in a better spot amid positive news from US-China talks over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I wouldn&apos;t place too much emphasis on the expiries today as such, with headline risks being paramount. We&apos;re still waiting for the joint-statement by the US and China on what the next steps will be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There&apos;s also one for USD/JPY at the 145.65 level but again, it&apos;s not one that ties to any technical significance either. As such, the impact of the expiries might be more muted as dollar and risk sentiment remain bigger drivers of how price action will behave in the session(s) ahead. That especially with headline risks also still taking center stage at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For now, the risk mood remains optimistic as equities race higher but dollar gains have not been all too material. There&apos;s a difference in levels to the exuberance so we&apos;ll have to see who has it right at the end of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs has raised its forecast for China&apos;s yuan</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-has-raised-its-forecast-for-chinas-yuan-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 03:34:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-has-raised-its-forecast-for-chinas-yuan-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs forecasts USD/CNY to dropping to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; 7.20 in 3 months &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;7.10 in six months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;7 over the next 12 months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs sees China&apos;s exports remaining strong. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; “The undervalued levels of the currency, both on a real trade-weighted basis but especially versus the dollar, all point to the possibility for a stronger onshore yuan as a potential offset to tariff reductions” &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Info comes via a Bloomberg (gated) piece on a GS note on Friday. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: US &amp; China officials upbeat on trade talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-us-china-officials-upbeat-on-trade-talks-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 03:24:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-us-china-officials-upbeat-on-trade-talks-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-ibit-sees-the-longest-streak-of-net-inflow-this-year-so-far-20250512/&quot;&gt;BlackRock&apos;s spot bitcoin ETF, IBIT, sees the longest streak of net inflow this year so far&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-england-speakers-monday-lombardelli-greene-mann-taylor-20250512/&quot;&gt;Bank of England speakers Monday: Lombardelli, Greene, Mann, Taylor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-autos-agriculture-airplane-parts-are-all-separate-from-security-matters-20250512/&quot;&gt;Japan PM Ishiba: Autos, agriculture, airplane parts are all separate from security matters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72066-vs-estimate-at-72429-20250512/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.2066 (vs. estimate at 7.2429)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-forecasts-brentwti-average-6056-in-the-rest-of-2025-and-5652-in-2026-20250512/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs forecasts - Brent/WTI average $60/56 in the rest of 2025, and $56/52 in 2026&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/awaiting-the-joint-statement-from-china-and-the-us-on-geneva-trade-talks-no-time-set-20250512/&quot;&gt;Awaiting the joint statement from China and the US on Geneva trade talks - no time set&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-april-bank-loans-rise-slower-than-march-march-current-account-surplus-as-expected-20250512/&quot;&gt;Japan: April bank loans rise slower than March; March current account surplus as expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korean-initial-exports-data-for-may-down-238-yy-in-first-10-days-of-the-month-20250512/&quot;&gt;South Korean initial exports data for May - down 23.8% y/y in first 10 days of the month&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-monday-12-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Monday, 12 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-hiring-outlook-hits-post-covid-low-as-employer-confidence-weakens-20250511/&quot;&gt;UK hiring outlook hits post-COVID low as employer confidence weakens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-for-chinese-president-xi-to-speak-publicly-on-may-13-20250511/&quot;&gt;Heads up for Chinese President Xi to speak publicly on May 13&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-prescription-drug-and-pharma-prices-will-be-reduced-almost-immediately-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trump says prescription drug and pharma prices will be reduced almost immediately&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-equity-index-futures-liking-the-vibes-from-us-and-china-officials-20250511/&quot;&gt;US equity index futures liking the vibes from US and China officials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/globex-is-open-us-equity-index-futures-open-higher-20250511/&quot;&gt;Globex is open! US equity index futures open higher.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ft-chinese-companies-accelerating-a-purge-of-foreign-components-from-their-supply-chains-20250511/&quot;&gt;FT: Chinese companies accelerating a purge of foreign components from their supply chains&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-chinese-cpi-and-ppi-data-over-the-weekend-showed-risk-of-further-deflation-spiral-20250511/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Chinese CPI and PPI data over the weekend showed risk of further deflation spiral&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-geneva-trade-talk-meeting-a-first-step-differences-frictions-remain-win-win-20250511/&quot;&gt;China says Geneva trade talk meeting a first step; differences &amp;amp;frictions remain; win-win&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/no-details-on-us-china-trade-talks-but-both-us-and-china-officials-are-upbeat-20250511/&quot;&gt;No details on US-China trade talks but both US and China officials are upbeat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-he-is-about-to-make-one-of-the-most-important-and-impactful-tweet-ever-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trump says he is about to make &quot;one of the most important and impactful&quot; tweet ever!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/monday-open-levels-indicative-fx-prices-may-12-2025-usdjpy-up-eurusd-down-20250511/&quot;&gt;Monday open levels, indicative FX prices, May 12, 2025 - USD/JPY up, EUR/USD down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/trump-tweets-great-progress-in-us-china-trade-talks-but-final-deal-remains-uncertain-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trump Tweets &quot;Great Progress&quot; in U.S.-China Trade Talks - But Final Deal Remains Uncertain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-sends-a-positive-message-on-trade-with-china-20250511/&quot;&gt;Trump sends a positive message on trade with China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-and-pakistan-declare-immediate-ceasefire-20250510/&quot;&gt;India and Pakistan declare immediate ceasefire&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-there-is-a-baseline-of-10-tariffs-but-could-be-excemptions-20250509/&quot;&gt;Trump: There is a baseline of 10% tariffs but could be excemptions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-canadian-jobs-market-continues-to-crack-20250509/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Canadian jobs market continues to crack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
US
and China initial trade talks wrapped up in Geneva on Sunday with
positive comments coming from both sides. In summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
China
side:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
	a
	mechanism for further talks has been agreed (agreed to establish a
	&apos;China-US trade consultation mechanism&apos;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
	the
	joint statement to come will be &quot;good news for the world&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
US
side:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
	Bessent
	said there had been &quot;substantial progress&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
	Greer
	said that &quot;perhaps the differences were not so large as maybe
	thought&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
two will issue a joint statement on Monday, no time for it has been
confirmed, where more details are promised. US equity futures gapped
higher upon reopening for the week and have not shown much
retracement at all. Hopes are up for substantive details of
improvement in China-US trade relations. Hopes have risen before and
dashed, so we’ll how this goes today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Across
FX USD/JPY gapped higher and has partially retraced. EUR/USD gapped
lower and has fully filled that gap. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Oil
gapped higher and has retraced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Further,
Fed rate cut bets faded back a little and gold dipped. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Also
of news, Trump says he’ll sign an executive order, at 9 am US
Eastern time on Monday, slashing US prescription drug prices by up to
80%,. Trump wants to align US prices with the world’s lowest,
calling it a long-overdue fix for fairness. Aligning US prices with
the world’s lowest sounds a very ambitious goal. Doubts have been
raised about courts blocking such moves. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;From
Japan today we had Prime Minister  Ishiba saying that the he would
not accept a trade agreement with the US that excludes auto tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BlackRock&apos;s spot bitcoin ETF, IBIT, sees the longest streak of net inflow this year so far</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-ibit-sees-the-longest-streak-of-net-inflow-this-year-so-far-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 02:28:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/blackrocks-spot-bitcoin-etf-ibit-sees-the-longest-streak-of-net-inflow-this-year-so-far-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Crypto &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theblock.co/post/353873/goldman-sachs-boosts-ibit-holdings-by-28-as-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-logs-longest-inflow-streak-of-2025&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;media &lt;/a&gt;with the report:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Goldman Sachs is now the largest holder of shares of IBIT, BlackRock’s spot bitcoin ETF, after boosting its holdings by 28% over the course of 2025’s first quarter. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
IBIT’s 20-day streak of net inflows is the longest such streak for any spot bitcoin ETF in 2025, drawing in over $5 billion over the period. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BTC update, such flows helping to underpin the price:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of England speakers Monday: Lombardelli, Greene, Mann, Taylor</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-england-speakers-monday-lombardelli-greene-mann-taylor-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 02:19:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-england-speakers-monday-lombardelli-greene-mann-taylor-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The times listed below are in GMT/US Eastern time format: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;0800/0400 Bank of England Deputy Governor Clare Lombardelli delivers speech at King&apos;s Business School &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1030/0630 Bank of England policymaker Megan Greene speaks on a panel at the BoE&apos;s Bank Watchers&apos; conference 2025 at King&apos;s College Business School &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;0850 /1250 Bank of England policymaker Catherine Mann speaks on a panel at the BoE&apos;s Bank Watchers&apos; conference&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1600/1200 Bank of England policymaker Alan Taylor delivers speech at King&apos;s Business School &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Bank cut its benchmark rate last week:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-cuts-bank-rate-by-25-bps-to-425-as-expected-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;BOE cuts bank rate by 25 bps to 4.25%, as expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-governor-bailey-interest-rates-are-not-on-auto-pilot-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;BOE governor Bailey: Interest rates are not on auto-pilot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan PM Ishiba: Autos, agriculture, airplane parts are all separate from security matters</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-autos-agriculture-airplane-parts-are-all-separate-from-security-matters-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 01:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-autos-agriculture-airplane-parts-are-all-separate-from-security-matters-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan PM Ishiba: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Autos, agriculture, airplane parts are all separate from security matters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economy minister Akazawa chimes in similarly:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Security and forex are not part of trade discussions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.2066 (vs. estimate at 7.2429)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72066-vs-estimate-at-72429-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 01:15:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72066-vs-estimate-at-72429-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous close was 7.2399&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC injects 43bn yuan via 7-day RR, sets rate at 1.4%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;there are no maturities today, hence the net injection is that 43bn yuan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big news re China is the trade talks, detail is due some time today:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/awaiting-the-joint-statement-from-china-and-the-us-on-geneva-trade-talks-no-time-set-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Awaiting the joint statement from China and the US on Geneva trade talks - no time set&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs forecasts - Brent/WTI average $60/56 in the rest of 2025, and $56/52 in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-forecasts-brentwti-average-6056-in-the-rest-of-2025-and-5652-in-2026-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 01:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-forecasts-brentwti-average-6056-in-the-rest-of-2025-and-5652-in-2026-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs on crude:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“We still expect Brent/WTI prices to edge down and average $60/56 in the rest of 2025 and $56/52 in 2026”
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expects solid supply growth outside US shale to weigh further on oil prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awaiting the joint statement from China and the US on Geneva trade talks - no time set</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/awaiting-the-joint-statement-from-china-and-the-us-on-geneva-trade-talks-no-time-set-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 01:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/awaiting-the-joint-statement-from-china-and-the-us-on-geneva-trade-talks-no-time-set-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Chinese Vice-Premier He Lifeng said a joint statement would be released in Geneva on Monday. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Vice-Commerce Minister Li Chenggang said it would contain &quot;good news for the world&quot;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As yet I haven&apos;t found a scheduled time for the release of this expected joint statement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What we have had so far from official statements has been a bit vague, as posted much earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China side:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
a mechanism for further talks has been agreed (agreed to establish a &apos;China-US trade consultation mechanism&apos; )
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;the joint statement to come will be &quot;good news for the world.&quot;
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;US side:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Bessent said there had been &quot;substantial progress&quot;
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Greer said that &quot;perhaps the differences were not so large as maybe thought&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for markets, in summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;EUR/USD traded a gap lower very early Monday but has more or less converted that gap&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;USD/JPY gapped higher in early trade and has retraced around 50% of the gap&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;USequity index futures opened with a gap higher and have barely retraced at all&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oil opened with a gap higher and has filled it&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;From earlier also:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC is expected to set the USD/CNY reference rate at 7.2429 – Reuters estimate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72429-reuters-estimate-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:36:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72429-reuters-estimate-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China USD/CNY reference rate is due around 0115 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How the process works:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type=&quot;disc&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily midpoint setting: Each morning, the PBOC sets a midpoint for the yuan against a basket of currencies, primarily the US dollar. The central bank takes into account factors such as market supply and demand, economic indicators, and international currency market fluctuations. The midpoint serves as a reference point for that day&apos;s trading.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The trading band: The PBOC allows the yuan to move within a specified range around the midpoint. The trading band is set at +/- 2%, meaning the yuan could appreciate or depreciate by a maximum of 2% from the midpoint during a single trading day. This range is subject to change by the PBOC based on economic conditions and policy objectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intervention: If the yuan&apos;s value approaches the limit of the trading band or experiences excessive volatility, the PBOC may intervene in the foreign exchange market by buying or selling the yuan to stabilize its value. This helps maintain a controlled and gradual adjustment of the currency&apos;s value.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan: April bank loans rise slower than March; March current account surplus as expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-april-bank-loans-rise-slower-than-march-march-current-account-surplus-as-expected-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:35:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-april-bank-loans-rise-slower-than-march-march-current-account-surplus-as-expected-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan data update. Not the focus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The focus is US-China relations and Trump&apos;s move to lower drug prices to US consumers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While we do not have any details on the US-China trade talks beyond the two side have agreed to meet further, at least its some sort of progress. The two sides will be issuing a joint statement that may contain some detail. The statement, they say, will be issued on Monday. Its Monday where I am so, yeah, get on with it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/no-details-on-us-china-trade-talks-but-both-us-and-china-officials-are-upbeat-20250511/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; data-font-size=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;No details on US-China trade talks but both US and China officials are upbeat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-geneva-trade-talk-meeting-a-first-step-differences-frictions-remain-win-win-20250511/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; data-font-size=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;China says Geneva trade talk meeting a first step; differences &amp;amp;frictions remain; win-win&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;On drugs:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-prescription-drug-and-pharma-prices-will-be-reduced-almost-immediately-20250511/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Trump says prescription drug and pharma prices will be reduced almost immediately&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean initial exports data for May - down 23.8% y/y in first 10 days of the month</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korean-initial-exports-data-for-may-down-238-yy-in-first-10-days-of-the-month-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 00:01:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korean-initial-exports-data-for-may-down-238-yy-in-first-10-days-of-the-month-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;South Korean initial exports data for May, the country&apos;s Customs Agency:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;May 1–10 exports -23.8% y/y&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;May 1–10 Imports -15.9% y/y &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trade balance at provisional $-1.74 bln&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade ideas thread - Monday, 12 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-monday-12-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250511/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 23:50:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-monday-12-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250511/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Good morning, afternoon and evening all. Any charts, technical analysis, trade ideas, thoughts, views, ForexLive traders would like to share and discuss with fellow ForexLive traders, please do so:
 &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK hiring outlook hits post-COVID low as employer confidence weakens</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-hiring-outlook-hits-post-covid-low-as-employer-confidence-weakens-20250511/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 23:32:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-hiring-outlook-hits-post-covid-low-as-employer-confidence-weakens-20250511/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;UK data - The Chartered Institute of Personnel and Development (CIPD) employment intentions gauge fell from +13 to +8, the lowest level on record excluding the COVID-19 period&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Large private-sector employers were the main contributors to the decline, reflecting broader uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CIPD’s economist says hiring reluctance reflects weak business confidence amid rising costs and global uncertainty. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Separately, the KPMG and the Recruitment and Employment Confederation (KPMG/REC) survey showed another decline in recruiter job placements, though the pace eased slightly from March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall demand for staff fell more sharply in April, reinforcing signs of a weakening labour market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data aligns with the Bank of England’s recent signals that the labour market is softening, despite ongoing concerns about high wage growth. Q1 official wage figures are due from the UK on Tuesday -  expected to show nearly 6% annual growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;CIPD puts median pay settlements at 3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;CIPD’s economist says hiring reluctance reflects weak business confidence amid rising costs and global uncertainty.

BDO employment gauge: BDO’s composite employment index hit a 12-year low in April, underlining the downturn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;info via Reuters. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heads up for Chinese President Xi to speak publicly on May 13</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-for-chinese-president-xi-to-speak-publicly-on-may-13-20250511/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 23:21:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-for-chinese-president-xi-to-speak-publicly-on-may-13-20250511/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;ICYMI,  a Chinese foreign ministry spokesperson announcement on Sunday:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping will attend and deliver a speech at the opening ceremony of the fourth ministerial meeting of the China-CELAC (Community of Latin American and Caribbean States) Forum in Beijing on May 13&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xi doesn&apos;t speak publicly as often as Trump. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: PRESCRIPTION DRUG AND PHARMACEUTICAL PRICES WILL BE REDUCED, ALMOST IMMEDIATELY, BY 30% TO 80%

TRUMP: U.S. WILL PAY THE SAME PRICE AS THE NATION THAT PAYS THE LOWEST PRICE ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.

TRUMP: WILL SIGN ORDER AT WHITE HOUSE AT 9 A.M. ON MONDAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921694636399026416#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:31:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921694636399026416#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: PRESCRIPTION DRUG AND PHARMACEUTICAL PRICES WILL BE REDUCED, ALMOST IMMEDIATELY, BY 30% TO 80%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: U.S. WILL PAY THE SAME PRICE AS THE NATION THAT PAYS THE LOWEST PRICE ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: WILL SIGN ORDER AT WHITE HOUSE AT 9 A.M. ON MONDAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: PRESCRIPTION DRUG &amp; PHARMA PRICES WILL BE REDUCED 30-80%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921694261151482212#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:29:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921694261151482212#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: PRESCRIPTION DRUG &amp;amp; PHARMA PRICES WILL BE REDUCED 30-80%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says prescription drug and pharma prices will be reduced almost immediately</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-prescription-drug-and-pharma-prices-will-be-reduced-almost-immediately-20250511/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:26:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-prescription-drug-and-pharma-prices-will-be-reduced-almost-immediately-20250511/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;While the news out of the weekend trade talk with China was long on feel goods it was very short on detail. This, on the other hand, appears to be more substantive. Its great news for those in the US reliant on medicines for their health. Trump says he&apos;ll be signing the order on Monday morning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prescription drug and pharmaceutical prices will be reduced, almost immediately, by 30% to 80%
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;U.S. will pay the same price as the nation that pays the lowest price anywhere in the world.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will sign order at White House at 9 a.m. on Monday&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The detail on how Trump will achieve this will be interesting to discover. We wait for that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Biotech stocks look likely to be a casualty of this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump &apos;tweet&apos;:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US equity index futures liking the vibes from US and China officials</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-equity-index-futures-liking-the-vibes-from-us-and-china-officials-20250511/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:11:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-equity-index-futures-liking-the-vibes-from-us-and-china-officials-20250511/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The news out of the China-US trade talks in Switzerland over the weekend is lacking substance, we await the joint statement on Monday, but officials are upbeat:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/no-details-on-us-china-trade-talks-but-both-us-and-china-officials-are-upbeat-20250511/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; data-font-size=&quot;&quot;&gt;No details on US-China trade talks but both US and China officials are upbeat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-geneva-trade-talk-meeting-a-first-step-differences-frictions-remain-win-win-20250511/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; data-font-size=&quot;&quot;&gt;China says Geneva trade talk meeting a first step; differences &amp;amp;frictions remain; win-win&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The early market response was a higher USD:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/monday-open-levels-indicative-fx-prices-may-12-2025-usdjpy-up-eurusd-down-20250511/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Monday open levels, indicative FX prices, May 12, 2025 - USD/JPY up, EUR/USD down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Futures have reopened for the week&apos;s trade, with equity indexes at odds with the dollar:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/globex-is-open-us-equity-index-futures-open-higher-20250511/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;US equity index futures open higher.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UST futures lower &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed funds trim rate cut prospect&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vibes winning on equities:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. 10-YEAR TREASURY FUTURES FALL 9 TICKS, FED FUND FUTURES FURTHER TRIM RATE CUTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921688786032836844#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 22:08:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921688786032836844#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. 10-YEAR TREASURY FUTURES FALL 9 TICKS, FED FUND FUTURES FURTHER TRIM RATE CUTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) DOLLAR UP 0.5% AT 146.20 YEN IN EARLY TRADE AMID US-CHINA TRADE HOPES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921680053743632839#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 21:33:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921680053743632839#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DOLLAR UP 0.5% AT 146.20 YEN IN EARLY TRADE AMID US-CHINA TRADE HOPES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RELEASE OF ISRAELI-AMERICAN HOSTAGE EDAN ALEXANDER TO HAPPEN ON TUESDAY, SOURCE FAMILIAR WITH THE MATTER TELLS REUTERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921648656618336725#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 19:28:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921648656618336725#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RELEASE OF ISRAELI-AMERICAN HOSTAGE EDAN ALEXANDER TO HAPPEN ON TUESDAY, SOURCE FAMILIAR WITH THE MATTER TELLS REUTERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINESE OFFICIAL IN GENEVA SAYS PROGRESS IN US TRADE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921636363788591264#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:39:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921636363788591264#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINESE OFFICIAL IN GENEVA SAYS PROGRESS IN US TRADE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA, US AGREED TO ESTABLISH TRADE CONSULTATION MECHANISM: RTRS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921636317282128354#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:39:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921636317282128354#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA, US AGREED TO ESTABLISH TRADE CONSULTATION MECHANISM: RTRS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: BOTH SIDES AGREED TO ESTABLISH CHINA-U.S. TRADE CONSULTATION MECHANISM</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921636066735313078#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921636066735313078#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: BOTH SIDES AGREED TO ESTABLISH CHINA-U.S. TRADE CONSULTATION MECHANISM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: BOTH SIDES REACHED IMPORTANT CONSENSUS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921636000129786365#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921636000129786365#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: BOTH SIDES REACHED IMPORTANT CONSENSUS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: TRADE TALKS WERE CONSTRUCTIVE, MADE SUBSTANTIVE PROGRESS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921635937659813970#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:38:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921635937659813970#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: TRADE TALKS WERE CONSTRUCTIVE, MADE SUBSTANTIVE PROGRESS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: ON CHINA-U.S. TRADE TALKS, BOTH SIDES HAD IN-DEPTH EXCHANGE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921635875655458839#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:37:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921635875655458839#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S VICE PREMIER HE LIFENG: ON CHINA-U.S. TRADE TALKS, BOTH SIDES HAD IN-DEPTH EXCHANGE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA OFFICIALS HOLD PRESS CONFERENCE IN GENEVA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921635729123238297#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:37:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921635729123238297#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA OFFICIALS HOLD PRESS CONFERENCE IN GENEVA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: NEXT TRUTH WILL BE ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT EVER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921634572158079220#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:32:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921634572158079220#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: NEXT TRUTH WILL BE ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT EVER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ZELENSKIY SAYS: I WILL MEET PUTIN IN TURKEY ON THURSDAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921612432838959406#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 17:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921612432838959406#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ZELENSKIY SAYS: I WILL MEET PUTIN IN TURKEY ON THURSDAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: STARTING TO DOUBT THAT UKRAINE WILL MAKE A DEAL WITH PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921605758677922082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 16:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921605758677922082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: STARTING TO DOUBT THAT UKRAINE WILL MAKE A DEAL WITH PUTIN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *GREER: THIS WAS A VERY CONSTRUCTIVE 2 DAYS

*GREER: DIFFERENCES NOT AS GREAT AS PREVIOUSLY THOUGHT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921595928005193922#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:59:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921595928005193922#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*GREER: THIS WAS A VERY CONSTRUCTIVE 2 DAYS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*GREER: DIFFERENCES NOT AS GREAT AS PREVIOUSLY THOUGHT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *BESSENT: WE WILL BE GIVING DETAILS MONDAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921595230437978571#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:56:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921595230437978571#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*BESSENT: WE WILL BE GIVING DETAILS MONDAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *BESSENT: WE HAVE MADE SUBSTANTIAL PROGRESS IN TRADE TALKS WITH CHINA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921595184833315101#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 15:56:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921595184833315101#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*BESSENT: WE HAVE MADE SUBSTANTIAL PROGRESS IN TRADE TALKS WITH CHINA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HASSETT: COMMERCE SECRETARY HOWARD LUTNICK HAS BRIEFED ME ON ABOUT 24 DEALS HE AND US TRADE REPRESENTATIVE GREER ARE WORKING ON -FOX NEWS SUNDAY MORNING FUTURES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921571139651842502#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 14:20:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921571139651842502#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HASSETT: COMMERCE SECRETARY HOWARD LUTNICK HAS BRIEFED ME ON ABOUT 24 DEALS HE AND US TRADE REPRESENTATIVE GREER ARE WORKING ON -FOX NEWS SUNDAY MORNING FUTURES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HASSETT: MORE TRADE DEALS COULD BE COMING AS SOON AS THIS WEEK -FOX NEWS SUNDAY MORNING FUTURES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921571023159197851#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 14:20:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921571023159197851#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HASSETT: MORE TRADE DEALS COULD BE COMING AS SOON AS THIS WEEK -FOX NEWS SUNDAY MORNING FUTURES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
