<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>The central bank to all central banks warns of a potential &quot;scramble&quot; for US dollars</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/the-central-bank-to-all-central-banks-warns-of-a-potential-scramble-for-us-dollars-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 22:20:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/the-central-bank-to-all-central-banks-warns-of-a-potential-scramble-for-us-dollars-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;64&quot; data-end=&quot;454&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Bank for International Settlements (BIS) has warned that growing U.S. financial volatility could spark a sudden scramble for dollars, particularly from non-bank investors holding vast off-balance-sheet FX swap positions. BIS official Hyun-Song Shin said more than $80 trillion in FX swaps—essentially short-term dollar debt—are held by funds and institutions outside the banking system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;456&quot; data-end=&quot;749&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;These swaps involve borrowing dollars while holding euros or yen, and a rapid unwinding of these positions could trigger a sharp surge in demand for the U.S. currency. “If you have to roll over that swap you have to join the scramble,” Shin said in a lecture at the London School of Economics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;751&quot; data-end=&quot;1097&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The warning follows a turbulent April marked by Trump’s tariff escalation and Moody’s downgrade of U.S. sovereign credit. Shin also questioned whether investor faith in U.S. assets—stocks, bonds, and the dollar—might be faltering, noting all three fell together, an unusual alignment that may prompt longer-term strategic reassessments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;751&quot; data-end=&quot;1097&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;751&quot; data-end=&quot;1097&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Info via Reuters. The warning seems to be of a worst-case scenario. You can be sure that such a scenario has been gamed out and those seeking USD will not be wondering what to do .... &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI: Nippon Steel sweetens U.S. Steel bid with US$14bn investment pledge</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/icymi-nippon-steel-sweetens-us-steel-bid-with-us14bn-investment-pledge-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:59:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/icymi-nippon-steel-sweetens-us-steel-bid-with-us14bn-investment-pledge-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;79&quot; data-end=&quot;269&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Nippon Steel plans to invest $14 billion in U.S. Steel, including $4 billion for a new mill, as part of a last-ditch effort to win U.S. approval for its takeover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;271&quot; data-end=&quot;461&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;273&quot; data-end=&quot;461&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The proposed acquisition has drawn bipartisan opposition, with both President Biden and former President Trump arguing U.S. Steel should remain American-owned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;463&quot; data-end=&quot;687&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;465&quot; data-end=&quot;687&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A fresh national security review is set to conclude by May 21, after Biden blocked the deal earlier this year. Trump would then have 15 days to decide, though the timeline could shift.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;689&quot; data-end=&quot;904&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;691&quot; data-end=&quot;904&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Nippon Steel initially pledged $1.4B in U.S. investments, later raised to $2.7B, and now up to $14B, including $11B through 2028 and $1B on a greenfield site—potentially expanding to $4B.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;906&quot; data-end=&quot;1094&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;908&quot; data-end=&quot;1094&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A lawyer close to the matter said the boosted investment could help secure approval, citing its importance to national security and domestic steel production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;906&quot; data-end=&quot;1094&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;908&quot; data-end=&quot;1094&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt; Nippon faces a $565 million breakup fee if the deal collapses, and continues to grapple with 25% U.S. steel tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1410&quot; data-end=&quot;1580&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1412&quot; data-end=&quot;1580&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;While Nippon has gone to great lengths to win approval, it’s still uncertain whether the Trump administration will ultimately endorse the transaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Info comes via Reuters report Monday US time. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Motors to stop exporting vehicles from the US to China</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/general-motors-to-stop-exporting-vehicles-from-the-us-to-china-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:49:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/general-motors-to-stop-exporting-vehicles-from-the-us-to-china-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;General Motors on Friday informed employees and dealers for its China export business that it would stop shipping vehicles to China from the United States, the company said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing further re details at this stage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GM general motors CEO Mary Barra&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: COULD BE A TIME WHEN RUSSIA SANCTIONS WILL HAPPEN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924577824523841981#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:28:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924577824523841981#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: COULD BE A TIME WHEN RUSSIA SANCTIONS WILL HAPPEN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: HAVE A RED LINE IN MY HEAD ON WHEN I&apos;LL STOP PUSHING ON RUSSIA-UKRAINE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924577696585044412#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:27:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924577696585044412#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: HAVE A RED LINE IN MY HEAD ON WHEN I&apos;LL STOP PUSHING ON RUSSIA-UKRAINE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: BELIEVE PUTIN WANTS TO STOP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924577581019373943#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:27:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924577581019373943#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: BELIEVE PUTIN WANTS TO STOP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 19 May: The Fed is uncertain.Moody downgrade fear subsides</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-19-may-the-fed-is-uncertainmoody-downgrade-fear-subsides-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:16:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-19-may-the-fed-is-uncertainmoody-downgrade-fear-subsides-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-stocks-close-marginally-higher-sp-up-for-the-sixth-consecutive-day-20250519/&quot;&gt;US stocks close marginally higher. S&amp;amp;P up for the sixth consecutive day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-does-not-anticipate-any-trade-deal-announcement-at-g7-meeting-this-week-20250519/&quot;&gt;US treasury does not anticipate any trade deal announcements at G7 meeting this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-dhingra-her-vote-for-50-bp-cut-was-partly-to-make-a-statement-on-direction-of-economy-20250519/&quot;&gt;BOE Dhingra: Her vote for 50 bp cut was partly to make a statement on direction of economy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-bostic-thinks-rates-in-the-us-are-mildly-restrictive-20250519/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Bostic: Thinks rates in the US are mildly restrictive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6269-20250519/&quot;&gt;Crude oil futures settle at $62.69&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/kremlin-trumpputin-did-not-discuss-ceasefire-timeframe-20250519/&quot;&gt;Kremlin: Trump/Putin did not discuss ceasefire timeframe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kashkari-there-is-big-uncertainty-now-in-the-economy-20250519/&quot;&gt;Feds Kashkari: There is big uncertainty now in the economy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-call-with-putin-went-very-well-20250519/&quot;&gt;Trump. Call with Putin went very well&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/snb-schlegal-snb-tolerates-negative-inflation-rate-in-the-short-term-20250519/&quot;&gt;SNB Schlegal: SNB tolerates negative inflation rate in the short term&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/russian-press-the-putintrump-phone-call-has-concluded-20250519/&quot;&gt;Russian Press: The Putin/Trump phone call has concluded&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/european-indices-end-the-day-with-mixed-results-20250519/&quot;&gt;European indices end the day with mixed results&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-uncertainty-has-led-the-fed-to-keep-interest-rates-steady-so-far-20250519/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Williams: Uncertainty has led the Fed to keep interest rates steady so far&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-huge-divergence-between-retail-and-fund-managers-continues-20250519/&quot;&gt;The huge divergence between retail and fund managers continues&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/white-house-world-has-confidence-in-the-us-economy-20250519/&quot;&gt;White House: World has confidence in the US economy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/fomc-gov-jefferson-the-impact-of-tariffs-on-the-feds-mandates-is-top-of-mind-20250519/&quot;&gt;FOMC Gov. Jefferson: The impact of tariffs on the Fed&apos;s mandates is top of mind&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-us-undermines-consensus-reached-in-geneva-talks-20250519/&quot;&gt;China: US undermines consensus reached in Geneva talks.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-recent-economic-data-has-been-very-good-20250519/&quot;&gt;Feds Williams: Recent economic data has been very good&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/wh-hassett-would-not-be-surprised-if-there-are-more-trade-deals-this-week-20250519/&quot;&gt;WH Hassett: Would not be surprised if there are more trade deals this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-signs-that-the-us-japan-trade-agreement-is-on-ice-20250519/&quot;&gt;More signs that the US-Japan trade agreement is on ice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-rough-day-for-usd-and-us-treasuries-20250519/&quot;&gt;Forexlive European FX news wrap: Rough day for USD and US Treasuries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-bostic-moodys-downgrade-will-cut-across-economics-financial-markets-20250519/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Bostic: Moody&apos;s downgrade will cut across economics, financial markets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;168&quot; data-end=&quot;410&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The late-Friday news of Moody’s downgrade of U.S. debt triggered broad market volatility to start the new trading week. Stocks opened lower, U.S. bond prices declined (sending yields higher), and the U.S. dollar weakened across the board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;412&quot; data-end=&quot;471&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;At the open, the USD was sharply lower, with losses of:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;472&quot; data-end=&quot;531&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;472&quot; data-end=&quot;491&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;474&quot; data-end=&quot;491&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;-0.90% vs EUR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;492&quot; data-end=&quot;511&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;494&quot; data-end=&quot;511&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;-0.81% vs GBP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;512&quot; data-end=&quot;531&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;514&quot; data-end=&quot;531&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;-0.45% vs JPY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;533&quot; data-end=&quot;605&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;By the end of the day, the dollar recovered modestly against most pairs:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;606&quot; data-end=&quot;747&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;606&quot; data-end=&quot;623&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;608&quot; data-end=&quot;623&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;EUR: -0.70%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;624&quot; data-end=&quot;641&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;626&quot; data-end=&quot;641&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;GBP: -0.65%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;642&quot; data-end=&quot;747&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;644&quot; data-end=&quot;747&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;JPY: -0.55%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;644&quot; data-end=&quot;747&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The dollar’s rebound was partial, with the decline extending further against the yen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;749&quot; data-end=&quot;1109&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bond markets saw a turnaround during the U.S. session. Earlier in the day, the 30-year yield spiked above the key 5% level, touching 5.007% at the open. However, a wave of buying brought it down to 4.904% by the close. Similarly, the 10-year yield fell from 4.536% to 4.493%, reflecting a flight to the US bonds as traders reevaluated the impact of the downgrade and realized that the US still remains a safe haven for money flows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1111&quot; data-end=&quot;1403&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Equities also rebounded sharply. After falling as much as -273 points, the NASDAQ reversed course and closed marginally higher by 0.02%. The S&amp;amp;P 500 erased an intraday drop of -62.69 points to finish up 5.22 points, or +0.09%, marking its sixth consecutive daily gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1405&quot; data-end=&quot;1914&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The day’s news flow was driven by geopolitical developments and Federal Reserve commentary. On the geopolitical front, concerns intensified over the Israel-Gaza conflict, as Israeli Finance Minister Smotrich stated the country aims to push Gaza’s population southward and potentially out of the territory, according to Sky News Arabia. Prime Minister Netanyahu also vowed to take full control of Gaza. Israeli forces expanded their ground operations and airstrikes, reportedly killing over 100 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1916&quot; data-end=&quot;2052&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A high-profile phone call between former President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin also captured market attention:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;2054&quot; data-end=&quot;3145&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2054&quot; data-end=&quot;2517&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2056&quot; data-end=&quot;2517&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;From Trump’s perspective, the call was “very well” received. Trump said Russia and Ukraine would immediately begin ceasefire negotiations and highlighted Russia’s interest in expanding trade with the U.S. once the war ends. He noted that Germany, France, Italy, Finland, and the Vatican were informed of the talks, with the Vatican offering to host. Trump emphasized a diplomatic tone and the potential for mutual economic benefit post-conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2519&quot; data-end=&quot;3145&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2521&quot; data-end=&quot;3145&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;From the Kremlin’s perspective, the call focused on normalizing U.S.-Russia relations, including discussions of a potential prisoner swap involving nine detainees from each country. Trump reportedly spoke emotionally about the desire to restore strong ties and identified Russia as a key future trade partner. While both leaders agreed to maintain dialogue and prepare for a personal meeting, the Kremlin clarified that no ceasefire timeframe was discussed. Moscow also noted Trump’s preference for diplomatic agreements over sanctions, and expressed support for U.S. efforts in the Middle East and Iran.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the Fed today, the theme from monetary policy perspective was that of uncertainty: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Atlanta Fed President Raphael Bostic this morning on CNBC warned that Moody’s downgrade could have wide-reaching effects across the economy and financial markets, particularly by raising the cost of capital and introducing greater uncertainty. He emphasized that it may take several months to fully understand the impact on U.S. debt demand and inflation from tariffs. Bostic noted the Fed is cautious on rate cuts, leaning toward just one this year due to the complex interplay of inflation, tariffs, and economic sentiment. While markets are functioning well, inflation remains above target and expectations are moving in a troubling way, although firms aren’t planning large layoffs. He highlighted a disconnect between economic sentiment and data and pointed to potential ripple effects from even reduced tariffs on China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New York Fed President John Williams struck a cautiously optimistic tone in his remarks to the Mortgage Bankers Association, noting that recent economic data has been “very good” and the labor market is now “pretty much in balance.” He acknowledged that inflation continues to decline slowly and monetary policy remains “in a good place,” characterizing it as slightly restrictive. While first-quarter growth was affected by unusual trade dynamics, Williams emphasized that uncertainty—particularly around trade—is a defining feature of the current economic environment. He noted that many businesses and households are in a “wait-and-see” mode. Williams said the Fed still has work to do in reducing its balance sheet, though the process so far has not disrupted market pricing. He reassured that the U.S. dollar retains its status as the world’s reserve currency and that investor demand for Treasuries remains strong. Core fixed income markets, he added, are functioning well. On the consumer side, Williams observed that while households remain generally healthy, there are early signs of increasing caution. He expects the economy to slow this year and stressed that the Fed can take its time with future policy decisions. He also warned that tariffs could add upward pressure to inflation and increase unemployment risks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FOMC Governor Philip Jefferson emphasized that the potential impact of tariffs on the Fed’s dual mandate of price stability and full employment is a key concern. He noted that the risks to inflation and jobs will largely depend on policy decisions from the administration, many of which have not yet been finalized. Jefferson warned that tariffs could lead to a one-time rise in price levels and stressed the importance of preventing such increases from becoming embedded in inflation expectations. He reiterated the Fed’s commitment to maintaining current policy to ensure inflation remains anchored. While acknowledging the labor market&apos;s resilience so far, he said it is still too early to assess how new trade policies might affect employment. Jefferson also confirmed that there are no active discussions about altering the Fed’s ample reserves framework. On the Moody’s downgrade of U.S. debt, he indicated the Fed will treat it like any other piece of incoming data—evaluating its implications for inflation and the labor market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: US IS NOT STEPPING BACK FROM RUSSIA-UKRAINE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924574409911627810#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:14:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924574409911627810#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: US IS NOT STEPPING BACK FROM RUSSIA-UKRAINE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Japan to seek market views on Japanese Government Bond buying</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-to-seek-market-views-on-japanese-government-bond-buying-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:48:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-to-seek-market-views-on-japanese-government-bond-buying-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Nikkei reporting on moves from the Bank of Japan to seek market opinion on JGB buying amounts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At present the BoJ is planning to reduce JGB buying after Spring 2026, this plan is currently unchanged. For now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news comes as Japanese bond yields have been persistently rising. On of the factors supporting the yen. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI - ECB&apos;s Muller said must be cautious on further rate cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-ecbs-muller-said-must-be-cautious-on-further-rate-cuts-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:42:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-ecbs-muller-said-must-be-cautious-on-further-rate-cuts-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt; Bank of Estonia Governor, and member of the European Central Bank Governing Council, Madis Müller, spoke in an interview. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bloomberg (gated) carried the report. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In brief:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can’t rule out further reductions in rates
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be cautious as there’s no clear need yet to actively support economic growth
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Muller said he think interest rates are already low enough, they are not holding back economic recovery
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Said that while further cuts might be justified, its not obvious that significantly lower rates are necessary
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Muller noted economic challenges include international trade and tariff confusion, says these will slow economic growth in the eurozone and may ease price pressure
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On the other hand, he noted the potential for inflation pressures from fiscal policy in Europe after governments promised to rasie defense outlays&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI - China&apos;s state banks are expected to cut deposit rates today (Tuesday China time)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-chinas-state-banks-are-expected-to-cut-deposit-rates-today-tuesday-china-time-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:20:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-chinas-state-banks-are-expected-to-cut-deposit-rates-today-tuesday-china-time-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China&apos;s major state banks expected  to cut their deposit rates today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;will cut rates on some fixed-term deposits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;no indication of the scale of the rate cuts has been given&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cuts would be part of stimulus efforts from China. The People&apos;s Bank of China cut its 7 day reverse repo benchmark rate by 10bp to 1.4% earlier this month. Governor Pan Gongsheng said a 10 basis point cut will lead to a reduction in the benchmark loan prime rate (LPR) of the same size.The monthly LPR fixing is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-reserve-bank-of-australia-rate-cut-expected-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;due at 0100 GMT&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LPR cuts should help banks lower their funding costs. Chinese banks are under pressure to support economic growth amid a property crisis, weak loan demand and record low interest margins.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE CUSTOMER DATA THEFT TO BE INVESTIGATED BY JUSTICE DEPARTMENT

$COIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924559885246583004#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:16:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924559885246583004#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE CUSTOMER DATA THEFT TO BE INVESTIGATED BY JUSTICE DEPARTMENT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks close marginally higher. S&amp;P up for the sixth consecutive day</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-stocks-close-marginally-higher-sp-up-for-the-sixth-consecutive-day-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:07:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-stocks-close-marginally-higher-sp-up-for-the-sixth-consecutive-day-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The S&amp;amp;P is closing higher for the 6th gain in a row. The Dow is up for 3 days. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The markets shook off the early-day declines due to the late Friday Moody&apos;s downgrade of the US debt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; The Dow was down  -317 points at session lows, but is closing up 137.33 points or 0.32% at 42792.07&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The S&amp;amp;P was down -62.69 points at session lows, but is closing up 5.22 points or 0.09% at 5963.60.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The NASDAQ index was down -273.68 points at session lows, but is closing up 4.36 points or 0.02% at 19215.46&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic calendar in Asia - Reserve Bank of Australia rate cut expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-reserve-bank-of-australia-rate-cut-expected-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-reserve-bank-of-australia-rate-cut-expected-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The G7 meting listed in the calendar is the meeting opg G7 finance minister and central bankers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China will be setting their Loan Prime Rates (LPRs) today. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;74&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Current LPR levels are: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;76&quot; data-end=&quot;231&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;76&quot; data-end=&quot;133&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;78&quot; data-end=&quot;133&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;One-year LPR: 3.10%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;134&quot; data-end=&quot;231&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;136&quot; data-end=&quot;231&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Five-year LPR: 3.60%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;233&quot; data-end=&quot;391&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;These rates have remained unchanged since October 2024, when the PBOC implemented a 25 basis point reduction for both maturities. The one-year LPR primarily influences corporate and household loans, while the five-year LPR serves as a reference for mortgage rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;190&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;LPRs are no longer as important as they once were. The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC) shifted its primary monetary policy tool to the seven-day reverse repurchase agreement (reverse repo) rate. This transition began in mid-2024. This move aligns China&apos;s monetary policy framework more closely with global standards, such as those of the U.S. Federal Reserve and the European Central Bank, which typically rely on a single short-term policy rate to guide market expectations and liquidity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;192&quot; data-end=&quot;350&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The 7-day reverse repo rate is a short-term interest rate used in the PBOC&apos;s open market operations to manage liquidity in the banking system. By adjusting this rate, the PBOC influences short-term borrowing costs, which in turn affect broader financial conditions, including the Loan Prime Rate (LPR), a key reference for lending rates in China. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;352&quot; data-end=&quot;510&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;As of May 8, 2025, the PBOC reduced the 7-day reverse repo rate by 10 basis points to 1.40%, marking the first cut since September 2024. This reduction is part of a broader strategy to stimulate the economy amid challenges such as trade tensions and a slowing property market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;352&quot; data-end=&quot;510&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Of more focus is the Reserve Bank of Australia, widely expected to cut its cash rate by 25bp today, and further in the months ahead:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/75bp-of-reserve-bank-of-australia-rate-cuts-to-come-reuters-poll-20250516/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;75bp of Reserve Bank of Australia rate cuts to come (Reuters poll)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;of the big 4 Australian banks ANZ, CBA and WPAC are tipping a 25bp cut, NAB a 50bp cut&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The times in the left-most column are GMT.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The numbers in the right-most column are the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month/quarter as the case may be) result. The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade ideas thread - Tuesday, 20 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-tuesday-20-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 20:00:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-tuesday-20-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Good morning, afternoon and evening all. Any charts, technical analysis, trade ideas, thoughts, views, ForexLive traders would like to share and discuss with fellow ForexLive traders, please do so:
 &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SUBARU OF AMERICA TO RAISE PRICES IN RESPONSE TO &quot;CURRENT MARKET CONDITIONS&quot; - COMPANY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924555009032585534#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:57:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924555009032585534#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SUBARU OF AMERICA TO RAISE PRICES IN RESPONSE TO &quot;CURRENT MARKET CONDITIONS&quot; - COMPANY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. TREASURY IS NOT PARTICULARLY CONCERNED ABOUT MOODY&apos;S DOWNGRADE OF U.S. CREDIT RATING; RATING AGENCIES ARE &apos;LAGGING INDICATORS&apos; -SOURCE BRIEFED ON U.S. PARTICIPATION IN G7 FINANCE MEETING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924550742565630242#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:40:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924550742565630242#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. TREASURY IS NOT PARTICULARLY CONCERNED ABOUT MOODY&apos;S DOWNGRADE OF U.S. CREDIT RATING; RATING AGENCIES ARE &apos;LAGGING INDICATORS&apos; -SOURCE BRIEFED ON U.S. PARTICIPATION IN G7 FINANCE MEETING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) THE SENATE IS PROBABLY NOT GOING TO FINISH ITS CRYPTO BILL ON STABLECOIN THIS WEEK - SEMAFOR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924549233622831545#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:34:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924549233622831545#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE SENATE IS PROBABLY NOT GOING TO FINISH ITS CRYPTO BILL ON STABLECOIN THIS WEEK - SEMAFOR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. SENATE DEMOCRATIC LEADER SCHUMER PROPOSES BAN ON FOREIGN AIRCRAFT TO BE USED AS U.S. PRESIDENT&apos;S AIR FORCE ONE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924547273976873249#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:26:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924547273976873249#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. SENATE DEMOCRATIC LEADER SCHUMER PROPOSES BAN ON FOREIGN AIRCRAFT TO BE USED AS U.S. PRESIDENT&apos;S AIR FORCE ONE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP DUE TO SIGN REVENGE PORN BILL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924547176262193361#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:26:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924547176262193361#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP DUE TO SIGN REVENGE PORN BILL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) - TRUMP: PROGRESS MADE DURING PUTIN CALL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924545999462072477#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:21:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924545999462072477#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;- TRUMP: PROGRESS MADE DURING PUTIN CALL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US treasury does not anticipate any trade deal announcements at G7 meeting this week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-does-not-anticipate-any-trade-deal-announcement-at-g7-meeting-this-week-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:16:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-does-not-anticipate-any-trade-deal-announcement-at-g7-meeting-this-week-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;According to a source briefed on US preparations for G7 finance meeting in Canada:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US treasury does not anticipate any trade deal announcements at G7 finance meeting in Canada. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. TREASURY DOES NOT ANTICIPATE ANY TRADE DEAL ANNOUNCEMENTS AT G7 FINANCE MEETING IN CANADA THIS WEEK-SOURCE BRIEFED ON U.S. PREPARATIONS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924544213837828248#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:14:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924544213837828248#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. TREASURY DOES NOT ANTICIPATE ANY TRADE DEAL ANNOUNCEMENTS AT G7 FINANCE MEETING IN CANADA THIS WEEK-SOURCE BRIEFED ON U.S. PREPARATIONS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOE Dhingra: Her vote for 50 bp cut was partly to make a statement on direction of economy</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-dhingra-her-vote-for-50-bp-cut-was-partly-to-make-a-statement-on-direction-of-economy-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:13:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-dhingra-her-vote-for-50-bp-cut-was-partly-to-make-a-statement-on-direction-of-economy-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Her vote for 50 basis point cut was partly to make a statement on direction of the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;might see some cost pass-through from US tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Argue that numbers would be quite small.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Won&apos;t rule out scenario where global trade breaks and UK suffers inflation, but don&apos;t think that&apos;s where we&apos;re headed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;My working hypothesis is that dollar depreciation is not going to put immense pressure on UK import prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If dollar starts to really go up we have to worry about what exchange-rate dynamics do for UK inflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MIRAN: TRUMP IS AWARE THAT THE DEFICIT IS A PROBLEM, AND HAS A PLAN TO REDUCE IT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924540965039100337#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 19:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924540965039100337#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MIRAN: TRUMP IS AWARE THAT THE DEFICIT IS A PROBLEM, AND HAS A PLAN TO REDUCE IT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S BOSTIC: SEES ONE INTEREST-RATE CUT THIS YEAR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924538864124731807#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:53:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924538864124731807#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S BOSTIC: SEES ONE INTEREST-RATE CUT THIS YEAR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Bostic: Thinks rates in the US are mildly restrictive</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-bostic-thinks-rates-in-the-us-are-mildly-restrictive-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:52:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-bostic-thinks-rates-in-the-us-are-mildly-restrictive-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fed&apos;s Bostic:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thinks current US rates are mildly restrictive. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is sticking with his one rate cut view or 2025, but does depend on how the tariff situation plays out&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hope that as the summer progresses, will get more clarity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil futures settle at $62.69</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6269-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:40:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6269-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Crude oil futures are settling at $62.69, up $0.20 or 0.32% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI and Brent opened lower due to risk-off sentiment after Moody’s downgraded the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;498&quot; data-end=&quot;588&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;500&quot; data-end=&quot;588&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A Trump-Putin phone call added a positive tone, helping limit downside pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;589&quot; data-end=&quot;707&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;591&quot; data-end=&quot;707&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trump described the call as very informative, suggesting Russia and Ukraine will start ceasefire talks soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin: Trump/Putin did not discuss ceasefire timeframe</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/kremlin-trumpputin-did-not-discuss-ceasefire-timeframe-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:05:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/kremlin-trumpputin-did-not-discuss-ceasefire-timeframe-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Kremlin is out with its accessment of the phone call between Putin and Trump: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;96&quot; data-end=&quot;178&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;98&quot; data-end=&quot;178&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Putin and Trump both said they favoured normalisation of U.S.-Russia relations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;179&quot; data-end=&quot;245&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;181&quot; data-end=&quot;245&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Putin and Trump discussed a possible Russia-U.S. prisoner swap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;246&quot; data-end=&quot;323&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;248&quot; data-end=&quot;323&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Putin and Trump discussed exchanging nine Russian and nine U.S. prisoners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;324&quot; data-end=&quot;432&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;326&quot; data-end=&quot;432&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trump spoke quite emotionally about prospects for ties with Russia, wants them to be mutually beneficial&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;433&quot; data-end=&quot;534&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;435&quot; data-end=&quot;534&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trump said there were impressive prospects for Russia-U.S. ties after Ukraine conflict is settled&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;535&quot; data-end=&quot;619&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;537&quot; data-end=&quot;619&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trump said U.S. sees Russia as one of most important trade and economic partners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;620&quot; data-end=&quot;731&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;622&quot; data-end=&quot;731&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trump and Putin agreed to continue dialogue on all issues, intend to agree a personal meeting in the future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;732&quot; data-end=&quot;838&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;734&quot; data-end=&quot;838&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A Putin-Trump meeting needs careful preparation, instructions have been given on both sides to do this&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;839&quot; data-end=&quot;893&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;841&quot; data-end=&quot;893&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;No venue has been agreed for a Putin-Trump meeting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;894&quot; data-end=&quot;944&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;896&quot; data-end=&quot;944&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trump told Putin he could call him at any time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;945&quot; data-end=&quot;1063&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;947&quot; data-end=&quot;1063&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Two leaders didn’t discuss ceasefire timeframe although Trump stressed his interest in reaching agreements quickly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1064&quot; data-end=&quot;1171&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1066&quot; data-end=&quot;1171&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trump said sanctions are being prepared in U.S. Senate but he himself favours agreements, not sanctions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1172&quot; data-end=&quot;1226&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1174&quot; data-end=&quot;1226&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Putin welcomed results of Trump’s Middle East trip&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1227&quot; data-end=&quot;1324&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1229&quot; data-end=&quot;1324&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Putin welcomed progress in U.S. talks with Iran on nuclear program, Russia is willing to help&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not a lot on ceasefire vs other stuff.  &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP SAID SANCTIONS ARE BEING PREPARED IN U.S. SENATE BUT HE HIMSELF FAVOURS AGREEMENTS, NOT SANCTIONS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924525868711387452#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924525868711387452#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP SAID SANCTIONS ARE BEING PREPARED IN U.S. SENATE BUT HE HIMSELF FAVOURS AGREEMENTS, NOT SANCTIONS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP TOLD PUTIN HE COULD CALL HIM AT ANY TIME</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924525749991608399#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924525749991608399#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP TOLD PUTIN HE COULD CALL HIM AT ANY TIME&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP SAID U.S. SEES RUSSIA AS ONE OF MOST IMPORTANT TRADE AND ECONOMIC PARTNERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924525714478358968#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924525714478358968#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP SAID U.S. SEES RUSSIA AS ONE OF MOST IMPORTANT TRADE AND ECONOMIC PARTNERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP SAID THERE WERE IMPRESSIVE PROSPECTS FOR RUSSIA-U.S. TIES AFTER UKRAINE CONFLICT IS SETTLED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924525660438978622#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:00:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924525660438978622#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP SAID THERE WERE IMPRESSIVE PROSPECTS FOR RUSSIA-U.S. TIES AFTER UKRAINE CONFLICT IS SETTLED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP SPOKE QUITE EMOTIONALLY ABOUT PROSPECTS FOR TIES WITIH RUSSIA, WANTS THEM TO BE MUTUALLY BENEFICIAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924525597629247741#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:00:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924525597629247741#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN AIDE: TRUMP SPOKE QUITE EMOTIONALLY ABOUT PROSPECTS FOR TIES WITIH RUSSIA, WANTS THEM TO BE MUTUALLY BENEFICIAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Kashkari: There is big uncertainty now in the economy</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kashkari-there-is-big-uncertainty-now-in-the-economy-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:39:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kashkari-there-is-big-uncertainty-now-in-the-economy-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Minneapolis Fed Pres. Kashkari is speaking and reiterates the &quot;uncertainty&quot;: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coming into the year, economic conditions were good.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is big uncertainty now in the economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Doesn&apos;t know when tariff landscape will settle out.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Businesses are holding off on investment amid uncertainty.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump. Call with Putin went very well</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-call-with-putin-went-very-well-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:37:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-call-with-putin-went-very-well-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Trump on call with Russians  Putin:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Call went very well.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russia and Ukraine will immediately start negotiations toward a cease-fire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russia wants large trade with the US when war is over&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can benefit from trade&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Negotiations will begin immediately.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vatican says it would be interested in hosting Russia Ukraine talks (HMMM)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany, France, Italy, Finland have been informed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks are now trading higher on the day:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow Industrial Average is up 175 points or 0.41%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index is up 7.66 points or 0.13%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index is up 4.18 points or 0.02%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD turns lower after failing at key resistance – eyes support at MAs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-turns-lower-after-failing-at-key-resistance-eyes-support-at-mas-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:25:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-turns-lower-after-failing-at-key-resistance-eyes-support-at-mas-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;80&quot; data-end=&quot;366&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The EURUSD attempted a move higher earlier today but failed to sustain a break above the key swing area between 1.1265 and 1.1276. This zone, which had previously acted as a support floor and more recently as resistance, once again attracted sellers, leading to a downside reversal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;368&quot; data-end=&quot;802&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Following the rejection at resistance, the pair has rotated lower and is now testing a key support zone defined by the 200- and 100-hour moving averages, currently at 1.1208 and 1.1197, respectively. These levels will serve as important short-term bias indicators. Holding above the MAs would keep the door open for renewed upside attempts. However, a sustained move below would tilt the bias back in favor of the sellers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;804&quot; data-end=&quot;1052&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Should the pair break below the moving average cluster, attention will turn to the Friday low at 1.1130, followed by the low from last week at 1.10636, and then the 38.2% retracement of the January 2025 low to the April high at 1.10395.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;945&quot; data-end=&quot;957&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;958&quot; data-end=&quot;1169&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;958&quot; data-end=&quot;1031&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;88&quot; data-end=&quot;111&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;112&quot; data-end=&quot;288&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;112&quot; data-end=&quot;201&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;114&quot; data-end=&quot;201&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1265–1.1276: Key swing area; failed break today; former support turned resistance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;202&quot; data-end=&quot;236&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;204&quot; data-end=&quot;236&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1345: Trendline resistance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;290&quot; data-end=&quot;310&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support Targets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;311&quot; data-end=&quot;521&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;311&quot; data-end=&quot;348&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;313&quot; data-end=&quot;348&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1208: 200-hour moving average&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;349&quot; data-end=&quot;386&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;351&quot; data-end=&quot;386&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1197: 100-hour moving average&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;387&quot; data-end=&quot;413&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;389&quot; data-end=&quot;413&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1130: Friday’s low&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;414&quot; data-end=&quot;447&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;416&quot; data-end=&quot;447&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.10636: Low from last week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;448&quot; data-end=&quot;521&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;450&quot; data-end=&quot;521&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.10395: 38.2% retracement of the move up from the January 2025 low&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNB Schlegal: SNB tolerates negative inflation rate in the short term</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/snb-schlegal-snb-tolerates-negative-inflation-rate-in-the-short-term-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/snb-schlegal-snb-tolerates-negative-inflation-rate-in-the-short-term-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;SNB Chairman Schlegal is on the wires saying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB will tolerate negative inflation rate in the short term&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty is currently very high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swiss franc is often sought as a safe haven in times of uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Policy rate is our main instrument, but when necessary we can intervene in the forex market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The outlook for Swiss inflation is currently very unclear&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is no alternative to US treasuries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB is not a currency manipulator.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It only intervened to pursue our mandate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have only intervened to slow overvaluation of the franc, not to gain a competitive advantage for Switzerland.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CHF is modestly weakening vs the USD but remains below the 200 hour MA at 0.83504. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the EURCHF, the price is above is just above teh 100 hour MA at 0.9375. The corrective low off the high today was above the 200 hour moving average of 0.9360.  Staying above the MAs is a bullish tilt, at least in the short-term. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Press: The Putin/Trump phone call has concluded</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russian-press-the-putintrump-phone-call-has-concluded-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:46:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russian-press-the-putintrump-phone-call-has-concluded-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;According to the Russian press, the phone call between Russian Pres. Putin and US President Trump is over.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The call was very informative and helpful&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The call lasted 2+ hours.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Citing Putin:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russia favors a peaceful resolution of crisis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russia ready to work with Kiev on a memorandum on future peace talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ceasefire is possible once agreements are reached.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are generally on the right track&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russia and Ukraine must find compromises that suit both sides&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Root causes of the crisis should be eliminated.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the call, Pres. Trump did speak with Ukrains Zelenskyy&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices end the day with mixed results</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/european-indices-end-the-day-with-mixed-results-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:16:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/european-indices-end-the-day-with-mixed-results-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The major European indices closed mixed on the day. Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB closed down -1.20% at 40166.76. The move to the downside took the price off the highest level going back to 2008 for the index.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The German DAX rose 0.71% and closed at a new record high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A snapshot of the closing level shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German Dax Rose 167.65 points or 0.71% at 23935.09&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC felt -3.07 points or -0.04% at 7883.63.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK&apos;s FTSE 100 rose 14.74 points or 0.17% at 8699.31.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex rose 34.50 points or 0.25% at 14099.00.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB fell -489.51 or -1.20% at 40166.76.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As London/European traders head for the exits, US stocks are rebounding from lower levels. The Dow industrial average is currently positive on the day. The S&amp;amp;P and NASDAQ indices are&apos;s marginally lower but well off lows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow Industrial Average up 24.66 points or 0.06% at 42678. The Index was down -317.03 points at session allows.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index -10.7 points or -0.18% at 5947.70. The Index was down -62.69 points at session lows.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index minus 69.5.2 or -0.36% at 19141.10. The Index was down -273.68 points at session lows&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at other markets, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil is trading up $0.58 or 0.94% at $62.55. The price is near the high for the day at $62.67.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold is trading up $28.32 or 0.89% at $3230.17.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin is trading down $1747 at $104,771&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market, yields have come off their high levels. The 30 year yield was back about 5% earlier in the day. It is now back below the key level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield 3.993%, +1.0 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5- year yield 4.096%, +3.3 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year yield 4.496%, +5.6 basis points.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year yield 4.962%, +6.5 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Williams: Uncertainty has led the Fed to keep interest rates steady so far</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-uncertainty-has-led-the-fed-to-keep-interest-rates-steady-so-far-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:06:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-uncertainty-has-led-the-fed-to-keep-interest-rates-steady-so-far-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fed&apos;s Williams (speaking to reporters?) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty has led the Fed to keep interest rates steady so far this year.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The path forward might not become clearer for months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s not going to be that in June, we&apos;re going to understand what&apos;s happening more in July&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s going to be a process of collecting data, getting a better picture, and watching those things develop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD slips below key moving averages as bearish momentum builds</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-slips-below-key-moving-averages-as-bearish-momentum-builds-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:51:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-slips-below-key-moving-averages-as-bearish-momentum-builds-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;71&quot; data-end=&quot;530&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCAD is under pressure to start the new trading week, with sellers regaining more control following last weeks rejection of the 200-day moving average (green line currently at 1.40144). The pair had stalled near that level on two separate times last week, leading to renewed downside interest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;71&quot; data-end=&quot;530&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;After trading above and below the 100-hour moving average (blue line currently at 1.39582), the price today has now fallen back below both that 100-hour and also the 200-hour moving averages (now at 1.39347), tilting the near-term bias more bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;532&quot; data-end=&quot;810&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The pair is now targeting the swing area between 1.38917 and 1.3904, which served as resistance earlier in April before breaking higher on May 8 and forming a floor.  That area could act as support on more selling and a retest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;532&quot; data-end=&quot;810&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A break below that zone would open the door to further downside, with the next technical support seen near the 1.3860 region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;812&quot; data-end=&quot;837&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;838&quot; data-end=&quot;1009&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;838&quot; data-end=&quot;953&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;840&quot; data-end=&quot;953&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.39347 (200-hour MA), 1.39582 (100-hour MA), 1.40097–1.40268 (swing area and the 200-day MA and daily resistance)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;954&quot; data-end=&quot;1009&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;956&quot; data-end=&quot;1009&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.38917–1.3904 (swing area), then 1.38607&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1011&quot; data-end=&quot;1173&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Sellers are more in control while price holds below the key hourly moving averages. A move back above the 100-hour MA would be needed to ease the downward pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD stretches to new highs and tests 200 day MA</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-stretches-to-new-highs-and-tests-200-day-ma-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:22:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-stretches-to-new-highs-and-tests-200-day-ma-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;94&quot; data-end=&quot;389&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The AUDUSD is starting the week on stronger footing, benefiting from broad U.S. dollar weakness following Friday’s Moody’s downgrade of the U.S. sovereign credit rating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;391&quot; data-end=&quot;700&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;From a technical perspective, the AUDUSD has extended above both the 100-hour (0.64228) and 200-hour (0.64327) moving averages, signaling a more bullish bias in the short term.  The price has been waffling above and below those MAs as the price action consolidates near highs for the year (and going back to November 2024 - not shown). The pair is also currently testing the 200-day moving average at 0.64558, a critical hurdle for further upside momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;702&quot; data-end=&quot;963&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;With the bullish tone strengthening, traders are now eyeing the next resistance zone between 0.6493 and 0.65135—the upper extreme from earlier in 2025. A break above that area would mark a key technical victory and open the path to broader upside potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;965&quot; data-end=&quot;989&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels to watch:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;990&quot; data-end=&quot;1128&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;990&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;992&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 0.64327 (200-hour MA), 0.64228 (100-hour MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1052&quot; data-end=&quot;1128&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1054&quot; data-end=&quot;1128&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.64558 (200-day MA), then 0.6493–0.65135 (2025 high area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1130&quot; data-end=&quot;1279&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Holding above the rising moving averages keeps the buyers in control, with a close above the 200-day MA likely to encourage further bullish momentum.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market shake-up: Tech edges up while energy and consumer stocks drag</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/market-shake-up-tech-edges-up-while-energy-and-consumer-stocks-drag-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:46:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/market-shake-up-tech-edges-up-while-energy-and-consumer-stocks-drag-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US stock market today exhibits a diversified portfolio of trends, as revealed by the latest heatmap snapshot. Technology stands out marginally in the green, while energy and major consumer stocks face notable downward pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;📊 Technology: Microsoft (MSFT) leads the tech sector with a slight increase of 0.29%, reflecting a cautious optimism among investors. However, Oracle (ORCL) remains nearly flat with a minimal gain of 0.04%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;💡 Semiconductors: Challenges continue as Nvidia (NVDA) marks a 0.26% drop and Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) slips by 2.02%, pointing to ongoing volatility in this critical subsector.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🚗 Consumer Cyclical: Tesla (TSLA) experiences a sharp decline of 3.04%, intensifying concerns over the auto manufacturer&apos;s performance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🏦 Financials: Visa (V) shows resilience with a 0.71% rise, contrasting JPMorgan Chase&apos;s (JPM) slight dip of 0.11%. Bank of America (BAC) is up 0.47%, contributing to mixed sentiments in this sector.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🩺 Healthcare: AstraZeneca (AZN) rockets up by 2.81%, while Eli Lilly (LLY) shows a notable drop of 0.95%, emphasizing the variability within the sector.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The overall market sentiment reflects a cautious optimism mingled with sector-specific concerns. Tech&apos;s marginal gains underscore investor interest, but the downturn in energy and consumer cyclical sectors suggests brewing caution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fall in semiconductor stocks aligns with broader tech concerns, driven possibly by global supply chain disruptions and regulatory issues. The bleak performance in energy, with companies like Chevron (CVX) down 2.67%, hints at fluctuating oil prices influencing investor behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering today&apos;s varied market dynamics, diversification remains key. Investors are advised to watch tech stocks like Microsoft for potential gains amidst volatility and consider rebalancing portfolios to offset energy sector risks. The healthcare sector&apos;s fluctuations suggest cautious observation, particularly with strong performers like AstraZeneca. Keep an eye on value stocks in financials to hedge against instability, and check regularly for updates on ForexLive.com for comprehensive insights, especially in these rapidly shifting markets.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
