<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Electric vehicle surge: Tesla powers ahead while tech and healthcare struggle</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/electric-vehicle-surge-tesla-powers-ahead-while-tech-and-healthcare-struggle-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:46:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/electric-vehicle-surge-tesla-powers-ahead-while-tech-and-healthcare-struggle-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stock market today presents a mixed tableau of sector performances, with electric vehicles taking center stage. Tesla (TSLA) leads the charge in the auto manufacturer space with a robust gain of 6.40%. This significant upswing is indicative of bullish sentiment surrounding the company, possibly fueled by positive sales figures or advancements in battery technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technology: Overall, the tech sector is experiencing a subdued day. Microsoft (MSFT) and other tech giants show slight declines, while Oracle (ORCL) manages a small gain of 0.27%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Semiconductors: The sector faces challenges, with Nvidia (NVDA) seeing a decline of 0.92%. This drop points toward continued caution among investors in the semiconductor landscape.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healthcare: It&apos;s a mixed bag today, with AbbVie (ABBV) rising by 1.78%, showcasing its stability amidst volatile market dynamics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consumer Cyclical: Amazon (AMZN) remains stable with a modest increase of 0.12%, reinforcing its resilience in the consumer market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Financials: Visa (V) edges up by 0.18%, and JPMorgan Chase (JPM) by 0.10%, reflecting tepid optimism in financial services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market sentiment today appears to be one of cautious optimism. The positive performance by Tesla highlights growing investor confidence in sustainable energy and transportation alternatives. However, the broader mixed signals, especially in tech and healthcare, indicate investor apprehension toward potential disruptions or policy changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decline in major tech companies like Google (GOOG) at -0.81% further underscores the tentative market attitude toward the sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For investors, it may be prudent to consider rebalancing portfolios to include more exposure to the electric vehicle sector and related sustainable energy investments. Tesla’s surge suggests momentum that could yield favorable returns. Adopting a diversified strategy might safeguard against the volatility observed in tech and healthcare stocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, staying informed on semiconductor trends is essential, given the ongoing fluctuations. Investors might explore opportunities outside of traditional tech, particularly in sectors showing sustainability growth potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As always, investors are urged to keep an eye on real-time data and market analyses for timely adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it taboo to talk about shipping fraud?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/is-it-taboo-to-talk-about-shipping-fraud-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/is-it-taboo-to-talk-about-shipping-fraud-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The funny thing about wonk economists is that they rarely look past the math.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With 145% tariffs on China (or today&apos;s Trump-floated number of 80%), they crunch the numbers and trade with China essentially stops. They run that through their models and that spits out assumptions around economic growth and inflation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the same thing when everyone announced sanctions on Russia and Iran.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What happened in reality? Cheating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can still get anything you want in Russia as the goods are simply shipped through a Russia-friendly country that then re-exports them. Otherwise, local officials turn a blind eye to where their own companies are shipping: After all, cutting exports means cutting jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on today&apos;s Chinese trade &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-january-april-yuan-denominated-exports-75-yy-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;data&lt;/a&gt;, it hasn&apos;t taken long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese exports to the US in today&apos;s trade report fell 21% but rose by an equal percentage with south-east Asian nations and the EU. The largest increases were with Indonesia, Thailand and Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justin &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-did-us-tariffs-impact-chinas-latest-trade-numbers-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;wrote about&lt;/a&gt; this earlier and has been way ahead on this angle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So while everyone is up-in-arms about the trade war the reality might be far more benign: The labels are changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I expect that the greatest bull market in the world right now is importing Chinese goods, changing the labels and re-exporting to the US. It&apos;s in almost everyone&apos;s best interest to look the other way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While I think this is all taboo to talk about in economic circles, maybe it should remain that way. Just no one tell Trump and the global economy can continue to hum along.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss president: Switzerland should be one of the next countries for US deal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/swiss-president-switzerland-should-be-one-of-the-next-countries-for-us-deal-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:24:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/swiss-president-switzerland-should-be-one-of-the-next-countries-for-us-deal-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Talks with Americans encouraging&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have the impression the US is looking for tailor-made solutions with countries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pause on tariffs not to be lifted during negotiations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Today the American side &apos;clearly committed&apos; to accelerating talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Switzerland does not subsidize industry, but other countries may, these are the points the US is interested in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Switzerland is now in a group of countries that are now treated swiftly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Switzerland has a large trade surplus with the United States and that&apos;s led to a 31% tariff on Swiss imports that&apos;s been lowered to 10% until July 8. That said, the imbalance is much smaller when excluding gold and gold trade is something that Trump referred to yesterday in the UK deal.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD:If the sellers are to remain in play/in control.This is where sellers need to enter</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusdif-the-sellers-are-to-remain-in-playin-controlthis-is-where-sellers-need-to-enter-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:23:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusdif-the-sellers-are-to-remain-in-playin-controlthis-is-where-sellers-need-to-enter-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;153&quot; data-end=&quot;439&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;EURUSD broke below a key floor area yesterday near 1.1256–1.1265 and is now retesting that level from the underside (see red numbered circles).This area is also where the 61.8% of the range since 2020 high is found (at 1.1271) and the July 2023 high is at 1.12754). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;153&quot; data-end=&quot;439&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;More recently, this zone, acted as a support floor, and is a critical pivot point. Staying below it will keep sellers in control in the short term and validate the downside break.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;441&quot; data-end=&quot;754&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Earlier today, the pair found support at a swing area that traces back to 2024 (not shown on the chart) between 1.12007 and 1.1213, and the bounce higher is currently testing broken support turned resistance. If sellers can defend this resistance ceiling zone and push back lower through 1.1200, the next major target comes into view at the 50% retracement level near 1.1145.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;756&quot; data-end=&quot;771&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key Levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;772&quot; data-end=&quot;944&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;772&quot; data-end=&quot;820&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;774&quot; data-end=&quot;820&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance (broken support): 1.1265–1.1275&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;821&quot; data-end=&quot;873&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;823&quot; data-end=&quot;873&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Next downside target: 1.1200 to 1.1213 (swing area from 2024)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;821&quot; data-end=&quot;873&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;823&quot; data-end=&quot;873&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Short-term control: Bears remain in charge below the 1.1265-75. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;946&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A move back above the former floor would weaken the bearish bias and open the door for a further rebound.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 CHINA COMMERCE MINISTER: CHINA FIRMLY OPPOSES U.S. ABUSE OF RECIPROCAL TARIFFS- CHINA COMMERCE MINISTRY STATEMENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920843161137561754#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:07:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920843161137561754#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 CHINA COMMERCE MINISTER: CHINA FIRMLY OPPOSES U.S. ABUSE OF RECIPROCAL TARIFFS- CHINA COMMERCE MINISTRY STATEMENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SWISS PRESIDENT KARIN KELLER-SUTTER: TODAY THE AMERICAN SIDE &apos;CLEARLY COMMITTED&apos; TO ACCELERATE THE PROCESS ON TARIFF TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920842802398736625#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:06:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920842802398736625#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SWISS PRESIDENT KARIN KELLER-SUTTER: TODAY THE AMERICAN SIDE &apos;CLEARLY COMMITTED&apos; TO ACCELERATE THE PROCESS ON TARIFF TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SWISS PRESIDENT KELLER-SUTTER:  GOOD NEWS THAT U.S. AND CHINA HOLDING TALKS IN SWITZERLAND</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920842529232072784#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:05:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920842529232072784#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SWISS PRESIDENT KELLER-SUTTER:  GOOD NEWS THAT U.S. AND CHINA HOLDING TALKS IN SWITZERLAND&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *INDIA SAYS ADEQUATE STOCKPILES OF ESSENTIAL FOOD AVAILABLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920842468368494727#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920842468368494727#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*INDIA SAYS ADEQUATE STOCKPILES OF ESSENTIAL FOOD AVAILABLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *AIR INDIA FLIGHTS TO, FROM NINE CITIES CANCELED TILL MAY 15</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920842427302080521#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920842427302080521#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*AIR INDIA FLIGHTS TO, FROM NINE CITIES CANCELED TILL MAY 15&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - TESLA SHARES HIT TWO-MONTH HIGH; LAST UP 6.3%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920841598708924817#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920841598708924817#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - TESLA SHARES HIT TWO-MONTH HIGH; LAST UP 6.3%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF fails at both ends of its recent range — price remains trapped</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-fails-at-both-ends-of-its-recent-range-price-remains-trapped-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:57:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-fails-at-both-ends-of-its-recent-range-price-remains-trapped-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;181&quot; data-end=&quot;439&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;USDCHF remains confined within a well-defined trading range after failed breakout attempts on both sides of a trading range going back April 23rd this week. On Wednesday, the pair dipped below the range floor at 0.8195, reaching a low of 0.8185, but momentum quickly faded and the move was reversed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;441&quot; data-end=&quot;753&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Today, the price pushed above the top of the box at 0.8333 and reached a high of 0.83405. However, that too failed to hold, falling just short of the key 38.2% retracement level at 0.83505. The inability to sustain momentum outside the range suggests indecision and a lack of directional conviction from traders. Ultimately if the price is to gain more momentum, getting about the 38.2% retracement is a minimum retracement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;755&quot; data-end=&quot;996&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For now, the red box range between 0.8195 and 0.8333 continues to define the battle lines. A convincing break and close outside either boundary—supported by momentum—will be needed to tilt the bias more clearly in favor of buyers or sellers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;755&quot; data-end=&quot;996&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In between the extremes of the red box at the converged 100 and 200 hour moving averages at 0.8253. There might be some support ahead of that between 0.8272 and 0.8280. With a price now trading at new laws, those levels become downside targets and risk/bias defining levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;998&quot; data-end=&quot;1013&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1014&quot; data-end=&quot;1240&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1014&quot; data-end=&quot;1106&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1016&quot; data-end=&quot;1106&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Range resistance: 0.8333 (failed breakout high: 0.83405, next target: 0.83505 – 38.2%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1107&quot; data-end=&quot;1164&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1109&quot; data-end=&quot;1164&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Range support: 0.8195 (failed breakout low: 0.8185)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1165&quot; data-end=&quot;1240&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1167&quot; data-end=&quot;1240&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Neutral zone: Within the box; moving averages clustered near midpoint&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stock indices are set to open higher</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stock-indices-are-set-to-open-higher-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:22:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stock-indices-are-set-to-open-higher-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;US stocks are set to open higher. Shares of banking on trade deals to come. US and China will meet in Switzerland. Pres. Trump said that 80% tariff seems about right (down from 145%). Realistically, 80% is still too high and will likely lead to higher inflation and higher unemployment as small businesses go out of business. Uncertainty remains high but hope springs eternal.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The futures are implying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow up 112 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index up 21 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ up 95 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coming into the day, the S&amp;amp;P and NASDAQ indexes are modestly lower: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index -0.40%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index -0.28%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, both the S&amp;amp;P and the NASDAQ indices are staying above their 50 day moving average at session lows this week. Looking at the S&amp;amp;P index the 50 day moving averages at 5555.65 (lots of 5&apos;s).  On the top side, the 200 day moving average is the next target at 5747.76)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Dow industrial average, the index is up 0.12% coming into the final day of the week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In premarket trading: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nvidia shares are trading up 0.34%. The price is up 2.51% for the trading week (at the close yesterday. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alphabet shares are down -0.34%. For the week, they are down -5.94%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft shares are up 0.36% for the day. For the week the index is up 0.66%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meta shares are up 1.01% in premarket trading. For the week into today, the shares are up 0.16%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apple shares are up 0.66%, but for the week the shares are down -3.83%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Amazon shares are up 0.53% in premarket trading, and are up 1.11% for the week&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tesla heirs are up 1.82% in premarket trading. At the close yesterday, the shares were down -0.83%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Williams: Policy is in a good place and the Fed has time</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/williams-policy-is-in-a-good-place-and-the-fed-has-time-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:18:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/williams-policy-is-in-a-good-place-and-the-fed-has-time-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The labor market has proved to be resilient&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We want to get an idea of what the tariff policies will be&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Things are in a good place&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s hard to speculate what the Fed will do&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If the economy weakens more than expected it would call for deeper rate cuts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The details on tariffs do matter for the economic impacts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trade policies are very-much in flux&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The US consumer never lets us down&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There was some front-loading ahead of tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monetary policy is modestly restrictive right now&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier he said:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets appear convinced Fed will get inflation back to 2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets are very focused on downside risks right now&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The factors still keeping the long run neutral rate low are still in place&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expects growth to slow considerably, inflation and unemployment to be higher&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expects growth to slow considerably, inflation and unemployment to be higher&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD pushes higher but runs into resistance. Watch the old ceiling for short-term clues</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-pushes-higher-but-runs-into-resistance-watch-the-old-ceiling-for-short-term-clues-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:05:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-pushes-higher-but-runs-into-resistance-watch-the-old-ceiling-for-short-term-clues-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Canada’s April 2025 jobs report showed a modest employment gain of 7.4K, beating the 2.5K forecast but coming off a sharp decline of 32.6K the prior month. The headline unemployment rate rose to 6.9%—above the 6.8% expected and the highest since 2021—partly due to a slight rise in labor force participation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full-time employment rebounded with a gain of 31.5K, but part-time jobs fell by 24.2K. Manufacturing employment dropped by 31K, and average hourly wages for permanent employees held steady at 3.5% year-over-year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the uptick in full-time work was encouraging, the report was weighed down by a rise in joblessness and a 37K temporary election-related hiring boost that is expected to reverse in May. Overall, the report was mixed with a slightly negative tilt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;71&quot; data-end=&quot;394&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Tthe USDCAD has seen little price action since the report.  Technicallly, the pair continues its upward push after failing to gain downside momentum earlier this week. The pair has broken through prior resistance at 1.38917–1.3904, turning that area into support. Holding above this new floor is crucial to maintain the bullish bias. A move back below would be a near-term disappointment for buyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;396&quot; data-end=&quot;555&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The next key challenge lies in the 1.3924–1.3933 swing area. Earlier today, the price did move above that area, but could not sustain the bullish momentum. To keep the momentum going, the price must not only break above this zone but also hold above it. They 38.2% retracement of the move down from the April high remains as a target that needs to be broken to show the buyers are taking back more control. The 200 day moving average is also near that level just above the 1.4000 level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;557&quot; data-end=&quot;622&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;If bulls succeed, the next targets on the topside come in at:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;623&quot; data-end=&quot;776&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;623&quot; data-end=&quot;663&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;625&quot; data-end=&quot;663&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.3977 – swing high from mid-April&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;664&quot; data-end=&quot;776&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;666&quot; data-end=&quot;776&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.4000 zone – where the 38.2% retracement of the broader move down and the 200-day moving average converge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;778&quot; data-end=&quot;975&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;With rising support and fading downside momentum, the path of least resistance currently leans higher, but follow-through above the 1.3933 level is essential to open the door for the 1.4000 target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;992&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key Levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;993&quot; data-end=&quot;1147&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;993&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;995&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.38917–1.3904 (prior ceiling, now a floor). Move below would disappoint buyers looking for more upside. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1052&quot; data-end=&quot;1105&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1054&quot; data-end=&quot;1105&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.3924–1.3933 (must break and hold)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1106&quot; data-end=&quot;1147&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1108&quot; data-end=&quot;1147&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Upside targets: 1.3977, then 1.4000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN SAYS RUSSIA, US DISCUSSED GAS SUPPLY TO EUROPE: TASS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920826961456198082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920826961456198082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN SAYS RUSSIA, US DISCUSSED GAS SUPPLY TO EUROPE: TASS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Williams: Expect growth to slow considerably, inflation and unemployment higher</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-williams-expect-growth-to-slow-considerably-inflation-and-unemployment-higher-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:03:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-williams-expect-growth-to-slow-considerably-inflation-and-unemployment-higher-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expect growth to slow considerably, inflation and unemployment higher.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are focused on keeping inflation as close to target as possible.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Key to think in scenarios in times of uncertainty.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Factors keeping the long-run neutral rate low are still in place.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I still see the long-run neutral rate as quite low.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The markets are very focused on downside risks at the moment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets appear convinced Fed will get inflation back to 2%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now is an inflection point between hard and soft data.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hard data is telling us the economy is good right now.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The next few quarters will help illuminate economy&apos;s state of affairs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New York Fed desk is also responsible to gathering &quot;market intelligence&quot; besides executing the FOMC policy. The part where he says that the markets are very focused on downside risks at the moment is likely coming from such market intelligence. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s not something new of course, but the rally in the stock market of the past weeks was based on optimism, and most of that optimism is now priced in. So, there are risks of disappointment ahead and there&apos;s no room for complacency.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Barkin: Consumer spending and business investment still very solid</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barkin-consumer-spending-and-business-investment-still-very-solid-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barkin-consumer-spending-and-business-investment-still-very-solid-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fed&apos;s Barkin  is starting to speak and says: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consumer spending and business investment still very solid&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DC weekly restaurant spending and job openings are down&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barkin is not a voting member until 2027&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says &apos;many trade deals in the hopper&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-many-trade-deals-in-the-hopper-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:45:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-many-trade-deals-in-the-hopper-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Hassett is on TV at the same time saying there are 24 deals that are close.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HASSETT: WILL SEE A LOT MORE DEALS LIKE UK DEAL IN COMING WEEKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920822298984022128#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:44:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920822298984022128#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HASSETT: WILL SEE A LOT MORE DEALS LIKE UK DEAL IN COMING WEEKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: MANY TRADE DEALS IN THE HOPPER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920822073737248794#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:44:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920822073737248794#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: MANY TRADE DEALS IN THE HOPPER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hassett: The UK trade deal is the framework for future deals</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/hassett-the-uk-trade-deal-is-the-framework-for-future-deals-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:41:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/hassett-the-uk-trade-deal-is-the-framework-for-future-deals-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;ve been briefed on about 24 other deals that are close&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets will see that the new rules aren&apos;t horribly disruptive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Everything that&apos;s been going on in Switzerland is positive for us, we&apos;re seeing respect on both sides&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The UK model is the one everyone is shooting for&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I think you&apos;re going to see a lot more deals like the UK deal in the coming weeks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump insists on &apos;no tax on tips&apos; and &apos;no tax on overtime&apos; and &apos;interest-free auto loans&apos;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some minor bids in stocks and USD/JPY as he speaks.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HASSETT: EVERYTHING GOING ON WITH SWISS MEETING WITH CHINESE IS POSITIVE -CNBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920821407258206232#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:41:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920821407258206232#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HASSETT: EVERYTHING GOING ON WITH SWISS MEETING WITH CHINESE IS POSITIVE -CNBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 HASSETT: 24 OTHER TRADE DEALS ARE CLOSED TO BEING RESOLVED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920821283547205791#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:40:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920821283547205791#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 HASSETT: 24 OTHER TRADE DEALS ARE CLOSED TO BEING RESOLVED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq Futures Analysis for Today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nasdaq-futures-analysis-for-today-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:39:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nasdaq-futures-analysis-for-today-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;105&quot; data-end=&quot;161&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Nasdaq Futures Analysis for Today – May 9, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;162&quot; data-end=&quot;248&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Current Price: 20,200
Bias: Range-bound, with key reversal levels to monitor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;250&quot; data-end=&quot;524&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Today’s session is shaped by caution ahead of this weekend’s expected developments in U.S.–China trade negotiations. With uncertainty in the air and Friday’s typical low-volatility tone, the Nasdaq futures are likely to remain range-bound unless there’s a surprise breakout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;526&quot; data-end=&quot;568&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Trade Compass Range and Key Levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;570&quot; data-end=&quot;625&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;We identify a central equilibrium zone forming between:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;626&quot; data-end=&quot;752&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;626&quot; data-end=&quot;667&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;628&quot; data-end=&quot;667&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Developing VWAP (Today): 20,181.5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;668&quot; data-end=&quot;695&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;670&quot; data-end=&quot;695&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;POC (May 2): 20,212&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;696&quot; data-end=&quot;752&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;698&quot; data-end=&quot;752&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Yesterday’s VWAP: Close to today’s developing VWAP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;754&quot; data-end=&quot;841&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;This tight clustering suggests 20,180–20,210 is the market’s current “fair value” area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;848&quot; data-end=&quot;899&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Topside Reversal Zone (Short Opportunity)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;900&quot; data-end=&quot;1239&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;900&quot; data-end=&quot;959&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;902&quot; data-end=&quot;959&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Threshold: 20,326 (Yesterday’s Value Area High)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;960&quot; data-end=&quot;1239&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;962&quot; data-end=&quot;1239&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Additional Confluence: 20,300 (POC and round number)
Plan: Look for signs of bearish reversal if price reaches this area.
Breakout Confirmation: Two consecutive 30-minute closes above 20,326 = bullish surprise
Upside Target on Breakout: 20,570&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1246&quot; data-end=&quot;1297&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Downside Reversal Zone (Long Opportunity)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1298&quot; data-end=&quot;1677&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1298&quot; data-end=&quot;1385&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1300&quot; data-end=&quot;1326&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key Support Cluster:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1329&quot; data-end=&quot;1385&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1329&quot; data-end=&quot;1356&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1331&quot; data-end=&quot;1356&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;20,075 (VWAP May 5)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1359&quot; data-end=&quot;1385&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1361&quot; data-end=&quot;1385&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;20,060 (POC May 5)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1386&quot; data-end=&quot;1677&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1388&quot; data-end=&quot;1424&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Lower Threshold for Breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1427&quot; data-end=&quot;1677&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1427&quot; data-end=&quot;1677&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1429&quot; data-end=&quot;1677&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;20,027 (VAH May 1)
Plan: Watch for bullish reversal in this zone.
Breakdown Confirmation: Two consecutive 30-minute closes below 20,025 = bearish surprise
Downside Target on Breakdown: 19,855 (Just above POC May 7)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1684&quot; data-end=&quot;1709&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Summary Outlook for Nasdaq Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1710&quot; data-end=&quot;1991&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Expect range-bound behavior unless triggered by surprise headlines or breakout volume. Today’s structure favors mean reversion within the defined bounds, not trend continuation. Both bulls and bears are likely to treat outer levels as inflection points for reversal trades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1998&quot; data-end=&quot;2043&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Reminder for Nasdaq Traders and Investors:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2044&quot; data-end=&quot;2193&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;tradeCompass offers a map, not a bias. Use the thresholds and key levels to adjust your strategy in real-time. Only act on breakouts once confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2195&quot; data-end=&quot;2415&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Stay alert and trade at your own risk. For more real-time updates and strategies, follow us at &lt;a data-start=&quot;2291&quot; data-end=&quot;2333&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; target=&quot;_new&quot; class=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt; — soon to be &lt;a data-start=&quot;2347&quot; data-end=&quot;2397&quot; rel=&quot;noopener follow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;https://www.investinglive.com&quot;&gt;investingLive.com&lt;/a&gt; later this year.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HASSETT: UK DEAL WILL BE GOOD FOR FARMERS -CNBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920820732289810736#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:38:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920820732289810736#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HASSETT: UK DEAL WILL BE GOOD FOR FARMERS -CNBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HASSETT: UK TRADE DEAL IS FRAMEWORK FOR FUTURE DEALS -CNBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920820509995946160#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:37:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920820509995946160#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HASSETT: UK TRADE DEAL IS FRAMEWORK FOR FUTURE DEALS -CNBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Williams: Now is a time of great uncertainty and change</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-williams-now-is-a-time-of-great-uncertainty-and-change-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:32:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-williams-now-is-a-time-of-great-uncertainty-and-change-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now is a time of great uncertainty and change.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Central bank independence delivers better outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;No comments on monetary policy or economic outlook. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US TO SEEK PREFERENTIAL TREATMENT FOR UK ON ANY PHARMA TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920818852788658568#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:31:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920818852788658568#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US TO SEEK PREFERENTIAL TREATMENT FOR UK ON ANY PHARMA TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada April employment change +7.4K versus +2.5K expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-employment-change-74k-versus-25k-expected-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:30:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-employment-change-74k-versus-25k-expected-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-employment-change-326k-versus-100k-estimate-20250404/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior &lt;/a&gt;was -32.6K&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Unemployment rate +6.9% vs. 6.8% expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior unemployment 6.7%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Full-time employment +31.5K vs -32.6K last month&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;part-time employment -24.2K vs. +29.5k last month.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participation rate 65.3% vs 65.2% last month.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Average hourly wages permanent employees 3.5% vs 3.5% y/ last month&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Unrounded unemployment 6.875% vs 6.715% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing employment -31K&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Total hours worked increased 0.4% in April and were up 0.9% compared with 12 months earlier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD was at 1.3909 beforehand and little changed afterwards. This is a mixed report but I see more negatives than positives. The main positive was the rebound in full-time jobs but the negative was that unemployment rose to 6.9% from 6.7%, though some of that was from a tick up in participation. The unemployment rate matches the worst reading since 2021 and excluding the pandemic, it&apos;s the worst since 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digging deeper in to the numbers, there was a 37K temporary boost to jobs for the election and that will be unwound in May. The Bank of Canada should take that into account and it sets up a poor number for the May report.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&apos;s Canadian jobs day. What to watch for</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/its-canadian-jobs-day-what-to-watch-for-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:21:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/its-canadian-jobs-day-what-to-watch-for-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;At least one person got a new job in Canada in April -- Mark Carney -- today we will get a better sense of the economy he inherited with the April jobs report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are clear signs of a slowdown in the Canadian economy with a drop in confidence and I&apos;m particularly worried about falling house prices. That said, the consumer has been holding up and announced layoffs have been modest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s report is expected to show 2.5K new jobs following a loss of 32.6K in March. Unemployment is expected to tick up to 6.8% from 6.7%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risks to the Canadian dollar are straight forward with the market pricing in a 46% chance of a cut at the June 4 meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickstart the US trading day for May w/ a technical look at the EURUSD, USDJPY &amp; GBPUSD</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/kickstart-the-us-trading-day-for-may-w-a-technical-look-at-the-eurusd-usdjpy-gbpusd-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:20:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/kickstart-the-us-trading-day-for-may-w-a-technical-look-at-the-eurusd-usdjpy-gbpusd-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the video above, I take a technical look at the EURUSD, USDJPY and GBPUSD to kickstart the US forex trading day. What levels are in play and why.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fed officials can now speak after the Fed decision on Wednesday:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed Governor Adriana Kugler said first-quarter growth data reflected frontloading of activity ahead of anticipated tariffs, adding that it&apos;s still unclear how trade policy will evolve. While she sees some upside risk to inflation from the tariffs, she noted the economy has remained resilient, giving the Fed room to continue its gradual approach to bringing inflation down.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed Governor Michael Barr warned that President Trump’s sweeping new tariffs will likely raise inflation, slow economic growth, and increase unemployment later this year, putting the Fed in a tough spot if both inflation and joblessness rise. He emphasized that the full impact of the tariffs remains uncertain but noted they could cause lasting supply chain disruptions and strain small businesses. Barr reiterated the Fed’s “wait-and-see” stance, saying policy is well-positioned to adjust as conditions evolve.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A day after a UK trade deal, Pres. Trump is saying an 80% tariff on China &quot;seems right&quot; but added it would ultimately be up to Treasury Secretary Bessent (or Scott B as he posted) to decide. The US and China will meet in Switzerland this weekend. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Senior Trade Advisor Navarro is on the wires saying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets should expect an active weekend with a steady flow of trade deals, which will be handled on a country-by-country basis. He highlighted the UK deal as a promising template for future agreements, especially in areas like agriculture. Regarding the EU, Navarro criticized recent retaliatory rhetoric and said while the EU is not low on the priority list, its actions—such as “firing shots across our bow”—are unfortunate and unhelpful to ongoing trade discussions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canada jobs data will be released at 8:30 AM ET, with employment change est at 2.5K vs -32.6K last month. THe unemployment rate is expected at 6.8% vs 6.7% last month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks in pre-market trading are higher as per the futures prices:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow up 64 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P up 15.06 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq +65 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market, yields are mixed with the short end lower, and the higher end higher:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 year yield 3.863% -3.1 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 3.983%, -1.1 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year yield 4.388%, +1.5 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year yield 4.861%, +0.3 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week, the 3 and 10 year note auctions were solid, but the 30 year bond auction yesterday was not so great (positive tail and lower bid to cover). &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive European FX news wrap: Trump floats cutting China tariffs to 80%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-trump-floats-cutting-china-tariffs-to-80-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:13:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-trump-floats-cutting-china-tariffs-to-80-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Headlines:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-that-80-tariffs-on-china-seems-right-20250509/&quot;&gt;Trump says that 80% tariffs on China &quot;seems right&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-that-china-should-open-up-its-market-to-the-us-20250509/&quot;&gt;Trump says that China should open up its market to the US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-reportedly-offers-to-cut-tariffs-gap-by-two-thirds-to-seal-trade-deal-with-the-us-20250509/&quot;&gt;India reportedly offers to cut tariffs gap by two-thirds to seal trade deal with the US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-first-trade-deal-20250509/&quot;&gt;How have interest rates expectations changed after the first trade deal?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-monetary-policy-is-in-a-good-position-to-adjust-as-conditions-unfold-20250509/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Barr: Monetary policy is in a good position to adjust as conditions unfold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-we-need-to-be-in-a-wait-and-see-approach-20250509/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Barr: We need to be in a wait and see approach&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-barkin-tariffs-to-lead-to-higher-inflation-and-lower-growth-in-us-and-abroad-20250509/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Barkin: Tariffs to lead to higher inflation and lower growth in US and abroad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-kugler-the-us-labour-market-is-stable-close-to-maximum-employment-20250509/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Kugler: The US labour market is stable, close to maximum employment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-feds-kugler-our-policy-right-now-is-moderately-restrictive-20250509/&quot;&gt;More from Fed&apos;s Kugler: Our policy right now is moderately restrictive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-rehn-disinflation-is-on-track-and-the-growth-outlook-is-weakening-20250509/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Rehn: Disinflation is on track and the growth outlook is weakening&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-simkus-eurozone-inflation-depends-on-eu-retaliation-to-the-us-20250509/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Simkus: Eurozone inflation depends on EU retaliation to the US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-bailey-our-commitment-to-the-2-inflation-target-is-unwavering-20250509/&quot;&gt;BoE&apos;s Bailey: Our commitment to the 2% inflation target is unwavering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-pill-not-seeing-a-dramatic-shift-in-the-uk-economy-after-tariff-announcements-20250509/&quot;&gt;BOE&apos;s Pill: Not seeing a dramatic shift in the UK economy after tariff announcements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-reaffirms-that-it-will-implement-moderately-loose-monetary-policy-20250509/&quot;&gt;PBOC reaffirms that it will implement moderately loose monetary policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/nippon-steel-says-position-on-planned-acquisition-of-us-steel-remains-unchanged-20250509/&quot;&gt;Nippon Steel says position on planned acquisition of US Steel remains unchanged&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;JPY leads, NZD lags on the day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;European equities higher; S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up 0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields up 1.9 bps to 4.392%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold up 0.8% to $3,334.02&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude up 2.2% to $61.25&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin up 0.3% to $102,988&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The main headline of the session came in the last half hour or so as Trump said that 80% tariffs on China would &quot;seem right&quot;. That before making sure that if anything goes south, Bessent would be pushed under the bus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the immediate aftermath, markets are not all too sure what to make of the headline. The figure is higher than the 50% touted in reports yesterday but whether 50% or 80%, it&apos;s a mere numbers game. If the idea is to get China to the negotiating table, it&apos;s not going to work surely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;US futures whipsawed on the headline before dipping a little lower to pare gains. But as we continue to digest the situation, S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are now back a little higher up by 0.3%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar is less enthused though, with USD/JPY now down 0.5% to 145.15 and EUR/USD up 0.2% on the day to 1.1250 levels. Meanwhile, USD/CHF is also lower by 0.1% to 0.8310 while AUD/USD has pared earlier losses to be flat at 0.6400 currently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In other markets, bonds are holding lower as well with 10-year yields now up to 4.39% and 30-year yields up to 4.87% on the day. Then, we have gold also keeping higher by 0.9% to $3,334 as traders continue to digest what this all means ahead of US-China talks tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s going to be an interesting end to the week, not least with market players eyeing more trade headlines before the end of the day. We&apos;ll also have to watch out for positioning plays ahead of US-China talks, as that could lead to a significant gap on either side at the open on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) NAVARRO: VAT TAX IN EUROPE IS THE PROBLEM FOR THE US</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920814146993459221#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:12:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920814146993459221#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NAVARRO: VAT TAX IN EUROPE IS THE PROBLEM FOR THE US&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 NAVARRO: EU VERY HIGH ON THE PRIORITY LIST IN TRADE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920813707594002536#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:10:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920813707594002536#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 NAVARRO: EU VERY HIGH ON THE PRIORITY LIST IN TRADE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) NAVARRO: JAPAN IS MOST CLEVER AT PROTECTING ITS OWN MARKETS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920813129254031453#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:08:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920813129254031453#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NAVARRO: JAPAN IS MOST CLEVER AT PROTECTING ITS OWN MARKETS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 NAVARRO: COUNTRIES LINING UP TO TALK TRADE WITH THE US</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920813056042360882#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920813056042360882#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 NAVARRO: COUNTRIES LINING UP TO TALK TRADE WITH THE US&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Trade Adviser Navarro: It will be an interesting weekend for the markets</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-adviser-navarro-it-will-be-an-interesting-weekend-for-the-markets-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:07:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-adviser-navarro-it-will-be-an-interesting-weekend-for-the-markets-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;It will be an interesting weekend for the markets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan is most clever at protecting its own markets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Countries lining up to talk trade with the US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The EU very high on the priority list in trade talks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;VAT tax in Europe is a problem for the US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The weekend risk here is high for indices traders. From a risk management perspective, unless you have positions from much lower prices, it would be better to go flat into the weekend and reassess next week.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN SAYS PUTIN AND TRUMP EXPRESSED CONGRATULATIONS ON VICTORY DAY VIA AIDES - TASS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920812286953857228#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:05:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920812286953857228#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN SAYS PUTIN AND TRUMP EXPRESSED CONGRATULATIONS ON VICTORY DAY VIA AIDES - TASS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE&apos;S PETER NAVARRO ON CHINA TALKS: INTERESTING WEEKEND FOR THE MARKETS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920812248299167800#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:05:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920812248299167800#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE&apos;S PETER NAVARRO ON CHINA TALKS: INTERESTING WEEKEND FOR THE MARKETS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed’s Kugler: Tariffs May Fuel Inflation While Weak Demand Slows Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/feds-kugler-tariffs-may-fuel-inflation-while-weak-demand-slows-growth-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:58:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/feds-kugler-tariffs-may-fuel-inflation-while-weak-demand-slows-growth-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;98&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Fed’s Kugler Flags Diverging Forces: Tariffs May Fuel Inflation While Weak Demand Slows Growth
Federal Reserve Governor Adriana Kugler highlighted the complex economic picture facing policymakers, noting that while headline GDP contracted by 0.3%, private domestic final purchases (PDFP) — a key gauge of consumer and business activity — grew at a solid 3%, signaling underlying resilience. However, early signs of tariff-related inflation and weakening confidence suggest headwinds ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;513&quot; data-end=&quot;1002&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Financial Implications:
Markets face a dual risk: tariffs could reignite inflation via higher input costs, particularly in goods, while weakening sentiment and slowing real incomes could drag down demand. This mix complicates the Fed’s outlook — inflation pressures may persist even as unemployment ticks higher. For equities, especially rate-sensitive sectors, this stagflationary risk profile is bearish. Manufacturing input costs and supply chain shifts may also weigh on margins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1004&quot; data-end=&quot;1030&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key Metrics/Details:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1031&quot; data-end=&quot;1438&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1031&quot; data-end=&quot;1060&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1033&quot; data-end=&quot;1060&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;GDP (headline): -0.3%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1061&quot; data-end=&quot;1115&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1063&quot; data-end=&quot;1115&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;PDFP (private domestic final purchases): +3.0%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1116&quot; data-end=&quot;1223&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1118&quot; data-end=&quot;1223&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Early indicators: Regional Fed surveys and ISM data show rising input costs, particularly in goods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1224&quot; data-end=&quot;1304&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1226&quot; data-end=&quot;1304&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Consumer sentiment: Falling confidence despite high recent retail sales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1305&quot; data-end=&quot;1438&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1307&quot; data-end=&quot;1438&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Outlook: Real income and asset value declines expected to suppress demand; productivity may fall due to supply chain reshoring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1440&quot; data-end=&quot;1854&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Investor Takeaway:
Investors should brace for policy complexity: the Fed may face inflationary pressure from tariffs at the same time that labor market weakness begins to bite. This reduces the likelihood of aggressive rate cuts, especially if goods inflation persists. Positioning should account for margin pressure in manufacturing and consumer cyclicals, while demand weakness may favor defensive sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1861&quot; data-end=&quot;2103&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;This article was generated at ForexLive.com (evolving to be investingLive.com at the end of this year) with the assistance of AI and may contain factual or contextual inaccuracies. It should not be solely relied upon without verification.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Kugler: Q1 growth data showed frontloading ahead of tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kugler-q1-growth-data-showed-frontloading-ahead-of-tariffs-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:53:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kugler-q1-growth-data-showed-frontloading-ahead-of-tariffs-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Unclear how tariffs policy will shake out&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;See some upside risk to inflation from tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economy has been resilient so far&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economic health gives  Fed time to make progress on inflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;On the headline remark, she&apos;s referring to this &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-q1-advance-gdp-03-vs-03-expected-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. However, this frontloading hasn&apos;t really shown up in other forms of data surprisingly. So, that is a bit interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOE&apos;s Pill: Not seeing a dramatic shift in the UK economy after tariff announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-pill-not-seeing-a-dramatic-shift-in-the-uk-economy-after-tariff-announcements-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:44:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-pill-not-seeing-a-dramatic-shift-in-the-uk-economy-after-tariff-announcements-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Limited economic reaction to tariffs partly reflects expectations of looser BOE policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Should not neglect longer-term upward pressures on inflation from wages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;Careful&quot; rate cuts should be understood to represent being alert, agile to economic changes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is still some way to go on disinflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This is a rather soft defense of his position to not want to cut rates in yesterday&apos;s vote. But as mentioned then, the BOE system does shed more transparency on the same discussion that all central banks are facing right now. If even the UK is seeing such a debate, what more other major central banks like the Fed and ECB.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says that 80% tariffs on China &quot;seems right&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-that-80-tariffs-on-china-seems-right-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:28:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-that-80-tariffs-on-china-seems-right-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;&quot;80% Tariff on China seems right! Up to Scott B.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I&apos;m not sure how exactly it is up to Bessent when Trump himself is already saying that it should be 80%. Funny. US futures are hitting a bit of a whipsaw on the headline here but at the balance, is nudging lower. Gold is also catching a bid, touching a high of $3,338 while USD/JPY is now down 0.5% to 145.10 on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The 80% figure is higher than what was reported yesterday &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/white-house-weighing-plan-to-slash-china-tariffs-to-as-low-as-50-report-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. But again, whether at 50% or 80%, the effect is more or less the same still. If the idea is to get China to the negotiating table, then it wouldn&apos;t work. So, is Trump just sending Bessent up for slaughter here?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The bigger picture continues to allude to the potential idea that Trump&apos;s tariffs are designed in a fashion to pursue further decoupling in US-China relations. The 10% tariffs elsewhere are also acting as an off-ramp for Trump in allowing for US firms to chase alternatives and substitutes in the meantime.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: 80% tariff on China seems right</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-80-tariff-on-china-seems-right-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:28:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-80-tariff-on-china-seems-right-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;80% tariff on China seems right, up to Scott Bessent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is in stark contrast to earlier reports suggesting that the US could lower tariffs on China to 50-54%. He added that it&apos;s up to the US Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent to decide the appropriate rate, as he&apos;s the one in charge of trade negotiations with China, but it still shows that Trump is favouring a more aggressive approach.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More from Fed&apos;s Kugler: Our policy right now is moderately restrictive</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-feds-kugler-our-policy-right-now-is-moderately-restrictive-20250509/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:26:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-feds-kugler-our-policy-right-now-is-moderately-restrictive-20250509/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our policy right now is moderately restrictive.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The labour market is stable and has been resilient.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Q1 GDP showed the real side of the economy is resilient.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scenarios are important amid high degrees of uncertainty.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Retail sales showed some front loading.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There could be some pullback in consumer spending.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Important to keep long-run inflation expectations stable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I see some upside risk to inflation from tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The economy has been resilient so far.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economic health gives the Fed time to make progress on inflation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s unclear how tairff policy will shake out.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fed policymakers are now working in scenarios amid the uncertainty on trade policies rather than trying to give a more concrete forward guidance. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
