<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Where ESG Meets Smart Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/where-esg-meets-smart-trading-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:11:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/where-esg-meets-smart-trading-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Award-winning online trading platform&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ironfx.com/en/?utm_source=publishers&amp;amp;utm_medium=media&amp;amp;utm_content=homepage&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt; IronFX&lt;/a&gt; is known for its long list of headlining sports sponsorships, from freediving championships in Korea to world-famous football clubs. Rising to the challenge is clearly a hallmark of this forex trading broker’s ethos. To this end, it also helps vulnerable groups in communities to make their lives better through charitable and Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;What do child welfare in Cyprus, earthquake victims in the Yunnan Province, and flood victims in Hungary have in common? IronFX Foundation has contributed to their relief with charity concerts, team contributions and donations as part of its corporate social responsibility (CSR) programme. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;In 2025, those who want to trade online - particularly those with significant experience and financial knowledge - expect a lot more than competitive pricing and advanced technology. They are also looking for higher standards of conduct from their brokers. An IronFX review from any of the 180 countries where it accepts clients shows this MT4 trading broker has a reputation as a trusted platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;This mindset shift is fundamentally changing what it means to be the best forex broker in the financial markets, and ESG factors have moved to the centre of investor and trader decision-making. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;IronFX has woven these principles into its DNA. The foundation has contributed to causes in countries around the world. Community support projects include donations for children with special needs, flood relief efforts in Malaysia, and assistance for students with financial difficulties amongst others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Through these ongoing activities, IronFX has set an example of what is possible, demonstrating that responsible trading can bring together market conduct and a positive role in society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Investor trends: standards drive broker choice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Recent feedback from the company’s clients underscores a clear trend: the trading competition has changed, and traders are increasingly seeking brokers who reflect their own values. Many, including those trading with an Islamic forex account, are choosing to partner with firms that prioritise fairness, social responsibility, and transparency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;From the new to the seasoned, traders are aligning their broker relationships with their professional and personal benchmarks. As a result, ESG practices are now a core advantage for brokers aiming to attract and retain discerning clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Aligning with sustainability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;As ESG considerations become more prominent, IronFX has taken practical steps to ensure its offerings and operations are aligned with the expectations of sustainability-minded clients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The company has gone digital-first, slashing paper waste and unnecessary travel to shrink its carbon footprint. It has also moved much of its client engagement, documentation, and educational content online. These changes have reduced paper usage and lowered the company’s environmental impact. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;In the spirit of showing that sustainability is more than just a buzzword, the company is rolling out eco-friendly office practices and exploring carbon-offset partnerships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Solid governance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;For experienced traders searching for a high-leverage forex broker, trust is built on robust governance. The broker places a strong emphasis on risk management and its platform is designed to be accessible, fair and secure, so that clients have confidence that the platform operates with integrity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Clear communication and a commitment to best practices underpin the firm’s approach, ensuring that the expectations of conscientious traders are consistently met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Education and empowerment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The company recognises that informed traders are empowered traders, and has expanded its educational resources to include ESG-focused content through its academy and blog. These materials will help clients understand the impact of ESG trends on global markets and trading behaviour, providing practical insights without promoting specific products. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;By encouraging a deeper understanding of trustworthy practices, IronFX aims to support its clients with the knowledge needed to master an increasingly complex financial landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The next steps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;This shift towards ESG is becoming a wider industry trend. Brokers are evaluated not just on their product offerings, but on their reliability and commitment to ethical conduct. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;From being awarded “Best Education Tools APAC” (UF Awards 2024) to its ongoing efforts to be recognised as the best forex broker for informed traders, IronFX continues to expand its educational content to include ESG-focused materials. A series of blog articles and IronFX Academy webinars are in the works which will discuss the implications of these trends on global markets and trader behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;As such principles become integral to investor expectations, the broker’s forward-thinking approach positions it as a platform of choice for those seeking both financial performance and ethical alignment. The company’s ongoing commitment to CSR, environmental responsibility, and transparent governance positions it as a leader in an evolving industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;For those who want their investments to mean more, ESG isn’t on the sidelines - it’s the new standard. The commitment to fairness and making a positive difference shows IronFX is resolute in its approach so that traders do not have to choose between performance and purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Start trading with this ESG-active broker &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ironfx.com/en/?utm_source=publishers&amp;amp;utm_medium=media&amp;amp;utm_content=homepage&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;by following this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany May Ifo business climate index 87.5 vs 87.4 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-ifo-business-climate-index-875-vs-874-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:04:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-ifo-business-climate-index-875-vs-874-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 86.9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current assessment 86.1 vs. 86.8 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 86.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expectations 88.9 vs. 88.0 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 87.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s getting tentatively better as we go forward. As seen in the German PMI report, fiscal boost and ECB rate cuts are helping the economy.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone May flash services PMI 48.9 vs 50.3 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-flash-services-pmi-489-vs-503-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 08:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-flash-services-pmi-489-vs-503-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 50.1&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing PMI 49.4 vs 49.3 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 49.0&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 49.5 vs 50.7 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 50.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Eurozone Composite PMI Output Index at 6-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Eurozone Services PMI Business Activity Index at 16-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Eurozone Manufacturing PMI Output Index at Unchanged pace of growth.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Eurozone Manufacturing PMI at 33-month high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the flash PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The eurozone economy just cannot seem to find its footing. Since January, the overall PMI has shown only the slightest hint
of growth and in May, the private sector actually slipped into contraction. Do not blame US tariffs for this one. In fact, efforts
to get ahead of those tariffs might partly explain why manufacturing has held up a bit better lately. Manufacturers have now
increased production for the third straight month, and for the first time since April 2022, new orders did not decline. On the
flip side, service providers, who are generally less exposed to US trade policy, except in areas like international logistics, are
seeing business activity shrink for the first time since November 2024. While foreign demand for services is softening, it is
the sluggish domestic demand that seems to be dragging the sector down.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“May’s snapshot is not pretty. Looking ahead, companies are only cautiously optimistic. The expectations index is still well
below its long-term average. However, there are reasons for confidence in the longer term. The recovery in manufacturing is
broad-based, with encouraging signs coming out of both Germany and France. Further interest rate cuts could provide a
boost, and lower oil prices compared to last year are also helping. Germany, in particular, might be gearing up to reclaim its
role as the eurozone’s economic engine, thanks to a potentially very expansionary fiscal policy. That is backed up by a
notable jump in Germany’s future production index, which has climbed to an above-average level.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For the European Central Bank, these numbers are likely to leave it with mixed feelings. Inflation in service sector sales
prices has ticked down slightly from an already low level, but input costs are still rising and even picking up speed. With
energy prices falling, higher wages are probably the main driver here. Still, the ECB seems inclined to continue with cautious
rate cuts, especially with purchase prices in manufacturing on the decline.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany May flash manufacturing PMI 48.8 vs 48.9 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-flash-manufacturing-pmi-488-vs-489-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 07:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-flash-manufacturing-pmi-488-vs-489-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Services PMI 47.2 vs 49.5 expected
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 49.0 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 48.6 vs 50.4 expected
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 50.1 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Germany Composite PMI Output Index at 5-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Germany Services PMI Business Activity Index at 30-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Germany Manufacturing PMI Output Index at 3-month low.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash Germany Manufacturing PMI at 33-month high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the flash PMI data, Dr. Cyrus de la Rubia, Chief Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These numbers paint a mixed picture - there are both positives and negatives here. On the bright side, manufacturing is
doing better, as output has been climbing for three months in a row, and new orders are following suit. In the service sector,
by contrast, activity has taken a sharper tumble. And since services make up a big chunk of the economy, that drop has
pulled overall activity into contraction. Considering the modest growth we saw in Q1, this latest data lines up with what the
German Council of Economic Experts are forecasting, namely that the economy might just be treading water this year.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In manufacturing things are looking up. While the headline PMI is still in recessionary territory, it’s been inching higher for
five straight months. That upward trend likely reflects a mix of short-term factors - like companies rushing orders ahead of
US tariffs - and broader cyclical improvements supported by ECB rate cuts. Looking ahead, increased defence spending and
a more defined infrastructure package could give the sector an extra push. Plus, falling input costs, which are driven by
cheaper energy, should offer manufacturers some breathing room.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Service providers are struggling a bit. Activity has been sliding for two months now, with new business drying up and pricing
power fading. Meanwhile, costs are still climbing fast, which could squeeze profit margins. On a more positive note, service
providers are still hiring, bucking the broader trend. And future expectations have ticked up a bit, though the level of
optimism is still well below the long-term average. Overall, our nowcast model, which considers the PMI among other
factors, calculates that activity of service providers will barely expand in the second quarter.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France May flash services PMI 47.4 vs 47.5 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-flash-services-pmi-474-vs-475-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 07:15:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-flash-services-pmi-474-vs-475-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 47.3&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing PMI 49.5 vs 48.9 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 48.7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Composite PMI 48.0 vs 48.0 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 47.8&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash France Composite PMI Output Index at 2-month high.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash France Services PMI Business Activity Index at 2-month high.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash France Manufacturing PMI Output Index at 37-month high.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HCOB Flash France Manufacturing PMI at 28-month high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenting on the flash PMI data, Jonas Feldhusen, Junior Economist at Hamburg Commercial Bank, said:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“France’s private sector remained subdued in May. The Flash Composite PMI continues to signal contraction, reflecting the
economic challenges France is facing amid domestic political instability and a fragile macroeconomic environment.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Diverging trends emerged across sectors. The services sector deteriorated, with business activity still weak. Looking ahead,
prospects are equally dim. The index measuring the order situation—an indicator of future business—remains well below the
long-term average and inside contraction territory. In contrast, the manufacturing sector showed signs of recovery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The
Manufacturing PMI improved for the fifth straight month, supported by increased factory output. Despite ongoing uncertainty
and trade-related headwinds, several factors may explain this upward trend, such as the ECB’s easing of credit conditions,
EU efforts to reduce regulatory burdens, and the push to increase defense spending. These developments could, despite
prevailing risks, pave the way for a cyclical rebound following the prolonged downturn in the sector.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Price dynamics raise new concerns for French businesses. While output prices slipped into deflationary territory in May,
input cost inflation accelerated, signalling a squeeze on profit margins, particularly in the services sector. This raises the
question of how trade frictions will influence European price levels in the coming months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;On one hand, supply chain
disruptions and frontloading could drive prices up. On the other hand, goods facing increased competition as a result of
supply being redirected to the European market away from the US might exert downward pressure on prices. Nevertheless,
HCOB Economics still expects three additional ECB rate cuts this year, as the subdued growth and inflation environment
leaves scope for further easing.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Despite improvements in manufacturing and President Macron’s recent efforts to position France as an attractive
destination for investment, research and development, the overall outlook for the private sector remains bleak, as seen by
the business outlook falling sharply in May, especially in the service sector.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France May business confidence 97 vs 99 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-business-confidence-97-vs-99-expected-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:45:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-business-confidence-97-vs-99-expected-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 99 (revised to 100)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not a market moving indicator but it&apos;s a bit of a disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House votes to advance revised tax plan in procedural vote</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-votes-to-advance-revised-tax-plan-in-procedural-vote-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:43:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-votes-to-advance-revised-tax-plan-in-procedural-vote-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US House votes to advance revised tax plan in procedural vote.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US House votes to open debate on Trump tax bill with vote on passage to follow.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here&apos;s the plan shared by Haley Talbot (CNN) on her X account (ET time):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;At approx 12:45 – 1:45 a.m., vote on the adoption of the rule
 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Next, the House will debate H.R. 1 - One Big Beautiful Bill Act
 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Following debate, at approx 4:30 – 5:30 a.m., vote on PASSAGE
 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Walk off the floor: 5:30 – 6:00 a.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are trying to do it as soon as possible before the long weekend as we have Memorial Day on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEC+ discusses another 411K B/D output hike in July</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/opec-discusses-another-411k-bd-output-hike-in-july-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:32:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/opec-discusses-another-411k-bd-output-hike-in-july-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;OPEC+ discusses another 411K B/D output hike in July.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crude oil is down on the headline as higher supply expectations continue to keep a lid on further gains.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoJ Noguchi: Recent rise in long-term rates likely won&apos;t have impact on bond taper plan</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boj-noguchi-recent-rise-in-long-term-rates-likely-wont-have-impact-on-bond-taper-plan-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boj-noguchi-recent-rise-in-long-term-rates-likely-wont-have-impact-on-bond-taper-plan-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recent rise in long-term rates likely won&apos;t have an impact on our new bond taper plan to be decided in June.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most important thing is that things are different now than during period when we had YCC.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don&apos;t look at the size of our JGB buying from standpoint of monetary policy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In tapering bond buying, giving market predictability, while maintaining flexibility, is most important.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whether to maintain current pace of bond taper beyond April 2026 will be something to be discussed leading up to the next policy meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recent rise in super-long bond yields likely driven by global trend in yields, they are rapid but not necessarily abnormal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Don&apos;t think it&apos;s appropriate to recklessly intervene to correct bond yield moves.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud of uncertainty clearing somewhat in US-China trade tension.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets restoring some calm, though uncertainty surrounding US tariff policy and impact on Japan&apos;s economy high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ shouldn&apos;t move on rates when there is lack of clarity on economic outlook.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shouldn&apos;t move on rates now, better to scrutinise developments for time being.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Focus on bond taper plan for next fiscal year onward should be to avoid disrupting markets, BoJ doesn&apos;t need to rush in trimming its huge bond holdings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ doesn&apos;t need to maintain its huge balance sheet at current levels, natural to shrink its size.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Long-term interest rates, at times, make volatile moves reflecting various views on outlook.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At times, central banks must take action to stabilise markets but don&apos;t think we are facing such conditions now.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Noguchi has talked a lot today but the core message is that he doesn&apos;t see any reason to intervene in the JGBs market or tweak the tapering because of the surge in long term yields. He&apos;s also in a wait and see mode regarding further rate hikes as he&apos;s waiting for more clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market is currently pricing 17 bps of tightening in 2025 which is basically a 50% chance of another hike by year-end.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 22 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-22-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 05:31:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-22-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;EUR/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1400 (EUR 751mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1315
(EUR 1.00bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1300 (EUR 624mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1175 (EUR 2.13bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
143.50
(US$ 601mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;GBP/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3500 (GBP 347mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3395 (GBP 456mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3260 (GBP 778mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CHF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8525 (CHF 598mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.4050
(US$ 1.41bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3700 (US$ 659mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6700 (AUD 286mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6100 (AUD 204mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETH Analysis for Today with TradeCompass</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/eth-analysis-for-today-with-tradecompass-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 04:59:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/eth-analysis-for-today-with-tradecompass-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Ethereum Futures Analysis Today – TradeCompass Methodology in Action&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello traders and crypto investors,
Today we bring you a fresh Ethereum futures analysis using the TradeCompass methodology—a professional-grade approach that incorporates volume profile, VWAPs, liquidity zones, and key historical levels to help you make more informed decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethereum (ETH) remains the second-largest crypto asset by market cap, with the most active developer community in the blockchain world. And while Bitcoin has already surged past its all-time high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethereum has not reached its all time high yet —which makes this market particularly interesting from both a technical and strategic standpoint (including having more historic levels and references to consider... more to work with).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why Ethereum Futures and Not Spot ETH?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We analyze ETH futures (not spot prices) because futures markets offer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More transparent volume and liquidity data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Institutional order flow visibility&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consistent structure across timeframes for analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time of writing, ETH futures are trading in the $2,624–$2,628 range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;tradeCompass Methodology: How It Works&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TradeCompass system combines several professional tools:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Volume Profile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shows where the majority of trading volume has taken place at specific price levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Highlights Point of Control (POC), Value Area High (VAH), and Value Area Low (VAL)—critical levels where price is likely to react.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. VWAP (Volume-Weighted Average Price)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP calculates the average price of Ethereum based on both price and volume during a session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Standard deviations of VWAP help define trend boundaries, breakout zones, and support/resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. Liquidity Zones &amp;amp; Round Numbers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Round numbers like $2,600, $2,500, and $2,700 attract heavy trading and stop orders. They act as magnets or reversal zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market makers often use these levels to create fakeouts and stop hunts, so we adjust our strategy accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. Partial Profit Framework&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;TradeCompass emphasizes taking profits in stages, reducing risk and protecting gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goal is not just accuracy, but sustainable profitability by managing trades dynamically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Ethereum Futures Levels Right Now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish Bias Above $2,600&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$2,600 is a round number and a major pivot level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aligned with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 16 VWAP: $2,600&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 16 POC: $2,602&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 22 (Today’s) POC: $2,604&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holding above this zone confirms buyer control. Dips to this region and rebounds can be viewed as long opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another CLOSE and RELEVANT Bullish Support Zone: $2,580–$2,586&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;May 13 VWAP: $2,580&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today’s VWAP: $2,586.4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If ETH futures dip here, it&apos;s a technical buy zone with clearly defined risk (stop just below) and strong reward potential&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;ETH Futures - Bearish If Below $2,538&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Ethereum futures break below $2,538, it could trigger a shift to bearish sentiment. This level will be updated further as we analyze liquidity clusters, lower VWAP deviations, and developing volume profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What to Do as a Crypto Trader or Investor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t chase long breakouts blindly.
Wait for retracements into support zones near VWAP or POC clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t short blindly.
Shorting into bullish support zones or near VAHs without confirmation often leads to losses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partial profits are key.
Whether you are long from $2,580 or $2,600, don’t wait for a fantasy top. Take profits along the way at pre-planned levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow Comments Below as ETH Price Updates May Come In&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will possibly add the profit-taking prices on both sides of the trade, so traders can plan their exits with discipline and structure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ETH Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethereum remains in a bullish zone for now. The best strategy today may be to buy retracements into support and avoid late-stage shorts. TradeCompass continues to guide decisions using proven institutional tools like volume profile and VWAP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade at your own risk. This is not financial advice, but a data-driven decision support framework.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;investingLive Crypto – sharp trades, news gems that matters, unique education &amp;amp; important updates, zero noise!  

Get important alerts, tradeCompass insights, and more decision support - without the spam. Join now for free!

🔗 &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/investingLiveCrypto&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;t.me/investingLiveCrypto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 04:26:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, the focus will be on the Flash PMIs where the market will want to see how business confidence changed since the new developments on the trade front and what&apos;s the sentiment going forward. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we have the US Jobless Claims and the US Flash PMIs. The Jobless Claims data will likely be ignored as usual as the labour market remains stable and therefore not a source of concerns. Only a spike above the 260K level for Initial Claims could trigger a repricing in expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Flash PMIs, on the other hand, will be important to see if there&apos;s a strong bounce back in activity (or expectations of that in the months ahead) and the picture around inflation. The market is currently pricing 51 bps of easing for the Fed in 2025 with the first cut in September. The data from now on could change those expectations and therefore move the markets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, the US House could also vote on the &quot;big, beautiful bill&quot; and if successful could add to inflationary concerns and therefore push long term yields higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;07:15 GMT/03:15 ET - BoE&apos;s Breeden (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:30 GMT/04:30 ET - RBA&apos;s Hauser (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:00 GMT/08:00 ET - BoE&apos;s Dhingra (uber dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:30 GMT/08:30 ET - BoE&apos;s Pill (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;18:00 GMT/14:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Williams (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan&apos;s Mimura says Japan, US did not discuss FX levels at finance ministers&apos; meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-mimura-says-japan-us-did-not-discuss-fx-levels-at-finance-ministers-meeting-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 03:47:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-mimura-says-japan-us-did-not-discuss-fx-levels-at-finance-ministers-meeting-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan&apos;s Mimura says Japan, US did not discuss FX levels at finance ministers&apos; meeting &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;reaffirmed that forex should be determined by the market &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not believe that there is any gap in understanding with the U.S.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Finance Minister Kato agreed with Bessent that FX rates should be set by markets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did not discuss current rates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did not discuss future rates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mimura is repeating what US Treasury told us much earlier, triggering a yen sell off:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-confirm-that-sec-bessent-met-with-japan-finance-minister-kato-20250521/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;US Treasury confirm that Sec. Bessent met with Japan finance minister Kato&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Atsushi Mimura is Japan&apos;s vice finance minister for international affairs, AKA &apos;top currency diplomat&apos;. Japan&apos;s finance ministry is the relevant authority in Japan for ordering intervention in the JPY. Mimura would be directing Bank of Japan intervention, should it come to that. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea fires multiple cruise missiles toward East Sea</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/north-korea-fires-multiple-cruise-missiles-toward-east-sea-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 03:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/north-korea-fires-multiple-cruise-missiles-toward-east-sea-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;North Korea fires multiple cruise missiles toward East Sea&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reports from South Korea media, Yonhap. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-to-roll-in-north-korea-kim-sees-negligence-and-irresponsibility-20250521/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Heads to roll in North Korea - Kim sees negligence and irresponsibility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: USD/JPY swings</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-usdjpy-swings-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 03:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-usdjpy-swings-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/morgan-stanley-sounding-alarm-on-ev-race-china-may-have-already-won-tesla-knows-it-20250522/&quot;&gt;Morgan Stanley sounding alarm on EV race, China may have already won &amp;amp; Tesla knows it.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/a-us-house-vote-on-trumps-tax-cut-bill-is-edging-closer-house-rules-committee-approves-20250522/&quot;&gt;A US House vote on Trump&apos;s tax cut bill is edging closer - House Rules Committee approves&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-noguchi-says-bank-should-only-ramp-up-bond-purchases-during-severe-market-disruption-20250522/&quot;&gt;BOJ Noguchi says Bank should only ramp up bond purchases during “severe market disruption”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-national-security-panel-has-submitted-its-recommendation-on-nippon-steel-us-steel-20250522/&quot;&gt;US national security panel has submitted its recommendation on Nippon Steel / U.S. Steel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-narrows-budget-deficit-forecast-eases-near-term-bond-issuance-plans-20250522/&quot;&gt;New Zealand narrows budget deficit forecast, eases near-term bond issuance plans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/cba-sees-gold-hitting-3750oz-by-year-end-on-safe-haven-flows-weaker-dollar-20250522/&quot;&gt;CBA sees gold hitting $3,750/oz by year-end on safe-haven flows, weaker dollar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-board-member-noguchi-japans-economy-is-growing-steadily-20250522/&quot;&gt;Bank of Japan board member Noguchi: Japan’s economy is growing steadily&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-and-10-asean-countries-have-concluded-negotiations-on-free-trade-agreement-20250522/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - China and 10 ASEAN countries have concluded negotiations on free trade agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71903-vs-estimate-at-72009-20250522/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1903 (vs. estimate at 7.2009)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-reports-that-trump-told-eu-heads-in-private-putin-isnt-ready-to-end-war-20250522/&quot;&gt;WSJ reports that Trump told EU heads in private Putin isn’t ready to end war&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/aud-traders-heads-up-for-rba-deputy-governor-hauser-to-speak-20250522/&quot;&gt;AUD traders - heads up for RBA Deputy Governor Hauser to speak&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/singapore-central-bank-official-says-current-monetary-policy-settings-remain-appropriate-20250522/&quot;&gt;Singapore central bank official says current monetary policy settings remain appropriate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-flash-may-manufacturing-pmi-490-prior-487-20250522/&quot;&gt;Japan flash May manufacturing PMI 49.0 (prior 48.7)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/singaporeq1gdp-06qq-expected-10-prior-08-20250522/&quot;&gt;Singapore Q1 GDP -0.6% q/q (expected -1.0%, prior -0.8%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-to-roll-in-north-korea-kim-sees-negligence-and-irresponsibility-20250521/&quot;&gt;Heads to roll in North Korea - Kim sees negligence and irresponsibility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-machinery-orders-surge-13-mm-expected-16-20250521/&quot;&gt;Japan machinery orders surge, +13% m/m (expected -1.6%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-fin-min-kato-says-unsustainable-imbalance-in-some-countries-behind-trade-imbalance-20250521/&quot;&gt;Japan fin min Kato says Unsustainable imbalance in some countries behind trade imbalance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/reuters-survey-two-thirdsofjapanesefirmswantbojtopauseratehikes-20250521/&quot;&gt;Reuters survey: Two-thirds of Japanese firms want BOJ to pause rate hikes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-sp-global-manufacturing-pmi-flash-reading-for-may-2025-517-prior-517-20250521/&quot;&gt;Australian S&amp;amp;P Global Manufacturing PMI Flash reading for May 2025: 51.7 (prior 51.7)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-seriously-considering-bringing-fannie-mae-freddie-mac-public-20250521/&quot;&gt;Trump says seriously considering bringing Fannie Mae, Freddie Mac, public&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-report-that-walmart-plans-to-cut-around-1500-jobs-20250521/&quot;&gt;WSJ report that Walmart plans to cut around 1,500 jobs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-treasury-confirm-that-sec-bessent-met-with-japan-finance-minister-kato-20250521/&quot;&gt;US Treasury confirm that Sec. Bessent met with Japan finance minister Kato&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-com-sec-lutnick-says-again-on-tariffs-that-10-is-baseline-no-ones-going-below-10-20250521/&quot;&gt;US Com Sec Lutnick says again on tariffs that 10 is baseline, no one’s going below 10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-sees-progress-on-tariffs-but-says-still-more-work-to-be-done-20250521/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Nagel sees progress on tariffs, but says still more work to be done&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-well-supported-expect-it-to-test-us3500-20250521/&quot;&gt;Gold well supported, expect it to test US$3500&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-speaker-johnson-says-yet-to-decide-on-vote-on-trump-tax-bill-today-or-tomorrow-20250521/&quot;&gt;US House Speaker Johnson says yet to decide on vote on Trump tax bill, today or tomorrow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/morgan-stanley-say-federal-reserve-rate-cuts-may-not-begin-until-september-20250521/&quot;&gt;Morgan Stanley say Federal Reserve rate cuts may not begin until September&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/nike-to-raise-prices-on-a-wide-range-of-products-as-soon-as-this-week-20250521/&quot;&gt;Nike to raise prices on a wide range of products as soon as this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-21-may-higher-us-yields-worry-markets30y-at-new-25-high-20250521/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 21 May: Higher US yields worry markets.30Y at new &apos;25 high&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/major-us-stock-indices-close-today-lower-as-yields-rise-20250521/&quot;&gt;Major US stock indices close today lower as yields rise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-falls-below-key-support-tests-fibonacci-retracement-zone-20250521/&quot;&gt;USDJPY falls below key support, tests Fibonacci retracement zone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-thursday-22-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250521/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Thursday, 22 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
The
yen was a notable mover during the session here, with yen crosses
fist surging higher and then giving it all back, and more. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
move higher of USD/JPY (and crosses) came on the back of a statement
from the US Treasury that Secretary Bessent had met with Japan
finance minister Kato and forex matters were discussed. It was an
innocuous statement of fact making points that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;the
two did not discuss foreign exchange levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;the
two shared
belief that exchange rates should be market determined
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;and
even made the point that the present the dollar-yen exchange rate
reflects fundamentals!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;But,
that’s all it took for USD/JPY to race from around 143.60 to highs
above 144.30 in just a few minutes. Admittedly, it was at a
low-liquidity part of the 24 hours FX cycle (just prior to 8am Sydney
time (10am New Zealand, 7 am Tokyo, 6am Singapore and Hong Kong, 6pm
US Eastern time, 12am/11 pm Frankfurt/London).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Over
the course of the rest of the session here USD/JPY gave it all back,
and more. Its currently below 143.20 as I post. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;We
heard from Trump via a social media post. Trump said he is “giving
very serious consideration” to bringing Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac
public and would decide in the near future. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;We
had data from Japan, a huge surge in machinery orders during March.
This is a volatile data set but the jump was impressive, +13.4% m/m
and +8.4% y/y. At the margin it’ll diminish recession fears. The
PMIs that followed, albeit on preliminary (for May), showed the
manufacturing sector improving but still in contraction, now for the
11th consecutive month. Services remained in expansion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Bank
of Japan (BOJ) board member Asahi Noguchi spoke. Noguchi tends to the
dovish end of the policy spectrum, but nevertheless said the Bank
should proceed gradually with rate hikes, albeit only with clear
evidence that inflation is sustainably anchored around the 2% target,
supported by wage growth. He also said there’s no need to make
major changes to the bank’s plan for tapering bond purchases.
Noguchis also reiterated that the Bank should only ramp up bond
purchases during “severe market disruption”, signaling no
immediate need to counter the recent spike in super-long bond yields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

Gold rose on the session, as did Bitcoin. BTC/USD above US$110K is a new high. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a heads up, it looks like the US House vote on Trump&apos;s tax bill is likely at 4.30am US Eastern time. This is still fluid but that&apos;s the current estimate. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Stanley sounding alarm on EV race, China may have already won &amp; Tesla knows it.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/morgan-stanley-sounding-alarm-on-ev-race-china-may-have-already-won-tesla-knows-it-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 03:06:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/morgan-stanley-sounding-alarm-on-ev-race-china-may-have-already-won-tesla-knows-it-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;100&quot; data-end=&quot;286&quot;&gt;Morgan Stanley is sounding the alarm on the rapidly intensifying electric vehicle (EV) race, suggesting China may have already clinched victory in the hardware battle—and Tesla knows it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;288&quot; data-end=&quot;776&quot;&gt;In a recent note, the investment bank argues that the launch of Xiaomi’s new SU7—which it describes as an “electric Ferrari at a Volkswagen price”—is a watershed moment. The SU7, and now the similarly styled YU7, blend premium design cues reminiscent of the Ferrari Purosangue and Aston Martin DBX with pricing closer to a Volkswagen ID.3 or Tesla Model Y, fundamentally raising the competitive bar for every global carmaker targeting the US$30,000–40,000 segment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;778&quot; data-end=&quot;1221&quot;&gt;The speed and scale at which Chinese tech firms are combining high performance with affordability is forcing Tesla to shift its value proposition:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;If China has already won the EV hardware race, the next battlefield—and margin pool—is full self-driving software and data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tesla’s pivot from “best car” to “best autonomy stack” is seen as a direct response to the shrinking defensibility of its traditional EV advantage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1223&quot; data-end=&quot;1526&quot;&gt;Xiaomi’s breakneck pace is especially notable. The YU7 is only its second model, but even Ford’s CEO has admitted that U.S. legacy automakers are years away from fielding a comparable offering. By the time they catch up, Xiaomi’s third-generation vehicles will likely have moved the goalposts again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1528&quot; data-end=&quot;1829&quot;&gt;Morgan Stanley projects Xiaomi’s EV business could generate RMB 233 billion (around US$32 billion) in revenue by 2027—roughly matching Tesla’s total automotive sales from 2020. That level of scaling in just three model generations compresses what used to take incumbent carmakers a decade or more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1831&quot; data-end=&quot;2220&quot;&gt;While Western governments may use tariffs to slow the tide, Morgan Stanley warns that top-tier Chinese EVs are likely to find their way to premium buyers regardless. In fact, some global automakers are already exploring joint ventures or tech licensing deals with Chinese firms to gain access to critical EV and autonomy expertise while limiting capital expenditure and execution risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2222&quot; data-end=&quot;2651&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;In the bank’s view, equity markets are placing too much emphasis on Tesla’s near-term vehicle margins, underestimating the impact of incoming low-cost Chinese competition. The note underscores Tesla’s strategic shift toward autonomy as the company’s next defensible growth engine—spanning robo-taxis, logistics, and other mobility platforms—as it braces for a future shaped increasingly in Beijing, not Detroit or Silicon Valley. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A US House vote on Trump&apos;s tax cut bill is edging closer - House Rules Committee approves</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/a-us-house-vote-on-trumps-tax-cut-bill-is-edging-closer-house-rules-committee-approves-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 02:44:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/a-us-house-vote-on-trumps-tax-cut-bill-is-edging-closer-house-rules-committee-approves-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;U.S. House Rules Committee approves Trump’s tax-cut bill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sets stage for full House floor vote on the bill&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;House Speaker Johnson and Trump&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJ Noguchi says Bank should only ramp up bond purchases during “severe market disruption”</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-noguchi-says-bank-should-only-ramp-up-bond-purchases-during-severe-market-disruption-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 02:25:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-noguchi-says-bank-should-only-ramp-up-bond-purchases-during-severe-market-disruption-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;77&quot; data-end=&quot;306&quot;&gt;Bank of Japan (BOJ) board member Asahi Noguchi says the central bank should only ramp up bond purchases during “severe market disruption”, signaling no immediate need to counter the recent spike in super-long bond yields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;308&quot; data-end=&quot;527&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;310&quot; data-end=&quot;527&quot;&gt;Noguchi believes no major changes are needed to the BOJ’s current bond tapering plan, which runs through March 2026, though he says the strategy beyond that should be reviewed from a long-term perspective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;529&quot; data-end=&quot;697&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;531&quot; data-end=&quot;697&quot;&gt;The BOJ plans to conduct an interim review of its tapering programme at its policy meeting next month and outline a new approach for the period beyond March 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;699&quot; data-end=&quot;958&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;701&quot; data-end=&quot;958&quot;&gt;A known dove on the BOJ board, Noguchi also urged caution on future interest rate hikes, saying they should proceed gradually and only with clear evidence that inflation is sustainably anchored around the 2% target, supported by wage growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;960&quot; data-end=&quot;1201&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;962&quot; data-end=&quot;1201&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;While the BOJ allows markets to determine long-term interest rates, Noguchi noted it retains the option to adjust bond buying in response to volatility—but such emergency operations should be used only in exceptional circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Noguchi spoke earlier, headlines are here:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-board-member-noguchi-japans-economy-is-growing-steadily-20250522/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Bank of Japan board member Noguchi: Japan’s economy is growing steadily&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;While his monetary policy outlook are garnering attention its his &apos;only ramp up bond purchases during “severe market disruption”&apos; comment grabbing the headlines.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US national security panel has submitted its recommendation on Nippon Steel / U.S. Steel</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-national-security-panel-has-submitted-its-recommendation-on-nippon-steel-us-steel-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 02:16:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-national-security-panel-has-submitted-its-recommendation-on-nippon-steel-us-steel-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;80&quot; data-end=&quot;276&quot;&gt;A U.S. national security panel (CFIUS) has submitted its recommendation to Trump on Nippon Steel’s $14.9 billion bid for U.S. Steel, though the content remains undisclosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;80&quot; data-end=&quot;276&quot;&gt;Reuters with the info. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;277&quot; data-end=&quot;452&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;279&quot; data-end=&quot;452&quot;&gt;Trump’s April executive order required CFIUS to assess whether proposed company measures address previously identified national security risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;453&quot; data-end=&quot;567&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;455&quot; data-end=&quot;567&quot;&gt;Trump now has 15 days to make a final decision on the deal, though the deadline may be extended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;568&quot; data-end=&quot;670&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;570&quot; data-end=&quot;670&quot;&gt;The Treasury Department (which leads CFIUS) and the companies involved have not yet commented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;671&quot; data-end=&quot;889&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;673&quot; data-end=&quot;889&quot;&gt;Biden previously blocked the deal in January, citing national security concerns; the companies have since sued, claiming the review process was unfair—an assertion the Biden administration denies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;890&quot; data-end=&quot;1056&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;892&quot; data-end=&quot;1056&quot;&gt;In a bid to address concerns, Nippon Steel has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/icymi-nippon-steel-sweetens-us-steel-bid-with-us14bn-investment-pledge-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;proposed a $14 billion U.S. investment&lt;/a&gt;, including $4 billion for a new steel mill, if the deal is approved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1057&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1059&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;The executive order also mandates that each CFIUS member agency submit a formal statement explaining its position and rationale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand narrows budget deficit forecast, eases near-term bond issuance plans</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-narrows-budget-deficit-forecast-eases-near-term-bond-issuance-plans-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 02:10:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-narrows-budget-deficit-forecast-eases-near-term-bond-issuance-plans-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;157&quot; data-end=&quot;328&quot;&gt;New Zealand has revised its fiscal outlook, projecting a smaller budget deficit and adjusting bond issuance plans as it navigates a still-challenging economic environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;330&quot; data-end=&quot;657&quot;&gt;On Thursday, the government forecast a budget deficit of NZ$14.74 billion for the fiscal year ending June 30, 2025, a notable improvement from the NZ$17.32 billion shortfall projected in its December half-year update. The narrowing reflects improved revenue expectations and a slightly firmer economic backdrop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;659&quot; data-end=&quot;897&quot;&gt;At the same time, net debt is now forecast to peak at 46% of GDP in 2027/28, slightly later but marginally lower than the 46.5% peak in 2026/27 projected last December. The shift suggests a more measured fiscal consolidation path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;899&quot; data-end=&quot;1152&quot;&gt;The New Zealand Debt Management Office (NZDMO) also trimmed its near-term bond issuance plans. For the 2025/26 fiscal year, gross bond issuance is expected to total NZ$38 billion, down from NZ$40 billion projected in the December update.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1154&quot; data-end=&quot;1434&quot;&gt;However, the government raised its total bond issuance forecast for the four-year period to June 2029 to NZ$132 billion, up from NZ$128 billion. The revision reflects longer-term funding needs amid a broader economic transition and continued infrastructure investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1436&quot; data-end=&quot;1593&quot;&gt;Despite the moderated borrowing profile in the near term, officials signaled a continued commitment to fiscal discipline and longer-term debt sustainability. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBA sees gold hitting $3,750/oz by year-end on safe-haven flows, weaker dollar</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/cba-sees-gold-hitting-3750oz-by-year-end-on-safe-haven-flows-weaker-dollar-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 02:09:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/cba-sees-gold-hitting-3750oz-by-year-end-on-safe-haven-flows-weaker-dollar-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;153&quot; data-end=&quot;367&quot;&gt;Gold prices are poised to rise to $3,750 per ounce by the fourth quarter, driven by rising safe-haven demand and a weakening U.S. dollar, according to a new report from Commonwealth Bank of Australia (CBA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;369&quot; data-end=&quot;735&quot;&gt;In a note from Vivek Dhar, director of mining and energy commodities research at CBA, the bank highlighted geopolitical tensions—particularly the risk of military escalation involving Iran—as a key upside risk for bullion. “The threat of military strikes against Iran cannot be ruled out, which raises the stakes if U.S.-Iran talks remain deadlocked,” Dhar said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;737&quot; data-end=&quot;947&quot;&gt;Gold’s traditional role as a safe haven may become even more pronounced, the report suggests, especially as it has recently outperformed both the U.S. dollar and U.S. Treasurys amid rising American tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;949&quot; data-end=&quot;1096&quot;&gt;CBA also expects the dollar to gradually weaken through the second half of 2025 and into 2026, further supporting the bullish gold outlook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;949&quot; data-end=&quot;1096&quot;&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;949&quot; data-end=&quot;1096&quot;&gt;China on the bid again today?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Japan board member Noguchi: Japan’s economy is growing steadily</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-board-member-noguchi-japans-economy-is-growing-steadily-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:32:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-board-member-noguchi-japans-economy-is-growing-steadily-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bank of Japan board member Noguchi:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s economy is growing steadily&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s economy is currently shifting to a new phase where sustainable inflation is realized accompanied by wage increases&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Downside risks to Japan economy stemming from overseas economies have rapidly heightened due to U.S. tariff policies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BOJ likely to keep adjusting policy rate while carefully examining whether underlying inflation would be stabilising around 2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BOJ shouldn’t pre-set terminal rate in raising rates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BOJ should spend time gauging impact of each rate hike on economy, scrutinise risks, before moving to next hike&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year JGB yield rose near 1.6% in March but I didn’t see it as disruptive as it reflected change in market’s view on terminal rate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Personally don’t see need to make big changes to existing BOJ taper plan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As for taper plan for April 2026 onward, we need to examine with a longer-term perspective&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BOJ can spend sufficient time reducing its balance sheet, doing so is desirable for market stability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BOJ is maintaining loose monetary policy as rise in inflation is mainly driven by import costs, not necessarily sustainable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monetary policy must focus on underlying price moves that are strongly linked to nominal wage developments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wage, domestic demand-driven price pressure not strong enough but steadily increasing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our basic monetary policy stance should be to cautiously move on policy adjustment while scrutinising economy and its risks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An oft-repeated line from the BoJ is that as long as inflation and economic targets are being hit, then rates will rise. Noguchi hasn&apos;t said this exactly but it seems to be his overall message. I&apos;d say he is sounding more dovish than hawkish though. Comments welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI - China and 10 ASEAN countries have concluded negotiations on free trade agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-and-10-asean-countries-have-concluded-negotiations-on-free-trade-agreement-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:26:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-and-10-asean-countries-have-concluded-negotiations-on-free-trade-agreement-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China and 10 ASEAN countries have concluded negotiations on CAFTA Version 3.0, a major upgrade of their free trade agreement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The deal introduces nine new chapters focused on areas like the digital economy, green economy, and supply chain connectivity, aiming to deepen regional integration and economic cooperation. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Officials say CAFTA 3.0 will enhance trade stability, foster industrial and technological collaboration, and provide institutional support for efficient and secure supply chains. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;With bilateral trade nearing USD 1 trillion in 2024, both sides see this as a key step toward high-quality development and a strong signal in favour of open, rule-based multilateral trade. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Formal signing of the agreement is expected by the end of 2025.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://english.news.cn/20250522/002d513015e846cf848b555bd64e52b5/c.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Link here for more.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China  + ASEAN Member States:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brunei Darussalam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cambodia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Indonesia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Laos&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Malaysia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Myanmar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Philippines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Singapore&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thailand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vietnam
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
These eleven countries form the CAFTA 3.0, an upgraded free trade agreement aiming to deepen economic integration between China and the ASEAN bloc.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1903 (vs. estimate at 7.2009)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71903-vs-estimate-at-72009-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:16:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71903-vs-estimate-at-72009-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous close was 7.2031&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC injected 154.5bn yuan via 7-day reverse repos at 1.40%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;64.5bn yuan matured today&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;net injection 90bn yuan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ reports that Trump told EU heads in private Putin isn’t ready to end war</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-reports-that-trump-told-eu-heads-in-private-putin-isnt-ready-to-end-war-20250522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 01:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-reports-that-trump-told-eu-heads-in-private-putin-isnt-ready-to-end-war-20250522/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/world/europe/trump-putin-call-russia-ukraine-83a6ef59&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;WSJ&lt;/a&gt; (gated) reports that Trump told EU heads in private Putin isn’t ready to end war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;On a call Monday, President Trump told European leaders that Russian President Vladimir Putin isn’t ready to end the war because he thinks he is winning, according to three people familiar with the conversation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key points in the Journal article:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;css-1ese8zm&quot;&gt;Trump told European leaders that Putin thinks he’s winning the war and isn’t ready for peace—a view they already held but hadn’t heard from Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;css-1ese8zm&quot;&gt;Trump shifted from suggesting sanctions to proposing lower-level talks at the Vatican between Russia and Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;css-1ese8zm&quot;&gt;Europeans sought to clarify Putin’s stance for Trump, underscoring their need to support Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: GIVING VERY SERIOUS CONSIDERATION TO BRINGING FANNIE MAE AND FREDDIE MAC PUBLIC.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925327060253159558#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 23:05:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925327060253159558#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: GIVING VERY SERIOUS CONSIDERATION TO BRINGING FANNIE MAE AND FREDDIE MAC PUBLIC.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, DOW JONES DOWN 2.00 PCT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925268317859622995#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:11:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925268317859622995#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, DOW JONES DOWN 2.00 PCT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) Kennedy Jr.&apos;s &apos;MAHA&apos; Report Expected to Criticize Chemicals in Food, Lobbyists and Vaccines, Sources Say -- WSJ

Report Goes Easier on Pesticides in Farming, People Briefed on Draft of Report Say -- WSJ

Final MAHA Report May Be Released as Soon as Thursday, Sources Say -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925254291582816315#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:16:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925254291582816315#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kennedy Jr.&apos;s &apos;MAHA&apos; Report Expected to Criticize Chemicals in Food, Lobbyists and Vaccines, Sources Say -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Report Goes Easier on Pesticides in Farming, People Briefed on Draft of Report Say -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Final MAHA Report May Be Released as Soon as Thursday, Sources Say -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TEXAS HOUSE APPROVES BILL TO CREATE BITCOIN RESERVE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925243245526708503#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:32:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925243245526708503#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TEXAS HOUSE APPROVES BILL TO CREATE BITCOIN RESERVE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, NASDAQ DOWN 1.00 PCT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925241804296777870#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:26:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925241804296777870#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. STOCKS EXTEND FALL, NASDAQ DOWN 1.00 PCT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 20-YEAR U.S. TREASURY YIELD CLIMBS TO 5.104%, HIGHEST SINCE NOV 2023; LAST UP 11.3 BASIS POINTS AT 5.103%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925241316511773006#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:24:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925241316511773006#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;20-YEAR U.S. TREASURY YIELD CLIMBS TO 5.104%, HIGHEST SINCE NOV 2023; LAST UP 11.3 BASIS POINTS AT 5.103%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) NASDAQ TURNS NEGATIVE, LAST DOWN 0.5%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925240572517744781#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:21:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925240572517744781#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NASDAQ TURNS NEGATIVE, LAST DOWN 0.5%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 ISRAEL PM NETANYAHU SAYS ISRAEL PROBABLY KILLED HAMAS LEADER MOHAMMED SINWAR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925239849562349959#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:18:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925239849562349959#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 ISRAEL PM NETANYAHU SAYS ISRAEL PROBABLY KILLED HAMAS LEADER MOHAMMED SINWAR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US REP. LAWLER: MADE GREAT PROCESS ON TAX BILL, WAITING FOR DETAILS

US REP. LAWLER: FEELING MUCH BETTER ABOUT TAX BILL NOW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925239768301879639#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:18:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925239768301879639#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US REP. LAWLER: MADE GREAT PROCESS ON TAX BILL, WAITING FOR DETAILS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
US REP. LAWLER: FEELING MUCH BETTER ABOUT TAX BILL NOW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SOUTH AFRICA&apos;S JOHANN RUPERT AT WHITE HOUSE: NEED STARLINK AT EVERY POLICE STATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925237345474773123#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:08:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925237345474773123#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SOUTH AFRICA&apos;S JOHANN RUPERT AT WHITE HOUSE: NEED STARLINK AT EVERY POLICE STATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US 20Y BONDS DRAW 5.047% VS 5.035% PRE-SALE WHEN-ISSUED YIELD</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925235856127696978#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925235856127696978#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US 20Y BONDS DRAW 5.047% VS 5.035% PRE-SALE WHEN-ISSUED YIELD&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TREASURY WI 20-YEAR YIELD 5.035% BEFORE $16B AUCTION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925235349430628863#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:00:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925235349430628863#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TREASURY WI 20-YEAR YIELD 5.035% BEFORE $16B AUCTION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: DON&apos;T WANT TO HAVE TO TALK TO MUSK ABOUT SOUTH AFRICA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925234189709857057#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:56:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925234189709857057#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: DON&apos;T WANT TO HAVE TO TALK TO MUSK ABOUT SOUTH AFRICA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP HOLDS PRINTED COPIES OF ARTICLES ON WHITE SOUTH AFRICANS, SAYS &apos;DEATH, DEATH&apos;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925231773710971217#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:46:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925231773710971217#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP HOLDS PRINTED COPIES OF ARTICLES ON WHITE SOUTH AFRICANS, SAYS &apos;DEATH, DEATH&apos;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SOUTH AFRICA&apos;S RAMAPHOSA: IMAGES FROM VIDEOS SHOWING WHITE CROSSES ARE THINGS I&apos;VE NEVER SEEN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925231238182216105#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925231238182216105#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SOUTH AFRICA&apos;S RAMAPHOSA: IMAGES FROM VIDEOS SHOWING WHITE CROSSES ARE THINGS I&apos;VE NEVER SEEN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP HAS STAFF PLAY VIDEOS PERTAINING TO SOUTH AFRICA GENOCIDE ALLEGATIONS DURING MEETING WITH RAMAPHOSA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925230266987032981#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:40:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925230266987032981#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP HAS STAFF PLAY VIDEOS PERTAINING TO SOUTH AFRICA GENOCIDE ALLEGATIONS DURING MEETING WITH RAMAPHOSA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SOUTH AFRICA&apos;S RAMAPHOSA ON WHAT IT WILL TAKE TO CHANGE TRUMP&apos;S MIND ON GENOCIDE: IT WILL TAKE TRUMP LISTENING TO SOUTH AFRICAN VOICES

TRUMP: HAVE HEARD THOUSANDS OF STORIES ABOUT IT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925230002171261422#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:39:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925230002171261422#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SOUTH AFRICA&apos;S RAMAPHOSA ON WHAT IT WILL TAKE TO CHANGE TRUMP&apos;S MIND ON GENOCIDE: IT WILL TAKE TRUMP LISTENING TO SOUTH AFRICAN VOICES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: HAVE HEARD THOUSANDS OF STORIES ABOUT IT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: DOING BIG DEALS WITH INDIA, PAKISTAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925228427407241703#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:33:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925228427407241703#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: DOING BIG DEALS WITH INDIA, PAKISTAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) kalshi.com/markets/kxqatarje…</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925226166530551889#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:24:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925226166530551889#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://kalshi.com/markets/kxqatarjet/qatari-jet&quot;&gt;kalshi.com/markets/kxqatarje…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925225771913687315#m&quot;&gt;localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925225771913687315#m&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:8080/pic/media%2FGrfG_CnW0AAPZ0I.png&quot; style=&quot;max-width:250px;&quot; /&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. FORMALLY ACCEPTS LUXURY JET FROM QATAR FOR TRUMP -NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925225771913687315#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:22:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925225771913687315#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. FORMALLY ACCEPTS LUXURY JET FROM QATAR FOR TRUMP -NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
