<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>UK and US have agreed on terms for trade deal - report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-and-us-have-agreed-on-terms-for-trade-deal-report-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:58:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-and-us-have-agreed-on-terms-for-trade-deal-report-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The report pretty much confirms that this is a &quot;heads of terms&quot; agreement. In other words, it is a preliminary agreement and a &quot;substantive&quot; step towards a full deal. As for the details, it is all still rather lacking at the moment. Sky&apos;s deputy political editor, Sam Coates, added that this is also a positive step ahead of the UK-EU summit on 19 May:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;I think it is politically helpful for Keir Starmer to have got the heads of terms, the kind of main points of a US-UK trade deal, nailed down before we see what we have negotiated with the EU - or, more importantly, Donald Trump sees what we have negotiated with the EU.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Dollar extends gains against the JPY on positive sentiment</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-dollar-extends-gains-against-the-jpy-on-positive-sentiment-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:38:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-dollar-extends-gains-against-the-jpy-on-positive-sentiment-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The positive news on trade deals continue to boost the US Dollar. This has more to do with positioning rather than fundamentals for now. In fact, the short dollar trade has been one of the most crowded ones and therefore it&apos;s at risk of unwindings on positive news on the trade front.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY is now up more than 0.6% on the day as the positive risk sentiment weighs on the Japanese Yen. For the USD, there&apos;s also a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-could-be-dead-wrong-on-rate-cuts-if-this-scenario-plays-out-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;scenario&lt;/a&gt; where we could see a bigger upside move if very good outcomes on the trade front make the market to reprice interest rate expectations all the way down to just one cut for the Fed in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK PM Starmer: You will hear more from me later today on US economic deal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-pm-starmer-you-will-hear-more-from-me-later-today-on-us-economic-deal-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 08:25:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-pm-starmer-you-will-hear-more-from-me-later-today-on-us-economic-deal-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will hear more from me later today on US economic deal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I will always act in national interest.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, now we just wait for the details...&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – Trump’s announcement weighs on the precious metal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-trumps-announcement-weighs-on-the-precious-metal-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 07:43:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-trumps-announcement-weighs-on-the-precious-metal-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fed yesterday kept its
usual neutral stance and Fed Chair Powell didn’t offer anything in terms of
forward guidance citing elevated uncertainty. The event didn’t move gold since
there wasn’t anything new.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What impacted gold negatively
was Trump saying that he would make a big announcement concerning a major trade
deal today. Reports are saying that it will be a framework for a trade deal
with the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the bigger picture, gold
remains in an uptrend as real yields will likely continue to fall amid Fed
easing. But in the short-term positive news on the tariffs front or a hawkish
Fed could trigger more downside for gold as the market prices out
stagflationary fears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that gold rallied back above the 3400 level recently on some negative tariff
related headlines. Trump’s announcement though triggered some downside on
positive expectations. From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have
a better risk to reward setup around the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt;, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into the 2957 level next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see the price recently broke above the key swing level at 3367 before extending
the rally above the 3400 level. The price fell back below the 3367 level and
from a risk management perspective, the sellers will likely want to see a
pullback into the level to position for further downside. The buyers, on the
other hand, will want to see the price rising back above the 3367 level to pile
in for a rally into a new all-time high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor downward trendline now defining the current pullback. If
the price gets there, we can expect the sellers to lean on the trendline with a
defined risk above it to position for a drop into the 3258 level next. The
buyers, on the other hand, will look for a break higher to increase the bullish
bets into new highs. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we get the latest US Jobless Claims figures and
Trump announcing the outline for a trade deal with the UK. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China&apos;s MOFCOM: US needs to be prepared to revoke unilateral tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-mofcom-us-needs-to-be-prepared-to-revoke-unilateral-tariffs-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 07:18:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-mofcom-us-needs-to-be-prepared-to-revoke-unilateral-tariffs-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US needs to be prepared to revoke unilateral tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a reminder, US and China will hold talks on trade this weekend in Switzerland although the expectations have been set low by the US Treasury Secretary Bessent as he said that it&apos;s more about de-escalation than negotiations for a trade deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump said that he won&apos;t drop tariffs unilaterally to bring China to the negotiating table, so if the Chinese insist on this point, then it could be a long way before we see anything substantial.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equities hold higher at the open today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-hold-higher-at-the-open-today-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 07:11:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-hold-higher-at-the-open-today-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx +0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 +0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The positive mood holds up as we get into European trading, with market players eyeing Trump&apos;s announcement of a trade deal with the UK later. Or at least the agreement of the framework of a deal, however you want to put it. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are also keeping higher, now up 0.8% on the day, as tech shares lead the rebound on the week.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China president Xi arrives in Kremlin for talks with Putin</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-arrives-in-kremlin-for-talks-with-putin-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 07:08:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-arrives-in-kremlin-for-talks-with-putin-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;From the day before: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/reminder-china-president-xi-to-visit-moscow-later-today-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;China president Xi to visit Moscow later today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar climbs as hopeful optimism builds on trade</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-climbs-as-hopeful-optimism-builds-on-trade-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 07:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-climbs-as-hopeful-optimism-builds-on-trade-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar is trading higher now to start European trading as the UK confirms that Trump&apos;s announcement later will be an agreement to a framework for a trade deal. This means laying out the groundwork and discussion points for negotiations over the next few weeks/months, but at least there is some progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;USD/JPY has raced higher to around 144.40 now with EUR/USD easing slightly to 1.1285 on the day from around 1.1305 earlier. GBP/USD is also down 0.1% to 1.3285 while USD/CHF is up 0.4% to 0.8270 currently. Meanwhile, gold is down 1.2% to $3,324 as sellers look to break the near-term bullish hold &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-dips-lower-as-market-hopes-build-on-us-uk-trade-deal-announcement-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As things stand, there are two main things that market players are hoping to be more optimistic about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The first will come today from Trump&apos;s announcement later at 1400 GMT. That will involve the agreement to the framework for a trade deal between the US and UK. It&apos;s a good first step to reaching a deal and while it might seem like a formality, you never know with Trump. But I think at this point, this should be a given - it&apos;s just a matter of when.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The interesting point to watch out for though is the details on what tariffs will be stuck in place for the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As a reminder, the UK is part of the shortlist of six countries that Trump has deemed as a &quot;priority&quot; to get a deal done. The others being India, South Korea, Japan, Vietnam, and Indonesia. And as another reminder, the UK was not part of the initial reciprocal tariffs list considering the more balanced nature of trade with the US. So, they were &quot;only&quot; slapped with a blanket 10% tariff alongside other tariffs on steel, aluminum, and autos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, it will be important to see what levels the UK will be stuck with on any deal. And that will also help set the tone on what to expect from other countries, in particular those higher up on the initial reciprocal tariffs list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The second main thing is the supposed trade talk between the US and China this weekend. While the US camp is saying that this is a &quot;starting point&quot; for negotiations, the Chinese camp has been labelling this meeting as a mere &quot;engagement&quot; or &quot;touch point&quot;. The exact wording used by the Chinese embassy is &apos;接触&apos;. So, that might offer some insight as to how both sides are going to approach the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;At best, we will get to see both sides engage in more talks over the coming weeks/months. But even so, what happens in between all of that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;If Trump&apos;s position is as what he said &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-he-isnt-open-to-lowering-china-tariffs-to-get-them-to-the-negotiating-table-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; yesterday, it is going to be tough to see any fruitful discussions between the two countries. We&apos;ll see the can keep being kicked down the road and in the meantime, the tariffs in place will continue to bite at both economies as well as the global economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For now, there&apos;s plenty of hope for things to turn out for the better as we look towards the end of the week. But it&apos;s also best to reminded that the reality of the situations above might end up differing a lot from what traders are hoping for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That might gear us towards a buy the rumour, sell the fact predicament in the bigger picture. That unless Trump continues to find new stories to keep propping up the market that is.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:35:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, the only highlight is the BoE policy decision. The central bank is expected to cut by 25 bps bringing the bank rate to 4.25% with a 9-0 vote split (although Dhingra could vote for a 50 bps cut). This is widely expected as the BoE has been repeating that cutting once every quarter would be their preferred plan. The focus will be on the language and a potential change to the &quot;gradual and careful&quot; guidance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, the focus will switch to the US Jobless Claims as it&apos;s the most timely indicator of the labour market. Initial Claims are expected at 230K vs 241K prior, while Continuing Claims are seen at 1886K vs 1916K prior. The market is unlikely to care much about the data unless we see a spike above the 260K level as that&apos;s been the highest level reached since 2022 and could trigger fears of a deterioration in the labour market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main event of the day will be at 14:00 GMT/10:00 ET when Trump said that he would make a big announcement concerning a major trade deal. Reports are saying that it will be a framework for a trade deal with the UK. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold dips lower as market hopes build on US-UK trade deal announcement</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-dips-lower-as-market-hopes-build-on-us-uk-trade-deal-announcement-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:32:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-dips-lower-as-market-hopes-build-on-us-uk-trade-deal-announcement-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar is gaining some slight ground but gold is among the more noticeable movers to start the session. The precious metal is now down 0.7% on the day and touching a low of $3,336. That is running close to the 100-hour moving average (red line) of $3,330. Keep above and the near-term bias stays more bullish but break below that and the bias will turn more neutral instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The latest headlines comes from the UK, with media reports confirming that Trump is to announce a &quot;heads of terms&quot; agreement i.e. framework of a deal. The announcement will take place at 1400 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Even with this though, there will be more negotiations to follow. But after a bit of a setback with Japan, this at least will help set the tone for what may come next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;However, it is best to be reminded that the UK was not on the reciprocal tariffs list from the onset. This is due to the balanced nature of goods trade between the UK and the US. So, they have only been subject to the 10% blanket tariffs and steel, aluminum, auto tariffs. Is that a key factor to help with moving things along? I would argue so. So, there&apos;s that to consider too.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK official confirms Trump expected to announce US deal outline</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-official-confirms-trump-expected-to-announce-us-deal-outline-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:23:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-official-confirms-trump-expected-to-announce-us-deal-outline-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;UK official confirms Trump expected to announce US deal outline. The official added that the two countries had made good progress that would likely include lower tariff quotas on steel and cars. As a reminder, the US imposed the baseline 10% global tariff rate on UK.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heads up on timing of BOE policy decision later today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-on-timing-of-boe-policy-decision-later-today-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:17:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-on-timing-of-boe-policy-decision-later-today-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;In light of the national two minutes of silence to commemorate the 80th anniversary of VE day, the Monetary Policy Report and minutes of the Monetary Policy Committee meeting will be published at 12.02pm (BST) on Thursday 8 May 2025, instead of the regular time of 12pm (BST).&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just a heads up ahead of the decision later, in case you might wonder why there is a &quot;delay&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +0.7% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-07-in-early-european-trading-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:08:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-07-in-early-european-trading-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The optimism comes as Trump touts a &quot;major&quot; trade deal announcement later in the day, in which he will be speaking about at 1400 GMT. The reports are suggesting this to be with the UK but the devil is in the details. As mentioned &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/risk-stays-buoyed-as-traders-eye-trumps-trade-deal-announcement-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, it might not be all that is hyped up to be. So, we&apos;ll see how Trump wants to sell the narrative and if markets can continue the rebound on the week after the fact. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are seen up 0.6% currently as well.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK April Halifax house prices +0.3% vs -0.1% m/m expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-halifax-house-prices-03-vs-01-mm-expected-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:00:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-halifax-house-prices-03-vs-01-mm-expected-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slight delay in the release by the source. UK house prices beat estimates to climb in April, with the average property price moving up to £297,781. Halifax notes that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We know the stamp duty changes prompted a surge in transactions in the early part of this year, as
buyers rushed to beat the tax-rise deadline. However, this didn&apos;t lead to a significant increase in property prices, with the last six months characterised by a stability in prices rarely seen since the
pandemic. While the market has cooled slightly since this rush, buyer activity remains strong in
comparison to recent years.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Mortgage rates have continued to fall, with most lenders now offering rates below 4%. Coupled with
positive earnings growth that has outpaced broader inflation, these factors have helped to steadily
improve affordability for many buyers.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Overall, the market continues to show resilience despite a subdued economic environment and risks
from geopolitical developments. There is likely to be a bump-up in consumer price inflation as
household bills increase, but with further base rate cuts also expected, we anticipate a similar trend of
modest price growth this year.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany March trade balance €21.1 billion vs €19.1 billion expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-march-trade-balance-211-billion-vs-191-billion-expected-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:00:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-march-trade-balance-211-billion-vs-191-billion-expected-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior €17.7 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The German trade surplus expanded slightly in March as exports were seen up 1.1% on the month while imports fell by 1.4% on the month. Overall, the foreign trade balance closed with a surplus of €21.1 billion and that is roughly the same as in March last year (a surplus of €20.5 billion).&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany March industrial production +3.0% vs +0.8% m/m expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-march-industrial-production-30-vs-08-mm-expected-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:00:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-march-industrial-production-30-vs-08-mm-expected-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -1.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;German industrial output bounced back after the drop in February, with increases seen across all main groups. The production of consumer goods and capital goods each rose by 4.9%, and production of intermediate goods by 1.1%. That if offset by a drop in energy production of 1.8% on the month.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China premier Li reportedly set for visit to Malaysia later this month</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-premier-li-reportedly-set-for-visit-to-malaysia-later-this-month-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 05:37:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-premier-li-reportedly-set-for-visit-to-malaysia-later-this-month-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The visit will be in conjunction with the 2nd ASEAN-Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) Summit that will take place on 27 May. The sources say that Chinese premier Li Qiang will be a high-profile attendee as Beijing hopes to rally more allies in fighting back against US tariffs. Li&apos;s visit will follow up on China president Xi&apos;s own visit to Malaysia as well from last month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;One of the sources mentioned that trade is expected to be high on the agenda with regards to discussions during the summit. It is unclear if Li will also be in attendance for the ASEAN Summit itself, which will take place on 26 May in Malaysia as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides the summit, Malaysia itself is an important strategic trade player caught in the US-China trade war. So, China&apos;s agenda here could be two-fold. For one, Malaysia is one of the more popular grounds for origin washing as noted &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-china-has-been-preparing-itself-ahead-of-this-tariffs-eventuality-with-the-us-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. And after China, Malaysia is the next biggest exporter of rare earth minerals to the US. The gap between the two is massive of course but at around 13% (rest of the world ex China combined is only 17%), it&apos;s not an insignificant amount.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 8 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-8-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 05:12:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-8-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There is just one to take note of on the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That being for EUR/USD at the 1.1300 level. It isn&apos;t one that ties to any technical significance though, so the impact might not be too striking. But amid a bit of a wait until we get to Trump&apos;s trade deal announcement, the expiries could help to provide a bit of a magnet for price action in the session ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But as has been the case in the past two to three weeks, it&apos;s all about trade headlines and the risk mood. So, those will remain as the key drivers of trading sentiment as we look to the day ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk stays buoyed as traders eye Trump&apos;s trade deal announcement</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/risk-stays-buoyed-as-traders-eye-trumps-trade-deal-announcement-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 04:42:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/risk-stays-buoyed-as-traders-eye-trumps-trade-deal-announcement-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But as per the latest report &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-trump-is-expected-to-announce-a-framework-of-a-trade-deal-with-the-uk-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, it seems that the so-called deal is just an agreement for negotiations to begin. It will just involve a framework for discussions over the coming weeks/months. So, we&apos;ll see about that. But as always, one can expect Trump to talk up a big game and that is keeping markets hopeful ahead of the announcement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Risk trades are holding up once again with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures now up 0.8%. That follows from the overnight gains but it was far from straightforward. The Fed stood their ground and that briefly saw US stocks pare gains before &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-to-rescind-global-chip-curbs-report-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;this late headline&lt;/a&gt; helped to salvage things. A word of caution of course that the devil is in the details regarding that report on chips but markets are running with it anyway for now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Going back to Trump&apos;s announcement, it will be interesting to see how he wants to sell the narrative. The details will also be of much importance, so be on the lookout for that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For now, it&apos;s still a case of buying the rumour. Will it end up being a sell the fact play before the end of today?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Trump&apos;s announcement is expected at 1400 GMT later.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Trump says he’ll announce “major” trade deal Thursday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-trump-says-hell-announce-major-trade-deal-thursday-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 03:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-trump-says-hell-announce-major-trade-deal-thursday-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Trump said he will announce a “major” trade deal on Thursday:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-trump-is-expected-to-announce-a-framework-of-a-trade-deal-with-the-uk-20250508/&quot;&gt;WSJ - Trump is expected to announce a framework of a trade deal with the U.K.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-york-times-says-trump-will-announce-a-trade-deal-with-the-uk-20250508/&quot;&gt;New York Times says Trump will announce a trade deal with the UK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-spruiks-a-major-trade-deal-announcement-thursday-morning-in-washington-20250508/&quot;&gt;Trump spruiks a major trade deal announcement Thursday morning in Washington&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-embassy-in-the-us-says-china-will-not-compromise-its-principles-in-trade-talks-20250508/&quot;&gt;Chinese Embassy in the US says China will not compromise its principles in trade talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/is-the-bank-of-japan-policy-board-split-on-when-to-hike-rates-again-20250508/&quot;&gt;Is the Bank of Japan policy board &apos;split&apos; on when to hike rates again?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-ueda-mindful-of-impact-of-rising-food-prices-on-underlying-inflation-20250508/&quot;&gt;BoJ Ueda: Mindful of impact of rising food prices on underlying inflation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/pavlovs-dog-takes-us-equities-higher-on-trumps-major-trade-deal-teaser-announcement-20250508/&quot;&gt;Pavlov&apos;s dog takes US equities higher on Trump&apos;s &quot;major trade deal&quot; teaser announcement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-mid-point-today-at-72073-vs-estimate-at-72385-20250508/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY mid-point today at 7.2073 (vs. estimate at 7.2385)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/arizona-passes-bill-to-establish-bitcoin-reserve-20250508/&quot;&gt;Arizona passes bill to establish Bitcoin reserve&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/former-boj-governor-kuroda-supports-uedas-normalization-steps-20250508/&quot;&gt;Former BOJ Governor Kuroda supports Ueda’s normalization steps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/nz-pm-luxon-says-markets-remain-volatile-but-hes-confident-about-nz-economic-recovedry-20250508/&quot;&gt;NZ PM Luxon says markets remain volatile, but he&apos;s confident about NZ economic recovedry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-is-expected-to-set-the-usdcny-reference-rate-at-72385-reuters-estimate-20250508/&quot;&gt;PBOC is expected to set the USD/CNY reference rate at 7.2385 – Reuters estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-drafting-plans-for-a-sovereign-wealth-fund-though-no-final-decisions-have-been-made-20250508/&quot;&gt;U.S. drafting plans for a sovereign wealth fund, though no final decisions have been made&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-minutes-bank-will-raise-rates-if-economic-and-price-projections-realised-20250507/&quot;&gt;BoJ minutes: Bank will raise rates if economic and price projections realised&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/barclays-says-us-equities-upside-difficult-cites-downgrades-recession-erratic-policy-20250507/&quot;&gt;Barclays says US equities upside difficult. Cites downgrades, recession, erratic policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-sees-the-federal-open-market-committee-fomc-on-an-extended-pause-20250507/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs sees the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) on an extended pause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/north-korea-fires-off-a-ballistic-missile-20250507/&quot;&gt;North Korea fires off a ballistic missile&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/rbnz-gov-hawkesby-recap-compares-trump-tariffs-to-covid-supply-side-impacts-20250507/&quot;&gt;RBNZ Gov Hawkesby recap - compares Trump tariffs to COVID supply side impacts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-expect-us-inflation-to-surge-higher-20250507/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs expect US inflation to surge higher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/citadels-griffin-says-tariffs-a-painfully-regressive-tax-fueling-risk-of-stagflation-20250507/&quot;&gt;Citadel&apos;s Griffin says tariffs a &quot;painfully regressive tax&quot;, fueling &quot;risk of stagflation&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/brazils-central-bank-raises-benchmark-interest-rate-to-1475-reuters-poll-1475-20250507/&quot;&gt;Brazil’s central bank raises benchmark interest rate to 14.75% (Reuters poll 14.75%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-koreas-foreign-exchange-reserves-have-dropped-to-the-lowest-level-in-five-years-20250507/&quot;&gt;South Korea&apos;s foreign exchange reserves have dropped to the lowest level in five years&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/rbnz-gov-hawkesby-labour-market-data-highlighted-subdued-nature-of-new-zealands-economy-20250507/&quot;&gt;RBNZ gov Hawkesby: Labour market data highlighted subdued nature of New Zealand’s economy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-7-may-fed-and-chair-powell-stay-noncommitted-20250507/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 7 May: Fed and Chair Powell stays noncommitted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ukraine-considering-a-shift-away-from-the-us-dollar-possibly-linking-more-closely-to-eur-20250507/&quot;&gt;Ukraine considering a shift away from the US dollar, possibly linking more closely to EUR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-close-higher-thanks-to-late-comments-on-chips-from-trump-20250507/&quot;&gt;US stocks close higher thanks to late comments on chips from Trump&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-thursday-8-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250507/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Thursday, 8 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
It was
a relatively quiet headline day today with just a couple of nuggets. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
Bank of Japan published the minutes of its March meeting. The Bank
left monetary policy unchanged at this meeting. There was debate
around the policy board table, summarised as:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;U.S.
tariff policies are seen as a key downside risk to Japan’s economy.
Some BOJ members thus urge caution in tightening policy further.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Others
believe decisive action may be necessary regardless of global risks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Its
unsurprising that there was some debate, with inflation in the country
having risen and real rates remaining very accommodative (negative!), but the cautious view prevailed, as it did again at the
subsequent meeting on April 30/May1 when policy was left once again
on hold. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;USD/JPY
didn’t do too much upon the release of the minutes, holding near
143.80 and thereabouts before drifting lower on the Trump
announcement later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Trump
posted to his own social media app that he will announce a “major”
trade deal on Thursday at 10am US Eastern time. US media (New York
Times) reports that the trade deal will be with the United Kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;US
equity index futures traded higher on Globex on the back of the post
from Trump. Across major FX the USD lost some ground alongside. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
Wall Street Journal took a more constrained view, reporting that 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“This
announcement is likely just an agreement to start the negotiations,
identifying a framework of issues to be discussed in the coming
months”.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets are responding to Trump more than the WSJ as I update, with US equity index futures extending their gains. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Embassy in the US says China will not compromise its principles in trade talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-embassy-in-the-us-says-china-will-not-compromise-its-principles-in-trade-talks-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 03:35:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-embassy-in-the-us-says-china-will-not-compromise-its-principles-in-trade-talks-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China is not going into the talks in Switterland without making its position  crystal clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Global Time convert the message from the Chinese Embassy in the US:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese embassy in the United States:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US reaches out via multiple channels for tariff talks; China agrees after evaluation at US request&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China’s consistent stand against US tariff abuse; defending its rights and WTO-based multilateral trade&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China condemns US-initiated tariff war, demands equal &amp;amp; respectful dialogue, refuses to compromise on principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ - Trump is expected to announce a framework of a trade deal with the U.K.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-trump-is-expected-to-announce-a-framework-of-a-trade-deal-with-the-uk-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 02:55:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-trump-is-expected-to-announce-a-framework-of-a-trade-deal-with-the-uk-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Uh-oh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wall Street Journal is pouring some cold water on the earlier headlines:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The announcement, which Trump teased late Wednesday on Truth Social as being with a “big, and highly respected country,” is expected to be a framework of an announcement with tariff adjustments. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;

“This announcement is likely just an agreement to start the negotiations, identifying a framework of issues to be discussed in the coming months,” said international trade attorney Tim Brightbill. “We suspect that tariff rates, non-tariff barriers, and digital trade are all on the list—and there are difficult issues to address on all of these.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bolding is mine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-spruiks-a-major-trade-deal-announcement-thursday-morning-in-washington-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Trump spruiks a major trade deal announcement Thursday morning in Washington&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/pavlovs-dog-takes-us-equities-higher-on-trumps-major-trade-deal-teaser-announcement-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Pavlov&apos;s dog takes US equities higher on Trump&apos;s &quot;major trade deal&quot; teaser announcement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-york-times-says-trump-will-announce-a-trade-deal-with-the-uk-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;New York Times says Trump will announce a trade deal with the UK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the Bank of Japan policy board &apos;split&apos; on when to hike rates again?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/is-the-bank-of-japan-policy-board-split-on-when-to-hike-rates-again-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 02:36:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/is-the-bank-of-japan-policy-board-split-on-when-to-hike-rates-again-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;I posted a summary of the Bank of Japan March meeting minutes here earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-minutes-bank-will-raise-rates-if-economic-and-price-projections-realised-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;BoJ minutes: Bank will raise rates if economic and price projections realised&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that post you&apos;ll find some points being made in favour of staying on hold, and other points being made saying the Bank needs to able to respond quickly if needed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reuters have summarised the minutes and say this divergence is views is a split. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOJ Split Over Next Rate Hike Amid U.S. Tariff Uncertainty

 Summary:

Bank of Japan policymakers were divided in March on when to raise rates again, as escalating U.S. tariff risks threatened Japan’s economic outlook.

While some called for caution, others argued the BOJ might still need to act decisively despite global uncertainties.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
 Key Points:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
•  BOJ minutes reveal division over the pace of future rate hikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

•  U.S. tariff policies are seen as a key downside risk to Japan’s economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

•  Some BOJ members urge caution in tightening policy further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

•  Others believe decisive action may be necessary regardless of global risks.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
•  The debate underscores rising pressure on Japan’s monetary strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think &apos;split&apos; is too strong a description. I think &apos;caution&apos; and &apos;decisive action may be necessary regardless of global risks&apos; are not, at this time, a split. The overall message from the minutes, and from subsequent BoJ communication, is that there is still time to watch and wait. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: BIG NEWS CONFERENCE TOMORROW 10AM EST IN OVAL, MAJOR TRADE DEAL WITH A BIG &amp; HIGHLY RESPECTED COUNTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920298519870452106#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 02:03:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920298519870452106#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: BIG NEWS CONFERENCE TOMORROW 10AM EST IN OVAL, MAJOR TRADE DEAL WITH A BIG &amp;amp; HIGHLY RESPECTED COUNTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Times says Trump will announce a trade deal with the UK</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-york-times-says-trump-will-announce-a-trade-deal-with-the-uk-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 01:57:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-york-times-says-trump-will-announce-a-trade-deal-with-the-uk-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Here&apos;s Trump&apos;s announcement post:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-spruiks-a-major-trade-deal-announcement-thursday-morning-in-washington-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Trump spruiks a major trade deal announcement Thursday morning in Washington&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New York Times says now it&apos;ll be with the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The U.S. and Britain have been in talks over lowering British tariffs on American cars and agricultural products, as well as removing UK digital taxes on U.S. tech firms. It remains unclear whether the deal is finalized or if it represents a framework for continued negotiations.
Unlike other countries, Britain was not hit with additional “reciprocal” tariffs due to its trade surplus with the U.S., though it remains subject to a 10% global tariff and a 25% levy on steel, aluminum, and cars. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UK was my pick. But ... I don&apos;t know about anyone else but I&apos;ve lost count of how many times the NYT has been wrong about what to expect from Trump. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoJ Ueda: Mindful of impact of rising food prices on underlying inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-ueda-mindful-of-impact-of-rising-food-prices-on-underlying-inflation-20250508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 01:31:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-ueda-mindful-of-impact-of-rising-food-prices-on-underlying-inflation-20250508/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bank of Japan Governor Ueda is answering questions in parliament:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainties over rice and other food prices remain high, but prices likely to settle down eventually&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mindful of impact of rising food prices on underlying inflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will closely monitor price situations as uncertainties over global economy remain high&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-minutes-bank-will-raise-rates-if-economic-and-price-projections-realised-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;BoJ minutes: Bank will raise rates if economic and price projections realised&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/former-boj-governor-kuroda-supports-uedas-normalization-steps-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Former BOJ Governor Kuroda supports Ueda’s normalization steps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: TRADE DEAL FIRST OF MANY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920282235673968878#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:58:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920282235673968878#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: TRADE DEAL FIRST OF MANY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: TRADE DEAL WITH &apos;HIGHLY RESPECTED&apos; COUNTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920282116585054626#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:58:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920282116585054626#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: TRADE DEAL WITH &apos;HIGHLY RESPECTED&apos; COUNTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: MAJOR TRADE DEAL NEWS CONFERENCE TOMORROW AT 10AM</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920282067121619159#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:58:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920282067121619159#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: MAJOR TRADE DEAL NEWS CONFERENCE TOMORROW AT 10AM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *U.S. PRESIDENT SCHEDULES NEWS CONFERENCE ON MAJOR TRADE DEAL WITH KEY NATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920281999769469094#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920281999769469094#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*U.S. PRESIDENT SCHEDULES NEWS CONFERENCE ON MAJOR TRADE DEAL WITH KEY NATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: BIG NEWS CONFERENCE TOMORROW 10AM EST IN OVAL, MAJOR TRADE DEAL WITH A BIG &amp; HIGHLY RESPECTED COUNTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920281893498483058#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 00:57:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920281893498483058#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: BIG NEWS CONFERENCE TOMORROW 10AM EST IN OVAL, MAJOR TRADE DEAL WITH A BIG &amp;amp; HIGHLY RESPECTED COUNTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CITADEL CEO KEN GRIFFIN SAYS THERE IS MODEST RISK OF STAGFLATION - CNBC INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920218779910340999#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:46:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920218779910340999#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CITADEL CEO KEN GRIFFIN SAYS THERE IS MODEST RISK OF STAGFLATION - CNBC INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP&apos;S &apos;BIG ANNOUNCEMENT&apos; IS MEDICARE DRUG PRICE PLAN: POLITICO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920213866002174449#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:27:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920213866002174449#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP&apos;S &apos;BIG ANNOUNCEMENT&apos; IS MEDICARE DRUG PRICE PLAN: POLITICO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: CAN&apos;T PREDICT WHETHER US-CHINA WILL GET ALONG</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920213796854919588#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:26:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920213796854919588#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: CAN&apos;T PREDICT WHETHER US-CHINA WILL GET ALONG&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *OFFICIALS READY REPEAL OF AI DIFFUSION RULE LAUNCHED BY BIDEN

*NVIDIA HAS OBJECTED TO RULE AND PRESSED US FOR ITS REVERSAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920202732868116756#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:43:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920202732868116756#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*OFFICIALS READY REPEAL OF AI DIFFUSION RULE LAUNCHED BY BIDEN&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*NVIDIA HAS OBJECTED TO RULE AND PRESSED US FOR ITS REVERSAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: I&apos;VE NEVER ASKED FOR A MEETING WITH PRESIDENT, WOULD NEVER DO THAT

POWELL: IT HASN&apos;T HAPPENED THAT THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO MEET WITH ME</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920196396440785269#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:17:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920196396440785269#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: I&apos;VE NEVER ASKED FOR A MEETING WITH PRESIDENT, WOULD NEVER DO THAT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
POWELL: IT HASN&apos;T HAPPENED THAT THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO MEET WITH ME&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: FOCUS IS ON MAKING BEST DECISIONS FOR AMERICAN PEOPLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920196224667303956#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:17:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920196224667303956#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: FOCUS IS ON MAKING BEST DECISIONS FOR AMERICAN PEOPLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: FED DOESN&apos;T HAVE TOOLS THAT ARE GOOD TO ADDRESS SUPPLY CHAIN ISSUES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920195794000298146#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920195794000298146#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: FED DOESN&apos;T HAVE TOOLS THAT ARE GOOD TO ADDRESS SUPPLY CHAIN ISSUES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BLACK SMOKE APPEARS FROM CHIMNEY OF SISTINE CHAPEL, INDICATING NO POPE HAS BEEN ELECTED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920192147052986513#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920192147052986513#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BLACK SMOKE APPEARS FROM CHIMNEY OF SISTINE CHAPEL, INDICATING NO POPE HAS BEEN ELECTED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: ASKED ABOUT MARCH PROJECTIONS FOR TWO RATE CUTS, SAYS CAN&apos;T MAKE A PROJECTION NOW, WAIT UNTIL JUNE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920191985496834064#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:00:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920191985496834064#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: ASKED ABOUT MARCH PROJECTIONS FOR TWO RATE CUTS, SAYS CAN&apos;T MAKE A PROJECTION NOW, WAIT UNTIL JUNE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: PEOPEL ARE WORRIED, BUT SHOCK HASN&apos;T HIT YET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920191426106675293#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:58:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920191426106675293#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: PEOPEL ARE WORRIED, BUT SHOCK HASN&apos;T HIT YET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: DON&apos;T SEE BIG ECONOMIC EFFECTS IN THE DATA YET FROM TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920191355793314010#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:57:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920191355793314010#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: DON&apos;T SEE BIG ECONOMIC EFFECTS IN THE DATA YET FROM TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: QE WASNT BEYOND THE CONFINES OF OUR MANDATE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920190277060366419#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:53:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920190277060366419#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: QE WASNT BEYOND THE CONFINES OF OUR MANDATE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: BUSINESSES AND HOUSEHOLDS VERY BROADLY ARE CONCERNED, POSTPONING DECISIONS

POWELL: IF NOTHING HAPPENS TO ALLEVIATE THOSE CONCERNS, WOULD EXPECT THAT TO SHOW UP IN DATA IN WEEKS, MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920189889951203550#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920189889951203550#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: BUSINESSES AND HOUSEHOLDS VERY BROADLY ARE CONCERNED, POSTPONING DECISIONS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
POWELL: IF NOTHING HAPPENS TO ALLEVIATE THOSE CONCERNS, WOULD EXPECT THAT TO SHOW UP IN DATA IN WEEKS, MONTHS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) POWELL: DOWNSIDE RISKS HAVE INCREASED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920189338505077192#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:49:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920189338505077192#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;POWELL: DOWNSIDE RISKS HAVE INCREASED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
