<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: ECONOMY IS ROARING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924812978727096705#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:02:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924812978727096705#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: ECONOMY IS ROARING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WE HAVE AN UNIFIED PARTY

TRUMP: IT&apos;S NOT A QUESTION OF HOLDOUTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924812884460138932#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924812884460138932#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WE HAVE AN UNIFIED PARTY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: IT&apos;S NOT A QUESTION OF HOLDOUTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ARRIVES AT THE CAPITOL FOR TAX BILL TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924812815069479091#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924812815069479091#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ARRIVES AT THE CAPITOL FOR TAX BILL TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US dollar climbs in early trade as yields tick up</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-dollar-climbs-in-early-trade-as-yields-tick-up-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:56:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-dollar-climbs-in-early-trade-as-yields-tick-up-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US dollar is on the front foot in early New York trade. The pound is at a session low against the dollar, down 14 pips to 1.3343 after rising as high as 1.3394 at the start of European trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD and NZD are also sliding after the RBA cut rates earlier and indicated there was a discussion about cutting by 50 bps. That has both as laggards today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big concern today is sovereign yields after Japanese 30-year yields went parabolic following a poor 20-year auction. The moves comes after Japan PM took an austere tone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our country’s fiscal situation is undoubtedly extremely poor,” he said, “worse than Greece’s.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&apos;re not supposed to say the quiet part out loud, particularly when your borrowing costs have been marching steadily higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s leading to some USD safe-haven buying but eyes are also on Treasury yields US 30s fell as low as 4.89% earlier but have crept back to 4.96% and are trading at a session high. There has been demand recent on every tick to 5% but at some point you run out of buyers, particularly with the President trying to coax Congress towards an even-larger deficit.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EU PLANS €2 FEE ON SMALL IMPORTS, TARGETING TEMU AND SHEIN

The EU is proposing a flat fee—likely around €2—on billions of small packages, mostly from China, to ease pressure on customs and raise funds. The move would hit online retailers like Temu and Shein.

The fee aims to reduce unsafe or non-compliant goods and address EU retailers&apos; concerns over unfair competition. The plan could add billions to the EU budget annually.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924811208684654860#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:55:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924811208684654860#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EU PLANS €2 FEE ON SMALL IMPORTS, TARGETING TEMU AND SHEIN&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The EU is proposing a flat fee—likely around €2—on billions of small packages, mostly from China, to ease pressure on customs and raise funds. The move would hit online retailers like Temu and Shein.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The fee aims to reduce unsafe or non-compliant goods and address EU retailers&apos; concerns over unfair competition. The plan could add billions to the EU budget annually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EU TO IMPOSE FLAT TAX ON SMALL ITEMS ORDERED ONLINE - FT

BRUSSELS COULD APPLY A €2 HANDLING FEE ON BILLIONS OF SMALL PACKAGES IMPORTED MAINLY FROM CHINA - FT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924810709935792625#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:53:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924810709935792625#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EU TO IMPOSE FLAT TAX ON SMALL ITEMS ORDERED ONLINE - FT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
BRUSSELS COULD APPLY A €2 HANDLING FEE ON BILLIONS OF SMALL PACKAGES IMPORTED MAINLY FROM CHINA - FT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SEC DATA BACKS BITCOIN $500K TARGET BY 2028: STANDARD CHARTERED

Standard Chartered&apos;s Geoff Kendrick says recent SEC 13F filings support a possible rise in Bitcoin to $500,000 by end-2028. While direct ETF holdings dipped in Q1, government entities boosted stakes in Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy), seen as a Bitcoin proxy. This may reflect efforts to gain Bitcoin exposure despite regulatory limits. Bitcoin is down 0.4% to $105,098.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924806090866250047#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924806090866250047#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SEC DATA BACKS BITCOIN $500K TARGET BY 2028: STANDARD CHARTERED&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Standard Chartered&apos;s Geoff Kendrick says recent SEC 13F filings support a possible rise in Bitcoin to $500,000 by end-2028. While direct ETF holdings dipped in Q1, government entities boosted stakes in Strategy (formerly MicroStrategy), seen as a Bitcoin proxy. This may reflect efforts to gain Bitcoin exposure despite regulatory limits. Bitcoin is down 0.4% to $105,098.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PRESIDENT&apos;S SCHEDULE – TUESDAY, MAY 20, 2025

🔸 7:45 AM – Press pool call time
🔸 8:40 AM – Departs White House for the Capitol
🔸 8:50 AM – Arrives at the Capitol
🔸 9:00 AM – Remarks at House GOP Conference
🔸 9:50 AM – Departs Capitol for the White House
🔸 10:00 AM – Arrives at the White House
🔸 11:55 AM – Joins Take Our Sons and Daughters to Work Day event
🔸 1:00 PM – Press briefing with Karoline Leavitt on the event (on camera)</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924805922032939268#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924805922032939268#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT&apos;S SCHEDULE – TUESDAY, MAY 20, 2025&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 7:45 AM – Press pool call time&lt;br&gt;
🔸 8:40 AM – Departs White House for the Capitol&lt;br&gt;
🔸 8:50 AM – Arrives at the Capitol&lt;br&gt;
🔸 9:00 AM – Remarks at House GOP Conference&lt;br&gt;
🔸 9:50 AM – Departs Capitol for the White House&lt;br&gt;
🔸 10:00 AM – Arrives at the White House&lt;br&gt;
🔸 11:55 AM – Joins Take Our Sons and Daughters to Work Day event&lt;br&gt;
🔸 1:00 PM – Press briefing with Karoline Leavitt on the event (on camera)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KRAKEN: ANNOUNCING LAUNCH OF REGULATED CRYPTO DERIVATIVES IN EUROPE - WEBSITE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924805226546053382#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:31:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924805226546053382#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KRAKEN: ANNOUNCING LAUNCH OF REGULATED CRYPTO DERIVATIVES IN EUROPE - WEBSITE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CANADA APRIL CONSUMER PRICES RISE 1.7% Y/Y; EST. +1.6% 
*CANADA APRIL MEDIAN CPI RISES 3.2% Y/Y; EST. +2.9% 
*CANADA APRIL TRIMMED CPI RISES 3.1% Y/Y; EST. +2.8% 
*CANADA APRIL CORE CPI RISES 2.5% Y/Y; PREV. 2.2%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924805130731348222#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:31:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924805130731348222#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CANADA APRIL CONSUMER PRICES RISE 1.7% Y/Y; EST. +1.6% &lt;br&gt;
*CANADA APRIL MEDIAN CPI RISES 3.2% Y/Y; EST. +2.9% &lt;br&gt;
*CANADA APRIL TRIMMED CPI RISES 3.1% Y/Y; EST. +2.8% &lt;br&gt;
*CANADA APRIL CORE CPI RISES 2.5% Y/Y; PREV. 2.2%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada April CPI +1.7% y/y vs +1.6% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-cpi-17-yy-vs-16-expected-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-cpi-17-yy-vs-16-expected-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-cpi-23-yy-vs-26-expected-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior &lt;/a&gt;month 2.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CPI m/m -0.1% versus -0.2% expected. Prior month +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI m/m +0.5% versus +0.1% last month&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI y/y +2.5% versus 2.2% last month&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CPI Median y/y 3.2% versus 2.9% estimate. Last month 2.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CPI Trim 3.1% versus 2.9% expected Last month 2.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CPI Common 2.5% versus 2.3% last month&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The quirk in Canadian CPI data is that there was a GST (Canada&apos;s VAT) holiday that ended on Feb 15 and that has been reverberating, followed by the removal of the carbon tax on April 1, lowering gasoline prices. That contributed to an 18.1% y/y decline in gasoline prices with natural gas prices down 14.1%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market was pricing in a 65% chance of a BOC rate cut in early June ahead of this data but that&apos;s quickly back to 51%. These core numbers are uncomfortably hot and may represent some trade war pass-thru.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One source of inflation was in food with grocery stores up 3.8% y/y and restaurant prices up 3.6%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD has quickly fallen to 1.3935 from 1.3960 on the headlines.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MIRAN: NO DOUBT OVER INFLATION, INTEREST RATES COMING DOWN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924804655810335076#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:29:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924804655810335076#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MIRAN: NO DOUBT OVER INFLATION, INTEREST RATES COMING DOWN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USD is modestly lower vs the 3 major currency pairs. The AUDUSD is the biggest mover.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-modestly-lower-vs-the-3-major-currency-pairs-the-audusd-is-the-biggest-mover-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:17:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-modestly-lower-vs-the-3-major-currency-pairs-the-audusd-is-the-biggest-mover-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The USD is little changed vs the EUR (-0.05%), JPY (-0.17%), and GBP (-0.06%) to start the US trading session.  The USD is also marginally lower vs the CHF and the CAD.  The biggest move in the US morning snapshot is versus the AUD with the dollar higher vs that currency aftet the RBA cut rates by 25 basis points, but did talk of cutting by 50 basis points. That gave the sellers an incentive to push the pair lower.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN summary, the Reserve Bank of Australia lowered its cash rate target to 3.85% from 4.10%, as expected, citing continued easing in inflation. While headline inflation may temporarily rise due to short-term factors, underlying inflation is forecasted to remain near the midpoint of the 2–3% target range. The RBA acknowledged ongoing global uncertainty stemming from tariff policy shifts and their potential impact on economic activity. Despite signs of recovery in private domestic demand and persistently tight labor market conditions, the Board views inflation risks as more balanced. With inflation now within the target band and upside pressures easing, the Board judged a rate cut appropriate to make policy less restrictive. However, it remains cautious and will closely monitor global and domestic developments to guide future decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RBA Governor Bullock stated that the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reserve Bank of Australia is prepared to take further rate actions if necessary, noting that price increases have slowed. She described the latest move as a confident rate cut and revealed that the Board discussed a range of options, including a 50 basis point or 25 basis point cut, as well as the possibility of holding rates steady. Ultimately, the consensus favored a 25bps cut, which she called the right move for now, although further adjustments remain on the table. Bullock noted that businesses are reporting margin pressures, and while there was some support for a larger 50bps cut, it was not the dominant view. She emphasized that it’s unclear whether this cut will lead to a longer series of reductions and clarified that the RBA does not endorse current market pricing, which anticipates around 55bps of cuts by year-end. Bullock added that if inflation continues to decline, it would create room for additional rate reductions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video above, I take a look at the four currency pairs from a technical perspective to kickstart your trading day in the USD.  What levels are in play and why. Be aware. Be prepared. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other central banker talk:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB&apos;s Klaas Knot stated that the mid-term inflation outlook remains too uncertain to commit to a rate cut in June. While he acknowledged that upcoming ECB projections are likely to show lower inflation for 2025 and 2026, the long-term trajectory of inflation is unclear. This uncertainty is making it difficult to determine the appropriate course of monetary policy at this stage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB&apos;s Isabel Schnabel commented that disinflation remains on track, but new external shocks are complicating the policy outlook. She noted that while tariffs could have a short-term disinflationary effect, they introduce upside inflation risks over the medium term. Schnabel also highlighted that the Euro’s recent appreciation presents a strategic opportunity to strengthen its role as a global currency.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB&apos;s Jose Luis Escrivá emphasized that the global financial environment is being shaped by heightened geopolitical tensions, evolving trade disputes, and increasingly unpredictable policy moves by the U.S. administration. He warned that these dynamics could pose risks to financial system stability. According to some scenarios, while higher tariffs may impact the U.S. more significantly, the Eurozone could also face secondary effects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, BoE’s Huw Pill described his recent vote against an interest rate cut as a &quot;skip&quot; rather than a reversal, emphasizing it was part of a continued, cautious withdrawal of monetary policy tightening. He expressed concern over persistent inflation pressures, noting that the structural changes in wage and price-setting behavior have made inflation in the UK more stubborn. Pill argued that the current pace of quarterly 25 bps cuts, ongoing since last summer, is too aggressive given the risks to price stability and the strength of some pay indicators. While he believes the broader disinflation process remains intact and agrees with the Monetary Policy Committee’s (MPC) overall outlook, he advocated for a more measured approach to rate reductions. He stressed that future cuts should be cautious and not overly reliant on short-term data surprises, especially in a climate where new economic shocks could prolong inflation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks are lower with the futures implying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow Industrial average futures are unchanged versus the close&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index futures are implying a decline of -8.85 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq futures are implying a decline of -53 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the European markets, the major indices are higher at the start of the US session:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German Dax, +.55%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC, +0.63%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE 100, +0.67%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex, +1.52%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB, +0.72&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market, yields are marginally lower. Yesterday, yields moved higher at the start of the day on the back of the Moody&apos;s downgrade, but reversed and closed little changed by the close. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield 3.968%, -1.5 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.068%, -1.4 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year yield 4.469%, -0.6 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year yield 4.939%, -0.1 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil down $0.16 or -0.30% at $61.95&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold is up $6.18 or 0.19% at $3236.41&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin is trading dow, -$527 at $105,085&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian CPI kicks off the agenda</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canadian-cpi-kicks-off-the-agenda-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 12:09:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canadian-cpi-kicks-off-the-agenda-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The RBA cut rate earlier today and the market is sensing that the Bank of Canada will continue to do the same. Their next meeting is June 4 and market pricing is now at 65% for a cut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A big swing in that could come at the bottom of the hour with Canadian inflation data via the CPI report for April. The consensus is for a 0.2% m/m decline on the headline to knock the y/y all the way to 1.6% from 2.3%. What could keep the BOC sidelined is hotter core number with the median measure expected steady at 2.9% and trim forecast to tick up to 2.9% from 2.8%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JAPAN TOP TARIFF NEGOTIATOR AKAZAWA INTENDS TO VISIT US AGAIN LATER THIS MONTH AFTER THIS WEEK&apos;S THIRD US-JAPAN TALKS, KYODO SAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924797125281366520#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:59:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924797125281366520#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JAPAN TOP TARIFF NEGOTIATOR AKAZAWA INTENDS TO VISIT US AGAIN LATER THIS MONTH AFTER THIS WEEK&apos;S THIRD US-JAPAN TALKS, KYODO SAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - MORGAN STANLEY: TESLA’S AUTONOMY PUSH DRIVEN BY RISING CHINA EV THREAT

Morgan Stanley says Tesla’s focus on autonomy is a response to growing competition from Chinese EV makers like Xiaomi, whose new YU7 could match the success of last year’s SU7. The firm believes China may have already won the EV race and warns that U.S. tariffs won’t keep Chinese EVs out of the market.

Tesla’s shift to autonomy reflects the increasing pressure from China’s rapid EV growth, which the firm says is underappreciated by the market. Morgan Stanley maintains an Overweight rating and $410 price target on Tesla.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924793869381554343#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:46:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924793869381554343#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - MORGAN STANLEY: TESLA’S AUTONOMY PUSH DRIVEN BY RISING CHINA EV THREAT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Morgan Stanley says Tesla’s focus on autonomy is a response to growing competition from Chinese EV makers like Xiaomi, whose new YU7 could match the success of last year’s SU7. The firm believes China may have already won the EV race and warns that U.S. tariffs won’t keep Chinese EVs out of the market.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Tesla’s shift to autonomy reflects the increasing pressure from China’s rapid EV growth, which the firm says is underappreciated by the market. Morgan Stanley maintains an Overweight rating and $410 price target on Tesla.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive European FX news wrap: RBA cut rates as expected, AUD falls on 50 bps debate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-rba-cut-rates-as-expected-aud-falls-on-50-bps-debate-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:40:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-rba-cut-rates-as-expected-aud-falls-on-50-bps-debate-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-pboc-reiterates-implementation-of-loose-monetary-policy-20250520/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;The PBoC reiterates implementation of loose monetary policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-current-interest-rates-expectations-for-the-major-central-banks-20250520/&quot;&gt;What are the current interest rates expectations for the major central banks?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-knot-mid-term-inflation-outlook-too-uncertain-to-say-whether-we-need-a-june-cut-20250520/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Knot: Mid-term inflation outlook too uncertain to say whether we need a June cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-pill-we-should-not-be-dependent-on-how-data-turns-out-20250520/&quot;&gt;More from BoE&apos;s Pill: We should not be dependent on how data turns out&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-mulls-accepting-us-tariff-reduction-not-exemption-kyodo-20250520/&quot;&gt;Japan mulls accepting US tariff reduction, not exemption - Kyodo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/irans-supreme-leader-khamenei-i-dont-think-nuclear-talks-with-the-us-will-be-successful-20250520/&quot;&gt;Iran&apos;s Supreme Leader Khamenei: I don&apos;t think nuclear talks with the US will be successful&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-pill-vote-against-interest-rate-cut-was-a-skip-within-a-continuing-withdrawal-20250520/&quot;&gt;BoE&apos;s Pill: Vote against interest rate cut was a &apos;skip&apos; within a continuing withdrawal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/boj-some-members-said-jgb-market-functionality-improving-as-a-trend-due-to-bojs-taper-20250520/&quot;&gt;BoJ: Some members said JGB market functionality improving as a trend due to BoJ&apos;s taper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-schnabel-disinflation-is-on-track-but-new-shocks-are-posing-new-challenges-20250520/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Schnabel: Disinflation is on track, but new shocks are posing new challenges&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-ppi-06-vs-03-mm-expected-20250520/&quot;&gt;Germany April PPI -0.6% vs -0.3% m/m expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-governor-bullock-did-discuss-25-bps-or-50-bps-cut-20250520/&quot;&gt;RBA Governor Bullock: Did discuss 25 bps or 50 bps cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-governor-bullock-must-now-keep-inflation-down-well-placed-to-do-so-20250520/&quot;&gt;RBA Governor Bullock: Must now keep inflation down, well placed to do so&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-lowers-the-cash-rate-target-to-385-vs-410-prior-as-widely-expected-20250520/&quot;&gt;RBA lowers the cash rate target to 3.85% vs 4.10% prior as widely expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been another light session in terms of data and news releases. The only highlight was the RBA policy decision where the central bank cut interest rates by 25 bps as expected and lowered growth and inflation forecasts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AUD fell initially on the dovish forecasts but eventually bounced back. The Aussie dollar couldn&apos;t sustain the pressure though after RBA&apos;s Governor Bullock mentioned that they debated between a 25 and 50 bps cut. That sent the AUD to new lows and the market increased the easing expectations for 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, we got some ECB speakers that are now starting to change their tone around the need for further cuts. The hawks are particularly wary of overdoing it on rate cuts and not reach their inflation target on a sustained basis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we have the Canadian CPI 
report where the Trimmed Mean Y/Y is expected at 2.9% vs. 2.8% prior and
 the Median Y/Y is seen at 2.9% vs. 2.9% prior. The market is pricing a 
62% chance of a 25 bps cut at the upcoming meeting and a total of 47 bps
 of easing by year-end. A higher than expected reading could see the 
market price out a rate cut at the upcoming meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We
 will also have some more Fedspeak and the focus will be on potential 
hawkish comments as the market is now back at pricing just two rate cuts
 in 2025. From now on, we will either price in more cuts or less cuts 
than expected and that will move markets.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PBoC reiterates implementation of loose monetary policy</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-pboc-reiterates-implementation-of-loose-monetary-policy-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:30:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-pboc-reiterates-implementation-of-loose-monetary-policy-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will meet real economy&apos;s financing needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will maintain reason growth of financial aggregates.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will increase efforts to support sci-tech innovation, boost consumption.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will support private economy, stabilise foreign trade.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will made good use of existing and incremental policies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will strengthen monetary policy implmentation and transmission.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will promote international use of yuan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will &apos;resolutely&apos; safeguard national financial security.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t see anything new here. We got some rate cuts recently and that certainly gives some support to the economy, but I would like them to go bigger on rate cuts given that they still have positive real rates amid deflationary forces.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PBOC GOVERNOR PAN: CHINA WILL PROMOTE INTERNATIONAL USE OF YUAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924789628629831904#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:29:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924789628629831904#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PBOC GOVERNOR PAN: CHINA WILL PROMOTE INTERNATIONAL USE OF YUAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUSSIAN FOREIGN MINISTRY: RUSSIA IS READY TO CONTINUE TALKS WITH UKRAINE, NOW IT&apos;S UP TO KYIV TO DECIDE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924784825170366764#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:10:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924784825170366764#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUSSIAN FOREIGN MINISTRY: RUSSIA IS READY TO CONTINUE TALKS WITH UKRAINE, NOW IT&apos;S UP TO KYIV TO DECIDE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HEALTH SECRETARY KENNEDY JR. TELLS FOX: BEEN IN CONTACT WITH LIKE-MINDED COUNTRIES TO CONSIDER JOINING US (IN LEAVING WHO)</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924781149986885674#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:56:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924781149986885674#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HEALTH SECRETARY KENNEDY JR. TELLS FOX: BEEN IN CONTACT WITH LIKE-MINDED COUNTRIES TO CONSIDER JOINING US (IN LEAVING WHO)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WELLS FARGO: BUY U.S. STOCKS, AVOID EMERGING MARKETS

Wells Fargo advises investors to reduce emerging market (EM) stock holdings, despite recent gains, citing weak long-term performance and structural risks like political instability and China’s economic issues.

The firm sees U.S. and developed market equities as more stable alternatives and recommends reallocating to U.S. large- and mid-cap stocks. For risk reduction, it suggests commodities or select fixed-income assets.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924779329717715293#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:48:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924779329717715293#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WELLS FARGO: BUY U.S. STOCKS, AVOID EMERGING MARKETS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Wells Fargo advises investors to reduce emerging market (EM) stock holdings, despite recent gains, citing weak long-term performance and structural risks like political instability and China’s economic issues.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The firm sees U.S. and developed market equities as more stable alternatives and recommends reallocating to U.S. large- and mid-cap stocks. For risk reduction, it suggests commodities or select fixed-income assets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S TAIWAN AFFAIRS OFFICE, ON TAIWAN PRESIDENT&apos;S REMARKS: NO MATTER WHAT TAIWAN LEADER SAYS, WON&apos;T CHANGE &apos;FACT THAT TAIWAN IS PART OF CHINA&apos;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924778906231423475#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:47:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924778906231423475#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S TAIWAN AFFAIRS OFFICE, ON TAIWAN PRESIDENT&apos;S REMARKS: NO MATTER WHAT TAIWAN LEADER SAYS, WON&apos;T CHANGE &apos;FACT THAT TAIWAN IS PART OF CHINA&apos;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the current interest rates expectations for the major central banks?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-current-interest-rates-expectations-for-the-major-central-banks-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:38:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-current-interest-rates-expectations-for-the-major-central-banks-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 54 bps (91% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 52 bps (93% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 45 bps (84% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 47 bps (64% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 73 bps (56% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 58 bps (82% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 47 bps (81% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;*for the SNB, the rest of the probability is for a 50 bps cut&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 17 bps (98% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pricing remained roughly unchanged for most central banks except the RBA where we saw a more dovish repricing after Governor Bullock&apos;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-governor-bullock-did-discuss-25-bps-or-50-bps-cut-20250520/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;50 bps comment&lt;/a&gt; today (it was 57 bps before that comment).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are now at a point where the market got back to previous expectations and from now on we will need stronger reasons to price out the rate cuts. That will obviously move the markets. Of course the same is true for pricing in more rate cuts than currently expected.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JAPAN&apos;S 30-YEAR YIELD CLIMBS TO HIGHEST ON RECORD</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924776340475002955#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:36:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924776340475002955#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JAPAN&apos;S 30-YEAR YIELD CLIMBS TO HIGHEST ON RECORD&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *SOUTH AFRICA TO OFFER MUSK STARLINK DEAL BEFORE TRUMP MEETING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924776213815447975#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:36:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924776213815447975#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*SOUTH AFRICA TO OFFER MUSK STARLINK DEAL BEFORE TRUMP MEETING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Knot: Mid-term inflation outlook too uncertain to say whether we need a June cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-knot-mid-term-inflation-outlook-too-uncertain-to-say-whether-we-need-a-june-cut-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:04:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-knot-mid-term-inflation-outlook-too-uncertain-to-say-whether-we-need-a-june-cut-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mid-term inflation outlook too uncertain to say whether we need a June cut.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB projections likely to show lower inflation this year and the next, but longer term is uncertain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I personally think the ECB shouldn&apos;t cut in June and pause now to see how things evolve. There&apos;s a scenario where they might have already over-eased and could struggle to bring inflation sustainably back to target.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More from BoE&apos;s Pill: We should not be dependent on how data turns out</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-pill-we-should-not-be-dependent-on-how-data-turns-out-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-pill-we-should-not-be-dependent-on-how-data-turns-out-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We should not be dependent on how data turns out.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We can&apos;t assume that inflation pain of new economic shocks will go away.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I agree with the MPC view that there is an easing in the labour market, question is about the pace.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some key pay indicators remain quite strong.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think he&apos;s suggesting that central bankers need to also have some forward looking thinking and not get too fixated on lagging indicators like inflation and employment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan mulls accepting US tariff reduction, not exemption - Kyodo</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-mulls-accepting-us-tariff-reduction-not-exemption-kyodo-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-mulls-accepting-us-tariff-reduction-not-exemption-kyodo-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan mulls accepting US tariff reduction, not exemption.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kyodo News is reporting the Japan is considering accepting a reduction in tariffs and not pushing too much for exemptions. The aim is to break through the stagnation in US-Japan trade talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan&apos;s top trade negotiator, Ryosei Akazawa, could travel to Washington
 as soon as next week for a third round of trade talks with the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;a href=&quot;https://nordot.app/1297480276588232924&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for the article&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran&apos;s Supreme Leader Khamenei: I don&apos;t think nuclear talks with the US will be successful</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/irans-supreme-leader-khamenei-i-dont-think-nuclear-talks-with-the-us-will-be-successful-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:09:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/irans-supreme-leader-khamenei-i-dont-think-nuclear-talks-with-the-us-will-be-successful-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;I don&apos;t think nuclear talks with the US will be successful.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US demand that Iran stops enrichment is outrageous.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The US should avoid talking nonsense in talks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This headline gave crude oil prices a boost as the markets continue to bounce around amid the US-Iran nuclear deal. A positive resolution is seen as bearish (at least in the near term) due to higher supply expectations. Conversely, negative outcomes are seen as bullish.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoE&apos;s Pill: Vote against interest rate cut was a &apos;skip&apos; within a continuing withdrawal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-pill-vote-against-interest-rate-cut-was-a-skip-within-a-continuing-withdrawal-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-pill-vote-against-interest-rate-cut-was-a-skip-within-a-continuing-withdrawal-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vote against interest rate cut was a &apos;skip&apos; within a continuing withdrawal of monetary policy restriction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inflation pressure indicators give me cause for concern.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Quarterly pace of 25 bps cuts seen since last summer is too rapid given the inflation outlook.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;My dissenting vote was favouring a &apos;skip&apos; in the quarterly pattern of bank rate cuts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It should not be seen as favouring a halt to withdrawal of restriction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Structural changes in price and wage setting behaviour have increased the intrinsic persistence of the UK inflation process.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pace of quarterly cuts too rapid given the balance of risks to price stability we face.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Believes that the underlying disinflation process remains intact.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prospective path of bank rate from here is downward.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;My dissent from that decision does not reflect a fundamental difference with the committee majority.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We now need cautious cuts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not new as Pill already mentioned last week that he wants to go more slowly on rate cuts now given the uncertainty. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So much fuss for nothing as US yields erase the downgrade rise</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/so-much-fuss-for-nothing-as-us-yields-erase-the-downgrade-rise-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:22:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/so-much-fuss-for-nothing-as-us-yields-erase-the-downgrade-rise-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There was so much noise over the weekend and yesterday about the Moody&apos;s downgrade with even some doomsday scenarios. I&apos;ve argued (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-30-year-treasury-yield-rises-to-5-for-the-first-time-since-april-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;) that it was no big deal and just a symbolic thing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you look at the US30Y chart now, the market erased the entire rise and we are basically back to where we were before the downgrade. We can now go back to focus on what really matters, which is future Fed policy and inflation expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-wants-lower-interest-rates-but-hes-strategy-is-likely-to-lead-to-higher-rates-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;,
 there&apos;s limited downside at the moment for yields and the path of least
 resistance remains to the upside as inflation risk increases. In fact, 
as we now price in better and better conditions for growth, the economic
 activity will 
likely start to accelerate and that could lead to inflationary 
pressures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fed is also in a difficult position because rate cuts now
 could exacerbate inflation fears and drive long term yields even 
higher. That&apos;s what will drive the bond market in the next months. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices slightly higher at the open as downgrade concerns vaporise</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-slightly-higher-at-the-open-as-downgrade-concerns-vaporise-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-slightly-higher-at-the-open-as-downgrade-concerns-vaporise-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end, the Moody&apos;s downgrade was indeed a nothingburger as expected. As the US session began yesterday, we saw markets reversing across the board and climbing to new highs. We can now go back to focusing on what really matters.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoJ: Some members said JGB market functionality improving as a trend due to BoJ&apos;s taper</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boj-some-members-said-jgb-market-functionality-improving-as-a-trend-due-to-bojs-taper-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:54:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boj-some-members-said-jgb-market-functionality-improving-as-a-trend-due-to-bojs-taper-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some members said JGB market functionality improving as a trend due to BoJ&apos;s taper.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other participants said there is distortion between super-long yields and yields for other maturities due to dwindling liquidity in super-long JGB market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some market participants called for faster pace of BoJ taper from fiscal 2026 though others called for maintaining or slowing pace.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Opinions from market players included those wanting new taper plan to cover about two years, and others saying BoJ should lay out a 1-year plan then maintain that taper level thereafter.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Opinions by market players on monthly BoJ bond buying amount at the end of new taper period ranged from zero, 1-2 trillion yen, and about 3 trillion yen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Opinions by market players included one calling for nimble response to sharp decline in liquidity for super-long JGBs such as termination of taper or increase in BoJ&apos;s purchase amount.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Others said worsening supply-demand for super-long JGBs is due to structural factor such as lack of investor demand, and not something BoJ can fix.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan’s long end yields continue to increase pretty fast, with the 30yr hitting the highest on record after the auction of 20-year bonds got the lowest demand since 2012. Here market participants lay out a few reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Schnabel: Disinflation is on track, but new shocks are posing new challenges</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-schnabel-disinflation-is-on-track-but-new-shocks-are-posing-new-challenges-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:47:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-schnabel-disinflation-is-on-track-but-new-shocks-are-posing-new-challenges-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Disinflation is on track, but new shocks are posing new challenges.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs may be disinflationary in the short run but pose upside risks over the medium term.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Appreciation of the Euro is historical opportunity to foster the international role of the Euro.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s nothing new here but I agree that tariffs are disinflationary in the short term given the negative demand shock but it could indeed pose upside risk on inflation going forward especially if you get the reversal in policies like we&apos;ve seen with Trump and therefore potential pick up in economic activity as uncertainty eases.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:39:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, the main event was the RBA policy decision. The central bank cut interest rates by 25 bps as expected but delivered some dovish messages. The RBA emphasised growth risk caused by trade policies and revised growth and inflation forecasts lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AUD got pushed lower after the release but started to recover most of the losses before RBA&apos;s Govenor Bullock mentioned that they did discuss a 50 bps cut. That pushed the Aussie dollar to new lows before another bounce as the following comments struck a more neutral tone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we have the Canadian CPI report where the Trimmed Mean Y/Y is expected at 2.9% vs. 2.8% prior and the Median Y/Y is seen at 2.9% vs. 2.9% prior. The market is pricing a 62% chance of a 25 bps cut at the upcoming meeting and a total of 47 bps of easing by year-end. A higher than expected reading could see the market put aside a rate cut at the upcoming meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will also have some more Fedspeak and the focus will be on potential hawkish comments as the market is now back at pricing just two rate cuts in 2025. From now on, we will either price in more cuts or less cuts than expected and that will move markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;08:00 GMT/04:00 ET - BoE&apos;s Pill (hawk - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10:00 GMT/06:00 ET - ECB&apos;s Cipollone (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10:00 GMT/06:00 ET - ECB&apos;s Knot (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;13:00 GMT/09:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Bostic (hawk - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;13:00 GMT/09:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Barkin (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;13:30 GMT/09:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Collins (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;17:00 GMT/13:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Musalem (hawk - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;21:00 GMT/17:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Kugler (dove - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;23:00 GMT/19:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Daly (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany April PPI -0.6% vs -0.3% m/m expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-ppi-06-vs-03-mm-expected-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 06:00:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-ppi-06-vs-03-mm-expected-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-march-ppi-07-vs-01-mm-expected-20250417/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior&lt;/a&gt; was -0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;PPI y/y -0.9% vs -0.6% expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lower energy prices were the main reason for the year-on-year decline in
 producer prices in April 2025. By contrast, non-durable and durable 
consumer goods, capital goods and intermediate goods were more expensive
 than in the same month of the previous year. When energy prices are 
excluded, producer prices in April 2025 were up 1.5% on April 2024 and 
increased by 0.4% compared with March 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBA Governor Bullock: Did discuss 25 bps or 50 bps cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-governor-bullock-did-discuss-25-bps-or-50-bps-cut-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:43:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-governor-bullock-did-discuss-25-bps-or-50-bps-cut-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did discuss 25 bps or 50 bps cut.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s more uncertainty than usual.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We would expect consumption to pick up amid rate cuts and falling inflation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;So far so good on inflation and jobs balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Market path for rates reflect risk of really bad global outcome.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not know if there will be long series of cuts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cannot say where the cash rate will end up, does not endorse market pricing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are data driven.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There was an argument for 50 bps, but it was not the strongest argument in the room.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We were blown out of the water by the scope of US tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The comment on the 50 bps is of course what pushed the AUD much lower.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBA Governor Bullock: Must now keep inflation down, well placed to do so</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-governor-bullock-must-now-keep-inflation-down-well-placed-to-do-so-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:33:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-governor-bullock-must-now-keep-inflation-down-well-placed-to-do-so-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must now keep inflation down, well placed to do so.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Board ready to take further action if required.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is a confidence cut in rates.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is the right cut for now, more adjustments are possible.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hearing from businesses that margins are being impacted.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On alert for potential market crises.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At the moment we are not looking at that.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The range of outcomes is quite wide.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It was a consensus decision, discussed holding rates or cutting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 20 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-20-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:30:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-20-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;EUR/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1300 (EUR1.43bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1250 (EUR1.17bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1245 (EUR1.20bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1195
(EUR2.30bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;145.50 (US$1.20bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;145.00
(US$1.12bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;GBP/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3350 (GBP250mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CHF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8325 (CHF585mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.3915
(US$454mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.3900
(US$398mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6350 (AUD367mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;NZD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.5915 (NZD522mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AUD falls on more dovish RBA forecasts</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-aud-falls-on-more-dovish-rba-forecasts-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:03:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-aud-falls-on-more-dovish-rba-forecasts-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The AUD is lower across the board following the RBA decision. The statement was basically the same of what we&apos;ve got in April although there&apos;s more emphasis on trade policies risk. What weighed on the Aussie dollar was the negative revision in growth and inflation forecasts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The forecasts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;GDP growth seen at 1.8% in June 2025, 2.2% in June 2026 and 2.2% in June 2027 (May forecasts)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;GDP growth seen at 2.0% in June 2025, 2.3% in June 2026 and 2.2% in June 2027 (February forecasts)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trimmed Mean Inflation seen at 2.6% in June 2025, 2.6% in June 2026 and 2.6% in June 2027 (May forecasts)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trimmed Mean Inflation seen at 2.7% in June 2025, 2.7% in June 2026 and 2.7% in June 2027 (February forecasts)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, this is no big deal because forecasts can change and the central banks have no conviction on what&apos;s next for policy and so on. My expectation is that we will have a rebound in growth and that would place upward pressure on inflation considering the recent rate cuts and fiscal boosts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Therefore, I would expect the central banks, including the RBA to deliver less rate cuts than currently priced in. So I would fade this reaction in the AUD, especially versus other currencies because I&apos;m still a bit bullish on the USD until further notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can see that we have a nice support zone around the 0.6350 level on AUDUSD. Of course the pair is 80% driven by the USD, so the US macro factors are more influential, but if the sellers manage to extend the pullback, the support zone could be a nice spot where the buyers can look for dip buying opportunities. A break lower though, should open the door for the 0.60 handle next.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBA lowers the cash rate target to 3.85% vs 4.10% prior as widely expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-lowers-the-cash-rate-target-to-385-vs-410-prior-as-widely-expected-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 04:30:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/rba-lowers-the-cash-rate-target-to-385-vs-410-prior-as-widely-expected-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Statement:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Data on inflation for the March quarter
						provided further evidence that inflation continues to ease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staff forecasts released today project that
						while headline inflation is likely to rise over the coming year to around the top of the band as
						temporary factors unwind, underlying inflation is now expected to be around the midpoint of the 2–3 per cent range throughout much of the forecast period.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;While recent announcements on tariffs have resulted in a rebound in
						financial market prices, there is still considerable uncertainty about the final scope of the tariffs and
						policy responses in other countries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These
						developments are expected to have an adverse effect on global economic activity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;World trade policy is
						changing rapidly, thereby making the central forecasts subject to considerable uncertainty.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Private domestic demand appears to have been recovering, real
						household incomes have picked up and there has been an easing in some measures of financial stress&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A range of indicators suggest that labour market conditions remain tight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There are uncertainties about the outlook for domestic economic activity and inflation stemming from both
						domestic and international developments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Board judged that the risks to inflation have become more balanced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inflation is in the target band
						and upside risks appear to have diminished as international developments are expected to weigh on the
						economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;With inflation expected to remain around target, the Board therefore judged that an easing in
						monetary policy at this meeting was appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Board assesses that this move will make monetary
						policy somewhat less restrictive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It nevertheless remains cautious about the outlook&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Board considered a severe
						downside scenario and noted that monetary policy is well placed to respond decisively to international
						developments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Board will be attentive to the data and the evolving assessment of risks to guide its decisions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In
						doing so, it will pay close attention to developments in the global economy and financial markets, trends
						in domestic demand, and the outlook for inflation and the labour market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;To sum up, this is what I anticipated in the &quot;heads up&quot; article. The RBA lowered the cash rate as an acknowledgement of inflation progress but remains cautious on the future outlook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The central bank emphasised the risks around trade policies though and the potential drag on growth. That&apos;s why it has cut growth and inflation forecasts, which is what is weighing on the AUD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RBA forecasts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trimmed Mean Inflation seen at 2.6% in June 2025, 2.6% in June 2026 and 2.6% in June 2027&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;GDP Growth seen at 1.8% in June 2025, 2.2% in June 2026 and 2.2% in June 2027&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Unemployment seen at 4.2% in June 2025, 4.3% in June 2026 and 4.3% in June 2027&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cash rate assumed at 4.0% in June 2025, 3.2% in June 2026 and 3.2% in June 2027&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full statement &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rba.gov.au/media-releases/2025/mr-25-13.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heads up: RBA monetary policy decision coming at the bottom of the hour</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-rba-monetary-policy-decision-coming-at-the-bottom-of-the-hour-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 04:17:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/heads-up-rba-monetary-policy-decision-coming-at-the-bottom-of-the-hour-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Reserve Bank of Australia is expected to cut its cash rate target by 25 bps bringing it to 3.85% vs 4.10% prior. Focus will be on macro forecasts and forward guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the RBA will keep its neutral stance as it lowers the cash rate just as acknowledgement of inflation progress and as an &quot;insurance&quot; for some potential slowdown given the recent economic uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: USD/JPY swings. PBoC cuts. RBA next.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-usdjpy-swings-pboc-cuts-rba-next-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 03:44:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-usdjpy-swings-pboc-cuts-rba-next-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/another-cascade-of-federal-reserve-speakers-due-on-tuesday-20250520/&quot;&gt;Another cascade of Federal Reserve speakers due on Tuesday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-and-japan-are-expected-to-hold-talks-on-friday-may-23-20250520/&quot;&gt;US and Japan are expected to hold talks on Friday, May 23&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-end-march-household-credit-marks-fastest-growth-yy-since-end-june-2022-20250520/&quot;&gt;South Korea end-March household credit marks fastest growth Y/Y since end-June 2022&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-centralbanks-knot-speaking-on-tuesday-and-three-other-ecb-officials-20250520/&quot;&gt;European Central Bank&apos;s Knot speaking on Tuesday (and three other ECB officials)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-england-chief-economist-huw-pill-speaking-tuesday-on-the-monetary-policy-outlook-20250520/&quot;&gt;Bank of England Chief Economist Huw Pill speaking Tuesday on &apos;The monetary policy outlook’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-state-planner-approved-27-fixed-asset-investment-projects-in-january-april-20250520/&quot;&gt;China&apos;s state planner approved 27 fixed asset investment projects in January - April&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-politics-opposition-coalition-splits-nationals-withdraw-20250520/&quot;&gt;Australian politics - Opposition coalition splits. Nationals withdraw.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-us-will-resume-tariff-talks-on-tuesday-aiming-for-july-trade-deal-20250520/&quot;&gt;South Korea, U.S. will resume tariff talks on Tuesday, aiming for July trade deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-hints-at-plans-to-speak-with-bessent-on-fx-this-week-20250520/&quot;&gt;Japan finance minister Kato hints at plans to speak with Bessent on FX this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-mid-point-today-at-71931-vs-estimate-at-72112-20250520/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY mid-point today at 7.1931 (vs. estimate at 7.2112)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-cuts-loan-prime-rates-lprs-by-10bp-for-both-1-and-5-year-loans-20250520/&quot;&gt;PBOC cuts Loan Prime Rates (LPRs) by 10bp for both 1- and 5-year loans&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/akazawa-japan-us-conducted-working-level-talks-on-bilateral-trade-dc-on-monday-20250520/&quot;&gt;Akazawa: Japan, U.S. conducted working-level talks on bilateral trade on Monday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/more-rate-cuts-coming-from-chinese-banks-as-expected-20250520/&quot;&gt;More rate cuts coming from Chinese banks - as expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/25bp-rba-rate-cut-today-is-baked-in-but-heres-what-to-watch-for-in-the-statement-20250519/&quot;&gt;25bp RBA rate cut today is baked in, but here&apos;s what to watch for in the Statement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/ubs-once-again-recommends-a-full-strategic-allocation-to-us-equities-20250519/&quot;&gt;UBS once again recommends &quot;a full strategic allocation&quot; to US equities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-said-the-us-has-undermined-the-consensus-reached-in-geneva-tariff-talks-20250519/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - China said the US has undermined the consensus reached in Geneva tariff talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-discussing-us-trade-deal-structured-in-three-tranches-interim-agreement-before-july-20250519/&quot;&gt;India discussing US trade deal structured in three tranches, interim agreement before July&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-bank-has-cut-its-yuan-deposit-rate-as-expected-20250519/&quot;&gt;Chinese bank has cut its yuan deposit rate, as expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/the-central-bank-to-all-central-banks-warns-of-a-potential-scramble-for-us-dollars-20250519/&quot;&gt;The central bank to all central banks warns of a potential &quot;scramble&quot; for US dollars&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/icymi-nippon-steel-sweetens-us-steel-bid-with-us14bn-investment-pledge-20250519/&quot;&gt;ICYMI: Nippon Steel sweetens U.S. Steel bid with US$14bn investment pledge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/general-motors-to-stop-exporting-vehicles-from-the-us-to-china-20250519/&quot;&gt;General Motors to stop exporting vehicles from the US to China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-19-may-the-fed-is-uncertainmoody-downgrade-fear-subsides-20250519/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 19 May: The Fed is uncertain.Moody downgrade fear subsides&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-to-seek-market-views-on-japanese-government-bond-buying-20250519/&quot;&gt;Bank of Japan to seek market views on Japanese Government Bond buying&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-ecbs-muller-said-must-be-cautious-on-further-rate-cuts-20250519/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - ECB&apos;s Muller said must be cautious on further rate cuts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-chinas-state-banks-are-expected-to-cut-deposit-rates-today-tuesday-china-time-20250519/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - China&apos;s state banks are expected to cut deposit rates today (Tuesday China time)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-stocks-close-marginally-higher-sp-up-for-the-sixth-consecutive-day-20250519/&quot;&gt;US stocks close marginally higher. S&amp;amp;P up for the sixth consecutive day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-tuesday-20-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250519/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Tuesday, 20 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;192&quot; data-end=&quot;364&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;USD/JPY volatility driven by Japan headlines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;192&quot; data-end=&quot;364&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
USD/JPY saw sharp swings during the session, initially jumping above 145.50 before quickly retreating below 144.80.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;365&quot; data-end=&quot;784&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;365&quot; data-end=&quot;567&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;367&quot; data-end=&quot;567&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Japan’s Economy Minister Akazawa said working-level bilateral trade talks took place Monday in Washington. He reiterated Tokyo&apos;s demand for the removal of U.S. tariffs on autos, steel, and aluminum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;568&quot; data-end=&quot;784&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;570&quot; data-end=&quot;784&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Finance Minister Kato followed, signaling openness to discussing FX matters with U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent at this week’s G7 meeting. Kato said he would stress the need to avoid excessive currency volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apart from the yen, major FX was fairly subdued with minor shifts only. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;786&quot; data-end=&quot;995&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;PBoC cuts LPRs by 10bps in measured easing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;786&quot; data-end=&quot;995&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
The People’s Bank of China cut its one- and five-year loan prime rates by 10 basis points to 3.0% and 3.5%, respectively — the first cut since October&apos;s 25bp cut for each. The minor trim today continues the trend of Chinese policy adjustment gradualism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;996&quot; data-end=&quot;1352&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;996&quot; data-end=&quot;1084&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;998&quot; data-end=&quot;1084&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The move follows a 10bp reduction in the 7-day reverse repo rate earlier this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1085&quot; data-end=&quot;1210&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1087&quot; data-end=&quot;1210&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;PBoC Governor Pan Gongsheng had signaled the LPR cuts, calling them a natural consequence of the earlier repo adjustment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1213&quot; data-end=&quot;1352&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;State-owned banks had earlier trimmed time deposit rates, as expected:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;by
5 bps to 0.05%
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
cuts
on one-year time deposits by 15 bps to 0.95%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;

25
bp cuts on three- and five- year time deposits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1354&quot; data-end=&quot;1634&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;US Senate advances landmark crypto legislation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1354&quot; data-end=&quot;1634&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The U.S. Senate voted 66–32 to advance a major cryptocurrency regulatory overhaul. Sixteen Democrats joined most Republicans in backing the procedural motion, opening the door to the chamber’s changes to crypto rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1636&quot; data-end=&quot;1805&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt; In regional equities, a strong debut for CATL in Hong Kong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1636&quot; data-end=&quot;1805&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Chinese EV battery maker CATL surged ~15% in its Hong Kong trading debut, marking the year’s largest regional listing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1807&quot; data-end=&quot;2152&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Australian politics: Coalition split after election rout&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1807&quot; data-end=&quot;2152&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
Australia’s Liberal-National coalition — a conservative partnership spanning 80 years — is set to end. The Nationals’ leader ruled out forming another coalition with the Liberals following a heavy election defeat earlier this month, which saw the Liberal Party leader lose his seat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1807&quot; data-end=&quot;2152&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Stay tuned, the Reserve Bank of Australia is next, due at 0430 GMT / 0030 US Eastern time - the Bank widely expected to cut its cash rate by 25bp. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: COULD BE A TIME WHEN RUSSIA SANCTIONS WILL HAPPEN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924577824523841981#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:28:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924577824523841981#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: COULD BE A TIME WHEN RUSSIA SANCTIONS WILL HAPPEN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
