<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA ADDS TO STATE GOLD RESERVES FOR SIXTH STRAIGHT MONTH</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1920027883851899102#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:08:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1920027883851899102#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA ADDS TO STATE GOLD RESERVES FOR SIXTH STRAIGHT MONTH&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China gold reserves rise for sixth straight month</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-gold-reserves-rise-for-sixth-straight-month-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 08:04:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-gold-reserves-rise-for-sixth-straight-month-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The latest data shows that China&apos;s gold reserves at the end of April were at 73.77 million ounces, up from 73.70 million ounces at the end of March. In value terms, the reserves at the end of April amount to $243.59 billion compared to $229.59 billion at the end of March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s the sixth consecutive month now that the PBOC has been increasing its gold reserves. Just keep swimming, swimming, swimming.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The market could be dead wrong on rate cuts if this scenario plays out</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-could-be-dead-wrong-on-rate-cuts-if-this-scenario-plays-out-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:48:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-could-be-dead-wrong-on-rate-cuts-if-this-scenario-plays-out-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Fed today is expected to keep interest rates steady at 4.25-4.50% and overall maintain a neutral stance given the uncertainty around tariffs and inflation expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market is pricing around 80 bps of easing by year-end
 but Fed Chair Powell could push back against such dovish 
expectations triggering a repricing to around 50 bps, which has been the Fed&apos;s baseline for 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a scenario though where the Fed doesn&apos;t cut at all or delivers just one cut in 2025. The main factor for that scenario revolves around trade negotiations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we get something very positive, like much lower than expected reciprocal tariffs or even free trade deals, there will likely be a strong surge in demand. We&apos;ve been hearing and seeing from the economic reports that business are cautious due to tariff uncertainty and that&apos;s holding back activity. With a positive resolution, economic activity will pick up fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this best case scenario, the Fed could be even more constrained because there will be upward pressure on inflation and the economic data will start to show a strong rebound in activity justifying a cautious approach to rate adjustments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is something to keep in mind because such changes offer great trading opportunities as the market readjusts to new conditions. Contingency planning is an essential part of a trader&apos;s analysis. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany April construction PMI 45.1 vs 40.3 prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-construction-pmi-451-vs-403-prior-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-construction-pmi-451-vs-403-prior-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 40.3&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The downturn in Germany&apos;s construction sector is continuing to ease, with improvements seen across all sectors at least. The pace of declines in overall activity and new orders were much slower, so that&apos;s at least a positive takeaway despite the continued struggle.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reaffirms that its position on talks has not changed</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-reaffirms-that-its-position-on-talks-has-not-changed-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:26:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-reaffirms-that-its-position-on-talks-has-not-changed-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;They are saying that if the US wants a deal, then they would have to stop threatening China. These are all fighting words but the bottom line is that we are at least taking a step towards de-escalation as both sides are set to sit down for initial talks. However, whether or not that step eventually leads to something is a separate issue though.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How China has been preparing itself ahead of this tariffs eventuality with the US</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-china-has-been-preparing-itself-ahead-of-this-tariffs-eventuality-with-the-us-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:21:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-china-has-been-preparing-itself-ahead-of-this-tariffs-eventuality-with-the-us-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Back in December last year, we already saw how Beijing opted for the Chinese yuan as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/is-this-beijings-first-line-of-defense-against-trump-20241203/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;its first line of defense&lt;/a&gt; in the trade war against the US. But since then, they&apos;ve also been taking other measures in safeguarding its interests. One of the more common trade practices to circumvent tariffs has been to resort to origin washing. And that is precisely what China has been actively pursuing since the turn of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The idea here is to redirect goods originally manufactured for the US market by pushing them to another port before being redirected again to finally arrive in the US. The most common workaround by China has been to export these goods to Southeast Asia as such.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It comes as no surprise then as Xi Jinping chose the likes of Vietnam and Malaysia as two key countries to visit during his international tour. But Thailand is also another popular destination for this so-called origin washing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And from the data by the Chinese customs, it is quite clear that this is taking place. There has been a spike in exports to Southeast Asia since the turn of the year already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As China looks to prepare itself for trade talks with the US, it has also been stealthily making other moves on the chess board. This is just something to take note of.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethereum Futures Analysis. Breakout May Happen Soon!</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/ethereum-futures-breakout-may-happen-soon-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:19:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/ethereum-futures-breakout-may-happen-soon-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Ethereum Futures (Micro ETH - MET) Analysis for May 7, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethereum futures have been consolidating within a clearly defined range over the past few days, bounded by key price levels established earlier in the month. Since May 1 and May 2, we&apos;ve seen Ethereum trade predominantly between the lower boundary set around $1780 and an upper limit near $1866.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent trading sessions (May 5-7) initially showed mixed signals. Earlier, selling pressure emerged notably, pushing prices lower, but buyer participation increased sharply thereafter, indicating that the market sees current levels as attractive. The midpoint around $1815, identified as a key point of control (POC)—an area where most trading occurred—has repeatedly acted as a pivotal zone. Initially serving as resistance, this level has gradually transformed into support, highlighting the subtle bullish shift underway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zooming into today&apos;s shorter-term action, Ethereum futures experienced initial bearishness in early hours, but importantly, this was short-lived. Buyer momentum swiftly reasserted itself, significantly turning market sentiment bullish, as seen by rising volumes and increasingly positive trading activity at recent lows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the way, as a side note, Ethereum Foundation is also working on improving things. This is the plan for the next year...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding our analysis method with orderFlow Intel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Order flow intelligence examines real-time buying and selling pressure, analyzing how aggressive traders are at specific price levels. It goes beyond traditional price charts by providing insights into actual market participation—revealing the strength of buyers or sellers at critical moments. By monitoring metrics such as the buying pressure since recent price lows (Delta since lows), Order Flow Intel helps traders anticipate price movements before they&apos;re clearly visible on regular charts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current Market Insights for Eth Futures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s order flow suggests a clear shift toward bullishness. The early bearish sentiment encountered substantial buyer support quickly, indicating potential institutional or larger traders stepping in. This reversal hints at increased likelihood that Ethereum futures may now target the upper part of the established range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Levels to Watch for Eth Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish Threshold: The upper boundary around $1866 remains a critical area. Traders and investors should closely watch if Ethereum prices decisively break above this level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immediate Support Level: Around $1828-$1830. Holding above this level keeps the short-term bullish view intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trader and Investor Guidance on Ethereum&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish Scenario: Investors and traders might look for confirmation of bullish strength through two consecutive 30-minute candle closes above the $1866 level. Such sustained moves suggest genuine buyer strength and reduce the probability of a fake breakout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearish Scenario: Alternatively, failure to sustain price action above the midpoint ($1815) and notably below immediate support ($1828-$1830) could signal renewed selling pressure, suggesting a retest of lower support levels near $1780.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Confirmation beyond the key levels above? You can grab some guidance from this potential bull flag (not activated yet)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Summary: Early Signs of strengthened bullish bias for ETH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current order flow analysis indicates a strengthening bullish bias for Ethereum futures, supported by recent buyer-driven market activity. Investors and traders should carefully observe price reactions near the critical $1866 threshold to confirm a genuine breakout opportunity. Sustained trading above this level, marked by consecutive 30-minute candle closes, could open further upside potential, whereas failure could suggest continued range-bound conditions or renewed downside risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not financial advice. Do your own research. Trade at your own risk. Always consider your individual strategy and risk tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says meeting with the US on trade is at the US&apos; request</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-meeting-with-the-us-on-trade-is-at-the-us-request-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:16:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-meeting-with-the-us-on-trade-is-at-the-us-request-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have always been open to dialogue with the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will safeguard our interests in talks with the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Egos aside, it is still a positive development no matter who decided to take the first step to engage. The question though is, will it eventually lead to anything? As much as this first step in agreeing to talk is vital, it&apos;s another thing to expect any quick resolution to the current situation. I would expect talks to drag on for quite a while but will there be scope to lower the 145% tariffs in the meantime?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equities lightly lower to start the session</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-lightly-lower-to-start-the-session-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:14:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-lightly-lower-to-start-the-session-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 -0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;German stocks were the highlight yesterday as it did recover with Merz securing the chancellor seat in the second time of asking. But looking to the overall mood today, things are looking fairly tentative. And that comes despite some enthusiasm in US futures, though somewhat more limited compared to earlier in the day. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are up 0.4% on hopeful optimism of US-China trade talks but the gains have been more than halved since the headlines crossed some nine hours ago.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDJPY Technical Analysis – Will the Fed push back against the dovish pricing?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-will-the-fed-push-back-against-the-dovish-pricing-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 07:09:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-will-the-fed-push-back-against-the-dovish-pricing-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD came under pressure
again this week as some disappointing headlines on the tariffs front hit the
sentiment. The de-escalation continues though and tonight we got the news that
the US and Chinese representatives will meet in Switzerland in the coming days
to start engaging in discussions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, we also have the
FOMC policy decision where the Fed is expected to keep interest rates unchanged
and could push back against the dovish market pricing giving the greenback a boost
in the short term. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the JPY side, the
currency has been driven mainly by global events rather than domestic
fundamentals. Alongside the Swiss Franc, it’s been the favoured safe haven in
the currencies space amid the swings in risk sentiment. On the monetary policy
front, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;BoJ&lt;/a&gt; kept interest rates unchanged as expected and
delivered a dovish message. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was then echoed by BoJ
Governor Ueda which placed a great deal on trade developments. In summary, the
central bank is likely to go faster on rate hikes in case we get a good trade
deal and delay rate adjustments in case the trade deal disappoints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that USDJPY erased most of last week’s gains in the past couple of days and
threatens to extend the bearish move into the 140.00 handle. From a risk
management perspective though, the sellers will have a better risk to reward
setup around the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt; to position for further
downside, while the buyers will look for a break higher to increase the bullish
bets into the 151.00 handle next. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see that we broke below the strong &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-support-and-resistance-20220405/&quot;&gt;support&lt;/a&gt; zone around the 144.00 handle where we had
also the upward minor trendline for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-confluence-20220318/&quot;&gt;confluence&lt;/a&gt;. The sellers piled in with more
conviction on the break to target the 142.00 handle next. The buyers, on the
other hand, will likely step in around the 142.00 handle to position for a
rally back into new highs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor downward trendline defining the bearish momentum on
this timeframe. The sellers will likely continue to lean on the trendline to
keep pushing into new lows, while the buyers will look for a break higher to pile
in for a rally into the major trendline. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we have the FOMC Rate Decision. Tomorrow, we get the
latest US Jobless Claims figures. On Friday, we conclude the week with the
Japanese wage data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France March trade balance -€6.25 billion vs -€7.87 billion prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-march-trade-balance-625-billion-vs-787-billion-prior-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:45:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-march-trade-balance-625-billion-vs-787-billion-prior-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -€7.87 billion; revised to -€7.70 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The French trade deficit narrowed in March as exports grew by 5.6% on the month while imports only grew by 2.3% on the month.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:20:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, we have a few low tier releases and the Eurozone Retail Sales report, but it&apos;s unlikely to see the market reacting to the data given that it won&apos;t change anything in terms of expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we&apos;ll have the main event of the day, which is the FOMC Policy Announcement. The central bank is expected to keep interest rates steady at 4.25-4.50% and maintain a neutral stance given the uncertainty around tariffs and inflation expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it wasn&apos;t for the market&apos;s expectations, I would have expected this decision to be a non-event, but there&apos;s some room for disappointment here. In fact, the market is pricing around 80 bps of easing by year-end and Fed Chair Powell will likely push back against such dovish expectations triggering a repricing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, the focus remains on tariff news as we continue to await the announcement of the first trade deal expected by the end of this week or Monday at the latest. Trump said that they will have a very big and very positive announcement before the Middle East trip which could come on Thursday, Friday or Monday. It could be about tariffs, so worth to keep an eye on that. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +0.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:07:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;French CAC 40 futures flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The more enthusiastic news involving US and China is being contained as we look towards the start of European trading at least. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures have also halved gains to be up just 0.5% currently. Meanwhile, the dollar has also pared the majority of its gains on the day. EUR/USD is now flat at 1.1363 with GBP/USD likewise at 1.3356. USD/JPY is still holding up though, seen at 143.05 - up 0.4% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany March industrial orders +3.6% vs +1.3% m/m expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-march-industrial-orders-36-vs-13-mm-expected-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 06:00:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-march-industrial-orders-36-vs-13-mm-expected-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 0.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There were increases across the board with orders for capital goods (+3.7%), intermediate goods (+2.5%), and consumer goods (+8.7%) all seen higher on the month. Even if you strip out large orders, new orders were 3.2% higher compared to February.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 7 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-7-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 05:26:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-7-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There aren&apos;t any major expiries to take note of on the day. As things stand, trade headlines remain the biggest driver of price action and we got a taste of that earlier with some positive news on US-China talks. That is keeping the risk mood underpinned with the dollar also catching a slight bid across the board. The gains for the greenback have eased back a little but as things stand, headline risks and risk sentiment are still the two key drivers to pay attention to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As for the expiries, there will be bigger fish to fry in the days ahead. But we&apos;ll see if they will factor into play depending on how price action plays out in the sessions ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China president Xi: We must firmly maintain post-war international order</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-we-must-firmly-maintain-post-war-international-order-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 05:01:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-we-must-firmly-maintain-post-war-international-order-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China, Russia have always firmly supported each other&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Should jointly resist any attempt to disrupt the friendship and mutual trust&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;China, Russia are both major powers with important influence in maintaining global strategic stability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No matter how the situation in Taiwan changes, China will eventually &apos;reunify&apos; with Taiwan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, speak of the devil. Reminder: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/reminder-china-president-xi-to-visit-moscow-later-today-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;China president Xi to visit Moscow later today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Xi might be in Moscow to offer his support to Putin against the West. But as mentioned, the solidarity on the military front is also one that strikes back home. And Xi is making that clear with the warning about Taiwan above again.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reminder: China president Xi to visit Moscow later today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/reminder-china-president-xi-to-visit-moscow-later-today-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 04:59:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/reminder-china-president-xi-to-visit-moscow-later-today-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s no doubt a symbolic show of support for Putin with Xi set to also attend a parade on Friday, one that commemorates the 80th anniversary of the World War II victory over Germany by Russia and its allies. The solidarity on the military front will also strike back home, with Taiwan and Vietnam in particular also watching closely as Beijing is concocting its own plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But perhaps there&apos;s also another thing on the agenda here. And that is the show of camaraderie in fighting back against the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Xi&apos;s visit no doubt comes at an interesting time now with US and China preparing for an early round of talks to take stock on trade later this weekend. Markets are hoping for de-escalation but China&apos;s posturing will depend a lot on how Xi wants to play this out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, be watchful of comments from the Chinese president during his time in Russia as well over the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk holds up on hopes for US-China de-escalation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/risk-holds-up-on-hopes-for-us-china-de-escalation-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 04:39:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/risk-holds-up-on-hopes-for-us-china-de-escalation-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/sources-say-us-bessent-and-greer-to-meet-with-china-rep-on-economic-matters-this-week-20250506/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;US&apos; Bessent and Greer to meet with China rep on Economic Matters this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-with-juicy-china-trade-talk-details-well-decide-what-we-are-going-to-talk-about-20250506/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Bessent with juicy China trade talk details - we&apos;ll decide what we are going to talk about&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-s-ministry-of-commerce-says-is-has-decided-to-agree-to-engage-with-the-us-20250506/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China&apos; s Ministry of Commerce says is has &quot;decided to agree to engage with the US&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-confirms-vice-premier-he-lifeng-to-talk-trade-with-bessent-this-week-20250506/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China confirms Vice Premier He Lifeng to talk trade with Bessent this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are now up 0.6%, getting a shot in the arm from the headlines above. China then doubled down to bolster risk sentiment further in Asia trading, by delivering a host of supportive measures including a slew of rate cuts. Eamonn&apos;s got the summary on that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboccsrc-china-supportive-measures-in-summary-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; before adding one more to the relending rate &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/pboc-to-also-cut-relending-rate-by-25-bps-to-150-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For now, hope springs eternal. There is good chance for de-escalation but what does that really mean is a separate discussion. But market players are taking on a more optimistic side for the time being. Buy the rumour, as one would put it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But as a reminder, the bar is set relatively low. At 145% tariffs currently, any step down to allow for some trade to be facilitated instead of no trade at all is an improvement. However, if we do move to 50-60% tariffs, it&apos;s still a major hit to both economies. But at least, there are signs of trying to work something out I guess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Come what may, the end goal is basically what markets have to really consider ultimately. If it is moving towards de-escalation and slow removal of tariffs or a much lower level, then sure there is something to be cheerful about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But if the base case is for higher tariffs in general i.e. Trump hoodwinking the world into forcing tariffs on everyone, I think that&apos;s a consequence towards the global economy that markets have yet to really price in. But for now, baby steps.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC to also cut relending rate by 25 bps to 1.50%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/pboc-to-also-cut-relending-rate-by-25-bps-to-150-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 04:10:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/pboc-to-also-cut-relending-rate-by-25-bps-to-150-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This adds to the slew of rate cuts and other measures from earlier. In case you missed it, Eamonn&apos;s got you covered &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-1-uschina-to-meet-on-trade-2-china-rate-cuts-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The relending facility is one that is mainly used to bolster the stock market, allowing for low-cost funding for specific purposes such as share buybacks and shareholding increases by firms.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: 1. US/China to meet on trade &amp; 2. China rate cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-1-uschina-to-meet-on-trade-2-china-rate-cuts-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 03:38:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-1-uschina-to-meet-on-trade-2-china-rate-cuts-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;US/China trade talks to begin:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/sources-say-us-bessent-and-greer-to-meet-with-china-rep-on-economic-matters-this-week-20250506/&quot;&gt; US&apos; Bessent and Greer to meet with China rep on Economic Matters this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-with-juicy-china-trade-talk-details-well-decide-what-we-are-going-to-talk-about-20250506/&quot;&gt;Bessent with juicy China trade talk details - we&apos;ll decide what we are going to talk about&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-s-ministry-of-commerce-says-is-has-decided-to-agree-to-engage-with-the-us-20250506/&quot;&gt;China&apos; s Ministry of Commerce says is has &quot;decided to agree to engage with the US&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-confirms-vice-premier-he-lifeng-to-talk-trade-with-bessent-this-week-20250506/&quot;&gt;China confirms Vice Premier He Lifeng to talk trade with Bessent this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC rate cuts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboccsrc-china-supportive-measures-in-summary-20250507/&quot;&gt;PBOC/CSRC China supportive measures - in summary&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-unlocks-more-insurance-capital-for-stocks-signals-property-support-20250507/&quot;&gt;China unlocks more insurance capital for stocks, signals property support&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-to-cut-standing-lending-facility-rate-by-10bp-20250507/&quot;&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China to cut Standing Lending Facility rate by 10bp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-promises-more-local-stock-market-support-from-sovereign-fund-20250507/&quot;&gt;China promises more local stock market support from sovereign fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-willhelpa-sharelistedcompaniesaffectedbytariffstocopewithdifficulties-20250507/&quot;&gt;China will help A-share listed companies affected by tariffs to cope with difficulties&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-says-will-lower-interest-rates-on-structural-policy-tools-by-25-bps-20250507/&quot;&gt;PBOC governor says will lower interest rates on structural policy tools by 25 bps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-sets-7-day-reverse-repo-rate-at-14-20250507/&quot;&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China sets 7-day reverse repo rate at 1.4% (from 1.5% previously)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-rate-cuts-7-day-rr-to-14-from-15-lpr-10bp-cut-also-rrr-50-bp-cut-20250507/&quot;&gt;PBOC rate cuts: 7-day RR to 1.4% (from 1.5%), LPR 10bp cut also, RRR 50 bp cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-72005-vs-estimate-at-72124-20250507/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.2005 (vs. estimate at 7.2124)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-pan-says-world-is-full-or-uncertainties-20250507/&quot;&gt;PBOC Governor Pan says world is full of uncertainties - cuts rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-has-been-slammed-lower-under-us3670-20250507/&quot;&gt;Gold has been slammed lower, under US$3370&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-expected-to-announce-the-us-will-refer-to-the-persian-gulf-as-the-arabian-gulf-20250507/&quot;&gt;Trump expected to announce the US will refer to the Persian Gulf as the &quot;Arabian Gulf&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-santos-ceo-says-over-200-wells-underwater-due-to-floods-in-cooper-basin-20250507/&quot;&gt;Australia - Santos CEO says over 200 wells underwater due to floods in Cooper Basin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-jibun-sp-global-services-pmi-for-april-524-flash-was-522-prior-500-20250507/&quot;&gt;Japan Jibun / S&amp;amp;P Global Services PMI for April 52.4 (flash was 52.2, prior 50.0)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-may-deport-people-to-libya-20250507/&quot;&gt;US may deport people to Libya&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/new-hampshire-governor-signs-crypto-reserve-bill-into-law-20250506/&quot;&gt;New Hampshire governor signs crypto reserve bill into law&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-us-uk-trade-talks-make-some-progress-on-steel-autos-but-deal-timing-still-unclear-20250506/&quot;&gt;ICYMI: US-UK trade talks make some progress on steel, autos, but deal timing still unclear&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/wsj-reports-us-orders-intelligence-agencies-to-step-up-spying-on-greenland-20250506/&quot;&gt;WSJ reports &quot;U.S. Orders Intelligence Agencies to Step Up Spying on Greenland&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-employment-report-unemployment-rate-51-vs-53-expected-20250506/&quot;&gt;New Zealand employment report, Unemployment rate 5.1% vs. 5.3% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japanese-media-reports-that-fujifilm-will-build-a-semiconductor-materials-factory-in-india-20250506/&quot;&gt;Japanese media reports that Fujifilm will build a semiconductor materials factory in India&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/58-wallets-made-over-10-million-each-from-trumps-meme-coin-vs-764000-wallets-that-lost-20250506/&quot;&gt;58 wallets made over $10 million each from Trump&apos;s meme coin vs. 764,000 wallets that lost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rbnz-says-riskstothefinancialsystemhaveincreasedoverthepastsixmonths-20250506/&quot;&gt;RBNZ says risks to the financial system have increased over the past six months&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;India/Pakistan conflict:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/reports-on-intense-shelling-between-indian-and-pakistani-troops-at-3-frontier-locations-20250506/&quot;&gt;Reports on intense shelling between Indian and Pakistani troops at 3 frontier locations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/india-launches-missile-strikes-on-alleged-terror-camps-in-pakistan-20250506/&quot;&gt;India Launches Missile Strikes on Alleged Terror Camps in Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-us-dollar-slumps-as-trade-deals-remain-stuck-20250506/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: US dollar slumps as trade deals remain stuck&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-private-survey-of-inventory-shows-headline-crude-oil-draw-larger-than-expected-20250506/&quot;&gt;Oil: private survey of inventory shows headline crude oil draw larger than expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-closes-lower-for-the-second-consecutive-day-20250506/&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P closes lower for the second consecutive day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-wednesday-7-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250506/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Wednesday, 7 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
It was an eventful day in Asia today with two nuclear powers
exchanging fire, a beginning to US/China talks scheduled, and rate
cuts/further supportive measures from the People’s Bank of China
and other Chinese authorities. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FX rates swing
around in response, as did gold and equities. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;India-Pakistan
tensions escalate after cross-border strikes. India and Pakistan are both nuclear powers.

India carried
out strikes on nine sites in Pakistan and Pakistan-administered
Kashmir early Wednesday, describing the taregts as “terrorist
infrastructure” used to plan and direct attacks. Indian authorities
stressed the operation was “focused, measured, and non-escalatory,”
adding that no Pakistani military assets were hit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pakistan responded
with artillery, resulting in both sides exchanging heavy fire along
the Line of Control that separates Pakistan-administered Kashmir from
Indian-administered Kashmir&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
India’s strikes follow
weeks of intensifying hostilities after a deadly assault in the town
of Pahalgam on April 22, where 26 civilians — mostly Hindu men —
were killed by militants. It was the worst attack on civilians in the
region in 20 years.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. and China to
(finally) begin high-level trade talks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;

The United States
and China will hold formal trade negotiations this weekend in Geneva,
their first high-level engagement since the eruption of a fresh
tariff-driven trade conflict. China’s Ministry of Commerce
confirmed Vice Premier He Lifeng will meet with U.S. Treasury
Secretary Scott Bessent and U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer,
in what both sides are framing as a critical effort to de-escalate
tensions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Treasury Secretary Bessent said the talks aim to
address &quot;shared interests&quot; and called current tariff levels
“unsustainable,” while rejecting the notion of decoupling. “What
we want is fair trade,” he said, noting that the world has been
engaging with the U.S., but “China has been the missing piece.”
The USTR added that Greer will engage directly with his Chinese
counterpart to discuss paths forward on trade.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
China, for
its part, said it agreed to the meeting after “repeated” outreach
from Washington and following consultations with its domestic
stakeholders. The Commerce Ministry emphasised that the talks must be
conducted on equal footing and warned it would not tolerate coercion
or double-dealing. The ministry also expressed concern that other
nations in ongoing trade discussions with the U.S. might coordinate
tariff measures against China, adding a strategic layer to Beijing’s
decision to engage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bessent tempered
expectations, saying that the two sides have agreed to talk. The plan
is that on  Saturday and Sunday, we’ll agree on what we’re going
to talk about. Bessent added that this initial meeting will be about
de-escalation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China rate cuts &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Then it was over to China, where a joint briefing by officials from the
People’s Bank of China, the National Financial Regulatory
Administration and the China Securities Regulatory Commission. The
officials included PBOC Governor Pan. 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I
posted a bit of a summary of the measures, repeating that here, but
there is more detail in the posts above. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Equity
Market Stabilisation:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	Central
	Huijin, along with the PBOC, will step in as a quasi-stabilisation
	fund to help maintain stock market confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	An
	additional 60 billion yuan (US$8.3 billion) from long-term insurance
	funds will be channelled into equities under an expanded pilot
	program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Targeted
Liquidity and Credit Support:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	RMB
	300 billion in new re-lending funds will be allocated to support
	technological innovation and industrial upgrades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	A
	new RMB 500 billion re-lending facility will be introduced to
	finance elderly care infrastructure and broader service consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	The
	People’s Bank of China (PBOC) will expand the quota for capital
	market support tools to RMB 800 billion to deepen market-based
	financing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	A
	new risk-sharing mechanism will be established to back technology
	innovation bonds, improving credit support for strategic sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Monetary
Tools and Interest Rate Adjustments from the People&apos;s Bank of China:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	The
	Reserve Requirement Ratio (RRR) will be lowered by 0.5 percentage
	points to boost banking system liquidity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	A
	temporary cut in the reserve ratio for auto finance and leasing
	firms will bring it down from 5% to 0%, aiming to ease
	sector-specific funding constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	The
	7-day Reverse Repo rate, a key short-term policy rate, will be
	trimmed by 10 basis points to 1.4%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	The
	structural monetary policy rate will be reduced by 25 basis points
	to support targeted credit expansion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	Interest
	rates on individual housing provident fund loans will be lowered by
	0.25 percentage points to reduce mortgage borrowing costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	The
	Standing Lending Facility (SLF) rate will be cut by 10 basis points,
	further easing interbank lending conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold
continued its Tuesday swing higher, getting to above US$3430. It
wobbled around that level and down just a touch on the news of the
India/Pakistan fighting. When news subsequently broke of the
Bessent/Greer/He meeting ahead gold sold of heavily to lows circa
US$3360 before stabilising. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major
FX was a little less wild. The USD broadly gained on the trade talk
meeting news. AUD/USD was an exception, the Australian dollar found
bids on China hopes. After topping above 0.6510 its subsided back
below 0.6490 though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY is 100 points higher on the trade talk news. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US
equity index futures rose on the trade talk news, these have
stabilised off their early highs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC/CSRC China supportive measures - in summary</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboccsrc-china-supportive-measures-in-summary-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:52:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboccsrc-china-supportive-measures-in-summary-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;All of these are in the posts earlier, but collating them here in brief. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1597&quot; data-end=&quot;1629&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Equity Market Stabilisation:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1631&quot; data-end=&quot;1904&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1631&quot; data-end=&quot;1756&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1633&quot; data-end=&quot;1756&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Central Huijin, along with the PBOC, will step in as a quasi-stabilisation fund to help maintain stock market confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1757&quot; data-end=&quot;1904&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1759&quot; data-end=&quot;1904&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;An additional 60 billion yuan (US$8.3 billion) from long-term insurance funds will be channelled into equities under an expanded pilot program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1010&quot; data-end=&quot;1052&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Targeted Liquidity and Credit Support:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1054&quot; data-end=&quot;1595&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1054&quot; data-end=&quot;1176&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1056&quot; data-end=&quot;1176&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;RMB 300 billion in new re-lending funds will be allocated to support technological innovation and industrial upgrades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1177&quot; data-end=&quot;1313&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1179&quot; data-end=&quot;1313&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A new RMB 500 billion re-lending facility will be introduced to finance elderly care infrastructure and broader service consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1314&quot; data-end=&quot;1459&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1316&quot; data-end=&quot;1459&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The People’s Bank of China (PBOC) will expand the quota for capital market support tools to RMB 800 billion to deepen market-based financing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1460&quot; data-end=&quot;1595&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1462&quot; data-end=&quot;1595&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A new risk-sharing mechanism will be established to back technology innovation bonds, improving credit support for strategic sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;200&quot; data-end=&quot;249&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Monetary Tools and Interest Rate Adjustments from the People&apos;s Bank of China:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;251&quot; data-end=&quot;1008&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;251&quot; data-end=&quot;366&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;253&quot; data-end=&quot;366&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Reserve Requirement Ratio (RRR) will be lowered by 0.5 percentage points to boost banking system liquidity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;367&quot; data-end=&quot;528&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;369&quot; data-end=&quot;528&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A temporary cut in the reserve ratio for auto finance and leasing firms will bring it down from 5% to 0%, aiming to ease sector-specific funding constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;529&quot; data-end=&quot;635&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;531&quot; data-end=&quot;635&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The 7-day Reverse Repo rate, a key short-term policy rate, will be trimmed by 10 basis points to 1.4%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;636&quot; data-end=&quot;748&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;638&quot; data-end=&quot;748&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The structural monetary policy rate will be reduced by 25 basis points to support targeted credit expansion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;749&quot; data-end=&quot;888&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;751&quot; data-end=&quot;888&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Interest rates on individual housing provident fund loans will be lowered by 0.25 percentage points to reduce mortgage borrowing costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;889&quot; data-end=&quot;1008&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;891&quot; data-end=&quot;1008&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Standing Lending Facility (SLF) rate will be cut by 10 basis points, further easing interbank lending conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China unlocks more insurance capital for stocks, signals property support</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-unlocks-more-insurance-capital-for-stocks-signals-property-support-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:27:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-unlocks-more-insurance-capital-for-stocks-signals-property-support-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;148&quot; data-end=&quot;475&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China will allow an additional 60 billion yuan (US$8.3 billion) from long-term insurance funds to be invested in equities as part of an expanded pilot program aimed at deepening capital market participation. The move is part of Beijing’s broader efforts to shore up financial stability and revive confidence across key sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;477&quot; data-end=&quot;682&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Li Yunze, head of China’s top financial regulator, announced the measure at a press briefing, adding that authorities are also preparing new initiatives to stabilise the country’s troubled property sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;929&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The expanded insurance investment scheme is a key pillar of ongoing capital market reforms. Together with anticipated property measures, it reflects a wider policy shift to support economic resilience amid persistent growth and market pressures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;929&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-pan-says-world-is-full-or-uncertainties-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;PBOC Governor Pan says world is full of uncertainties - cuts rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-rate-cuts-7-day-rr-to-14-from-15-lpr-10bp-cut-also-rrr-50-bp-cut-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;PBOC rate cuts: 7-day RR to 1.4% (from 1.5%), LPR 10bp cut also, RRR 50 bp cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-sets-7-day-reverse-repo-rate-at-14-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China sets 7-day reverse repo rate at 1.4% (from 1.5% previously)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-says-will-lower-interest-rates-on-structural-policy-tools-by-25-bps-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;PBOC governor says will lower interest rates on structural policy tools by 25 bps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article-slot__title title top&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-to-cut-standing-lending-facility-rate-by-10bp-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China to cut Standing Lending Facility rate by 10bp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;More:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-willhelpa-sharelistedcompaniesaffectedbytariffstocopewithdifficulties-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;China will help A-share listed companies affected by tariffs to cope with difficulties&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-promises-more-local-stock-market-support-from-sovereign-fund-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;China promises more local stock market support from sovereign fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People&apos;s Bank of China to cut Standing Lending Facility rate by 10bp</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-to-cut-standing-lending-facility-rate-by-10bp-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:22:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-to-cut-standing-lending-facility-rate-by-10bp-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China to cut Standing Lending Facility rate by 10bp&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;from May 8&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RRR cut referred to earlier will be cut from May 15&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-pan-says-world-is-full-or-uncertainties-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;PBOC Governor Pan says world is full of uncertainties - cuts rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-rate-cuts-7-day-rr-to-14-from-15-lpr-10bp-cut-also-rrr-50-bp-cut-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;PBOC rate cuts: 7-day RR to 1.4% (from 1.5%), LPR 10bp cut also, RRR 50 bp cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-sets-7-day-reverse-repo-rate-at-14-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China sets 7-day reverse repo rate at 1.4% (from 1.5% previously)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-says-will-lower-interest-rates-on-structural-policy-tools-by-25-bps-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;PBOC governor says will lower interest rates on structural policy tools by 25 bps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;More:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-willhelpa-sharelistedcompaniesaffectedbytariffstocopewithdifficulties-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China will help A-share listed companies affected by tariffs to cope with difficulties&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-promises-more-local-stock-market-support-from-sovereign-fund-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China promises more local stock market support from sovereign fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Standing Lending Facility (SLF)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;

Aimed mainly at small- and medium-sized financial institutions
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum maturity has been kept at one month or below for the past years&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China promises more local stock market support from sovereign fund</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-promises-more-local-stock-market-support-from-sovereign-fund-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 02:18:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-promises-more-local-stock-market-support-from-sovereign-fund-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China Securities Regulatory Commission (CSRC) head:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;To support Central Huijin to bolster markets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Central Huijin, PBOC acting as quasi-stabilization fund.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China will roll out reform measures for tech boards.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ample preparations made for dealing with external shocks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will forcefully promote long-term capital into the stock market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confident to achieve stable development of China’s stock market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shanghai Composite update:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China will help A-share listed companies affected by tariffs to cope with difficulties</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-willhelpa-sharelistedcompaniesaffectedbytariffstocopewithdifficulties-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-willhelpa-sharelistedcompaniesaffectedbytariffstocopewithdifficulties-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China securities regulator head:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says US tariffs will have bigger impact on A-share listed companies with bigger share of exports to US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will help a-share listed companies affected by tariffs to cope with difficulties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says will support mergers and acquisitions among listed companies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-pan-says-world-is-full-or-uncertainties-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;PBOC Governor Pan says world is full of uncertainties - cuts rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-rate-cuts-7-day-rr-to-14-from-15-lpr-10bp-cut-also-rrr-50-bp-cut-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;PBOC rate cuts: 7-day RR to 1.4% (from 1.5%), LPR 10bp cut also, RRR 50 bp cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-sets-7-day-reverse-repo-rate-at-14-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China sets 7-day reverse repo rate at 1.4% (from 1.5% previously)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-says-will-lower-interest-rates-on-structural-policy-tools-by-25-bps-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;PBOC governor says will lower interest rates on structural policy tools by 25 bps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC governor says will lower interest rates on structural policy tools by 25 bps</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-says-will-lower-interest-rates-on-structural-policy-tools-by-25-bps-20250507/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 01:37:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-says-will-lower-interest-rates-on-structural-policy-tools-by-25-bps-20250507/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;More from People&apos;s Bank of China Governor Pan:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;will lower interest rates on structural policy tools by 25 bps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;will guide banks in reducing deposit rates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-governor-pan-says-world-is-full-or-uncertainties-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;PBOC Governor Pan says world is full of uncertainties - cuts rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-rate-cuts-7-day-rr-to-14-from-15-lpr-10bp-cut-also-rrr-50-bp-cut-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;PBOC rate cuts: 7-day RR to 1.4% (from 1.5%), LPR 10bp cut also, RRR 50 bp cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/peoples-bank-of-china-sets-7-day-reverse-repo-rate-at-14-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;People&apos;s Bank of China sets 7-day reverse repo rate at 1.4% (from 1.5% previously)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EMERGENCY DECLARED IN PAKISTANI PROVINCE OF PUNJAB - PROVINCIAL CHIEF MINISTER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919871238173778119#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919871238173778119#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EMERGENCY DECLARED IN PAKISTANI PROVINCE OF PUNJAB - PROVINCIAL CHIEF MINISTER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PAKISTAN IS RESPONDING TO INDIAN ATTACKS - PAKISTAN PRIME MINISTER SHARIF</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919867218357047498#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:29:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919867218357047498#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAKISTAN IS RESPONDING TO INDIAN ATTACKS - PAKISTAN PRIME MINISTER SHARIF&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: IRAN WILL NOT HAVE NUCLEAR WEAPON</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919864385738047573#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:18:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919864385738047573#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: IRAN WILL NOT HAVE NUCLEAR WEAPON&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: RUSSIA WANTED TO TAKE ALL OF UKRAINE AND THEY&apos;VE STOPPED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919864300316885206#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:18:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919864300316885206#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: RUSSIA WANTED TO TAKE ALL OF UKRAINE AND THEY&apos;VE STOPPED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: &apos;EARTH-SHATTERING&apos; ANNOUNCEMENT TO COME</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919864241319755877#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:17:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919864241319755877#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: &apos;EARTH-SHATTERING&apos; ANNOUNCEMENT TO COME&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: IT’S A SHAME, WE JUST HEARD ABOUT INDIA STRIKES AGAINST PAKISTAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919864137489752460#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:17:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919864137489752460#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: IT’S A SHAME, WE JUST HEARD ABOUT INDIA STRIKES AGAINST PAKISTAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: HOUTHIS HAVE DECIDED THAT THEY DON&apos;T WANT TO DO THIS ANYMORE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919864052563460462#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:17:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919864052563460462#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: HOUTHIS HAVE DECIDED THAT THEY DON&apos;T WANT TO DO THIS ANYMORE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PAKISTAN DEFENCE MINISTER ON GEO: ALL TARGETS HIT ARE CIVILIAN SPOTS, NOT MILITANT CAMPS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919861032295477286#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919861032295477286#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAKISTAN DEFENCE MINISTER ON GEO: ALL TARGETS HIT ARE CIVILIAN SPOTS, NOT MILITANT CAMPS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SPOT GOLD RISES NEARLY 3% TO $3,432.04/OZ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919858959059410948#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:56:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919858959059410948#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPOT GOLD RISES NEARLY 3% TO $3,432.04/OZ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIA GOVT ON PRECISION STRIKE: INDIA HAS DEMONSTRATED CONSIDERABLE RESTRAINT IN SELECTION OF TARGETS AND METHOD OF EXECUTION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919856130756399349#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919856130756399349#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIA GOVT ON PRECISION STRIKE: INDIA HAS DEMONSTRATED CONSIDERABLE RESTRAINT IN SELECTION OF TARGETS AND METHOD OF EXECUTION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: LOOKING AT A LOT OF COUNTRIES FOR TRADE DEALS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919854324131287198#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:38:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919854324131287198#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: LOOKING AT A LOT OF COUNTRIES FOR TRADE DEALS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PAKISTAN SECURITY SOURCE SAYS AT LEAST ONE CHILD KILLED IN ATTACK AND TWO INJURED NEAR BAHAWALPUR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919854187698913765#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:38:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919854187698913765#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAKISTAN SECURITY SOURCE SAYS AT LEAST ONE CHILD KILLED IN ATTACK AND TWO INJURED NEAR BAHAWALPUR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: HAVEN&apos;T CALLED CARNEY GOVERNOR YET AND MAYBE I WON&apos;T; HAD A LOT OF FUN WITH TRUDEAU</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919854093704552946#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:37:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919854093704552946#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: HAVEN&apos;T CALLED CARNEY GOVERNOR YET AND MAYBE I WON&apos;T; HAD A LOT OF FUN WITH TRUDEAU&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIAN ARMY SAYS IN POST ON X &quot; JUSTICE IS SERVED&quot; AFTER INDIA LAUNCHES ATTACK ON SITES IN PAKISTAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919852885946286455#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:32:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919852885946286455#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIAN ARMY SAYS IN POST ON X &quot; JUSTICE IS SERVED&quot; AFTER INDIA LAUNCHES ATTACK ON SITES IN PAKISTAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: HAD GREAT MEETING WITH CARNEY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919852263796867494#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:30:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919852263796867494#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: HAD GREAT MEETING WITH CARNEY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INTENSE SHELLING, LOUD EXPLOSIONS HEARD IN TWO BORDER AREAS OF INDIAN KASHMIR - POLICE OFFICER, WITNESSES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919850667205624037#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:24:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919850667205624037#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INTENSE SHELLING, LOUD EXPLOSIONS HEARD IN TWO BORDER AREAS OF INDIAN KASHMIR - POLICE OFFICER, WITNESSES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIA GOVT: NINE SITES TARGETED AS PART OF ‘OPERATION SINDOOR’

INDIA GOVT: &quot;OUR ACTIONS HAVE BEEN FOCUSED, MEASURED AND NON-ESCALATORY IN NATURE&quot;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919850038068424707#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:21:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919850038068424707#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIA GOVT: NINE SITES TARGETED AS PART OF ‘OPERATION SINDOOR’&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
INDIA GOVT: &quot;OUR ACTIONS HAVE BEEN FOCUSED, MEASURED AND NON-ESCALATORY IN NATURE&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) THE INDIAN ARMED FORCES LAUNCHED ‘OPERATION SINDOOR’, HITTING TERRORIST INFRASTRUCTURE IN PAKISTAN AND PAKISTAN-OCCUPIED JAMMU AND KASHMIR -STATEMENT

NO PAKISTANI MILITARY FACILITIES HAVE BEEN TARGETED-STATEMENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919849363095818591#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:18:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919849363095818591#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE INDIAN ARMED FORCES LAUNCHED ‘OPERATION SINDOOR’, HITTING TERRORIST INFRASTRUCTURE IN PAKISTAN AND PAKISTAN-OCCUPIED JAMMU AND KASHMIR -STATEMENT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
NO PAKISTANI MILITARY FACILITIES HAVE BEEN TARGETED-STATEMENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PAKISTAN INTERNATIONAL AIRLINES SPOKESPERSON SAYS FLIGHTS ALREADY AIRBORNE HAVE BEEN DIVERTED TO KARACHI</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1919848968600646071#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 20:17:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1919848968600646071#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PAKISTAN INTERNATIONAL AIRLINES SPOKESPERSON SAYS FLIGHTS ALREADY AIRBORNE HAVE BEEN DIVERTED TO KARACHI&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
