<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>More signs that the US-Japan trade agreement is on ice</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-signs-that-the-us-japan-trade-agreement-is-on-ice-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 12:26:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-signs-that-the-us-japan-trade-agreement-is-on-ice-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There was a report in the FT last week indicating that US-Japan trade negotiations were on hold and would likely stay that way through the July Japanese elections. Kowtowing to the US ahead of July elections would be deeply unpopular in Japan and it looks like they&apos;re going to punt until afterwards, even at the risk of rising reciprocal tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fox Business&apos; Charlie Gasparino has repeatedly said a Japan agreement was close but now he&apos;s reporting that&apos;s not the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;The US-Japan trade agreement framework is being delayed in part over negotiations over so-called burden sharing, or how much money Japan has to kick in to support US military in Japan (also known as protection from Chinese aggression)&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, there might be a deal to be made around military spending and investment in Alaska LNG but it&apos;s tough to get there unless the US is willing to take tariffs to zero. There was also an interesting report this weekend via Bloomberg suggesting that China got a better deal by punching back and that could be the playbook now.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USD is lower vs the 3 major currency pairs as traders react to Moody&apos;s downgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-lower-vs-the-3-major-currency-pairs-as-traders-react-to-moodys-downgrade-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 12:12:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-lower-vs-the-3-major-currency-pairs-as-traders-react-to-moodys-downgrade-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The USD is lower to start the trading week as investors sell US stocks, bonds after the Moody&apos;s downgrade of US debt late Friday.  The USD is down -0.90% vs the EUR, and -0.81% vs the GBP. to start the session The greenback is down -0.42% vs the JPY. The video above outlines the technical levels in play for those three major currency pairs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you likely know already, the rating agency Moody’s downgraded the U.S. sovereign credit rating on Friday from Aaa to Aa1, citing the nation’s soaring $36 trillion debt and persistent fiscal deficits. The move, which comes after similar downgrades by other agencies a year of so ago, signals growing concern over America’s long-term fiscal outlook and rising interest costs. While Moody’s shifted its outlook from “negative” to “stable,” the downgrade sparked backlash from Trump allies, who criticized the decision as politically motivated. The change could complicate President Trump’s efforts to cut taxes and balance the budget, especially as investors remain unconvinced by revenue-raising tariffs and cost-cutting measures. The announcement sent Treasury yields higher after the market close, raising the risk of bond market instability when trading resumes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhiile, the House panel approved the Trump Tax cut plan. That will lead to a vote this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the Fed,  Atlanta Fed President Raphael Bostic this morning on CNBC warned that Moody’s downgrade could have wide-reaching effects across the economy and financial markets, particularly by raising the cost of capital and introducing greater uncertainty. He emphasized that it may take several months to fully understand the impact on U.S. debt demand and inflation from tariffs. Bostic noted the Fed is cautious on rate cuts, leaning toward just one this year due to the complex interplay of inflation, tariffs, and economic sentiment. While markets are functioning well, inflation remains above target and expectations are moving in a troubling way, although firms aren’t planning large layoffs. He highlighted a disconnect between economic sentiment and data and pointed to potential ripple effects from even reduced tariffs on China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In geopolitical news, Israeli Finance Minister Smotrich stated that Israel aims to continue the war to push Gaza’s population southward and potentially out of the territory, according to Sky News Arabia. This comes as Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu vowed to take full control of Gaza, while Israeli forces expanded ground operations and conducted airstrikes that killed at least 100 people. Israel&apos;s government also said it would allow limited humanitarian aid into Gaza to prevent a hunger crisis. Pres. Trump said on Friday a lot of good things are going to happen over the next month in Gaza, but warned that something bad would happen if Iran does not move in nuclear talks.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Ukraine stated that Kyiv prioritizes a ceasefire in its ongoing discussions with the Russian delegation and is open to exploring a potential meeting between President Zelensky and President Putin. This aligns with earlier remarks from U.S. President Trump, who expressed willingness to meet with both leaders once arrangements are made. Attention now turns to determining the specific timing of any such meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks are lower with the futures implying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow Industrial average futures implying a decline of -258 point&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index futures are implying a decline of -63 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq futures are implying a decline of -311 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the European markets, the major indices are mixed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German Dax, unchange&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC, -0.68%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE 100, -0.36%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex, -0.24% &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB, -1.80%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market, yields are higher after the Moody&apos;s downgrade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield 4.025%, +4.2 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.131%, +6.9 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year yield 4.536%, +9.7 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year yield 5.007%, +11.0 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil down $0.57 or -0.90% at $61.41&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Silver up $0.32 or 1.01% at $32.60&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold is up $40.62 or 1.27% at $3242.41&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin is trading down $3790 at $102,719&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&apos;s an official holiday in Canada (and an unofficial one)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/its-an-official-holiday-in-canada-and-an-unofficial-one-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 12:12:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/its-an-official-holiday-in-canada-and-an-unofficial-one-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Canadian dollar is lagging today and a portion of that is likely due to the local holiday. Canadian markets are closed today for Victoria Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s also an unofficial holiday for the large part of the country that can&apos;t stand the Toronto Maple Leafs as they were routed in a playoff elimination game yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JPMORGAN CFO JEREMY BARNUM SAYS THERE IS SIGNIFICANT ECONOMIC UNCERTAINTY - INVESTOR DAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924436630171013311#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 12:07:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924436630171013311#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JPMORGAN CFO JEREMY BARNUM SAYS THERE IS SIGNIFICANT ECONOMIC UNCERTAINTY - INVESTOR DAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $MSTR - MICROSTRATEGY INC - CLASS ACTION LAWSUIT FILED AGAINST MICROSTRATEGY AND EXECUTIVES - SEC FILING

MICROSTRATEGY INC - LAWSUIT ALLEGES MISLEADING STATEMENTS ON BITCOIN STRATEGY - SEC FILING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924435527542997363#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 12:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924435527542997363#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23MSTR&quot;&gt;$MSTR&lt;/a&gt; - MICROSTRATEGY INC - CLASS ACTION LAWSUIT FILED AGAINST MICROSTRATEGY AND EXECUTIVES - SEC FILING&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
MICROSTRATEGY INC - LAWSUIT ALLEGES MISLEADING STATEMENTS ON BITCOIN STRATEGY - SEC FILING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $MSTR - MICROSTRATEGY PURCHASES 7,390 BITCOINS BETWEEN MAY 12 - MAY 18 AT AN AVERAGE OF $103,498 (TOTAL: $764.90M)1</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924435106925527520#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 12:00:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924435106925527520#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23MSTR&quot;&gt;$MSTR&lt;/a&gt; - MICROSTRATEGY PURCHASES 7,390 BITCOINS BETWEEN MAY 12 - MAY 18 AT AN AVERAGE OF $103,498 (TOTAL: $764.90M)1&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BARCLAYS: U.S. GROWTH TO SLOW, BUT RECESSION UNLIKELY

Barclays expects U.S. economic growth to slow in the coming quarters, but no longer forecasts a recession in the second half of 2025, thanks to easing U.S.-China trade tensions.

Tariffs have dropped to around 14% (17% excluding a temporary electronics exemption), reducing inflationary pressure. Barclays now sees core PCE inflation at 3.3% in Q4 2025 (down from 3.8%) and 2.2% by the end of 2026.

With a stronger outlook, unemployment is expected to peak at just 4.3% in late 2025. As a result, the Fed is now seen making only one rate cut this year, likely in December.

In Europe, Barclays’ new base case for the Stoxx 600 is 540, expecting potential for equities to overshoot despite limited near-term fundamentals.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924431822319919434#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:47:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924431822319919434#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BARCLAYS: U.S. GROWTH TO SLOW, BUT RECESSION UNLIKELY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Barclays expects U.S. economic growth to slow in the coming quarters, but no longer forecasts a recession in the second half of 2025, thanks to easing U.S.-China trade tensions.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Tariffs have dropped to around 14% (17% excluding a temporary electronics exemption), reducing inflationary pressure. Barclays now sees core PCE inflation at 3.3% in Q4 2025 (down from 3.8%) and 2.2% by the end of 2026.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
With a stronger outlook, unemployment is expected to peak at just 4.3% in late 2025. As a result, the Fed is now seen making only one rate cut this year, likely in December.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In Europe, Barclays’ new base case for the Stoxx 600 is 540, expecting potential for equities to overshoot despite limited near-term fundamentals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive European FX news wrap: Rough day for USD and US Treasuries</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-rough-day-for-usd-and-us-treasuries-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-rough-day-for-usd-and-us-treasuries-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-government-releases-further-details-of-eu-reset-deal-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;UK Government releases further details of EU reset deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article__title&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-bostic-moodys-downgrade-will-cut-across-economics-financial-markets-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Bostic: Moody&apos;s downgrade will cut across economics, financial markets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/kremlin-putin-trump-to-hold-phone-call-at-1700-moscow-time-on-monday-20250519/&quot;&gt;Kremlin: Putin, Trump to hold phone call at 17:00 Moscow time on Monday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-cpi-22-vs-22-yy-prelim-20250519/&quot;&gt;Eurozone April final CPI +2.2% vs +2.2% y/y prelim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-16-may-chf-44318-bn-vs-chf-45324-bn-prior-20250519/&quot;&gt;SNB total sight deposits w.e. 16 May CHF 443.18 bn vs CHF 453.24 bn prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-19th-23rd-may-20250519/&quot;&gt;Market Outlook for the week of 19th - 23rd May&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-and-uk-said-to-reach-outline-deal-to-strengthen-ties-20250519/&quot;&gt;EU and UK said to reach outline deal to strengthen ties&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-30-year-treasury-yield-rises-to-5-for-the-first-time-since-april-20250519/&quot;&gt;US 30 year Treasury yield rises to 5% for the first time since April&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-19-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250519/&quot;&gt;FX option expiries for 19 May 10am New York cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-tertiary-industry-index-for-march-158-vs-09-prior-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan Tertiary Industry Index for March 15.8% vs -0.9% prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250519/&quot;&gt;What are the main events for today?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/barclays-expects-the-ecb-to-cut-rates-by-25bp-in-june-september-and-december-20250519/&quot;&gt;Barclays expects the ECB to cut rates by 25bp in June, September and December&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been a very boring session in terms of data and news releases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been more lively in the markets though where some of the moves that began earlier in the Asian session, extended in the European session. The most notable ones have been the US Dollar and the long term US Treasuries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The greenback got beaten up hour after hour as the session progressed. It&apos;s been particularly weak against the EUR and GBP where the positive news on the &quot;EU-UK reset deal&quot; were likely a contributing factor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US bond market, long term Treasury yields continued to rise following the Moody&apos;s downgrade with the newswires reporting on every bps increase after the US 30 year yield crossed the 5% level. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, Bitcoin erased all the weekend gains as it followed the US stock market lower. And in the last part of the session, we got Fed&apos;s Bostic repeating that his base case remains one rate cut in 2025 as he&apos;s worrying about the inflation part of the mandate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, the calendar is still empty on the data front but we will have more Fed speakers sharing their views. Fed&apos;s Williams in particular could be important. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) YIELD ON 10-YR U.S. TREASURY NOTES  EXTENDS RISE TO HIGHEST SINCE APRIL 11, LAST UP 12 BPS AT 4.5584%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924428345309011979#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:34:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924428345309011979#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;YIELD ON 10-YR U.S. TREASURY NOTES  EXTENDS RISE TO HIGHEST SINCE APRIL 11, LAST UP 12 BPS AT 4.5584%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: THE MARKET VOLATILITY IN APRIL DID NOT FEEL THAT CLOSE TO A SIGNIFICANT FINANCIAL EVENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924427567009865947#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924427567009865947#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: THE MARKET VOLATILITY IN APRIL DID NOT FEEL THAT CLOSE TO A SIGNIFICANT FINANCIAL EVENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: INFLATION EXPECTATIONS ARE MOVING IN A TROUBLING WAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924426425198608420#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:26:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924426425198608420#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: INFLATION EXPECTATIONS ARE MOVING IN A TROUBLING WAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: INFLATION NOT MOVING TO TARGET AS FAST AS ANTICIPATED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924425853603139835#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:24:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924425853603139835#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: INFLATION NOT MOVING TO TARGET AS FAST AS ANTICIPATED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: TREASURY MARKETS ARE FUNCTIONING QUITE WELL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924425742814683307#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:23:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924425742814683307#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: TREASURY MARKETS ARE FUNCTIONING QUITE WELL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: LEANING MORE TOWARDS ONLY ONE CUT THIS YEAR BECAUSE IT WILL TAKE TIME TO UNDERSTAND TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924425441303056847#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:22:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924425441303056847#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: LEANING MORE TOWARDS ONLY ONE CUT THIS YEAR BECAUSE IT WILL TAKE TIME TO UNDERSTAND TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: NUMBER OF RATE CUTS THIS YEAR DEPENDS ON HOW THINGS TURN OUT, THE DETAILS OF THE TARIFFS WILL MATTER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924425379562901585#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:22:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924425379562901585#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: NUMBER OF RATE CUTS THIS YEAR DEPENDS ON HOW THINGS TURN OUT, THE DETAILS OF THE TARIFFS WILL MATTER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: IT IS UNCLEAR IF CONSUMERS TODAY CAN TAKE ON THE FULL COST OF TARIFFS GIVEN STATE OF HOUSEHOLD BALANCE SHEETS, RECENT INFLATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924424764103282886#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:19:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924424764103282886#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: IT IS UNCLEAR IF CONSUMERS TODAY CAN TAKE ON THE FULL COST OF TARIFFS GIVEN STATE OF HOUSEHOLD BALANCE SHEETS, RECENT INFLATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Bostic: Moody&apos;s downgrade will cut across economics, financial markets</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-bostic-moodys-downgrade-will-cut-across-economics-financial-markets-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:19:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-bostic-moodys-downgrade-will-cut-across-economics-financial-markets-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moody&apos;s downgrade will cut across economics, financial markets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Downgrade will have implications for cost of capital, could ripple through economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will have to wait and see about impact of downgrade on demand for US debt.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Fed will have to determine how the downgrade effects an outlook that is already in flux.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s unclear if consumers today can take on the full cost of tariffs given the state of household balance sheets, recent inflation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have to wait 3-6 months to see how uncertainty settles.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Number of rate cuts this year depends on how things turn out, the details of the tariffs will matter.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leaning more towards only one cut this year because it will take time to understand tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s a scenario where tariffs become less of a story over time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If the tariff transition is longer, it may impact consumer behavior.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Treasury markets are functioning quite well.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inflation not moving to target as fast as anticipated.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty means there is higher risk, the Fed only controls one part of the price of capital.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As things get more expensive, it changes the choices policymakers, households and businesses face, that will influence the path of the economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have not seen much movement on the jobs side, firms say they don&apos;t have plans for large layoffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inflation expectations are moving in a troubling way.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I worry a lot about the inflation side of out mandate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Right now see more risk of higher inflation than the employment side of the mandate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Decline in sentiment is not yet playing out in the marketplace.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;May be at a point where the distance between sentiment and data starts to narrow; inventory rundown may be nearing an end.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The market volatility in April did not feel that close to a significant financial event.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Volatility reflected people adjusting to new expectations, information about tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Even the reduced tariffs on China are economically significant.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bostic is a hawk and he&apos;s not a voting member in 2025. He&apos;s been supporting just one rate cut this year as he&apos;s placing more weight on the inflation side of the mandate given that inflation hasn&apos;t moved to target as fast as anticipated. He&apos;s also worrying about inflation expectations.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: WILL HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE ABOUT IMPACT OF DOWNGRADE ON DEMAND FOR U.S. DEBT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924424327715258501#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:18:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924424327715258501#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: WILL HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE ABOUT IMPACT OF DOWNGRADE ON DEMAND FOR U.S. DEBT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BOSTIC: DOWNGRADE WILL HAVE IMPLICATIONS FOR COST OF CAPITAL, COULD RIPPLE THROUGH ECONOMY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924424155014787357#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:17:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924424155014787357#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BOSTIC: DOWNGRADE WILL HAVE IMPLICATIONS FOR COST OF CAPITAL, COULD RIPPLE THROUGH ECONOMY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S BOSTIC: MOODY&apos;S DOWNGRADE WILL CUT ACROSS ECONOMICS, FINANCIAL MARKETS - CNBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924424068876451911#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:17:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924424068876451911#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S BOSTIC: MOODY&apos;S DOWNGRADE WILL CUT ACROSS ECONOMICS, FINANCIAL MARKETS - CNBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PRESIDENT’S SCHEDULE – MONDAY, MAY 19, 2025

🔸 8:30 AM – In-Town Pool Call Time

🔸 9:00 AM – Press Briefing by Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt (James S. Brady Briefing Room – On Camera)

🔸 3:00 PM – The President and First Lady attend a Bill Signing (Rose Garden – Pre-Credentialed Media)

🔸 4:30 PM – The President joins a Law Enforcement Event (Oval Office – Closed Press)

🔸 7:00 PM – The President attends a Kennedy Center Board Dinner (State Dining Room – Press Pool Coverage)</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924423192262627565#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:13:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924423192262627565#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT’S SCHEDULE – MONDAY, MAY 19, 2025&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 8:30 AM – In-Town Pool Call Time&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 9:00 AM – Press Briefing by Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt (James S. Brady Briefing Room – On Camera)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 3:00 PM – The President and First Lady attend a Bill Signing (Rose Garden – Pre-Credentialed Media)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 4:30 PM – The President joins a Law Enforcement Event (Oval Office – Closed Press)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 7:00 PM – The President attends a Kennedy Center Board Dinner (State Dining Room – Press Pool Coverage)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Government releases further details of EU reset deal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-government-releases-further-details-of-eu-reset-deal-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:05:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-government-releases-further-details-of-eu-reset-deal-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK and EU also agree security and defence partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The partnership paves way for UK firms to access EU&apos;s 150bln pound defence fund.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sanitary and phytosanitary deal has no time limit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Closer co-operation on emissions trading systems will mean UK businesses not hit by EU carbon tax.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK economy to add nearly 9 bln pounds by 2040 as a result of deals on food and drink, emissions trading.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deal will protect British steel exports from new EU rules and tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK and EU to discuss access to EU facial image databases.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Britsh holidaymakers will be able to use more passport e-gates in Europe.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK and EU agree to co-operate on youth mobility scheme, scheme will be capped and time-limited.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, this is good news for the UK economy, although I don&apos;t think the market is focused on this right now. Trump&apos;s trade war seems to at least have sped up lots of trade deals, which should be good for the global economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More details &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gov.uk/government/news/pm-secures-new-agreement-with-eu-to-benefit-british-people&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 MISSILE DANGER WARNING ISSUED IN RUSSIA&apos;S SOCHI, NOVOROSSIISK - RIA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924420670085079331#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924420670085079331#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 MISSILE DANGER WARNING ISSUED IN RUSSIA&apos;S SOCHI, NOVOROSSIISK - RIA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - CANTOR FITZGERALD REITERATES TESLA OVERWEIGHT RATING, $425 PRICE TARGET

Analyst Andres Sheppard remains bullish on Tesla, highlighting several key drivers:

🔸 Robotaxi launch in Texas set for June.

🔸 Low-cost EV (~$30K with tax credit) expected in 1H25, well-timed amid tariffs and potential tax credit cuts.

🔸 Elon Musk will shift focus back to Tesla starting in May.

🔸 FSD rollout in China (already begun) and Europe (expected 1H25).

🔸 Optimus Bot production to scale in 2026, with customer deliveries by 2027.

🔸 Semi Truck production starts in 2026, entering autonomous trucking.

Tesla is well-positioned to handle tariffs due to its global manufacturing and vertical integration. Long-term growth is expected from FSD, Robotaxi, Energy Storage, and Optimus.

Near-term risks include macro headwinds, tariffs, Musk’s political image, and potential EV tax credit removal (expected by late 2025/2026). Tesla may revise its 2025 auto growth and energy storage targets next quarter.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924418891465290088#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:56:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924418891465290088#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - CANTOR FITZGERALD REITERATES TESLA OVERWEIGHT RATING, $425 PRICE TARGET&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Analyst Andres Sheppard remains bullish on Tesla, highlighting several key drivers:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Robotaxi launch in Texas set for June.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Low-cost EV (~$30K with tax credit) expected in 1H25, well-timed amid tariffs and potential tax credit cuts.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Elon Musk will shift focus back to Tesla starting in May.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 FSD rollout in China (already begun) and Europe (expected 1H25).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Optimus Bot production to scale in 2026, with customer deliveries by 2027.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Semi Truck production starts in 2026, entering autonomous trucking.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Tesla is well-positioned to handle tariffs due to its global manufacturing and vertical integration. Long-term growth is expected from FSD, Robotaxi, Energy Storage, and Optimus.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Near-term risks include macro headwinds, tariffs, Musk’s political image, and potential EV tax credit removal (expected by late 2025/2026). Tesla may revise its 2025 auto growth and energy storage targets next quarter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USD is not the only one having a rough day as Bitcoin erased all the weekend gains</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-usd-is-not-the-only-one-having-a-rough-day-as-bitcoin-erased-all-the-weekend-gains-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:43:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-usd-is-not-the-only-one-having-a-rough-day-as-bitcoin-erased-all-the-weekend-gains-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There have been lots of people cheering for the Bitcoin rally over the weekend saying that events like the US credit rating downgrade are bullish for the cryptocurrency. Unfortunately for them, Bitcoin is just another risk asset and, given similar drivers, it&apos;s correlated to the stock market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart below, we can see that Bitcoin is bouncing on a major trendline. We are also overextended on the day, so the dip buyers could start piling in around these levels looking for a rally into new all-time highs. The sellers, on the other hand, will want to see the price breaking lower to start targeting a deeper pullback into the 95,000 price area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t see much downside for the stock market or bitcoin at the moment, but the &quot;easy&quot; gains were made from the bottom as we repriced growth expectations. Now we are near overstretched levels as greed and FOMO are keeping the momentum going. The risks I see ahead is a hawkish Fed that triggers another repricing in interest rates expectatios, which would weigh on bitcoin in the short-term. Economic data and inflation risks will be key. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BUY THE DIP AFTER MOODY’S DOWNGRADE: MORGAN STANLEY’S WILSON

Morgan Stanley’s Michael Wilson sees the recent U.S. stock selloff after Moody’s credit downgrade as a buying opportunity, driven more by interest rate fears than fundamentals.

He notes that Moody’s is the last major agency to downgrade U.S. debt—following moves that began back in 2011. Rising bond yields, especially if the 10-year tops 4.5%, could increase pressure on equities.

Despite concerns, volatility eased after a surprise U.S.-China trade deal, which cut effective tariffs from 145% to 30%. However, further market gains depend on earnings strength. Without rate cuts, EPS growth must carry the rally past 6100.

If yields rise above 4.5%, Morgan Stanley expects a modest 5% valuation pullback—but would view that as a buying chance. They favor cyclical sectors like Industrials, and remain cautious on Consumer Discretionary and Staples.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924414646955483346#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:39:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924414646955483346#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BUY THE DIP AFTER MOODY’S DOWNGRADE: MORGAN STANLEY’S WILSON&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Morgan Stanley’s Michael Wilson sees the recent U.S. stock selloff after Moody’s credit downgrade as a buying opportunity, driven more by interest rate fears than fundamentals.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
He notes that Moody’s is the last major agency to downgrade U.S. debt—following moves that began back in 2011. Rising bond yields, especially if the 10-year tops 4.5%, could increase pressure on equities.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Despite concerns, volatility eased after a surprise U.S.-China trade deal, which cut effective tariffs from 145% to 30%. However, further market gains depend on earnings strength. Without rate cuts, EPS growth must carry the rally past 6100.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
If yields rise above 4.5%, Morgan Stanley expects a modest 5% valuation pullback—but would view that as a buying chance. They favor cyclical sectors like Industrials, and remain cautious on Consumer Discretionary and Staples.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $BABA - U.S.-LISTED SHARES OF ALIBABA DOWN 1.9% PREMARKET AFTER REPORT OF US SCRUTINY OF COMPANY&apos;S AI DEAL WITH APPLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924407705466175997#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:12:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924407705466175997#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23BABA&quot;&gt;$BABA&lt;/a&gt; - U.S.-LISTED SHARES OF ALIBABA DOWN 1.9% PREMARKET AFTER REPORT OF US SCRUTINY OF COMPANY&apos;S AI DEAL WITH APPLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD is back at the key resistance but unlikely to break through today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-is-back-at-the-key-resistance-but-unlikely-to-break-through-today-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-is-back-at-the-key-resistance-but-unlikely-to-break-through-today-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been a rough day for the US Dollar so far. This is just the daily trend that was set &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-dollar-under-pressure-again-to-start-the-session-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;earlier in the morning&lt;/a&gt;. The &quot;good news&quot; for the greenback is that we might have reached the peak in the bearish momentum today. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the EURUSD chart below, we can see that the price is now near the top of the average daily range (red line), which stands right at the key 1.1278 resistance zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is where we can expect the sellers to step in with a defined risk above the resistance to position for a drop into the 1.10 handle. The buyers, on the other hand, will look for a break higher to start targeting new highs, but from a risk management perspective, entering at the highs would be pretty bad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s not much on the agenda today that could help the greenback, but Fed speakers might give it a boost if we get some more hawkish comments, especially from Fed&apos;s Williams.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin: Putin, Trump to hold phone call at 17:00 Moscow time on Monday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/kremlin-putin-trump-to-hold-phone-call-at-1700-moscow-time-on-monday-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:11:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/kremlin-putin-trump-to-hold-phone-call-at-1700-moscow-time-on-monday-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kremlin: Putin, Trump to hold phone call at 17:00 Moscow time on Monday.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is at 14:00 GMT or 10:00 ET. Trump will likely push for a ceasefire until they get a peace deal but the Russians don&apos;t seem on the same page.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone April final CPI +2.2% vs +2.2% y/y prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-cpi-22-vs-22-yy-prelim-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-cpi-22-vs-22-yy-prelim-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI +2.7% vs +2.7% y/y prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;No changes to the initial estimates. The market is pricing 91% chance of another 25 bps cut at the June ECB meeting and a total of 51 bps of easing by year-end. The June cut might be hard to avoid, but it might also be the last one for 2025. Data will tell.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNB total sight deposits w.e. 16 May CHF 443.18 bn vs CHF 453.24 bn prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-16-may-chf-44318-bn-vs-chf-45324-bn-prior-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-16-may-chf-44318-bn-vs-chf-45324-bn-prior-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Domestic sight deposits CHF 434.8 bn vs CHF 444.8 bn prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The SNB publishes these figures weekly, and they can show whether the SNB is intervening in currency markets or adjusting liquidity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;885&quot; data-end=&quot;1131&quot;&gt;An increase in total sight deposits usually indicates that the SNB is injecting liquidity into the system, possibly through foreign exchange interventions (buying foreign currencies to weaken the CHF) or other forms of quantitative easing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1134&quot; data-end=&quot;1249&quot;&gt;A decrease may suggest tightening monetary policy, withdrawing liquidity, or not intervening in FX markets.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Dollar under pressure again to start the session</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-dollar-under-pressure-again-to-start-the-session-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:33:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-dollar-under-pressure-again-to-start-the-session-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US Dollar opened lower today and after a bit of a consolidation during the Asian session, started to depreciate again in the European session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Moody&apos;s downgrade is cited as the culprit although there are also other drivers. One above all is that the market has repriced interest rates expectations for the Fed to reflect the central bank&apos;s base case of two cuts in 2025. Therefore, we would need stronger reasons to price out the remaining cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had some upside in the greenback following the higher inflation expectations in the UMich survey last Friday but those gains didn&apos;t last for long. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only bullish scenario for the dollar now is that we get strong economic data or more hawkish Fed comments, so that the remaining rate cuts get priced out and give the greenback another short-term boost. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As long as better global growth remains the main driver, the USD should keep on depreciating against its peers, but if inflation starts to become a concern, then we will likely see more upside for the dollar.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Outlook for the week of 19th - 23rd May</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-19th-23rd-may-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:14:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-19th-23rd-may-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;On Monday, Canada has a bank holiday for Victoria Day, and in the U.S., several FOMC members are expected to deliver remarks.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, the focus will be on the RBA monetary policy announcement, followed later in the day by Canadian inflation data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; On Wednesday, the U.K. will release its inflation data and on Thursday, flash manufacturing and services PMIs will be released for the eurozone, the U.K., and the U.S.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, on Friday, Japan will publish its national core CPI y/y, while the U.K. and Canada will release their retail sales data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this week&apos;s meeting, the RBA is widely expected to deliver a 25 bps rate cut, lowering the cash rate from 4.10% to 3.85%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, inflation data in Australia has softened, with the trimmed mean CPI dipping to 2.9%, now within the RBA&apos;s target range. Headline inflation held steady at 2.4%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wages rose 3.4% y/y, driven by public sector agreements, while private sector wage growth remained stable. April’s jobs report surprised to the upside, adding 89,000 positions, and the unemployment rate held at 4.1%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The RBA is expected to continue cutting rates through the end of the year. However, Wells Fargo analysts argue that solid domestic data and easing China-U.S. trade tensions reduce the likelihood of further policy easing.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consensus for the CPI m/m is 0.5%, up from the prior 0.3%. The median CPI y/y is expected to remain unchanged at 2.9%, while the trimmed CPI y/y is projected to rise from 2.8% to 2.9%, and the common CPI y/y is likely to increase from 2.3% to 2.4%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Analysts from RBC argue that Canada’s April CPI is likely to reflect a drop in headline inflation, primarily due to the removal of the consumer carbon tax on energy products at the beginning of the month. They emphasize that the distortion stems from a temporary federal tax relief measure, which included the GST rebate and ended in February. As a result, annual inflation is forecast to fall sharply from 2.3% in March to 1.6%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Analysts do not expect the effects of tariffs to be reflected in this month’s data just yet. Retaliatory tariffs are anticipated to have a limited impact on consumer prices, as businesses pivot to alternative import sources and consumers shift toward non-tariffed goods.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canadian food price growth is expected to remain elevated at 3.2% y/y in April, with core inflation rising to 2.6%. March retail sales, due this week, are expected to have rebounded to 0.7% from a February decline, driven by pre-tariff auto purchases. While auto sales likely dipped in April, broader consumer spending appears resilient despite weaker sentiment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the U.K., the consensus for CPI y/y is 3.3%, up from the prior 2.6%. Core CPI y/y is likely to rise from 3.4% to 3.6%, while services inflation is expected to come in below the BoE’s forecast of 5%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysts at ING emphasized that April’s inflation data carries extra weight, as it is typically the month when a wide range of services prices are reset for the year. Both April 2023 and 2024 delivered surprises that jolted markets, often with stronger-than-expected prints.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of monetary policy, the BoE is not finished with rate cuts just yet, with another reduction expected at either the June or August meeting.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week&apos;s PMI data for the eurozone will offer a clearer picture of how the economy is holding up. Last month, the services sector declined to 50.1, while manufacturing remained in contractionary territory at 49, and the composite PMI slipped from 50.9 to 50.4.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, conditions in the euro area appear to have stabilized, supported by easing E.U.–U.S. trade tensions, political stability in Germany, and softening inflation data, all of which point to a modest pickup in activity.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Japan, the consensus for the national core CPI y/y is for an increase from 3.2% to 3.5%. This rise is largely attributed to the effects of reduced energy subsidies and new price hikes in sectors such as food and education. Tokyo CPI, often viewed as a bellwether, surprised to the upside earlier this month, climbing to 3.4% y/y, while the core print excluding fresh food and energy surged to 3.1%, its highest level in over a year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; As a reminder, the BoJ left rates unchanged at its May meeting but signaled openness to further hikes if inflation remains persistent. Uncertainty surrounding U.S. tariffs and signs of weakening global demand complicate the outlook.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Gina Constantin at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equities slightly lower at the open</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-slightly-lower-at-the-open-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:07:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-slightly-lower-at-the-open-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s been a bit of a risk-off mood throughout the Asian session with the Moody&apos;s downgrade cited as the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Price Prediction for End of May 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-price-prediction-for-end-of-may-2025-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:24:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-price-prediction-for-end-of-may-2025-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;What Price Will Bitcoin Hit in May? Polymarket Bets Provide Insight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As investors and traders navigate the volatile crypto market, many ask, &quot;What price will Bitcoin hit in May?&quot; Prediction markets such as Polymarket have gained popularity by offering speculative insight through aggregated bets, potentially indicating the market&apos;s collective sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, Polymarket’s betting data for Bitcoin&apos;s price by the end of May shows significant predictions:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below $80k: 2% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$85k: 5% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$90k: 11% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$110k: 38% probability (highest probability)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$115k: 15% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$125k: 2% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$150k: 1% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$200k: less than 1% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the strongest sentiment among bettors anticipates Bitcoin will reach around $110,000 by the month&apos;s end, reflected in a notable 38% likelihood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is Polymarket Accurate in Predicting Bitcoin Prices?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polymarket&apos;s accuracy has been the subject of research. A recent study from CoinDesk (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/03/21/polymarket-is-94-accurate-in-predicting-world-events-research&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/03/21/polymarket-is-94-accurate-in-predicting-world-events-research&lt;/a&gt;) suggests Polymarket is approximately 94% accurate when predicting outcomes within hours of resolution. Even one month in advance, its accuracy remains impressively high, above 90%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, the predictive strength varies significantly with longer-term forecasts. CoinCodex (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coincodex.com/article/65963/is-polymarket-accurate&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://www.coincodex.com/article/65963/is-polymarket-accurate&lt;/a&gt;) highlights that accuracy diminishes as the prediction timeframe extends, due to increased unpredictability and market volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cautions for Investors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its strengths, bettors should be aware that Polymarket reflects sentiment rather than guaranteed outcomes. Additionally, a Medium article (medium.com/@balajibal/why-are-polymarket-betters-losing-money-af3cc506fd9a) highlights that the majority of bettors typically experience losses, underscoring the speculative nature of these bets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using Polymarket as a Sentiment Gauge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While not a crystal ball, Polymarket provides a useful barometer of market expectations. Traders and investors can combine Polymarket insights with technical and fundamental analysis for a comprehensive approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As May progresses, Bitcoin watchers can continue monitoring Polymarket&apos;s evolving probabilities to better understand where collective market sentiment might push prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Price Forecast for the End of May 2025 is Apx. $110k (... but do not take any of this as a guarantee!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what price will Bitcoin hit in May? While no method guarantees results, Polymarket’s current sentiment strongly suggests a target near $110,000. Investors are encouraged to use this insight prudently alongside broader market analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU and UK said to reach outline deal to strengthen ties</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-and-uk-said-to-reach-outline-deal-to-strengthen-ties-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 05:58:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-and-uk-said-to-reach-outline-deal-to-strengthen-ties-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;EU and UK said to reach outline deal to strengthen ties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;EU-UK deal agreed by negotiators, needs political sign off.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EU and UK will meet today in London for the first official summit since Brexit. The meeting is to pave the way for closer ties between both sides. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-pm-starmer-expected-to-announce-brexit-reset-deal-on-monday-is-brexin-the-word-20250518/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; you can find earlier news.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US 30 year Treasury yield rises to 5% for the first time since April</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-30-year-treasury-yield-rises-to-5-for-the-first-time-since-april-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 05:26:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-30-year-treasury-yield-rises-to-5-for-the-first-time-since-april-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Everyone is talking about the Moody&apos;s downgrade and there are of course the usual doomsday-like opinions spreading. In my opinion, this is no big deal. It&apos;s more of a symbolic thing. The S&amp;amp;P Global Ratings downgraded the US in 2011 and Fitch did so in 2023. Why should we care now about Moody&apos;s downgrade?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some say that the context is different because of the deficits and the recent trade war, and I can get behind that idea, but the biggest drivers of advanced economies long term yields is future central bank policy and inflation expectations. As you can see from the chart below, long term Treasury yields have been ranging between 4% and 5% mainly because of pro-growth fiscal policies and the Fed keeping rates higher for longer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the Fed were to hike now and trigger a recession, the long term yields would drop below 4% pretty quickly and nobody would care about the Moody&apos;s downgrade. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-wants-lower-interest-rates-but-hes-strategy-is-likely-to-lead-to-higher-rates-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, there&apos;s limited downside at the moment for yields and the path of least resistance remains to the upside as inflation risk increases. In fact, as we now price in better and better conditions for growth, the economic activity will 
likely start to accelerate and that could lead to inflationary pressures. The Fed is also in a difficult position because rate cuts now could exacerbate inflation fears and drive long term yields even higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s also the thing about consumer inflation expectations continuing to increase in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/umich-may-prelim-consumer-sentiment-508-vs-534-expected-20250516/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;UMich survey&lt;/a&gt; released on Friday, which by the way, was the catalyst for the increase in yields before the Moody&apos;s downgrade. Now, one can trash the UMich survey for the political bias and so on, but the Fed hasn&apos;t met the target for almost 5 years and at some point the time factor could pose a risk for a de-anchoring of inflation expectations, so one cannot dismiss it. Better to be open-minded. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 19 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-19-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:58:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-19-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;EUR/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.1150
(EUR375mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
145.00
(US$474mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
145.55
(US$510mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;146.50 (US$1.16bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;147.00 (US$1.50bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;GBP/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3300 (GBP559mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CHF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8420 (CHF159mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.3985
(US$587mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.3675
(US$529mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6525 (AUD563mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6480 (AUD310mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6355
(AUD595mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;NZD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.5915 (NZD1.06bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Tertiary Industry Index for March 15.8% vs -0.9% prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-tertiary-industry-index-for-march-158-vs-09-prior-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:32:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-tertiary-industry-index-for-march-158-vs-09-prior-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -0.9% (revised to -0.3%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This indicator measures the change in output in the service (tertiary) sector of the Japanese economy. It&apos;s not a market moving release.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:17:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;It&apos;s kind of a synthetic Sunday today on the data front given the empty calendar. There&apos;s just the final Eurozone CPI reading in the European session but it won&apos;t be market moving unless we see big deviations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fed speakers will be the main highlight today. It will be interesting to hear from them about consumer inflation expectations in the UMich report which rose further despite the easing in trade tensions. At the moment, there&apos;s also some angst about the Moody&apos;s downgrade, although in my opinion it&apos;s not a big deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, it&apos;s said that Trump and Putin will speak on the phone today to push for a ceasefire and get the peace deal done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:30 GMT/08:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Bostic (hawk - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:45 GMT/08:45 ET - Fed&apos;s Williams (neutral - voter) --- the most important one&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:45 GMT/08:45 ET - Fed&apos;s Bostic (hawk - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;17:15 GMT/13:15 ET - Fed&apos;s Logan (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;17:30 GMT/13:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Kashkari (hawk - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays expects the ECB to cut rates by 25bp in June, September and December</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/barclays-expects-the-ecb-to-cut-rates-by-25bp-in-june-september-and-december-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/barclays-expects-the-ecb-to-cut-rates-by-25bp-in-june-september-and-december-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;European Central Bank forecast from Barclays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ECB&apos;s next monetary policy meeting is scheduled for June 5, 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market expectations suggest a high probability of another 25 basis point cut, potentially bringing the deposit rate down to 2.00%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This outlook is influenced by concerns over global trade tensions and their impact on eurozone inflation and growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barclays suggest the June cut is on, with another 25bp cut at each of the September and December meetings. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: USD opened week lower as Moody’s US downgrade weighs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-usd-opened-week-lower-as-moodys-us-downgrade-weighs-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-usd-opened-week-lower-as-moodys-us-downgrade-weighs-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-speaks-monday-on-economic-outlook-bostic-logan-and-kashkari-speak-also-20250519/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Williams speaks Monday on economic outlook. Bostic, Logan and Kashkari speak also,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-will-strengthen-policy-coordination-20250519/&quot;&gt;China NBS spokesman (more): Will strengthen policy coordination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-foreigntradeovercamedifficulties-maintainedsteadygrowth-20250519/&quot;&gt;China NBS spokesman (more): Foreign trade overcame difficulties, maintained steady growth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-fin-min-kato-says-japan-not-facing-problem-getting-funds-via-debt-issuance-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan fin min Kato says Japan not facing problem getting funds via debt issuance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/centrist-victory-in-romania-defeats-far-right-candidate-a-democratic-signal-20250519/&quot;&gt;Centrist Victory in Romania Defeats Far-Right Candidate: A Democratic Signal?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-panel-approve-trump-tax-cut-bill-setting-up-a-possible-vote-on-passage-this-week-20250519/&quot;&gt;US House panel approve Trump tax cut bill, setting up a possible vote on passage this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-prime-minister-ishiba-japan-financial-situation-worse-than-greece-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan Prime Minister Ishiba: Japan financial situation worse than Greece&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-stats-spokesman-contribution-of-consumptiontoecogrowthwillcontinuetoincrease-20250519/&quot;&gt;China Stats spokesman: contribution of consumption to eco growth will continue to increase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/&quot;&gt;Chinese officials say the economy is growing steadily in the face of pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/sp-500-analysis-for-today-by-tradecompass-20250519/&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 Analysis for Today by tradeCompass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-industrial-output-april-2025-61-yy-expected-55-prior-77-20250519/&quot;&gt;China Industrial Output April 2025 +6.1% y/y (expected 5.5%, prior +7.7%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-depgov-uchida-will-keep-raising-interest-rates-if-economy-prices-improve-as-forecast-20250519/&quot;&gt;BOJ DepGov Uchida  Will keep raising interest rates if economy, prices improve as forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-new-home-prices-unchanged-mm-in-april-4-yy-20250519/&quot;&gt;China new home prices unchanged m/m in April, -4% y/y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71916-vs-estimate-at-72057-20250519/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1916 (vs. estimate at 7.2057)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-agriculture-ministry-suspended-imports-of-poultry-from-parts-of-brazil-bird-flu-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan’s Agriculture Ministry  suspended imports of poultry from parts of Brazil - bird flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-says-again-cant-accept-us-tariffs-on-autos-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan PM Ishiba says again can&apos;t accept US tariffs on autos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-hitting-its-highest-since-the-end-of-january-circa-usd106400-20250519/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin hitting its highest since the end of January, circa USD106,400+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-goldman-sachs-us-tariffs-may-weaken-the-dollar-as-growth-slows-20250518/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Goldman Sachs: US tariffs may weaken the dollar as growth slows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-house-price-indicator-shows-smallest-springtime-rise-since-2016-20250518/&quot;&gt;UK house price indicator shows smallest Springtime rise since 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-q1-ppi-inputs-and-outputs-both-higher-qq-20250518/&quot;&gt;New Zealand Q1 PPI inputs and outputs both higher q/q&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-data-april-services-pmi-drops-deeper-into-contraction-at-485-prior-491-20250518/&quot;&gt;New Zealand data: April Services PMI drops deeper into contraction at 48.5 (prior 49.1)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/globex-is-open-us-equity-index-futures-drop-sp500-es-down-07-nasdaq-nq-down-09-20250518/&quot;&gt;Globex is open! US equity index futures drop. S&amp;amp;P500 (ES) down 0.7%. NASDAQ (NQ) down 0.9%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-19-may-2025-chinese-economic-activity-data-for-april-20250518/&quot;&gt;Economic calendar in Asia 19 May 2025 - Chinese economic activity data for April&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-monday-19-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250518/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Monday, 19 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/binance-and-kraken-said-to-have-been-targets-of-coinbase-like-hack-attacks-20250518/&quot;&gt;Binance and Kraken said to have been targets of Coinbase-like hack attacks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/monday-morning-forex-rates-update-jpy-and-eur-higher-20250518/&quot;&gt;Monday morning forex rates update - JPY and EUR higher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/romanian-centrist-presidential-candidate-ahead-with-543-after-97-of-votes-counted-20250518/&quot;&gt;Romanian centrist Presidential candidate ahead with 54.3% after 97% of votes counted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/weekend-bessent-threatens-tariff-rates-to-return-to-reciprocal-levels-if-no-trade-deal-20250518/&quot;&gt;Weekend: Bessent threatens tariff rates to return to ‘reciprocal’ levels if no trade deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/former-president-joe-biden-was-diagnosed-with-an-aggressive-form-of-prostate-cancer-20250518/&quot;&gt;Former President Joe Biden was diagnosed with an &quot;aggressive form&quot; of prostate cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eyes-on-euro-politics-romania-centrist-dan-appears-on-course-to-win-romanian-presidency-20250518/&quot;&gt;Eyes on Euro politics - Romania centrist Dan appears on course to win Romanian presidency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/monday-open-levels-indicative-fx-prices-19-may-2025-20250518/&quot;&gt;Monday open levels, indicative FX prices, 19 May 2025&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weekend:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-weekend-news-hasnt-been-great-for-market-confidence-20250518/&quot;&gt;The weekend news hasn&apos;t been great for market confidence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-pm-starmer-expected-to-announce-brexit-reset-deal-on-monday-is-brexin-the-word-20250518/&quot;&gt;UK PM Starmer expected to announce Brexit ­&quot;reset&quot; deal on Monday. (Is Brexin the word?)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-pm-albanese-says-hes-up-for-a-deal-with-europe-on-free-trade-20250518/&quot;&gt;Australian PM Albanese says he&apos;s &quot;up for a deal&quot; with Europe on free trade&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-lagardeeurusd-up-justified-by-the-uncertainty-loss-of-confidence-in-us-policies-20250518/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Lagarde:EUR/USD up justified by the uncertainty &amp;amp; loss of confidence in US policies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-central-bank-board-member-schnabel-cautious-on-a-june-ecb-rate-cut-20250517/&quot;&gt;European Central Bank Board Member Schnabel cautious on a June ECB rate cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-kazaks-rate-cuts-may-be-nearing-end-but-outlook-still-uncertain-20250517/&quot;&gt;ECB’s Kazaks: Rate cuts may be nearing end, but outlook still uncertain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/newsquawk-week-ahead-uk-eu-summit-rba-china-activity-data-global-pmi-data-canada-cpi-20250517/&quot;&gt;Newsquawk Week Ahead: UK-EU Summit, RBA, China Activity Data, Global PMI Data, Canada CPI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/friday-bombshell-moodys-downgrades-the-us-credit-rating-20250516/&quot;&gt;Friday bombshell: Moody&apos;s downgrades US credit rating&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-hot-umich-inflation-expectations-cool-fed-rate-cut-talk-20250516/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Hot UMich inflation expectations cool Fed rate cut talk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;225&quot; data-end=&quot;450&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Markets reopened for the new week digesting the late-Friday US credit rating downgrade by Moody’s. The agency announced the move after US markets had closed, a decision some have called oddly timed—perhaps even irresponsible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;452&quot; data-end=&quot;867&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Opening FX trade saw a generally weaker US dollar, with the most notable move in USD/JPY, which fell more than 60 points from Friday’s close. EUR/USD also edged higher, with gains extending after Romania’s presidential election results came in. Pro-EU and pro-NATO candidate Dan won, defeating a far-right challenger. The outcome was interpreted as a win for EU political stability, lending the euro a modest boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;869&quot; data-end=&quot;970&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;As the session wore on, the dollar continued to soften a touch, the move was far from a rout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;972&quot; data-end=&quot;1108&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;US equity index futures gapped lower on the Globex open, as did US Treasury futures. As of writing, equity futures have slipped further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1110&quot; data-end=&quot;1163&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China&apos;s April data was the key focus for the session:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1165&quot; data-end=&quot;1477&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1165&quot; data-end=&quot;1236&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1167&quot; data-end=&quot;1236&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Industrial output rose 6.1% y/y (vs. 5.5% expected, prior 7.7%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1237&quot; data-end=&quot;1303&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1239&quot; data-end=&quot;1303&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Retail sales grew 5.1% y/y (vs. 5.5% expected, prior 5.9%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1304&quot; data-end=&quot;1380&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1306&quot; data-end=&quot;1380&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Fixed asset investment was up 4.0% YTD (vs. 4.2% expected and prior)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1381&quot; data-end=&quot;1444&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1383&quot; data-end=&quot;1444&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Surveyed jobless rate dipped to 5.1% from 5.2% in March&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1445&quot; data-end=&quot;1477&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1447&quot; data-end=&quot;1477&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;House prices remained soft&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1479&quot; data-end=&quot;1772&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Overall, the data were mixed. Industrial activity held up well, even as signs of weaker consumption and ongoing deflationary pressures linger. Trump’s tariffs have yet to cause significant damage, though slowing exports and falling bank lending suggest headwinds are mounting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1774&quot; data-end=&quot;2158&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In Japan, Prime Minister Ishiba ruled out tax cuts funded by new debt, acknowledging that with market interest rates now positive, the country’s fiscal health is &quot;worse than Greece.&quot; Finance Minister Kato added that Japan is not facing problems issuing debt but warned that a loss of market trust could weaken the yen and trigger inflationary stress. JPY barely moved on the comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2160&quot; data-end=&quot;2468&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In the US, a House committee narrowly advanced President Trump’s tax cut package in a 17–16 vote on Sunday evening. Interestingly, four GOP “hardliners” who had opposed it earlier shifted their &quot;no&quot; stance to “present.” Hardliners? That label seems generous if they caved so easily—perhaps just political theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2470&quot; data-end=&quot;2546&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin has continued its ascent, climbing to fresh highs above USD 106,500.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former US President Joe Biden has been diagnosed with an &apos;aggressive form&apos; of prostate cancer that has metastasized to the bone, his office said in a statement, adding that &apos;the cancer appears to be hormone-sensitive which allows for effective management&apos; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We wish him well. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Williams speaks Monday on economic outlook. Bostic, Logan and Kashkari speak also,</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-speaks-monday-on-economic-outlook-bostic-logan-and-kashkari-speak-also-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-speaks-monday-on-economic-outlook-bostic-logan-and-kashkari-speak-also-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The times listed below are GMT/US Eastern time:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1230/0830		Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic gives welcome remarks before the 2025 Financial Markets Conference - &quot;Financial Intermediation In Transition: How Will Policy Adapt?&quot; hosted by the Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1245/0845		Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams speaks on the economic outlook before the Mortgage Bankers Association Secondary and Capital Markets Conference, in New York&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1245/0845		Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic moderates a discussion before the 2025 Financial Markets Conference - &quot;Financial Intermediation In Transition: How Will Policy Adapt?&quot; hosted by the Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1715/1315	 Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas President Lorie Logan is a panel moderator at the &quot;Policy Session 2: The Increasing Role of Nonbank Institutions in the Treasury and Money Markets&quot; before the 2025 Financial Markets Conference&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1730/1330		Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis President Neel Kashkari participates in conversation before the Minnesota Young American Leaders Program (MYALP) at the University of Minnesota, in Minneapolis, Minn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Williams speech would seem the most pertinent for traders. Doubly so as Williams, being NY Fed chief, has a permanent vote on the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC), and indeed is vice-chair of the committee. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China NBS spokesman (more): Will strengthen policy coordination</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-will-strengthen-policy-coordination-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-will-strengthen-policy-coordination-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China National Bureau of Statistics (NBS) spokesman:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability of foreign trade enterprises to develop market has increased, have strong adjustment capabilities during trade friction and fluctuations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China has the conditions, ability and confidence to deal with various challenges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Necessary to see that the current overall low prices will increase the pressure on enterprises and affect the income growth of residents&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Structural contradiction of employment is still prominent, and employment pressure on youth group is great.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will strengthen policy coordination and promote urban renewal and affordable housing construction, for stable and healthy development of real estate market&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-foreigntradeovercamedifficulties-maintainedsteadygrowth-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China NBS spokesman (more): Foreign trade overcame difficulties, maintained steady growth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-stats-spokesman-contribution-of-consumptiontoecogrowthwillcontinuetoincrease-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;China Stats spokesman: contribution of consumption to eco growth will continue to increase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-industrial-output-april-2025-61-yy-expected-55-prior-77-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;China Industrial Output April 2025 +6.1% y/y (expected 5.5%, prior +7.7%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;Chinese officials say the economy is growing steadily in the face of pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China NBS spokesman (more): Foreign trade overcame difficulties, maintained steady growth</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-foreigntradeovercamedifficulties-maintainedsteadygrowth-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:45:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-foreigntradeovercamedifficulties-maintainedsteadygrowth-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt; China National Bureau of Statistics (NBS) spokesman:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We need to recognize that the internal driving force for investment growth is ‘obviously insufficient’&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We need to improve the efficiency of investment and continue to optimize the structure of investment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Foreign trade overcame difficulties and maintained steady growth in April, demonstrated strong resilience and international competitiveness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The reduction of tariffs by China and the United States in the next stage is conducive to the growth of bilateral trade and the recovery of the world economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Against increased external shocks, China’s foreign trade has been able to withstand pressure and continue to grow &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article-slot__title title top&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-stats-spokesman-contribution-of-consumptiontoecogrowthwillcontinuetoincrease-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China Stats spokesman: contribution of consumption to eco growth will continue to increase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-industrial-output-april-2025-61-yy-expected-55-prior-77-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;China Industrial Output April 2025 +6.1% y/y (expected 5.5%, prior +7.7%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Chinese officials say the economy is growing steadily in the face of pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
