<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 *MORGAN STANLEY PLANS TO OFFER CRYPTO TRADING TO E*TRADE CLIENTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917885701397299485#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:15:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917885701397299485#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 *MORGAN STANLEY PLANS TO OFFER CRYPTO TRADING TO E*TRADE CLIENTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - TESLA CHAIR DENIES PLANS TO LOOK FOR NEW CEO TO REPLACE MUSK

Robyn Denholm, the board chair of Tesla, has denied a Wall Street Journal report that said board members have reached out to several executive search firms to facilitate finding the next CEO for the company. Denholm says the report is &quot;absolutely false&quot; and said that the EV maker&apos;s board is &quot;highly confident&quot; in Musk&apos;s ability to &quot;continue executing on the exciting growth plan ahead.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917881191320928734#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:58:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917881191320928734#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - TESLA CHAIR DENIES PLANS TO LOOK FOR NEW CEO TO REPLACE MUSK&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Robyn Denholm, the board chair of Tesla, has denied a Wall Street Journal report that said board members have reached out to several executive search firms to facilitate finding the next CEO for the company. Denholm says the report is &quot;absolutely false&quot; and said that the EV maker&apos;s board is &quot;highly confident&quot; in Musk&apos;s ability to &quot;continue executing on the exciting growth plan ahead.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JANET YELLEN WARNS TRUMP TARIFFS WILL HAVE ‘TREMENDOUSLY ADVERSE’ IMPACT: FT

“[The tariff strategy] will have tremendously adverse consequences for the United States, for consumers, for the competitiveness of firms that rely on imported inputs,” Yellen told the Financial Times, noting that about 40 per cent of goods imported into the country were inputs for domestic production.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917880140287115427#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917880140287115427#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JANET YELLEN WARNS TRUMP TARIFFS WILL HAVE ‘TREMENDOUSLY ADVERSE’ IMPACT: FT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
“[The tariff strategy] will have tremendously adverse consequences for the United States, for consumers, for the competitiveness of firms that rely on imported inputs,” Yellen told the Financial Times, noting that about 40 per cent of goods imported into the country were inputs for domestic production.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) UKRAINE&apos;S FOREIGN MINISTER SAYS HE HAS INFORMED EU&apos;S TOP DIPLOMAT ABOUT MINERALS DEAL WITH U.S.

UKRAINE&apos;S FOREIGN MINISTER SAYS THE DEAL MARKS AN IMPORTANT MILESTONE IN PARTNERSHIP WITH U.S.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917879355541471720#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:50:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917879355541471720#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UKRAINE&apos;S FOREIGN MINISTER SAYS HE HAS INFORMED EU&apos;S TOP DIPLOMAT ABOUT MINERALS DEAL WITH U.S.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
UKRAINE&apos;S FOREIGN MINISTER SAYS THE DEAL MARKS AN IMPORTANT MILESTONE IN PARTNERSHIP WITH U.S.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former US Treasury Secretary Yellen: Trump tariffs to have &apos;tremendously adverse&apos; impact</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/former-us-treasury-secretary-yellen-trump-tariffs-to-have-tremendously-adverse-impact-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:16:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/former-us-treasury-secretary-yellen-trump-tariffs-to-have-tremendously-adverse-impact-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump tariffs to have &apos;tremendously adverse&apos; impact on the US economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;They &apos;hobble&apos; companies that rely on critical minerals supplies from China.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;About 40% of goods imported into the country were inputs for domestic production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The odds for a recession have gone up.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs could be particularly problematic for the US clean energy sector.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are highly dependent on China for most of the critical minerals that go into the clean energy technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s a very consensus view that tariffs will likely have an adverse impact on the US economy and that the recession probabilities have gone up. The market priced that in soon after the April 2 announcement, but started to price out that view after Trump&apos;s pause on April 9.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market is now looking forward to positive resolutions that will eventually trigger the opposite effect: the US economy will bounce back and economic activity will rise. That&apos;s why trade talks and negotiations are critical. If they disappoint the market, then we will likely go back to price in the recession. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MUSK SAYS DOGE ‘SHOULD DEFINITELY’ EXAMINE FEDERAL RESERVE COSTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917869107493405026#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 09:10:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917869107493405026#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MUSK SAYS DOGE ‘SHOULD DEFINITELY’ EXAMINE FEDERAL RESERVE COSTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US futures continue to hold up in European morning trade</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-futures-continue-to-hold-up-in-european-morning-trade-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:42:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-futures-continue-to-hold-up-in-european-morning-trade-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It is mostly tech shares leading the charge though with Nasdaq futures marked up by 1.4% currently. The late rebound yesterday was certainly intriguing but it&apos;s been followed up with some better earnings releases from Meta and Microsoft. Dip buyers are continuing to hold the line with the S&amp;amp;P 500 looking to build on last week&apos;s push above 5,500. Some relevant headlines in case you missed them:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-q1-advance-gdp-03-vs-03-expected-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US Q1 advance GDP -0.3% vs +0.3% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-sees-more-fed-rate-cuts-after-the-weak-us-gdp-but-it-could-be-wrong-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;The market sees more Fed rate cuts after the weak US GDP but it could be wrong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-recently-reached-out-to-china-for-tariff-talks-report-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US recently reached out to China for tariff talks - report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/meta-eps-643-versus-521-estimate-revenues-4231b-versus-4136b-estimate-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Meta EPS $6.43 versus $5.21 estimate. Revenues $42.31B versus $41.36B estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/microsoft-earnings-beat-expectations-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Microsoft earnings beat expectations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelpForAfricanAmericans is Expanding Access to Financial Aid for African Americans</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/helpforafricanamericans-is-expanding-access-to-financial-aid-for-african-americans-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:40:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/helpforafricanamericans-is-expanding-access-to-financial-aid-for-african-americans-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Many individuals and families across the United States face
financial hardship, often struggling to cover essential expenses such as rent,
utilities, childcare, and medical bills. Navigating the complex landscape of
financial assistance programs can be overwhelming, especially for those who are
unsure of where to start or what resources are available to them. This is where
HelpForAfricanAmericans, the largest directory of financial assistance programs
for African Americans, steps in to provide crucial support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HelpForAfricanAmericans operates an extensive database that
compiles information on financial aid opportunities for African Americans in
all 50 states and Washington, D.C. Through its website, users can access a
comprehensive list of programs offering support for various needs, including
help with groceries, rent, utility bills, college expenses, medical bills, and
more. The goal is to connect individuals with the resources that can provide
meaningful assistance during times of financial strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key aspect of the website’s mission is accessibility. By
centralizing information on available financial aid programs, the directory
eliminates much of the guesswork and frustration that often accompanies the
search for assistance. Instead of combing through multiple sources, individuals
can quickly find relevant programs in their state, making it easier to apply
for the help they need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The directory covers a wide range of financial aid topics,
ensuring that people can find assistance tailored to their specific
circumstances. Programs listed include grants for home and car repairs, food
assistance, legal aid, childcare support, and help with medical expenses. There
are also resources for those seeking debt consolidation, foreclosure
prevention, and college scholarships. Additionally, specialized programs cater
to individuals with disabilities, seniors, and those facing unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the most popular topics among users include rent
assistance, cash aid for those in need, support for purchasing a car or
computer, and help with groceries. These high-demand programs reflect the
common financial challenges faced by many African Americans and highlight the
organization’s commitment to addressing pressing concerns within the community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond individual financial assistance, the directory also
provides information on broader government welfare programs and nonprofit
organizations dedicated to supporting African Americans. Users can explore
options such as Section 8 housing assistance, food stamps, and state-specific
grants designed to alleviate financial burdens. The inclusion of these
resources ensures that individuals have a comprehensive understanding of the
aid available to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The website’s approach is rooted in empowerment. Equipping
people with knowledge about financial assistance programs enables them to make
informed decisions about their financial well-being. The platform also serves
as an educational resource, helping individuals understand eligibility
requirements, application processes, and the scope of available aid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to providing a directory of financial
assistance programs, HelpForAfricanAmericans actively works to keep its
information up to date. The landscape of financial aid is constantly evolving,
with new programs being introduced and existing ones undergoing changes.
Maintaining accurate and current information ensures that users can rely on the
directory as a trusted resource.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those seeking financial relief, finding the right
assistance program can make a significant difference. Whether it’s a grant for
college tuition, support for managing debt, or help covering medical expenses,
https://helpforafricanamericans.org/ simplifies the search process and connects
African Americans with the resources they need. With a commitment to
accessibility, accuracy, and comprehensive coverage, this financial assistance
directory plays a crucial role in bridging the gap between individuals in need
and the support systems designed to help them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About HelpforAfricanAmericans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Help for African Americans, the mission is to empower
and uplift the African American community by providing accessible resources,
vital information, and support for those in need. The platform works to bridge
gaps in healthcare, education, social justice, and economic opportunity by
fostering a nationwide network of information and solidarity.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK April final manufacturing PMI 45.4 vs 44.0 prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-454-vs-440-prelim-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:31:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-final-manufacturing-pmi-454-vs-440-prelim-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing PMI 45.4 vs 44.0 prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 44.9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key details:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;New orders and employment all decrease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Input cost inflation at 28-month high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rob Dobson, Director at S&amp;amp;P Global Market Intelligence
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The start of the second quarter saw UK manufacturing
buffeted by adverse global market conditions, rising cost
pressures, deteriorating supply chains and increased
trade uncertainty. April saw further contractions in
output, new orders and exports, as well as a slump in
business confidence to its lowest ebb since November
2022.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Although domestic demand remains soft, overseas
demand is especially weak. New export business fell
at the quickest pace for nearly five years, with demand
from clients in the US, Europe and mainland China all
declining. Surveyed manufacturers noted that US tariff
announcements were having a noticeable impact on
global markets as trading partners adapt to increased
trade volatility.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Manufacturers are also seeing an increasingly harsh
cost environment, with purchase price inflation hitting
a 28-month high. Alongside general raw material price
increases on global markets, UK producers are also facing
domestic inflationary pressure from increases to National
Insurance, minimum wages and the knock-on impact of
the latter on higher pay grades. These increased costs
are resulting in a combination of higher selling prices
and cutbacks to non-essential spending on staffing
and purchasing, potentially reinforcing the &apos;rising costs,
declining demand&apos; backdrop.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK March mortgage approvals 64.31k vs 64.80k expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-mortgage-approvals-6431k-vs-6480k-expected-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:30:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-mortgage-approvals-6431k-vs-6480k-expected-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 65.48k; revised to 65.09k&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Net consumer credit £0.9 billion vs £1.2 billion expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior £1.3 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;After a decrease of £1.0 billion in February, net borrowing of mortgage debt by UK individuals rebounded sharply in March by by £9.7 billion to £13.0 billion. Meanwhile, net consumer credit is seen falling with the annual growth rate also easing further to 6.1% - down from 6.4% in February.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The S&amp;P 500 confirms the breakout as the de-escalation trend continues</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-sp-500-confirms-the-breakout-as-the-de-escalation-trend-continues-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 08:26:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-sp-500-confirms-the-breakout-as-the-de-escalation-trend-continues-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The stock market bottomed a week after the April 2 announcement when President Trump paused the reciprocal tariffs for 90 days on April 9. That week we reached the peak in trade escalation and from that moment onwards, the risk/reward picture favoured the upside for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/this-is-the-key-line-from-chinas-retaliation-you-should-focus-on-20250411/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;de-escalation trend&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The negative data continues to be faded because it&apos;s old news and the market is looking forward to positive resolutions and eventually higher economic activity as the trade uncertainty wanes. This trend is likely to remain intact until we get the details of the first trade deal. If the average tariff rate is 10% or lower, we should see the market continuing higher and eventually make new all-time highs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, a rate above 10% would likely be a disappointment and the market could go back pricing in slower growth with the stock market selling off again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can see that the S&amp;amp;P 500 broke above the key resistance level and the major trendline. We got a retest of the broken resistance yesterday when the US GDP triggered some short-term weakness, but eventually we got back to the highs and even made new ones. The next target is the swing level around 5,800 price region. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can see the short-term selloff triggered by the US GDP that eventually bottomed around the key 5,480 level where the dip buyers piled in and got some support from good US Core PCE data. Later in the day, we also got the news that the US reached to China for tariff talks which supported further upside. And everything culminated with strong tech earnings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We now have the 5,596 level as the closest support where the buyers could step in with a defined risk below the level to position for further upside. In case of a break though, the sellers will likely push the price all the way back to the 5,520 level where we will find a minor upward trendline. That will be the next support for the dip-buyers. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The market sees more Fed rate cuts after the weak US GDP but it could be wrong</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-sees-more-fed-rate-cuts-after-the-weak-us-gdp-but-it-could-be-wrong-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:51:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-sees-more-fed-rate-cuts-after-the-weak-us-gdp-but-it-could-be-wrong-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Rate cuts by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 100 bps (91% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 64 bps (86% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 96 bps (96% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 53 bps (55% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 118 bps (92% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 78 bps (75% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 33 bps (81% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 10 bps (97% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We can see that since the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-interest-rate-expectations-for-g8fx-20250428/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;last update&lt;/a&gt;, the biggest moves in interest rate expectations happened with the Fed and the BoJ. The market increased the easing bets for the Fed following the weaker than expected US Q1 GDP yesterday. and decreased the tightening bets for the BoJ following the dovish policy decision and Governor Ueda&apos;s comments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These expectations hinge on the trade deals though. If the details of the first trade deal show that the average tariff rate will be at or below 10%, then we can expect the market to reprice the expectations on a more hawkish side. Markets tend to overshoot expectations and that&apos;s what provides traders with mean reversion opportunities. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJ governor Ueda: If the outlook changes, then we will need to adjust our policy</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-if-the-outlook-changes-then-we-will-need-to-adjust-our-policy-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:25:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-if-the-outlook-changes-then-we-will-need-to-adjust-our-policy-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The outlook could be less accurate than before&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We can&apos;t ignore US tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But also should not overemphasise their impact&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If US tariffs are zero or at low level, then quicker rate hike could be possible&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But no need to raise rates hastily when underlying inflation is stalling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For not wanting to put too much emphasis on its impact, he sure talked a lot about tariffs today. USD/JPY currently trades at 144.57 on the day, up from around 144.20 prior to Ueda&apos;s presser.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – The stagflationary risk continues to be priced out</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-the-stagflationary-risk-continues-to-be-priced-out-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:09:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-the-stagflationary-risk-continues-to-be-priced-out-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold continues to correct
lower as the market unwinds some of the stagflationary risk that was priced in
in the past months. The de-escalation trend will likely remain intact until the
first trade deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stagflationary pricing is
what got gold to such high prices, and as we start to price out that risk, it’s
normal to see a correction, especially considering that “long gold” has been
the most crowded trade. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the bigger picture, gold
remains in an uptrend as real yields will likely continue to fall amid Fed
easing. But in the short-term more positive news on the tariffs front should see
more downside for gold as the market readjusts to new conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that gold broke out of the recent range to the downside as the market
continues to reprice the stagflationary risks. From a risk management
perspective, the buyers will have a better risk to reward setup around the previous
high at 3167 to position for further upside, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into the major trendline around the
3100 level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see more clearly the breakout of the range between the 3258 support and the
3367 resistance. We now have a downward trendline defining the bearish
momentum. The sellers will likely step in around the broken support and the
trendline to position for further downside, while the buyers will want to see
the price breaking higher to target the 3367 level next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart,
there’s not much else we can add here as the sellers will likely step in both
at the broken support and the trendline, while the buyers will pile in at every
break higher. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt; we get the latest US Jobless Claims
figures and the US ISM Manufacturing PMI. Tomorrow, we conclude the week with
the US NFP report. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJ governor Ueda: Timing of next rate hike could be swayed a lot depending on tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-timing-of-next-rate-hike-could-be-swayed-a-lot-depending-on-tariffs-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-timing-of-next-rate-hike-could-be-swayed-a-lot-depending-on-tariffs-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Tariffs could negatively impact corporate profits and wage negotiations next year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But it doesn&apos;t mean we have to wait for all of that to make a policy decision&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Even when US tariffs are decided, the impact would be hard to read&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This just reinforces his points from earlier, justifying that they have hit the pause button until there is further clarity on how Trump&apos;s tariffs are going to play out.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJ governor Ueda says would expect US tariffs to be above the base 10% levied</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-says-would-expect-us-tariffs-to-be-above-the-base-10-levied-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:56:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-says-would-expect-us-tariffs-to-be-above-the-base-10-levied-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This is definitely an interesting comment, especially coming from someone in Ueda&apos;s position. Even if he isn&apos;t in the know, it would be less than prudent to speculate as such though. Or maybe I&apos;m just reading too much into it. But either way, good to keep this in the back of your mind just in case.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD/JPY extends gains as Ueda delivers more dovish messaging</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdjpy-extends-gains-as-ueda-delivers-more-dovish-messaging-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:53:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdjpy-extends-gains-as-ueda-delivers-more-dovish-messaging-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the bigger picture, the pair is seeing a neat double-bottom bounce off the 140.00 mark. And the jump higher today sees the pair now move to its highest in three weeks. It&apos;s largely a yen move here as the BOJ left interest rates unchanged, before governor Ueda came out to deliver some less hawkish (more dovish) messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Ueda said that there&apos;s a lot of uncertainty now stemming from US tariffs and how that is impacting the global outlook. He adds that inflation and wage pressures are now expected to cool and that there will be a delay to reaching their 2% price target. On the latter, Ueda says that it is &quot;not simple&quot; anymore to just talk about hitting the inflation target as such.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Overall, it points to a further pause in the current monetary policy stance. As things stand, that is likely to extend to June at the very least.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJ governor Ueda: Underlying inflation to cool down due to tariffs, slower global growth</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-underlying-inflation-to-cool-down-due-to-tariffs-slower-global-growth-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:41:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-underlying-inflation-to-cool-down-due-to-tariffs-slower-global-growth-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;But would expect underlying inflation to gradually pick up eventually&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expect inflation, wage growth to slow down due to tariffs, slower growth&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Outlook is not as certain as it was before&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Timing of underlying inflation to achieve 2% goal will be somewhat delayed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Appropriate to support the economy while maintaining easy monetary environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will guide policy from a standpoint of sustainably, stably achieving price target&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The remarks on slower growth and softer price pressures are aimed to justify the pause today and perhaps in June as well. It&apos;s no doubt a more dovish take. Analysts are largely seeing Q3 as the next point in which the BOJ will hike next. But we&apos;ll have to see how the narrative changes depending on Trump&apos;s tariffs as well in the weeks/months ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJ governor Ueda: Uncertainty stemming from trade policies have heightened sharply</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-uncertainty-stemming-from-trade-policies-have-heightened-sharply-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:32:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-governor-ueda-uncertainty-stemming-from-trade-policies-have-heightened-sharply-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan&apos;s economy is recovery moderately, although some weakness is still seen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economic growth likely to moderate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Economic, price projections could change vastly depending on how countries deal with US tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Must pay due attention to financial, FX markets and impact to Japan&apos;s economy, prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Expected to keep raising rates if economy, prices move in line with projections&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The key guidance of expecting to stick with rate hikes if the economic and inflation outlook plays out accordingly is still there, but there&apos;s now dovish elements introduced in the assessment towards the economy at least. It isn&apos;t all too surprising though with Trump tariffs becoming a negative drag towards the global outlook. But in the case of the BOJ, it does dampen the spirits of pushing too hawkishly on hiking rates. From before: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economists-now-more-split-on-next-boj-rate-hike-poll-20250423/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Economists now more split on next BOJ rate hike - poll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 06:23:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session we don&apos;t have much on the agenda given that it&apos;s a holiday in Europe and therefore we should have a quiet session. There&apos;s just the final UK Manufacturing PMI, which is most likely going to be ignored. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we have the US Jobless Claims and the US ISM Manufacturing PMI. As it&apos;s been the case since April 2 (and as you saw yesterday), the market is not focused on the data because it&apos;s old news. The focus is on trade negotiations and the market continues to maintain positive expectations trading into the first trade deal announcement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ISM PMI is expected to be weak given the other regional releases, so it won&apos;t be a surprise. The only data I can see mattering is the US Jobless Claims, but the figure must be at very least above the 260K mark to gather attention. Initial Claims
remain inside the 200K-260K range created since 2022, while Continuing Claims hover
around cycle highs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The expectations are for Initial Claims to come at 224K vs 222K prior, while Continuing Claims are seen at 1864K vs 1841K prior. Other than that, keep an eye on tariff related news as that what matters on a forward looking basis. For now, we are in a de-escalation trend and it will likely remain intact until the first trade deal announcement.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 1 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-1-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 05:33:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-1-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There are a couple to take note of on the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The first ones are for EUR/USD, layered in between 1.1250 through to 1.1330. The expiries don&apos;t tie in to any technical significance but could play a part in limiting price action, especially to the downside in the session ahead. That since the dollar is putting up a stronger showing since overnight trading, with the pair slipping past recent lows around 1.1310-15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Then, there is one for USD/JPY at the 144.00 level. It also isn&apos;t one that ties to any technical significance, so I wouldn&apos;t expect the expiries to factor too much into play for this one. The post-BOJ mood and dollar sentiment remain stronger drivers of price action at this stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day holiday to keep things quiet in Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/labor-day-holiday-to-keep-things-quiet-in-europe-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 04:47:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/labor-day-holiday-to-keep-things-quiet-in-europe-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;London markets will be open for trading though but the other major hubs in Europe are all closed in observance of Labor Day. As such, there will be lighter flows in general but that won&apos;t stop an already busy-looking market to start the new month. The dollar is keeping steadier across the board, keeping with overnight gains. But was it all just month-end?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That comes after a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-q1-advance-gdp-03-vs-03-expected-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;dismal Q1 advance GDP report&lt;/a&gt;, owing largely to trade, one which &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-blames-biden-says-to-be-patient-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Trump is shifting the blame away from&lt;/a&gt;. Equities also staged a neat comeback yesterday, before US futures are seen advancing today after earnings beat from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/meta-eps-643-versus-521-estimate-revenues-4231b-versus-4136b-estimate-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Meta&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/microsoft-earnings-beat-expectations-20250430/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;. Tech shares are leading the charge with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up 0.9% and Nasdaq futures up 1.4% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Earlier, the BOJ left interest rates unchanged as expected but the yen is down on some minor disappointment. Ueda&apos;s press conference will be up next at 0630 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides that, there&apos;s not much else on the agenda in European trading besides the UK mortgage/credit conditions report for March at 0830 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Bank of Japan kept short-term interest rate at 0.5%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-bank-of-japan-kept-short-term-interest-rate-at-05-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:51:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-bank-of-japan-kept-short-term-interest-rate-at-05-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;Bank of Japan leaves policy unchanged, as widely expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/tesla-sales-fell-nearly-60-in-april-in-france-20250501/&quot;&gt;Tesla sales fell nearly 60% in April in France&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tesla-board-begins-quiet-search-for-possible-musk-successor-more-on-this-20250501/&quot;&gt;Tesla board begins quiet search for possible Musk successor - more on this&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tesla-has-opened-a-search-for-a-ceo-to-succeed-elon-musk-20250501/&quot;&gt;Tesla has opened a search for a CEO to succeed Elon Musk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/defense-secretary-pete-hegseth-threatens-iran-you-will-pay-the-consequence-20250501/&quot;&gt;Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth threatens Iran: &quot;You will pay the CONSEQUENCE&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-exports-76-mm-prior-42-imports-22-prior-18-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Australian March exports +7.6% m/m (prior -4.2%) &amp;amp; Imports -2.2% (prior +1.8%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-export-q1-price-index-21-qq-prior-36-import-33-qq-prior-02-20250501/&quot;&gt;Australian Export Q1 price index +2.1% q/q (prior +3.6%) &amp;amp; import +3.3% q/q (prior +0.2%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/reminder-chinese-markets-are-closed-for-holidays-will-reopen-on-tuesday-next-week-20250501/&quot;&gt;Reminder - Chinese markets are closed for holidays, will reopen on Tuesday next week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-jibun-bank-pmi-manufacturing-april-2025-final-487-prior-484-preliminary-485-20250501/&quot;&gt;Japan Jibun Bank PMI Manufacturing April 2025 Final 48.7 (prior 48.4, preliminary 48.5)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/china-is-right-behind-us-nvidia-ceo-warns-ai-chip-race-is-neck-and-neck-20250501/&quot;&gt;“China Is Right Behind Us”: Nvidia CEO Warns AI chip race is neck and neck&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korean-exports-rose-in-april-vs-fall-expected-20250501/&quot;&gt;South Korean exports rose in April vs. fall expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bnp-paribas-on-another-likely-catalyst-for-a-higher-eurusd-20250430/&quot;&gt;BNP Paribas on another likely catalyst for a higher EUR/USD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/april-uk-business-confidence-improved-to-its-highest-level-since-september-2023-20250430/&quot;&gt;April UK business confidence improved to its highest level since September 2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-sp-global-pmi-manufacturing-april-2025-final-517-prior-521-20250430/&quot;&gt;Australia S&amp;amp;P Global PMI Manufacturing April 2025, final 51.7 (prior 52.1)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-senate-narrowly-rejects-bipartisan-measure-to-block-trump-tariffs-20250430/&quot;&gt;U.S. Senate narrowly rejects bipartisan measure to block Trump tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/ford-has-abandoned-its-project-to-develop-tesla-like-electronic-brain-20250430/&quot;&gt;Ford has abandoned its project to develop Tesla-like electronic brain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/united-states-trade-representative-admits-there-are-no-official-talks-with-china-on-trade-20250430/&quot;&gt;United States trade representative admits there are no official talks with China on trade&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-rep-greer-says-initial-trade-deals-are-still-weeks-away-20250430/&quot;&gt;US Trade Rep Greer says &apos;initial&apos; trade deals are still weeks away&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/us-equity-index-have-gapped-higher-upon-globex-reopening-for-evening-trade-20250430/&quot;&gt;US equity index have gapped higher upon Globex reopening for evening trade&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ustreasuryannouncesagreementtoestablishus-ukrainereconstructioninvestmentfund-20250430/&quot;&gt;US Treasury announces agreement to establish US-Ukraine reconstruction investment fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-repeats-himself-says-fed-should-cut-interest-rates-20250430/&quot;&gt;Trump repeats himself, says Fed should cut interest rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-ukraine-have-signed-the-closely-watched-minerals-deal-bloomberg-cite-unnamed-source-20250430/&quot;&gt;US &amp;amp; Ukraine have signed the closely watched minerals deal - Bloomberg cite unnamed source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-us-gdp-dips-into-negative-territory-20250430/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: US GDP dips into negative territory&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-european-union-will-present-new-trade-proposals-to-us-negotiators-next-week-20250430/&quot;&gt;The European Union will present new trade proposals to us negotiators next week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-thursday-1-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250430/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Thursday, 1 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
The
Bank of Japan kept its short-term interest rate at 0.5%, a widely
exp4ected on hold decision. The BoJ cited growing headwinds from
higher US tariffs. The Bank cut its 2025 and 2026 economic growth
forecasts in its quarterly outlook report. This was a not unexpected
move. A cautious BoJ today. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;USD/JPY has risen towards 143.50 with the net dovish statement
and report. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Dialling
back the clock a little to before that focal point for the session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;In
late US time United
States trade representative Greer
admitted
that
there are no official talks with China on trade, He
said also that ‘initial’ trade deals with some other countries
are still weeks away. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Australia
published March trade data, showing a widening surplus on a surge in
exports, up 7.6% m/m on gold (26% rise in non-monetary gold
shipments) and other commodity shipments. Iron ore exports recovered
from weather disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Exports
to the US jumped. Australia runs a trade deficit with the US but in
March recorded a surplus ahead of tariffs. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Imports
dropped by 2.2% m/m, capital goods showing a notable drop. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Also
from Australia today were export and import price indexes. Consumer
goods import prices rose, which may impact inflation ahead if such
rises continue. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Of
note for those with an interest in equities, the Wall Street Journal
reported that Tesla’s board has begun discussions with search firms
to explore potential successors to CEO Elon Musk. In the reports the
Journal noted that Some directors, including Tesla co-founder JB
Straubel, have been meeting with major investors to reassure them the
company is in good hands. This will be in reference to the damage
Musk has inflicted on the brand through his political and ideological
activities. Data from France released today gave some insight into
this. While new
car registrations in France fell 5.64% in April from a year earlier
the figure for Tesla was an order of magnitude worse, Tesla sales
fell 59.45%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;US
equity indexes rose in ‘overnight’ Globex trade, adding to their
solid bounce during Wednesday RTH trade. 
&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian March exports +7.6% m/m (prior -4.2%) &amp; Imports -2.2% (prior +1.8%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-exports-76-mm-prior-42-imports-22-prior-18-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:44:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-march-exports-76-mm-prior-42-imports-22-prior-18-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;NOTE: MY BAD. i HAD THIS WRITTEN BUT DIDN&apos;T REALISE I HAD FORGOTTEN TO PUBLISH THIS EARLIER. APOLOGIES. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia Trade Balance for March 2025: AUD6900mn surplus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;expected +3200mn, prior +2968mn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exports +7.6% m/m&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior -3.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imports -2.2% m/m&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;prior +1.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-export-q1-price-index-21-qq-prior-36-import-33-qq-prior-02-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Australian Export Q1 price index +2.1% q/q (prior +3.6%) &amp;amp; import +3.3% q/q (prior +0.2%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD/JPY has popped a little higher after the BoJ statement and report - mixed but dovey</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/usdjpy-has-popped-a-little-higher-after-the-boj-statement-and-report-mixed-but-dovey-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:18:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/usdjpy-has-popped-a-little-higher-after-the-boj-statement-and-report-mixed-but-dovey-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;I posted the main points here:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Bank of Japan leaves policy unchanged, as widely expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In very brief:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;kept interest rates steady, short-term policy rate unchanged at 0.5% by a unanimous vote&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;cut its growth forecasts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;cited the damage to global demand from higher U.S. tariffs impacting Japan&apos;s nascent economic recovery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOJ Governor Ueda press conference is at 0630 GMT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY update:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Japan leaves policy unchanged, as widely expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:02:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bank of Japan leaves policy unchanged, as widely expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BOJ maintains short-term interestst rate target at 0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Board’s core CPI fiscal 2025 median forecast at +2.2% vs +2.4% in January&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI fiscal 2026 median forecast at +1.7% vs +2.0% in January&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI fiscal 2027 median forecast at +1.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core-core CPI fiscal 2025 median forecast at +2.3% vs +2.1% in January&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core-core CPI fiscal 2026 median forecast at +1.8% vs +2.1% in January&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core-core CPI fiscal 2027 median forecast at +2.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;BoJ report: will continue to raise policy rate if economy, prices move in line with its forecast&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s economic growth likely to moderate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Underlying consumer inflation likely to be at level generally consistent with 2% target in second half of projection period from fiscal 2025 through 2027&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty surrounding Japan’s economy, prices remain high&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be vigilant to financial, FX market moves and their impact on economy, prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Risks to economic outlook skewed to downside&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Risks to inflation outlook skewed to downside&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s economy recovering moderately, although some weaknesses are seen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Real interest rates are at significant low levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will conduct monetary policy as appropriate from perspective of sustainably, stably achieving 2% inflation target&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOJ report on risks: trade policy recently announced in each jurisdiction is likely to push down domestic and overseas economies through various channels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Introduction of wide-ranging tariffs is expected to impact global trade activity, uncertainties regarding policies including tariffs are likely to have large impact on business, household sentiment, global financial, capital markets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Import prices could rise, and push down domestic demand if disruptions in global logistics were to arise or moves to restructure supply chains were to take place and incur considerable costs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOJ quarterly report: Important for BoJ to carefully examine factors such as developments in economic activity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Important to judge whether the outlook will be realised without any preconception&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extreme uncertain how trade and other policies in each jurisdiction will evolve&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertain how overseas econimic activities and prices will react to them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s financial system has maintained stability on the whole&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If disruptions in global logistics were to arise or moves to restructure supply chains were to take place and incur considerable costs, import prices could rise&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This could in turn push down domestic demand&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Households’ defensive attitudes toward spending could strengthen further, and this could push down the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A prolonged period of high uncertainties regarding trade and otherpolicies in each jurisdiction could lead firms to focus more on cost cutting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moves to reflect price rises in wages could also weaken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background to this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/headlines-crossing-saying-the-boj-is-likely-to-slash-its-gdp-forecasts-from-4-days-ago-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Headlines crossing saying the BoJ is likely to slash its GDP forecasts - from 4 days ago&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still to come is Bank of Japan Governor Ueda&apos;s press conference at 0630 GMT / 0230 US Eastern time. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla sales fell nearly 60% in April in France</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tesla-sales-fell-nearly-60-in-april-in-france-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 02:27:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tesla-sales-fell-nearly-60-in-april-in-france-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The news broke earlier that Tesla is replacing Elon Musk as CEO:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tesla-board-begins-quiet-search-for-possible-musk-successor-more-on-this-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Tesla board begins quiet search for possible Musk successor - more on this&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data release from France earlier gives an indication to the urgency of this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While new
car registrations in France fell 5.64% in April from a year earlier the figure for Tesla was an order of magnitude worse:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla
 sales fell 59.45%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Year to date figures paint a similar picture:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;French market shrunk by 7.28%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tesla&apos;s sales have declined by 43.98%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The picture of Musk&apos;s Nazi salute flashed to screens globally and have done damage to Tesla&apos;s brand, along with other Musk missteps. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth threatens Iran: &quot;You will pay the CONSEQUENCE&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/defense-secretary-pete-hegseth-threatens-iran-you-will-pay-the-consequence-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 02:09:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/defense-secretary-pete-hegseth-threatens-iran-you-will-pay-the-consequence-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;174&quot; data-end=&quot;352&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth issued a stern warning to Iran over its support for Yemen’s Houthi rebels, who have been targeting Red Sea shipping in support of Palestinians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;353&quot; data-end=&quot;460&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;355&quot; data-end=&quot;460&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On social media, Hegseth wrote: “You will pay the CONSEQUENCE at the time and place of our choosing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;461&quot; data-end=&quot;583&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;463&quot; data-end=&quot;583&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The warning comes just days before U.S. and Iranian negotiators are set to resume nuclear talks in Rome on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;584&quot; data-end=&quot;714&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;586&quot; data-end=&quot;714&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Hegseth also reposted a message from former President Trump, reinforcing that Iran would be held accountable for Houthi attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;715&quot; data-end=&quot;795&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;717&quot; data-end=&quot;795&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Iran maintains that the Houthis act independently, denying direct control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;796&quot; data-end=&quot;890&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;798&quot; data-end=&quot;890&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The U.S. has already conducted over 1,000 airstrikes against Houthi targets since March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;891&quot; data-end=&quot;1175&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;893&quot; data-end=&quot;949&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;To bolster regional military presence, the Pentagon has:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;952&quot; data-end=&quot;1175&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;952&quot; data-end=&quot;1049&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;954&quot; data-end=&quot;1049&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Deployed six B-2 bombers to Diego Garcia, strategically located for Middle East operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1052&quot; data-end=&quot;1109&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1054&quot; data-end=&quot;1109&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Stationed two U.S. aircraft carriers in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1112&quot; data-end=&quot;1175&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1114&quot; data-end=&quot;1175&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Shifted air defense systems from Asia to the Middle East.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil traders will be watching for escalation in the Middle East. It may be sooner than we think?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla board begins quiet search for possible Musk successor - more on this</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tesla-board-begins-quiet-search-for-possible-musk-successor-more-on-this-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:45:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tesla-board-begins-quiet-search-for-possible-musk-successor-more-on-this-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;175&quot; data-end=&quot;447&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Tesla’s board has begun early discussions with executive search firms to explore potential successors to CEO Elon Musk, according to a report by the Wall Street Journal. The move reflects growing investor concern over Musk’s demanding schedule across multiple companies:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some directors, including Tesla co-founder JB Straubel, have been meeting with major investors to reassure them the company is in good hands.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;449&quot; data-end=&quot;464&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Wall Street Journal is gate, here are the key points from the piece:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;466&quot; data-end=&quot;863&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;466&quot; data-end=&quot;555&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;468&quot; data-end=&quot;555&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Tesla board members reached out to search firms last month, sources told the WSJ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;556&quot; data-end=&quot;625&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;558&quot; data-end=&quot;625&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The talks are described as exploratory and in the early stages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;626&quot; data-end=&quot;695&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;628&quot; data-end=&quot;695&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Musk currently leads Tesla, SpaceX, and several other ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;696&quot; data-end=&quot;749&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;698&quot; data-end=&quot;749&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Tesla has not commented publicly on the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;750&quot; data-end=&quot;863&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;752&quot; data-end=&quot;863&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Succession planning has been a longstanding concern among shareholders, given Musk’s many responsibilities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Musk&apos;s political activities have caused damage to the brand. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Export Q1 price index +2.1% q/q (prior +3.6%) &amp; import +3.3% q/q (prior +0.2%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-export-q1-price-index-21-qq-prior-36-import-33-qq-prior-02-20250501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:30:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-export-q1-price-index-21-qq-prior-36-import-33-qq-prior-02-20250501/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Australian terms of trade data for Q1 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD barely changed. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TESLA BOARD OPENED SEARCH FOR CEO TO SUCCEED ELON MUSK: WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917749392158908561#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:14:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917749392158908561#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TESLA BOARD OPENED SEARCH FOR CEO TO SUCCEED ELON MUSK: WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. SENATE NARROWLY REJECTS BIPARTISAN MEASURE TO BLOCK TRUMP TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917714267543068692#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:54:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917714267543068692#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. SENATE NARROWLY REJECTS BIPARTISAN MEASURE TO BLOCK TRUMP TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *U.S. TRADE REP: *NO OFFICIAL TALKS YET WITH CHINA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917707133757301160#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:26:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917707133757301160#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*U.S. TRADE REP: *NO OFFICIAL TALKS YET WITH CHINA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *NO OFFICIAL TALKS YET WITH CHINA: GREER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917705984908177443#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:21:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917705984908177443#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*NO OFFICIAL TALKS YET WITH CHINA: GREER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *GREER SAYS THERE ARE NO OFFICIAL TALKS W/ CHINA YET: RTRS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917705575791747323#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:20:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917705575791747323#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*GREER SAYS THERE ARE NO OFFICIAL TALKS W/ CHINA YET: RTRS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US AND UKRAINE SIGN NATURAL RESOURCES DEAL: PERSON FAMILIAR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917692184297451601#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917692184297451601#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US AND UKRAINE SIGN NATURAL RESOURCES DEAL: PERSON FAMILIAR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *EU TO PRESENT TRADE PROPOSALS TO US NEXT WEEK, OFFICIALS SAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917683513156894887#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:52:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917683513156894887#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*EU TO PRESENT TRADE PROPOSALS TO US NEXT WEEK, OFFICIALS SAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HASSETT: WOULDN&apos;T BE SURPRISED IF GDP DATA IS REVISED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917674948891664732#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:18:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917674948891664732#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HASSETT: WOULDN&apos;T BE SURPRISED IF GDP DATA IS REVISED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) META PLATFORMS SHARES UP 2.9% AFTER THE BELL FOLLOWING RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917672270241079602#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:07:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917672270241079602#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;META PLATFORMS SHARES UP 2.9% AFTER THE BELL FOLLOWING RESULTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *META 1Q EPS $6.43, EST. $5.25
*META 1Q REV. $42.31B, EST. $41.38B</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917672015722385704#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:06:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917672015722385704#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*META 1Q EPS $6.43, EST. $5.25&lt;br&gt;
*META 1Q REV. $42.31B, EST. $41.38B&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MICROSOFT SHARES ADD TO AFTER-HOURS GAINS; LAST UP 6.4%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917671331216384410#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:04:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917671331216384410#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MICROSOFT SHARES ADD TO AFTER-HOURS GAINS; LAST UP 6.4%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *MICROSOFT 3Q AZURE &amp; OTHER CLOUD REV EX-FX +33%, EST. +31%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917671087082533343#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:03:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917671087082533343#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*MICROSOFT 3Q AZURE &amp;amp; OTHER CLOUD REV EX-FX +33%, EST. +31%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *MICROSOFT 3Q REV. $70.07B, EST. $68.48B
*MICROSOFT Q3 EPS $3.46; IBES ESTIMATE $3.22</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917670990709956811#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917670990709956811#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*MICROSOFT 3Q REV. $70.07B, EST. $68.48B&lt;br&gt;
*MICROSOFT Q3 EPS $3.46; IBES ESTIMATE $3.22&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) m.weibo.cn/status/5161297214…</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917644532004311281#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:17:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917644532004311281#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://m.weibo.cn/status/5161297214704166&quot;&gt;m.weibo.cn/status/5161297214…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917642055607804230#m&quot;&gt;localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917642055607804230#m&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:8080/pic/media%2FGpzXcVsWEAAGiEQ.jpg&quot; style=&quot;max-width:250px;&quot; /&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CIRCLE IS SAID TO HAVE REJECTED RIPPLE BID AS TOO LOW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1917644352903426273#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:16:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917644352903426273#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CIRCLE IS SAID TO HAVE REJECTED RIPPLE BID AS TOO LOW&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917643831802986886#m&quot;&gt;localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1917643831802986886#m&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
