<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Makhlouf: Uncertainty is weighing on investment</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-makhlouf-uncertainty-is-weighing-on-investment-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:11:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-makhlouf-uncertainty-is-weighing-on-investment-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty is weighing on investment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soft data pointing to a significant cooling in business and consumer sentiment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Global economic integretion is now stalled, if not reversing; last few weeks have seen an acceleration in pace and scale of change.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Even if a full-blown trade war turns out to be short-lived, uncertainty effects will persist for some time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monetary policy must adapt to the new nature of supply shocks generated by geoeconomic fragmentation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Given effects of size, scale and more persistent nature of fragmentation-induced shocks, and their impact on prices, monetary policy responses will need careful calibration.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Threats of inflation de-anchoring, from both above and below, warrant forceful and persistent responses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interest rates remains default policy lever in our toolbox; when constrained by lower bound, other tools such as targeted lending and balance sheet operations have their uses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He&apos;s suggesting a more careful approach to interest rates adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar holds slightly lower so far on the session</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-holds-slightly-lower-so-far-on-the-session-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:10:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-holds-slightly-lower-so-far-on-the-session-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;After the strong gains yesterday, the dollar is catching a bit of a breather in trading today. This comes as US futures are also just down slightly after the surging gains in the day before. Market players are digesting the US-China trade truce and will have to wait to see if the optimism can be justified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;USD/JPY is down 0.4% to 147.85 but it doesn&apos;t take much away from the over 300 pips jump from yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Meanwhile, EUR/USD is up 0.2% to 1.1115 and GBP/USD up 0.3% to 1.3215 on the day. USD/CHF is also marked down by 0.7% to 0.8395 but is still well higher compared to the Friday close last week near 0.8300. The antipodes are also faring better with AUD/USD recovering a large chunk of its losses yesterday to 0.6405 - up 0.6% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Elsewhere, gold is also seen recovering back to $3,259 and holding the line near its 1 May low of $3,201 amid the drop yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Coming up later today, we&apos;ll have the US CPI report to add to the mix. We&apos;re not likely to see any major impact from tariffs show up though, so any kneejerk reaction to the numbers should be easily brushed aside.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BofA Fund Manager Survey: Fund Managers most underweight US Dollars since 2006</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-fund-manager-survey-fund-managers-most-underweight-us-dollars-since-2006-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:17:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-fund-manager-survey-fund-managers-most-underweight-us-dollars-since-2006-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fund Managers most underweight US Dollars since 2006.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US-China trade war ceasefire prevents recession/credit event.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior to US-China talks in Geneva, fund managers saw US tariffs on China goods at 37%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;61% of fund managers see soft landing for the economy versus 37% in April.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;26% see hard landing, down from 49% in April.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We can see here that the &quot;short US Dollar trade&quot; has been (and I think it&apos;s still is) a pretty overcrowded trade. I can see some more upside for the greenback in the next weeks but we might need strong economic data to make the market to price in an even less dovish path for interest rates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe an upside surprise in today&apos;s US CPI report might do it.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices lightly changed at the open today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-lightly-changed-at-the-open-today-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-lightly-changed-at-the-open-today-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down slightly by 0.4% but that follows from the surging gains overnight as the index closed at the highs with over 3% gains.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDJPY Technical Analysis – The greenback is back</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-the-greenback-is-back-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-the-greenback-is-back-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD got a boost across
the board yesterday as the US-China tariff relief was much better than
expected. The market is now looking at the more hawkish scenario where we get
an average 10% global tariff rate and economic activity picks up on an easing
in growth fears and general uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is leading to a
hawkish repricing in interest rates expectations with the market now seeing 56
bps of easing for the Fed by year-end compared to like 120 bps at the peak of
the fears in April. The short dollar trade was also pretty overcrowded so the
unwinding in positioning is giving the greenback even more strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the JPY side, the
currency has been driven mainly by global events rather than domestic
fundamentals. Alongside the Swiss Franc, it’s been the favoured safe haven in
the currencies space amid the swings in risk sentiment. The recent positive
mood in the markets weighed on the Japanese Yen which lost ground against all
the major currencies despite the market increasing the expectations for another
rate hike this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that USDJPY broke above the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt; yesterday following the much
better than expected US-China tariff relief. The buyers piled in on the
breakout and will now target the 151.00 handle. The sellers, on the other hand,
will want to see the price falling back below the trendline to position for a
drop into the 140.00 handle next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see that we have now an upward trendline defining the bullish momentum on this
timeframe. From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a better
risk to reward setup around the trendline, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into new lows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, there’s
not much else we can add here as the buyers will look for a bounce around the trendline,
while the sellers will look for a break lower. If the bullish momentum stays
strong, we can expect the buyers to increase the bullish bets on the break of
the recent high at 148.60. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we have the US CPI report. On Thursday, we get the
latest US Jobless Claims figures, the US PPI and the US Retail Sales data. On
Friday, we conclude the week with the Japanese Q1 GDP report and the University
of Michigan Consumer Sentiment survey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says fentanyl issue is not their responsibility</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-fentanyl-issue-is-not-their-responsibility-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:55:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-fentanyl-issue-is-not-their-responsibility-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, it was noted yesterday &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-is-the-china-camp-painting-the-trade-deal-situation-back-home-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; how China avoided mentioning the fentanyl issue in their communication/statement and now we&apos;re starting to see why. That comes despite the many comments by Bessent that China had supposedly come to understand the US&apos; position on the matter over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The Chinese foreign ministry was asked today whether fentanyl would be discussed in trade talks moving forward. And their response is that fentanyl is a US issue and the responsibility for tackling that lies within the US itself. Adding that the 20% tariffs imposed on China due to the matter is &quot;unreasonable&quot;. Only one day gone and a chink in the armor already? Hmm.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China lifts ban on Boeing deliveries amid latest trade agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-lifts-ban-on-boeing-deliveries-amid-latest-trade-agreement-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-lifts-ban-on-boeing-deliveries-amid-latest-trade-agreement-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;From before: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-calls-for-its-airlines-to-halt-any-further-boeing-jet-deliveries-amid-trade-strife-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;China calls for its airlines to halt any further Boeing jet deliveries amid trade strife&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That helps to some extent but with the relative uncertainty of what might come next in the US-China trade war, I reckon Chinese airlines will continue to lean more and more towards Airbus - which already holds the dominant market share.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Bessent: Talks in Geneva with China resulted in a mechanism to avoid escalation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-bessent-talks-in-geneva-with-china-resulted-in-a-mechanism-to-avoid-escalation-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:25:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-bessent-talks-in-geneva-with-china-resulted-in-a-mechanism-to-avoid-escalation-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Talks in Geneva with China resulted in a mechanism to avoid escalation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;President Trump wants to rebalance the US economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China needs to rebalance towards consumption economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We do not want a generalised decoupling between the two largest economies in the world.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;United States will bring medicine, semiconductor and other strategic industries home.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Very productive discussions with Japan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Focused on Asia deals, Indonesia has been very forthcoming, Taiwan presented very good proposals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s nothing new here as he&apos;s just repeating what was said in the prior days and weeks. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +0.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:15:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;US stocks ended yesterday with a flourish, so that&apos;s helping to steady the ship on the week. Things are settling down now as we take a light breather to digest the US-China tariffs reduction and 90-day pause for talks to progress. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down 0.3% but that follows from 3.3% gains overnight, in which the index cleared both its 100 and 200-day moving averages comfortably.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:12:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, we don&apos;t have much on the agenda other than the German ZEW survey and BoE&apos;s Pill speech. The ZEW index is expected to rebound on easing trade fears and BoE&apos;s Pill is unlikely to say anything new since he spoke just last week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we get the US CPI report where the Core Y/Y figure is expected at 2.8% vs. 2.8% prior, while the M/M measure is seen at 0.3% vs. 0.1% prior. I think the data will now start to get more and more important as the expectations around an average 10% global tariff rate solidify. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk going forward shouldn&apos;t be growth anymore. It will likely be inflation as economic activity picks up. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK March ILO unemployment rate 4.5% vs 4.5% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-ilo-unemployment-rate-45-vs-45-expected-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-ilo-unemployment-rate-45-vs-45-expected-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 4.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Employment change 112k vs 115k expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 206k&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Average weekly earnings +5.5% vs +5.2% 3m/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +5.6%; revised to +5.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Average weekly earnings ex bonus +5.6% vs +5.7% 3m/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +5.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;April payrolls change -33k&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -78k; revised to -47k&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The jobless continues to allude to added softness in the labour market with payrolls once again falling in April. ONS might still have some data inconsistencies on accuracy but the bigger picture trend has been playing out quite straightforward at least. As for wages, real earnings is at least continuing to come down a little but is still on the higher side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s hard to read too much into the data given the mix of things. But balancing this out with the BOE messaging, it won&apos;t press policymakers to desperately go with a rate cut next month.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariffs policy can change overnight but supply chains cannot</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariffs-policy-can-change-overnight-but-supply-chains-cannot-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:47:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariffs-policy-can-change-overnight-but-supply-chains-cannot-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With the US and China striking a deal to lower tariffs after the talks over the weekend, we&apos;re going to see things go back to normal now right? Well, not quite. The thing is tariffs policy can change on a flick of a dime. However, the issue with the impact that it causes is that supply chains cannot adjust and change up that quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;After the tit-for-tat retaliation last month, the tariff levels have effectively placed a trade embargo between both countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In essence, that has caused shipments to be paused with empty containers building up at major ports. Meanwhile, some factories have also surely decided to halt production during this period. When shipments are paused, suppliers will also stop production as there is little certainty on how this tariffs war was going to play out previously. It&apos;s only prudent from a cost-saving perspective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But what happens now that the US and China have suddenly decided to drop back tariff levels again?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Sure, 30% is still high but now that&apos;s a cost that some firms will have to decide whether they can absorb. I mean after 90 days, who is to say that tariffs won&apos;t return to be higher again? That&apos;s the risk and uncertainty that many firms are squaring up to right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;If you can absorb that, it means trying to rush as many orders out in the next 90 days as possible. However, supply chains can&apos;t turn back on with a flip of a switch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Everyone scrambling to stock up on inventory again and shipments will resume. But amid the rush, vessels will face space limitations and ports will face heavy congestion and bottlenecks. Just think back to how it was back during the Covid pandemic when lockdowns eased. It&apos;s the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And even for factories resuming production, it&apos;s not that simple. It takes time for production lines to get back to full speed and some may have even already reallocated labour work during the past month. This may take weeks in certain situations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s all very messy and less straightforward as saying that with lower tariffs, things can easily go back to where they were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All this is not to mention the thousands of backlogs that have been caused in the last month that still needs catching up to do. If you haven&apos;t already booked shipments from China to the US, you&apos;re already probably too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So even with the reduction in tariffs, firms will still have to plan for potential delays due to backlogs and the time needed for shipments and factories to ramp up again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;At best, these delays might just last for a month or so. However, they could easily be prolonged for the next three to four months in some cases as well. That will make for a challenging summer for major firms reliant on supplies/inventories from China. If you&apos;re a big player like Amazon or Walmart, you&apos;ll do fine. But for the smaller guys, it&apos;s going to be tough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The good news at least is that the tariffs reduction looks to be coming just before major ports in the US are to receive shipments from China in any case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, any major disruptions from the initial tariffs that caused the trade embargo was due to hit around mid-to-end May at the earliest. But I guess, that can be course corrected now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That being said, the cascading effect to supply chains is something that won&apos;t be so easy to fix. With the 90 days pause, US consumers are also going to get in as much orders as they can now in case there might be future price hikes again. And in turn, that will drain existing inventory at a much quicker pace too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All of this will lead to a bullwhip effect that will just exacerbate the supply chain problems as listed above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The spike in demand that we&apos;ll see during this period will lead to shipments being overbooked (shipping costs to surge as such) with not enough vessels to accommodate the surge in orders. That will then lead to ports being congested and facing bottlenecks (causing delays and adding to backlogs of inventories). Eventually when it all dies down, firms may fall into an overstock cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And if tariffs are to be raised again, then we&apos;ll just start this whole process once more. And again, it will take months for supply chains to return to normal - if it ever does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, yeah. Tariffs policy can change overnight but supply chains cannot.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US to reduce de minimis tariff on China shipments from 120% to 54%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-to-reduce-de-minimis-tariff-on-china-shipments-from-120-to-54-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:21:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-to-reduce-de-minimis-tariff-on-china-shipments-from-120-to-54-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This follows up from this part here yesterday: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-deal-reportedly-does-not-cover-de-minimis-exemption-for-e-commerce-shipments-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US-China deal reportedly does not cover de minimis exemption for e-commerce shipments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s some comfort I guess that the duty/import charges will be reduced. But at 54%, it is still high for the average consumer. The de minimis exemption was eliminated previously so I don&apos;t believe the $800 threshold is back in place. Also, just be aware that the $100 fee will be increased to $200 after 1 June as per the previous arrangement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I mean even at 54%, it&apos;s still a taxing amount. It&apos;s not as bad as paying double the amount now but consumers will essentially still pay at least 1.5 times the amount for goods with country of origin (COO) labeled China.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB reportedly to largely endorse past policy measures in strategy review</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecb-reportedly-to-largely-endorse-past-policy-measures-in-strategy-review-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 05:08:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecb-reportedly-to-largely-endorse-past-policy-measures-in-strategy-review-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The report says that the ECB will brush aside calls for self-criticism and stand by its aggressive stimulus policy during the past decade in its strategy review. The review began in March and is believed to try and address issues such as whether QE, negative rates, and forward guidance have been appropriate tools in policymaking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The sources said that the ECB is likely to keep a reference to the need for &quot;especially forceful or persistent action&quot; in justifying their past decisions to push for QE and other stimulus measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Meanwhile, there is said to be a general agreement that forward guidance should be used parsimoniously especially after it led to the ECB reacting too late to the inflation surge in 2021 and 2022. I think that was more of a case of ignorance though. Remember the whole &quot;inflation is transitory&quot; episode? Geez.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As for the review as a whole, the report notes that some policymakers are feeling a bit displeased with the preliminary conclusions though. They were hoping for it to be more critical on past policy decisions but it doesn&apos;t feel like it when viewing the sentiment above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, much like the whole &quot;inflation is transitory&quot; episode in the past years, they&apos;re just not wanting to admit to any possible missteps they have made. Egoistic.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs scale back on Fed rate cut projections amid latest tariff developments</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-scale-back-on-fed-rate-cut-projections-amid-latest-tariff-developments-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 04:19:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-scale-back-on-fed-rate-cut-projections-amid-latest-tariff-developments-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Amid the latest agreement struck between the US and China, Goldman Sachs is now seeing the probability of a recession in the US over the next 12 months at 35%. Their previous projection was 45%. Given that, they are now expecting the Fed to only deliver one rate cut this year as compared to their previous forecast of three rate cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Meanwhile, the firm also raises its year-end target for the S&amp;amp;P 500 to 6,100 now - up from 5,900 previously.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 13 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-13-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:54:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-13-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There aren&apos;t any major expiries to take note of on the board for today. As such, traders will be sticking to the broader risk mood as the key driver of trading sentiment. After the bustling gains in risk yesterday, we&apos;re seeing things settle down a bit. And that&apos;s also leading to some cooling off in the dollar gains so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That&apos;s the main factor that will drive price action in the session ahead, to see if the mood music from yesterday will continue or if we&apos;re going to settle down to digest the situation a bit more. But coming up later, there is the US CPI report to watch out for as an added key risk event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBS sees better growth prospects for China as tariffs impact eases</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ubs-sees-better-growth-prospects-for-china-as-tariffs-impact-eases-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 03:23:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ubs-sees-better-growth-prospects-for-china-as-tariffs-impact-eases-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With that, UBS is forecasting the Chinese economy to grow between 3.7% to 4.0% in 2025. That is an upgrade from their previous forecast of 3.4% &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ubs-has-cut-its-china-gdp-growth-forecast-to-34-for-2025-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; last month.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China  President Xi Jinping says that tariff and trade wars produce no winners</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-jinping-says-that-tariff-and-trade-wars-produce-no-winners-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 02:54:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-jinping-says-that-tariff-and-trade-wars-produce-no-winners-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping stated that tariff and trade wars produce no winners, emphasizing that global peace, stability, and development can only be achieved through international cooperation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;He warned that acts of bullying and domination will ultimately lead to isolation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;62&quot; data-end=&quot;174&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;64&quot; data-end=&quot;174&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China backs Latin America and the Caribbean in strengthening their role in global multilateral institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;175&quot; data-end=&quot;317&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;177&quot; data-end=&quot;317&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Beijing remains committed to mutual support with Latin American countries on key issues tied to their core interests and major priorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;318&quot; data-end=&quot;470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;320&quot; data-end=&quot;470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China aims to expand collaboration with the region across sectors including infrastructure, agriculture, food security, energy, and mineral resources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;318&quot; data-end=&quot;470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;320&quot; data-end=&quot;470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China to offer 66 billion yuan credit line to support Latin America and Caribbean countries:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping is delivering a speech at the opening ceremony of the fourth ministerial meeting of the China-CELAC (Community of Latin American and Caribbean States) Forum in Beijing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Yen rebound on Kato comment; China signal CNY support</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-yen-rebound-on-kato-comment-china-signal-cny-support-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 02:48:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-yen-rebound-on-kato-comment-china-signal-cny-support-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-sasac-calls-for-advancement-of-major-projects-aligned-with-national-priorities-20250513/&quot;&gt;ICYMI China SASAC calls for advancement of major projects aligned with national priorities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-is-building-megaports-in-south-america-to-feed-its-need-for-crops-20250513/&quot;&gt;China is building megaports in South America to feed its need for crops&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-dep-gov-uchida-says-there-is-upside-downside-risk-from-us-tariffs-on-japans-prices-20250513/&quot;&gt;BoJ Dep Gov Uchida says there is upside &amp;amp; downside risk from US tariffs on Japan&apos;s prices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-april-business-confidence-1-prior-4-20250513/&quot;&gt;Australian April business confidence -1 (prior -4)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-central-rate-at-71991-vs-estimate-at-72180-20250513/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY central rate at 7.1991 (vs. estimate at 7.2180)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-wants-to-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250513/&quot;&gt;Japan finance minister Kato wants to discuss FX with Bessent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-westpac-consumer-sentiment-may-2025-22-prior-60-20250513/&quot;&gt;Australia Westpac Consumer Sentiment (May 2025) +2.2% (prior -6.0%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-april-summary-shows-uncertainty-a-high-priority-discussion-item-20250512/&quot;&gt;BoJ April Summary  shows uncertainty a high priority discussion item&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-foreign-minister-meets-brazil-counterpart-in-beijing-20250512/&quot;&gt;China’s foreign minister meets Brazil counterpart in Beijing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/the-trump-put-is-alive-and-well-says-bofa-after-us-china-trade-ceasefire-boosts-stocks-20250512/&quot;&gt;&quot;The Trump Put is alive and well&quot; says BofA after US - China trade ceasefire boosts stocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-representative-greer-if-things-dont-work-out-china-tariffs-can-go-back-up-20250512/&quot;&gt;U.S. Trade Representative Greer: If things don’t work out, China tariffs can go back up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-consumer-spending-shows-its-biggest-increase-since-june-2023-20250512/&quot;&gt;UK April consumer spending shows its biggest increase since June 2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/deutsche-sees-first-fed-cut-in-december-despite-trade-relief-20250512/&quot;&gt;Deutsche sees first Fed cut in December despite trade relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/citi-trims-near-term-gold-target-sees-consolidation-at-30003300oz-20250512/&quot;&gt;Citi trims near-term gold target, sees consolidation at $3,000–$3,300/oz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/icymi-citi-forecasts-a-july-federal-reserve-rate-cut-instead-of-in-june-20250512/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Citi forecasts a July Federal Reserve rate cut instead of in June&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-massive-across-the-board-on-trade-war-relief-20250512/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Massive across the board on trade war relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trumps-hassett-says-there-are-24-countries-lined-up-for-trade-talks-over-the-next-weeks-20250512/&quot;&gt;Trump&apos;s Hassett says there are 24 countries lined up for trade talks over the next weeks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-expect-a-federal-reserve-rate-cut-now-in-december-instead-of-in-july-20250512/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs expect a Federal Reserve rate cut now in December, instead of in July&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-close-sharply-higher-on-us-china-tariff-news-20250512/&quot;&gt;US stocks close sharply higher on US China tariff news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-tuesday-13-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250512/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Tuesday, 13 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;216&quot; data-end=&quot;305&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;After Monday’s sharp swings, Asia markets settled into a more subdued session on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;307&quot; data-end=&quot;731&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Japanese yen found some relief, rebounding from early highs above 148.40 to around 147.75. The move was spurred by comments from Japan’s Finance Minister Kato, who said he hopes to speak with U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent on FX matters during the upcoming G7 meetings in Banff, Canada (May 20–22). The remarks were seen as a subtle warning about the yen’s recent weakness and a possible prelude to verbal intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;733&quot; data-end=&quot;1181&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Earlier in the session, the Bank of Japan released its “Summary of Opinions” from the April 30–May 1 policy meeting, with members emphasizing heightened uncertainty—particularly around U.S. trade policy. The tone underscored the Bank’s cautious stance, suggesting limited scope for near-term action until global developments stabilise. Since then, the U.S.-China trade talks have yielded a modest tariff rollback and a 90-day pause in new measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1183&quot; data-end=&quot;1379&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;BoJ Deputy Governor Uchida echoed the theme of uncertainty in separate remarks, but reiterated that the Bank still expects to raise rates gradually if the economy and inflation evolve as forecast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1381&quot; data-end=&quot;1596&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In China, the yuan strengthened after the People’s Bank of China set the daily USD/CNY reference rate below 7.2 for the first time since April 7, signalling support for currency stability amid easing trade tensions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1598&quot; data-end=&quot;1817&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Australian data offered a slightly improved but still cautious tone. Consumer confidence edged higher from previous lows, while business confidence ticked up modestly. Business conditions, however, slipped on the month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1819&quot; data-end=&quot;1898&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Elsewhere in FX, major currency pairs excluding the yen traded in tight ranges.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI China SASAC calls for advancement of major projects aligned with national priorities</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-sasac-calls-for-advancement-of-major-projects-aligned-with-national-priorities-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 02:24:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-sasac-calls-for-advancement-of-major-projects-aligned-with-national-priorities-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;173&quot; data-end=&quot;490&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China’s State-owned Assets Supervision and Administration Commission (SASAC) has called on central state-owned enterprises (SOEs) to accelerate innovation and strengthen their role in strategic and emerging industries, as part of efforts to meet 2025 targets and prepare for the 15th Five-Year Plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;492&quot; data-end=&quot;851&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;At an expanded Party Committee meeting, SASAC emphasized the need to implement key directives from the CPC Central Committee and the State Council, urging SOEs to focus on high-quality development and national strategic priorities. Officials called for a fact-based review of SOE performance under the current 14th Five-Year Plan to help guide future reforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;853&quot; data-end=&quot;1193&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The Commission highlighted growing external uncertainties and shifts in global technology and industry, stressing the importance of forward-looking strategies in SOE reform, governance, and Party building. It also urged enterprises to enhance their contribution to “new quality productive forces” and prioritize localization in key sectors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1195&quot; data-end=&quot;1462&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;SOEs were directed to optimize their presence in strategic emerging and future industries, accelerate breakthroughs in critical and core technologies, and reinforce their role in supporting national security, industrial resilience, and technological self-sufficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1464&quot; data-end=&quot;1685&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;SASAC also called for greater momentum in advancing major national projects and leveraging SOEs’ capabilities in strategic, foundational, and frontier sectors to consolidate the leadership role of the state-owned economy.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is building megaports in South America to feed its need for crops</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-is-building-megaports-in-south-america-to-feed-its-need-for-crops-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 01:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-is-building-megaports-in-south-america-to-feed-its-need-for-crops-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China is building megaports in South America to feed its need for crops - China has reassured its citizens they would have enough to eat without U.S. crops. It will have to unclog Latin America’s largest port first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wall Street Journal is gated,&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/world/americas/china-is-building-megaports-in-south-america-to-feed-its-need-for-crops-8831748e&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt; link here&lt;/a&gt; if you can access. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China state grain trader Cofco plans world’s biggest export terminal in Brazil to substitute U.S. soybeans and other foodstuffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China is investing in South American infrastructure to secure agricultural imports.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Santos, Brazil’s main port for exports to China, is struggling with capacity and infrastructure.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Brazil’s fertilizer supply issues and soil nutrient depletion pose challenges to increased crop production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I speculated earlier on this, it seems pretty obvious. What else is China gonna do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinas-foreign-minister-meets-brazil-counterpart-in-beijing-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China’s foreign minister meets Brazil counterpart in Beijing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;And, last week:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-intends-to-buy-around-us900-million-of-soybeans-corn-vegetable-oil-from-argentina-20250508/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China intends to buy around US$900 million of soybeans, corn, vegetable oil from Argentina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoJ Dep Gov Uchida says there is upside &amp; downside risk from US tariffs on Japan&apos;s prices</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-dep-gov-uchida-says-there-is-upside-downside-risk-from-us-tariffs-on-japans-prices-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 01:48:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-dep-gov-uchida-says-there-is-upside-downside-risk-from-us-tariffs-on-japans-prices-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bank of Japan deputy governor Uchida:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US tariffs put downward pressure on Japan’s economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There are both upside, downside risks from US tariffs on Japan’s prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s economic growth to slow to around potential before accelerating again as overseas growth resumes moderate growth path&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s output gap to remain around current levels, after which it will resume improvement toward end of BOJ’s 3-year projection period through fiscal 2027&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It sounds like Uchida is uncertain of where to go with policy from here? At least in the near to medium term. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ahh, here is some more, a little more confident on hikes now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BOJ expected to keep raising interest rates if economy, prices improve as we project&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan’s underlying inflation, medium- and long-term inflation expectations will likely stagnate temporarily&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But even during that period, wages are expected to continue rising as Japan’s job market very tight, firms likely to continue passing on rising labour costs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Once global economy resumes uptrend, Japan’s economy likely to recover and heighten underlying inflation, inflation expectations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty surrounding our forecasts is extremely high, so we will determine without pre-conception whether our forecasts will materialise&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong yen has negative impact on exports, big manufacturers’ profits but improves households’ real income and pushes up retailers’ profits via falling import costs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid FX moves make it difficult for firms to set business plans, heighten uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, USD/JPY has dribbled lower since Kato&apos;s verbal intervention efforts a little while ago:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-wants-to-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan finance minister Kato wants to discuss FX with Bessent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian April business confidence -1 (prior -4)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-april-business-confidence-1-prior-4-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 01:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-april-business-confidence-1-prior-4-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;National Australia Bank business survey for April 2025 (survey conducted at the end of that month)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;business confidence -1 (prior -4)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;business conditions +2 (prior +3), well below the long-run average&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the sub measures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; sales index held relatively steady at +5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;employment relatively steady at +4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;profitability down 4 points to -4, NAB point to higher purchase costs pressuring margins&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;fall of 6 points in the capital spending index to a below average +1, NAB says firms staying away from new investment due to uncertainty over US trade policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Reserve Bank of Australia is expected to cut interest rates again when it meets on May 20. This should help support sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC sets USD/ CNY central rate at 7.1991 (vs. estimate at 7.2180)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-central-rate-at-71991-vs-estimate-at-72180-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 01:15:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-central-rate-at-71991-vs-estimate-at-72180-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mid-rate today is the strongest (for CNY) since April 7. It&apos;s the first setting below 7.2 since that date also. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous close was 7.2075&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC injected 180bn yuan via 7-day reverse repos at 1.40%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;405bn yuan mature today
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;net drains 225bn yuan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan finance minister Kato wants to discuss FX with Bessent</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-wants-to-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:44:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-wants-to-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan finance minister Kato &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Making preparations to join G7 meetings in Banff&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If have a chance, hope to have a meeting with U.S. Treasury Secretary Bessent to discuss forex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Possible to discuss tariff deal if meeting with Bessent is realised&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will closely monitor U.S.-China tariff deal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Won’t comment on forex levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will closely watch out markets developments caused by U.S.-China tariff deal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yen lost ground since the weekend&apos;s US-China tariff trim-and-pause:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-massive-across-the-board-on-trade-war-relief-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Massive across the board on trade war relief&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-us-china-strike-deal-to-lower-tariffs-after-talks-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;ForexLive European FX news wrap: US, China strike deal to lower tariffs after talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. TRADE REPRESENTATIVE GREER: CHINA HAS AGREED TO REMOVE COUNTERMEASURES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922068851912552645#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:18:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922068851912552645#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. TRADE REPRESENTATIVE GREER: CHINA HAS AGREED TO REMOVE COUNTERMEASURES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *COINBASE GLOBAL SET TO JOIN S&amp;P 500

$COIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922038165398839438#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:16:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922038165398839438#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*COINBASE GLOBAL SET TO JOIN S&amp;amp;P 500&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *GOLDMAN NOW SEES NEXT FED RATE CUT IN DECEMBER INSTEAD OF JULY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922033143437054343#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922033143437054343#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*GOLDMAN NOW SEES NEXT FED RATE CUT IN DECEMBER INSTEAD OF JULY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) AMAZON STRIKES A NEW PARTNERSHIP WITH FEDEX AFTER UPS PULLBACK - BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922026103784321333#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:28:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922026103784321333#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AMAZON STRIKES A NEW PARTNERSHIP WITH FEDEX AFTER UPS PULLBACK - BUSINESS INSIDER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *UAE CHIP DEAL &apos;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS&apos; OF GPUS: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922016641228976315#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:50:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922016641228976315#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*UAE CHIP DEAL &apos;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS&apos; OF GPUS: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US MULLS LARGE CHIP SALE TO EMIRATI AI FIRM G42: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922016471397372338#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:50:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922016471397372338#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US MULLS LARGE CHIP SALE TO EMIRATI AI FIRM G42: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TAX BILL OMITS TRUMP PROPOSAL FOR MILLIONAIRE TAX BRACKET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922003610021310516#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:59:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922003610021310516#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TAX BILL OMITS TRUMP PROPOSAL FOR MILLIONAIRE TAX BRACKET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *REPUBLICAN TAX BILL RAISES DEBT LIMIT BY $4 TRILLION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922003557055639806#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:58:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922003557055639806#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*REPUBLICAN TAX BILL RAISES DEBT LIMIT BY $4 TRILLION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PENTAGON CANCELS ALL GENDER AFFIRMING HEALTHCARE FOR TRANSGENDER TROOPS AS IT MOVES TO KICK THEM OUT OF THE MILITARY, MEMO SEEN BY REUTERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002831847854223#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002831847854223#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PENTAGON CANCELS ALL GENDER AFFIRMING HEALTHCARE FOR TRANSGENDER TROOPS AS IT MOVES TO KICK THEM OUT OF THE MILITARY, MEMO SEEN BY REUTERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GOP TAX BILL CALLS TO END ELECTRIC VEHICLE TAX CREDIT EARLY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002171203055726#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:53:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002171203055726#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GOP TAX BILL CALLS TO END ELECTRIC VEHICLE TAX CREDIT EARLY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE REPUBLICANS SEEK &quot;ENHANCED DEDUCTION&quot; FOR SENIOR CITIZENS BY $4,000, WITH EXCEPTIONS -BILL TEXT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002130732245429#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:53:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002130732245429#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE REPUBLICANS SEEK &quot;ENHANCED DEDUCTION&quot; FOR SENIOR CITIZENS BY $4,000, WITH EXCEPTIONS -BILL TEXT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GOOLSBEE: TARIFFS WILL STILL HAVE STAGFLATIONARY IMPLUSE: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922000611878355067#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:47:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922000611878355067#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GOOLSBEE: TARIFFS WILL STILL HAVE STAGFLATIONARY IMPLUSE: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL INCLUDES EXEMPTION ON WORKERS&apos; OVERTIME PAY, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922000568353980860#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922000568353980860#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL INCLUDES EXEMPTION ON WORKERS&apos; OVERTIME PAY, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL WOULD EXEMPT WORKERS&apos; TIPS FROM INCOME TAX, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921999715534561550#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:43:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921999715534561550#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL WOULD EXEMPT WORKERS&apos; TIPS FROM INCOME TAX, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HOUSE REPUBLICANS RELEASE TEXT OF TAX BILL SOUGHT BY TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921998714861662449#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:39:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921998714861662449#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HOUSE REPUBLICANS RELEASE TEXT OF TAX BILL SOUGHT BY TRUMP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $AAPL - APPLE PLANS AI-POWERED BATTERY MANAGEMENT MODE FOR DEVICES IN IOS 19</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921994052645408782#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:21:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921994052645408782#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AAPL&quot;&gt;$AAPL&lt;/a&gt; - APPLE PLANS AI-POWERED BATTERY MANAGEMENT MODE FOR DEVICES IN IOS 19&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. POSTS $258B APRIL BUDGET SURPLUS, UP 23%

Strong tax payments and record import tariffs boosted the U.S. April surplus to $258B, Treasury reported.

🔸 $16B in customs duties, up $9B from last year.
🔸 U.S. collected $500M/day from tariffs, far below Trump&apos;s $2B/day claim.
🔸 Tariff revenue will fall as U.S.-China agreed to cut tariffs (U.S. to 30%, China to 10%) for 90 days.

For fiscal 2025 (Oct-Apr):

🔸 Deficit: $1.049T, up 23%.
🔸 Receipts: $3.11T, Outlays: $4.16T — both April records.
🔸 Adjusted for timing effects, the deficit rose 4%.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921989411522146372#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921989411522146372#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. POSTS $258B APRIL BUDGET SURPLUS, UP 23%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Strong tax payments and record import tariffs boosted the U.S. April surplus to $258B, Treasury reported.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 $16B in customs duties, up $9B from last year.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 U.S. collected $500M/day from tariffs, far below Trump&apos;s $2B/day claim.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Tariff revenue will fall as U.S.-China agreed to cut tariffs (U.S. to 30%, China to 10%) for 90 days.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
For fiscal 2025 (Oct-Apr):&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Deficit: $1.049T, up 23%.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Receipts: $3.11T, Outlays: $4.16T — both April records.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Adjusted for timing effects, the deficit rose 4%.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US BUDGET SURPLUS RISES 23% TO $258 BILLION IN APRIL, CUSTOMS REVENUE SURGES

The U.S. government posted a $258 billion budget surplus for April, up 23% from a year earlier, reflecting strong tax receipts in the final month of the tax season and surging collections of import duties, the Treasury Department said on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921988910256738470#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921988910256738470#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US BUDGET SURPLUS RISES 23% TO $258 BILLION IN APRIL, CUSTOMS REVENUE SURGES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The U.S. government posted a $258 billion budget surplus for April, up 23% from a year earlier, reflecting strong tax receipts in the final month of the tax season and surging collections of import duties, the Treasury Department said on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA TRADE EASING DOESN&apos;T MEAN A QUICK FED CUT: DEUTSCHE BANK

A big drop in U.S.-China trade barriers lessens the prospects of a serious inflationary supply crunch. Even so, inflation remains stubborn enough that the Fed probably still won&apos;t be in a rush to cut interest rates, economists at Deutsche Bank write. Despite the trade war&apos;s easing, &quot;policies are likely to keep inflation at uncomfortably high levels for the Fed,&quot; Deutsche&apos;s team suggests. &quot;This announcement therefore reinforces our view that the Fed is going to be slow to cut rates this year.&quot; Deutsche&apos;s baseline assumption is that the Fed&apos;s next rate cut won&apos;t come before December</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921976766329192614#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:12:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921976766329192614#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA TRADE EASING DOESN&apos;T MEAN A QUICK FED CUT: DEUTSCHE BANK&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
A big drop in U.S.-China trade barriers lessens the prospects of a serious inflationary supply crunch. Even so, inflation remains stubborn enough that the Fed probably still won&apos;t be in a rush to cut interest rates, economists at Deutsche Bank write. Despite the trade war&apos;s easing, &quot;policies are likely to keep inflation at uncomfortably high levels for the Fed,&quot; Deutsche&apos;s team suggests. &quot;This announcement therefore reinforces our view that the Fed is going to be slow to cut rates this year.&quot; Deutsche&apos;s baseline assumption is that the Fed&apos;s next rate cut won&apos;t come before December&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED’S KUGLER: I AM ONE OF THOSE WHO BELIEVES THERE COULD BE SOME PERMANENCY FROM PRICE INCREASES RELATED TO TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921947847651447018#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:17:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921947847651447018#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED’S KUGLER: I AM ONE OF THOSE WHO BELIEVES THERE COULD BE SOME PERMANENCY FROM PRICE INCREASES RELATED TO TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
