<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>SNB&apos;s Schlegel: Switzerland is not a currency manipulator</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snbs-schlegel-switzerland-is-not-a-currency-manipulator-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 11:06:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snbs-schlegel-switzerland-is-not-a-currency-manipulator-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Switzerland is not a currency manipulator.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have only acted to dampen the overvaluation of the Franc which threatened price stability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Currency market interventions are not about gaining a competitive advantage for Switzerland.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technical experts in the US understand the Swiss position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;More:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cannot rule out that negative rates could be a necessary instrument in the future.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;National bank does not like negative rates.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a couple of remarks on currency intervention. The SNB and the BoJ are the two most active ones among the major central banks in currency interventions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A currency manipulator though is a country that deliberately influences the exchange rate of its currency to gain unfair advantages in international trade. That&apos;s not the case for the SNB and the BoJ. They care about the impact on price stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The part on negative rates is not new. We&apos;ve heard those same comments for months.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYCServers Expands London Infrastructure with LD4 Launch, Enhancing Forex VPS</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/nycservers-expands-london-infrastructure-with-ld4-launch-enhancing-forex-vps-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:45:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/nycservers-expands-london-infrastructure-with-ld4-launch-enhancing-forex-vps-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;NewYorkCityServers, a leading provider of
performance-optimized &lt;a href=&quot;https://newyorkcityservers.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Forex VPS&lt;/a&gt; hosting,
has announced the expansion of its global infrastructure with the deployment of
new hardware inside the LD4 datacenter in London. This move marks a significant
step forward in providing ultra-low latency connectivity for traders operating
across Europe and global markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The LD4 facility, located just outside London, is
considered one of the most important financial data centers in the world —
hosting infrastructure for top-tier liquidity providers, brokers, and
exchanges. By launching a dedicated presence within LD4, NYCServers is now able
to offer direct cross-connect proximity to many of the largest forex brokers,
reducing latency to less than single-digit milliseconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“London remains a critical hub for the FX ecosystem,” said
Nick Esposito, founder of NYCServers. “With LD4, we’re putting our clients
right where the action happens — next to the execution engines of their
brokers. It’s a game-changer for traders who care about speed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Built for Serious Traders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new London infrastructure is powered by the same
high-performance infrastructure NYCServers is known for: AMD Ryzen 7950X CPUs,
fast NVMe storage, and virtualized environments tuned specifically for trading
platforms like MetaTrader 4 and MetaTrader 5. Combined with optimized routing
and premium bandwidth providers, clients can expect robust performance and
minimal latency regardless of market volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the company&apos;s New York location (located in NY4)
continues to serve North American traders with outstanding connectivity, the
LD4 deployment ensures that European clients — or those trading with brokers
hosted in London — can now benefit from an equally optimized experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This expansion is especially relevant for clients trading
with brokers such as Tickmill, Blueberry Markets, KeyToMarkets, FTMO, and other
firms that maintain infrastructure within LD4. With direct peering and no
unnecessary network hops, the time between order submission and execution is
reduced to its bare minimum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is a Forex VPS?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Forex VPS (Virtual Private Server) is a dedicated virtual
environment specifically optimized to run trading platforms 24/7 with
consistent uptime, fast execution, and minimal delays. It allows traders to
deploy Expert Advisors (EAs), custom indicators, and automated strategies
without relying on their local internet connection or hardware.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For serious retail traders, especially those who trade with
automation or during volatile news events, hosting MetaTrader platforms on a
Forex VPS can provide a significant edge. Reduced latency means better order
fills, lower slippage, and faster reaction times to market movements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NYCServers’ Forex VPS offerings are particularly suited for
this purpose. With years of experience and thousands of active clients, the
company continues to refine its infrastructure to meet the demands of modern
traders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why LD4 Matters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latency — the time it takes for an order to travel from the
trader’s platform to the broker’s server — can have a measurable impact on
execution quality. In high-speed forex environments, even a few milliseconds
can determine whether an order is filled at the expected price or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LD4 is home to many of the world’s most active brokers and
liquidity providers. Hosting your trading platform in the same facility as your
broker removes unnecessary geographic distance and improves the speed of
execution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With this launch, NYCServers clients now have the ability
to deploy VPS instances in either LD4 or NY4 — depending on their broker’s
location and trading needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Broker-Focused Integration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of NYCServers’ key advantages is its broker-focused
approach. The company partners with multiple forex brokerages to offer
sponsored or discounted VPS plans to eligible clients. These partnerships often
allow traders to receive free or reduced-cost hosting when they meet minimum
trading volume requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This LD4 expansion is expected to deepen those
relationships, enabling brokers in London to offer their clients faster, more
stable VPS services without needing to build their own infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Many of our broker partners want to ensure their clients
have access to fast, reliable VPS hosting — especially those using EAs or
scalping strategies,” said Esposito. “Our LD4 expansion gives them a reliable
solution right where they need it most.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Client-Controlled,
Broker-Ready&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NYCServers offers a streamlined deployment experience
tailored for forex traders. Clients can launch their VPS with MetaTrader 4 or 5
pre-installed — already configured with their preferred broker — dramatically
reducing setup time and allowing them to start trading in minutes. With support
for over 100 brokers available for instant deployment, the process is designed
for speed, simplicity, and compatibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each VPS includes full administrator access, a dedicated
public IP address, and flexible server locations — including New York (NY4) and
London (LD4) — so traders can choose the datacenter closest to their broker for
optimal latency. A built-in latency checker is also available on the NYCServers
website to help clients identify the fastest connection for their trading
setup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Built for the Future&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As algorithmic strategies, prop firm challenges, and
time-sensitive trading models become more widespread, low-latency
infrastructure is no longer optional — it’s essential. NYCServers is meeting
that demand head-on by continuing to invest in enterprise-grade hardware,
optimized routing, and strategic datacenter placement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With LD4 now live alongside its established NY4 presence,
NYCServers is focused on delivering best-in-class performance where traders
need it most — and is actively exploring new opportunities to bring its
infrastructure even closer to the global trading community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our mission is to give traders a competitive edge —
wherever they’re located,” said Nick Esposito. “This isn’t just about servers.
It’s about giving our clients the speed, reliability, and proximity they need
to perform at the highest level.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About NYCServers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2012, NYCServers specializes in premium hosting
for traders. Its Forex VPS infrastructure is trusted by thousands of clients
around the world, including retail traders, prop firms, and institutional
partners. With a focus on performance, uptime, and support, the company
continues to be a go-to provider for those seeking execution speed without
compromise.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia-Ukraine talks in Istanbul set to begin shortly</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-ukraine-talks-in-istanbul-set-to-begin-shortly-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:30:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-ukraine-talks-in-istanbul-set-to-begin-shortly-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, that&apos;s a long enough delay. The talks were supposed to begin at around 0900 GMT. But earlier, Russia&apos;s Medinsky had talks on the side with the US before this. There were also some alleged pushback as seen &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-demands-that-talks-with-ukraine-take-place-without-us-turkish-representatives-20250516/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but at least now we&apos;re starting to get this over and done with.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the interest rates expectations after this week&apos;s events and data?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-interest-rates-expectations-after-this-weeks-events-and-data-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-interest-rates-expectations-after-this-weeks-events-and-data-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 56 bps (92% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 52 bps (91% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 47 bps (89% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 47 bps (64% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 77 bps (98% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 60 bps (76% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 44 bps (83% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;*for the SNB, the rest of the probability is for a 50 bps cut&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 16 bps (98% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia demands that talks with Ukraine take place without US, Turkish representatives</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-demands-that-talks-with-ukraine-take-place-without-us-turkish-representatives-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russia-demands-that-talks-with-ukraine-take-place-without-us-turkish-representatives-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Ukraine is meanwhile not too happy about said demand, saying that it is a sign that Russia is undermining peace efforts by putting forward demands and conditions. It&apos;s all falling apart before it even begins, which is not surprising after Putin&apos;s no-show. The talks were supposedly to have started at 0900 GMT.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What drives the repricing in interest rates expectations is key for the market</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-drives-the-repricing-in-interest-rates-expectations-is-key-for-the-market-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:19:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-drives-the-repricing-in-interest-rates-expectations-is-key-for-the-market-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;When you look at rising interest rates, you need to distinguish what is the driver behind it because it can change the market outcomes. When interest rates rise due to growth expectations, you have a positive outcome for the stock market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s because earnings expectations improve and investors tolerate higher rates because they anticipate stronger performance. One recent example of that is the 2016-2018 period when the stock market rallied despite the increase in interest rates. That was when we had Trump&apos;s tax cuts and inflation wasn&apos;t a problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When interest rates rise due to inflation expectations, you generally have a negative outcome for the stock market. That&apos;s because returns start to get revised downwards and you have the spectre of monetary tightening. The most recent example is the 2022 period when the Fed had to tighten policy fast to bring inflation down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, the context matters a lot. Rising rates aren&apos;t inherently bad for stocks. It depends on why they’re rising. Markets tend to embrace growth-driven rate increases but fear inflation-driven ones.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea says there is possibility trade deal might come after 8 July deadline</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-says-there-is-possibility-trade-deal-might-come-after-8-july-deadline-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:14:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-says-there-is-possibility-trade-deal-might-come-after-8-july-deadline-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Emphasised importance of auto, steel sectors during talks with Greer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Has set up formal negotiation framework with the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Next ministerial-level meeting expected to be held in the middle of June&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, keep in mind that the delay here also comes as South Korea is due to have a presidential election on 3 June. So, any significant discussions on trade will only be held after that. Hence, why Ahn is saying that he only expects the next ministerial-level meeting to be during mid-June.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone March trade balance €36.8 billion vs €24.0 billion prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-march-trade-balance-368-billion-vs-240-billion-prior-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 09:00:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-march-trade-balance-368-billion-vs-240-billion-prior-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In seasonally adjusted terms, the trade balance was €27.9 billion on the month. This comes as exports were seen up 2.9% while imports were up by only 1.0% on the month.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FMAS:25 Agenda Highlights – Africa’s Premier Summit Delivers Key Insights for Traders</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/fmas25-agenda-highlights-africas-premier-summit-delivers-key-insights-for-traders-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:58:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/fmas25-agenda-highlights-africas-premier-summit-delivers-key-insights-for-traders-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;With less than three weeks to go, FMAS:25 is set to take
over Cape Town with its&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.financemagnates.com/event/FMAS25/agenda&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt; most
powerful agenda yet&lt;/a&gt;. From trading and
investing to payments, crypto, and fintech innovation, this year’s summit is
bringing together the biggest names and sharpest minds in financial services
for two days of high-impact content and unmatched networking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FMAS:25 will open with a high-level “Leaders
Roundtable,” where executives from top brokers, leading traders, and regulatory
bodies will set the tone for discussions on the future of trading in Africa.
The agenda quickly dives into the trends and technologies shaping the
multi-asset trading strategies, prop firm strategies, and the explosive rise of
retail investing across the continent. Traders can expect deep dives into new
platforms, automation tools, AI-powered strategies, and how mobile-first
infrastructure is changing investor behavior from onboarding to execution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year’s programme also puts a spotlight on payments
innovation, examining how Africa’s evolving rails, embedded finance, and
SuperApp ecosystems are unlocking new growth. Expect headline speakers from Exness,
Binance, Mastercard, IG Markets, FP Markets, Equiti, and many more to take
the stage alongside rising challengers making waves in the space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Highlighting the traders’ side, the agenda unpacks
everything from liquidity and automation to AI, risk, and regulation—offering
direct insights into how markets are evolving and what strategies are working
right now. Whether you&apos;re running a prop desk, trading crypto, or just entering
the markets, FMAS:25 brings the tech, tools, and tactics that matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With over 40 sessions spanning panels, fireside chats,
workshops, masterclasses and live debates, FMAS:25 is a one-of-a-kind
opportunity to plug into the people and ideas driving Africa’s trading
evolution. The countdown to Cape Town is on—&lt;a href=&quot;https://events.financemagnates.com/event/633313d8-3cf8-4e77-9639-36312d50b07e/summary?tm=RCclhU2zWsVFdIEcKIc6WVivOz5CNdL2hXUunGPDt2o&amp;amp;locale=en-US&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;secure
your place now&lt;/a&gt; and be part of the continent’s most
important financial conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B2PRIME Strengthens Institutional Team’s Growth with Appointment of Lee Shmuel Goldfarb</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/b2prime-strengthens-institutional-teams-growth-with-appointment-of-lee-shmuel-goldfarb-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:49:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/b2prime-strengthens-institutional-teams-growth-with-appointment-of-lee-shmuel-goldfarb-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;B2PRIME Group, a global financial
services provider for institutional and professional clients, has announced the
appointment of Lee Shmuel Goldfarb as its new Executive Sales Trader. With a
strong background in eFX liquidity, institutional sales, and partnership development,
Lee brings a diverse set of skills and a hands-on approach to client engagement
and market growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee joins B2PRIME from Edgewater Markets, where he led
institutional sales and account management for clients with emerging markets
trade flows. His experience spans bank, hedge fund, and prop trading sales
across precious metals, eFX, and NDFs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before that, he held the position of Partnership &amp;amp;
Account Manager for Israel at Currencies Direct, where he consistently
delivered high revenue performance and streamlined compliance processes for
onboarding corporate and high net worth individuals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee Shmuel stated, &quot;Joining B2PRIME represents a
logical progression in my professional journey. It is uncommon to discover a
firm that offers such a diverse selection of trading solutions alongside the
capability to develop internal institutional-grade solutions. The team&apos;s
dedication to clarity, accuracy, and exceptional client support particularly
appeals to me, and I eagerly anticipate contributing to their
efforts.&quot;Eugenia Mykuliak, Founder &amp;amp; Executive Director at B2PRIME
Group, commented: “We’re thrilled to have Lee join us. Strengthening our team
with professionals who understand both the technical and relational sides of
the business is a key element of growth for a business. Lee’s experience and
client-first mentality make him a perfect fit for our expanding institutional
focus.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lee’s appointment reinforces B2PRIME’s mission to serve
institutional clients with top-tier liquidity, best-in-class technology, and a
long-term vision of excellence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About B2PRIME Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;B2PRIME Group
(https://b2prime.com) is a global financial services provider for institutional
and professional clients. Regulated by leading authorities — including CySEC,
SFSA, FSCA, and FSC Mauritius — the company offers deep liquidity across
multiple asset classes. Committed to the highest compliance standards, B2PRIME
delivers institutional-grade trading solutions with a focus on reliability,
transparency, and operational excellence.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SignalRank Announces v4 of Investment Selection Model</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/signalrank-announces-v4-of-investment-selection-model-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:33:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/signalrank-announces-v4-of-investment-selection-model-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;SignalRank, the Palo Alto-based technology-driven venture investment platform, today announced several key milestones, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;· Two years of performance data for The SignalRank Index&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;· Launch of Version 4 (v4) of its investment selection model&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;· Availability of the SignalRank Index to accredited U.S. investors and overseas equivalents&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;· 35 Series B investments completed in 24 months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Since making its first Series B investment in May 2023, SignalRank has emerged as the world’s second most active Series B investor—trailing only Andreessen Horowitz in completed deals. SignalRank has participated in 35 financings alongside leading firms such as Sequoia Capital, General Catalyst, Lightspeed, Khosla Ventures, Accel, Founders Fund, and Kleiner Perkins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The SignalRank Index—a first-of-its-kind venture capital index—offers qualified investors access to a diversified portfolio of high-growth AI and technology companies. Notable Index constituents include Mercor, Saronic, Chainguard, and Together AI. Shares of the Index are priced daily and are available for purchase by accredited investors and equivalent entities outside the United States. The company ultimately aims to list the Index, expanding access to retail investors and wealth managers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Early Performance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;While venture investing requires a long-term view, preliminary results are promising. As of May 2025, the SignalRank Index reports:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;· 2023 cohort: 1.26x multiple on invested capital (MOIC)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;· 2024 cohort: 1.2x MOIC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;These early returns place the Index in the top decile of performance among comparable venture investments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;“We’re encouraged by the growth of our partner network—now nearing 300 early-stage firms,” said Rob Hodgkinson, Head of Investments at SignalRank. “The quality of both deal selection and access continues to improve, helping us deliver a compelling investment product while supporting our partners at a critical stage of company growth”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Details are available in the SignalRank Index Two-Year Briefing Report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Launch of v4: Ensemble-Based Investment Selection Model&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;SignalRank also announced the release of v4, its most advanced company selection model to date. The v4 model combines heuristic and machine learning techniques in an ensemble architecture to identify high-potential Series B investments. Backtesting indicates that v4 can:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;· Reject up to 87% of Series B opportunities as unlikely to perform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;· Generate a projected average 6x return over five years for annual investment cohorts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Keith Teare, CEO and CTO, said: “This is the first time we’ve blended heuristics with machine learning into a true ensemble model. The backtest shows performance that exceeds that of any known Series B investor over a five-year horizon. For our partners, it’s a decision support engine; for Index investors, it signals potential returns far ahead of public market benchmarks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The full v4 Technical Report is available here: v4 detailed report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;About SignalRank&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Founded in 2021, SignalRank Inc. (https://signalrank.ai/) is a C Corporation headquartered in Palo Alto, CA. The company has developed proprietary algorithms to select high-potential companies for Series B investment and partners with nearly 300 early-stage investors to provide follow-on capital to their most promising portfolio companies. Its flagship product, The SignalRank Index, is available to qualified purchasers at a publicly quoted share price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Notable investors in SignalRank include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;·  Lip-Bu Tan (CEO, Intel)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;·  Tim Draper (Draper Associates)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;·  Blake Grossman (former Vice Chair, BlackRock and iShares CEO)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;·  Garry Tan (CEO, Y Combinator)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;·  Sanjay Jha (former CEO, GlobalFoundries)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;·  Vint Cerf (VP, Google and TCP/IP co-inventor)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;·  Ray Lane (former Oracle President and Kleiner Perkins partner)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Important Disclaimer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;This release is for informational purposes only and does not constitute investment advice or an offer or solicitation to buy or sell any security or financial product. A back test is not the same as a promise of market performance and cannot be relied upon for that. Please consult your advisors to consider an investment. Investments in early-stage companies are risky and should be made only by accredited investors after seeking independent professional advice. Any future plans of the Company depends on the satisfaction of a variety of conditions, including, but not limited to, market conditions, regulatory approvals, and the company’s performance at the time. Past performance—including actual or backtested—is not indicative of future results. Signal Rank Corp. is not a registered investment company or advisor under the Investment Company Act of 1940. Our algorithm identifies potential Series B investment opportunities based on historical data which may or may not be complete and does not guarantee any future results. Our portfolio companies are generally private, which means that they do not trade like public securities and may be illiquid and difficult to sell, rending our own securities illiquid and difficult to sell as well. Our securities might be sold at a discount due to their illiquid nature, causing all or part of investments to be lost.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea delegation to visit US next week for further tariff negotiations</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-delegation-to-visit-us-next-week-for-further-tariff-negotiations-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:33:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-korea-delegation-to-visit-us-next-week-for-further-tariff-negotiations-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;South Korea&apos;s trade chief Ahn Duk-geun adds that he requested again for a waiver from US tariff measures at the APEC conference. But he&apos;s not offering any word on how Greer took to that. There&apos;s no precedent set just yet on a full exemption to US tariffs. And it would be a slippery slope in terms of setting up expectations if Trump were to allow even just one country to get that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;ll start the whole ordeal of &quot;if X country can get an exemption, then why can&apos;t we?&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Bostic sees just one rate cut this year amid uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-bostic-sees-just-one-rate-cuts-this-year-amid-uncertainty-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:11:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/feds-bostic-sees-just-one-rate-cuts-this-year-amid-uncertainty-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economic growth may be 1% or 0.5% this year.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expect slower growth but recession isn&apos;t in my outlook.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;May have to push against inflation pressures from tariffs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US-China de-escalation changes my outlook &apos;a little&apos;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bostic has been a hawk for quite some time and he&apos;s not a voter this year. Nonetheless, this might be the next thing the market will need to price in, that is inflation risk and therefore scale back further the rate cut bets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;May have to push against inflation pressures from tariffs&quot; - is he suggesting a rate hike here?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says US officials will send letters out soon to countries for trade deals</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-us-officials-will-send-letters-out-soon-to-countries-for-trade-deals-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:07:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-says-us-officials-will-send-letters-out-soon-to-countries-for-trade-deals-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are going to be very fair&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We reached a fantastic deal with the UK, and we reached another with China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Not exactly the main cause but these remarks don&apos;t hurt. US futures have been steadily climbing since European traders entered the fray in the past hour, with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures now up 0.3% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – Are we done with the repricing?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-are-we-done-with-the-repricing-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-are-we-done-with-the-repricing-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold has been under
pressure for a few weeks as the market priced out the stagflationary
expectations and repriced the rate cut bets. The market is now seeing around 58
bps of easing for the Fed by year-end compared to like 120 bps at the peak of
the fears in April. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the bigger picture, gold
remains in an uptrend as real yields will likely continue to fall amid Fed
easing. But in the short-term the repricing in rate cuts expectations could
weigh on gold, so watch out for the economic data and Fed comments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that gold eventually pulled all the way back to the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt; where the buyers stepped in
with a defined risk below the trendline to position for a rally into a new
all-time high. The sellers will need to see the price breaking lower to start
targeting the 2960 level next. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see that we had quite strong bounce around the trendline as the buyers kept pushing
into the key 3260 level. The sellers stepped in around the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-support-and-resistance-20220405/&quot;&gt;resistance&lt;/a&gt;
to position for a drop back into the trendline, while the buyers will need to
see the price breaking above the 3260 level to extend the rally into the downward
trendline around the 3360 level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor support zone around the 3200 level. This is where we
can expect the buyers to step in with a defined risk below the support to
position for a break above the 3260 level. The sellers, on the other hand, will
look for a break lower to increase the bearish bets into the lows. The red
lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we conclude the week with the University of Michigan
Consumer Sentiment report.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy April final CPI +1.9% vs +2.0% y/y prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-final-cpi-19-vs-20-yy-prelim-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:01:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/italy-april-final-cpi-19-vs-20-yy-prelim-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +1.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HICP +2.0% vs +2.1% y/y prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Slight delay in the release by the source. A concern here is that core annual inflation is seen accelerating again, up to 2.1% from 1.7% in March. That comes amid a jump in services inflation in particular, up to 3.0% from 2.5% in the month before.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-China trade truce should be extended, says Global Times</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-trade-truce-should-be-extended-says-global-times-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-trade-truce-should-be-extended-says-global-times-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The outlet says that: &quot;The window for mutually beneficial cooperation should extend far beyond a mere 90-day period. Hopefully, the US side will build on the outcomes of the recent talks and continue to meet China halfway.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, I don&apos;t think anyone is expecting any miracles in the next 90 days. And as mentioned at the time of the trade truce, this period is likely to be a subjective one rather than a firm deadline. If negotiations are in progress, I don&apos;t see why they wouldn&apos;t extend it beyond the 90-day period. That unless Trump loses patience with China of course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Analysts speaking to the paper did note that Beijing is unlikely to rush to announce how exactly it will meet all of its pledges though. Adding that there might not be too much clarity on non-tariff barriers as both sides look to engage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Even if we do end up getting purchase agreements and what not, I would highly expect all of this to be a charade of sorts. Just think back to the failure of the Phase One trade deal and we&apos;re pretty much going down that same exact path this time around.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Futures Analysis with tradeCompass</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-futures-analysis-with-tradecompass-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:34:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-futures-analysis-with-tradecompass-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Futures Analysis by tradeCompass – May 16, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instrument in Focus: Micro Bitcoin Futures (closely tracking Bitcoin futures and spot BTC)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&apos;re trading micro Bitcoin futures, standard BTC futures, CFDs, or perpetuals on your preferred platform, this Bitcoin analysis is designed to align with futures price action and help guide decision-making at key levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Analysis: Current Market Structure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of May 16, 2025, Bitcoin futures are trading inside a tight 4-day consolidation range, suggesting a market in temporary equilibrium. Unless broken with strong momentum, the path of least resistance may remain range-bound, and today&apos;s tradeCompass reflects that caution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volume Profile Highlights (from May 15, 2025):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Value Area High (VAH): 104,360&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Value Area Low (VAL): 103,550&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP (May 15): 103,920&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Point of Control (POC): Just under VWAP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Cluster Zone: 103,920 — reinforced by VWAP closings from May 13 and May 12&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This confluence of multiple volume-based levels makes 103,920 a pivotal spot for Bitcoin futures today. Price action above this area supports a bullish Bitcoin outlook, while a move below 103,450 could shift sentiment to bearish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Futures Bullish Threshold for Today:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key breakout level: Above 103,920–103,950&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upside Targets for Bitcoin Futures Today:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;104,590 – Aligns with May 13 VAH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;105,000 – Just beneath May 12’s upper VWAP deviation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;106,165 – Below May 12’s Value Area High&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swing Target (Runner): A move toward new all-time highs in Bitcoin futures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;TradeCompass Pro Tip:
These Bitcoin upside targets are chosen to reflect high-probability turning points. Partial profit-taking near initial targets is essential in today&apos;s range-bound Bitcoin market, and runners should be handled cautiously with stops trailed behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Futures Bearish Threshold for Today:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breakdown trigger: Below 103,450&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Downside Targets for Bitcoin Futures Today:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;103,185 – Overlapping May 9 and May 12 VAL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;102,700 – Sits just above May 13’s Value Area Low&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swing Runner: 100,000 – Major psychological round number and structural support level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;TradeCompass Note:
With Bitcoin futures still moving within a high-volume equilibrium zone, any dip to these downside targets should be viewed with an eye on buyer re-entry or reversal attempts. Leaning too hard into breakdowns without confirmation increases risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Insights for Today’s Bitcoin Analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-Inertia Environment: Bitcoin futures remain inside the 102,500–106,500 trading box. Breakouts may fail without strong volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP &amp;amp; Volume Profile Edge: tradeCompass uses these tools to map institutional behavior. Watch how price reacts near 103,920 and 103,450 to gauge control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Range Play is Still in Control: Until Bitcoin analysis shows sustained volume breakouts, tradeCompass favors adaptive intraday targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weekend Risk Reminder: If you’re using CME Bitcoin futures, manage exposure through Sunday. For 24/7 traders in spot BTC or CFDs, shift stops once partials are hit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using tradeCompass for Bitcoin Analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;tradeCompass helps eliminate bias by offering clear bullish and bearish thresholds based on professional order flow models and volume profile data. Every Bitcoin analysis from tradeCompass is designed to serve as a decision support system, whether you&apos;re day trading or swing trading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By following Bitcoin futures price reactions at the levels noted, traders can improve entry precision, stop placement, and partial profit strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Final Takeaway – Bitcoin Futures Map for May 16&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pivot zone around 103,920 holds special importance due to overlapping VWAP and POC levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bullish confirmation: Break and hold above 103,950&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bearish signal: Break and sustain below 103,450&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Range boundaries to watch: 102,500 (lower) and 106,500 (upper)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade with awareness of the compressed range and be cautious when aiming for long-distance trades without confirmation. The Bitcoin futures market is still in consolidation mode—and smart traders use this map to extract gains from both directions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer:
This Bitcoin analysis is a product of the tradeCompass decision support tool. It is not financial advice. Trade at your own risk, use proper stops, and always adapt to real-time market behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Would you like some occassional golden nuggets relating to crypto? Hop over to our new and free &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/investingLiveCrypto&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;investingLive Crypto Telegram Channel&lt;/a&gt; t.me/investingLiveCrypto, @investingLiveCrypto on Telegram. Always trade crypto at your own risk only.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices slightly higher at the open in final stretch of the week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-slightly-higher-at-the-open-in-final-stretch-of-the-week-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:17:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-slightly-higher-at-the-open-in-final-stretch-of-the-week-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Most indices in Europe will be looking to make it five straight weeks of gains now. The DAX itself is hovering at fresh record highs while the CAC 40 index is looking to top its early April high. The positive mood holds for now while US futures are looking more tentative and taking a bit of a breather. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are flat as we get the session underway.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:25:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, we don&apos;t have much other than a couple of low tier releases that won&apos;t influence market expectations at all. In the American session, we have the US Building Permits and Housing Starts, the US Import prices and the University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of those three, I would say that the UMich report is the one that could be market moving. The consensus sees an uptick to 53.4 vs. 52.2 prior. Compared to the  Conference Board consumer confidence, which is more biased towards the  labour market, the consumer sentiment survey is more weighted towards  consumers’ finances. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, analysts believe that it’s a better  predictor of consumer spending than the consumer confidence report, which is also why  the expectations index in the survey is included in the Leading  Economic Index (LEI).

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This  is generally more market-moving at turning points in the cycles or when  we have big deviations from the expected numbers. The sentiment has  been falling off a cliff in the past months due to Trump&apos;s trade  war. The biggest concern has been the rise in inflation expectations,  particularly the long-term ones which reached the highest level since 1991.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;15:00 GMT/11:00 ET - ECB&apos;s Lane (neutral - voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;22:00 GMT/18:00 ET - Fed&apos;s Barkin (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;01:40 GMT/21:40 ET - Fed&apos;s Daly (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +0.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This follows from the modest gains yesterday, with US stocks also performing decently outside of tech shares. For today, the mood music is more tentative with US futures also not suggestive of much. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are flat currently as we look towards European trading.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays no longer expects a US recession in the second half of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/barclays-no-longer-expects-a-us-recession-in-the-second-half-of-the-year-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/barclays-no-longer-expects-a-us-recession-in-the-second-half-of-the-year-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The change in forecast basically just speaks to the change in sentiment. Just last week, it was all still doom and gloom. So, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In any case, Barclays is now forecasting the US economy to grow by 0.5% this year and 1.6% next year. That&apos;s a step up from their previous forecasts of -0.3% and 1.5% respectively. They also see better prospects for the euro area now, expecting the economy to come in flat for the year as compared to their previous forecast of a 0.2% contraction.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One key chart to watch out for in the months ahead</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/one-key-chart-to-watch-out-for-in-the-months-ahead-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:56:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/one-key-chart-to-watch-out-for-in-the-months-ahead-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;From the previous trade embargo, it&apos;s basically a complete reversal in circumstances now. Customers and businesses are all piling in orders during this 90-day rush period. But what does it all really mean? Well, all you have to do is think back to the second half of 2020 of the Covid pandemic. We went from major lockdowns across the globe and then restarting everything again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That increased pressure on supply chains as global shipments suddenly skyrocketed again. This time around, the &quot;lockdown&quot; period is less and it mainly only pertains to China. However, that still has a major impact on supply chains and it will likely only start showing up more evidently in the months ahead and in the second half of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And even more so when we still don&apos;t know the fate of US-China negotiations in the coming 90 days or longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As mentioned before: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariffs-policy-can-change-overnight-but-supply-chains-cannot-20250513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Tariffs policy can change overnight but supply chains cannot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With the easing on tariffs earlier this week, it is reported that ocean freight bookings from China to the US are already up 275% this week compared to last week (h/t @ typesfast). That&apos;s the first step of how things are going to play out as per the linked post above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Eventually, the main worry here is that all of this will be one part that leads to higher prices and in turn, higher inflationary pressures. That was part of the equation that contributed to the surge in price pressures in 2021 and 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Central banks at the time kept insisting that it was all &quot;transitory&quot; but look where we are today. Sure, it looks to be that way but nobody said anything about the timeline for &quot;transitory&quot; I guess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, just be wary of the situation that&apos;s unfolding now as US-China tariffs do come down for the time being. This chart above is going to be one to watch to see how material the impact might be on the supply chain, amongst other hard data.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil traders: Watch Potential U.S. sanctions Against Russia</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-traders-watch-potential-us-sanctions-against-russia-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:12:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-traders-watch-potential-us-sanctions-against-russia-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Putin&apos;s Absence Raises Prospect of New Sanctions – Oil Traders Stay Alert&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vladimir Putin&apos;s recent absence from scheduled peace talks in Turkey, intended to address the ongoing conflict with Ukraine, has escalated geopolitical tensions and raised speculation about the potential for harsher U.S. sanctions against Russia. Traders and investors are now closely watching developments as Senator Lindsey Graham sponsors a new round of proposed sanctions specifically targeting Russia’s critical oil and gas refining sectors, alongside third-party nations indirectly supporting Russia by purchasing its energy products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be prepared. Should these sanctions be enacted, markets can expect volatility in oil prices. Historically, sanctions limiting Russian oil and refined product exports tighten global supply, often resulting in upward pressure on oil prices—bullish for oil futures (WTI and Brent). Conversely, Russian-linked assets, including the ruble, could face bearish pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors and traders seeking to capitalize or hedge positions should closely monitor:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. legislative updates: Signals from the Trump administration or key senators indicating movement towards sanctions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil price movements: Particularly futures contracts for WTI and Brent crude, as traders preemptively price in supply disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currency reactions: The Russian ruble may experience downward volatility, offering forex traders speculative and hedging opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the situation evolves, traders should stay alert to official announcements from Washington and Moscow, closely following ForexLive.com, evolving later this year to investingLive.com, for timely updates and actionable insights.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Kazāks: Meeting-by-meeting approach is right</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-kazks-meeting-by-meeting-approach-is-right-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:09:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-kazks-meeting-by-meeting-approach-is-right-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A lot of uncertainty around trade measures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Even if they are seemingly taking things one step at a time, they are finding it a bit tough to defy market expectations if need be. As things stand, another 25 bps rate cut in June is all but lined up. Traders are pricing in a ~91% probability of that as of now.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *NVIDIA REPORTS 7% STAKE IN COREWEAVE IN 13G</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923114324479869131#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:32:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923114324479869131#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*NVIDIA REPORTS 7% STAKE IN COREWEAVE IN 13G&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *ACKMANS PERSHING EXITS NKE IN Q1:13F

$NKE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923108871356166577#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:10:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923108871356166577#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*ACKMANS PERSHING EXITS NKE IN Q1:13F&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NKE&quot;&gt;$NKE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *S&amp;P 500 CLOSES UP 0.3%, NASDAQ FALLS 0.2%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923106366782079010#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923106366782079010#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*S&amp;amp;P 500 CLOSES UP 0.3%, NASDAQ FALLS 0.2%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HHS TO STOP RECOMMENDING ROUTINE COVID SHOTS FOR CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923103658792616242#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:50:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923103658792616242#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HHS TO STOP RECOMMENDING ROUTINE COVID SHOTS FOR CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *META TO DELAY ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP: WSJ

*META&apos;S &apos;BEHEMOTH&apos; WAS INTERNALLY SLATED FOR APRIL RELEASE: WSJ

*META ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP AI MODEL DELAYED TO FALL OR LATER: WSJ

$META</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923096475015274849#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:21:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923096475015274849#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*META TO DELAY ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*META&apos;S &apos;BEHEMOTH&apos; WAS INTERNALLY SLATED FOR APRIL RELEASE: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*META ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP AI MODEL DELAYED TO FALL OR LATER: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23META&quot;&gt;$META&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *COINBASE HACKERS HAD ACCESS TO CUSTOMER DATA SINCE JANUARY

$COIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923092251049177096#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923092251049177096#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*COINBASE HACKERS HAD ACCESS TO CUSTOMER DATA SINCE JANUARY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *STATE OF WISCONSIN INVESTMENT BOARD EXITS BITCOIN ETF POSITION: SEC FILING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923090409468711385#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923090409468711385#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*STATE OF WISCONSIN INVESTMENT BOARD EXITS BITCOIN ETF POSITION: SEC FILING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US-UAE AI CAMPUS WILL PARTNER WITH &apos;SEVERAL&apos; US COMPANIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085920363831532#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:39:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085920363831532#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US-UAE AI CAMPUS WILL PARTNER WITH &apos;SEVERAL&apos; US COMPANIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *DOJ PROBING IF HARVARD ADMISSIONS DEFRAUDED GOVERNMENT: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085187870576740#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085187870576740#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*DOJ PROBING IF HARVARD ADMISSIONS DEFRAUDED GOVERNMENT: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *STATE DEPARTMENT IS LEADING CAMPAIGN ACCUSING EUROPE OF LIMITING FREE SPEECH AND PROMOTING CENSORSHIP -- WSJ

*ADMINISTRATION SEES EU AS PART OF ‘GLOBAL CENSORSHIP-INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX’ HURTING U.S. TECH -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085085919641778#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085085919641778#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*STATE DEPARTMENT IS LEADING CAMPAIGN ACCUSING EUROPE OF LIMITING FREE SPEECH AND PROMOTING CENSORSHIP -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*ADMINISTRATION SEES EU AS PART OF ‘GLOBAL CENSORSHIP-INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX’ HURTING U.S. TECH -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *RUSSIA DEPLOYS 640,000 TROOPS IN WAR AGAINST UKRAINE: MILITARY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923074660993835285#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:55:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923074660993835285#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*RUSSIA DEPLOYS 640,000 TROOPS IN WAR AGAINST UKRAINE: MILITARY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE LEGAL HEAD CALLS SEC INVESTIGATION A RELIC OF PAST ADMINISTRATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923072444299915747#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:46:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923072444299915747#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE LEGAL HEAD CALLS SEC INVESTIGATION A RELIC OF PAST ADMINISTRATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE CHIEF LEGAL OFFICER: REPORTED SEC INVESTIGATION IS A HOLD-OVER FROM PRIOR ADMINISTRATION ABOUT A METRIC WE STOPPED REPORTING 2.5 YEARS AGO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923072369427354065#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923072369427354065#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE CHIEF LEGAL OFFICER: REPORTED SEC INVESTIGATION IS A HOLD-OVER FROM PRIOR ADMINISTRATION ABOUT A METRIC WE STOPPED REPORTING 2.5 YEARS AGO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $NVDA - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $COIN - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt; - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade

🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:54:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
