<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>USDJPY stalls at familiar resistance after tariff‑sparked surge; softer CPI tempers buyers</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-stalls-at-familiar-resistance-after-tariffsparked-surge-softer-cpi-tempers-buyers-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:39:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-stalls-at-familiar-resistance-after-tariffsparked-surge-softer-cpi-tempers-buyers-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;104&quot; data-end=&quot;463&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Yesterday’s announcement of a 90‑day suspension of some US‑China tariffs lit a fire under USDJPY, propelling the pair from a gap higher low 145.71, to a session peak at 148.64.
That rally stopped cold in a long‑standing swing zone between 148.56 and 148.73 (red arrows on the chart) — the same band that capped price action multiple times in February–March and going back to December 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;465&quot; data-end=&quot;720&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Today, the mood has shifted. A lower‑than‑expected US CPI print clipped US yields and the dollar, knocking USDJPY back lower.  Despite the setback, buyers still hold the near‑term edge while price remains above the first support target:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;722&quot; data-end=&quot;828&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;722&quot; data-end=&quot;776&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;724&quot; data-end=&quot;776&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;147.20‑147.34 swing area dating to August 2024 (not shown)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;777&quot; data-end=&quot;828&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;779&quot; data-end=&quot;828&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;38.2 % retrace of the April rebound at 147.14&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;830&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Hold above that risk‑defining zone and the upside bias survives; break below and the recovery narrative starts to unravel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;958&quot; data-end=&quot;1089&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the topside, the market must clear yesterday’s 148.73 high to reignite momentum.  A break would expose a cluster of hurdles including the::&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1091&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1091&quot; data-end=&quot;1144&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1093&quot; data-end=&quot;1144&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;50 % retrace of the 2025 decline at 149.38&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1145&quot; data-end=&quot;1176&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1147&quot; data-end=&quot;1176&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Daily 200‑MA at ≈149.58&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1145&quot; data-end=&quot;1176&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1147&quot; data-end=&quot;1176&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Psychological 150.00 level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1177&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1179&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Daily 100‑MA 150.30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1387&quot; data-end=&quot;1424&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels (single‑line bullets):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1426&quot; data-end=&quot;1703&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1426&quot; data-end=&quot;1531&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1428&quot; data-end=&quot;1531&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 148.56‑148.73 (swing area), 149.38 (50 % retracement), 149.58 (200 day moving average), 150.30 (100 day moving average)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1532&quot; data-end=&quot;1622&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1534&quot; data-end=&quot;1622&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 147.20‑147.34 (swing), 147.14 (38.2 %), 146.53 (prev low from March)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1623&quot; data-end=&quot;1703&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1625&quot; data-end=&quot;1703&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bullish while &amp;gt; 147-13 -147.20; break &amp;lt; 147.13 shifts focus to the downside&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ADMINISTRATION SAYS IT WILL TERMINATE ANOTHER $450 MILLION IN GRANTS TO HARVARD UNIVERSITY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922284972846592062#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:37:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922284972846592062#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ADMINISTRATION SAYS IT WILL TERMINATE ANOTHER $450 MILLION IN GRANTS TO HARVARD UNIVERSITY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $COIN - COINBASE SHARES RISE AS MUCH AS 13% ON S&amp;P 500 INCLUSION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922283859778916795#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:32:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922283859778916795#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt; - COINBASE SHARES RISE AS MUCH AS 13% ON S&amp;amp;P 500 INCLUSION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ZELENSKIY SAYS &apos;WE INVITED&apos; TRUMP TO JOIN ISTANBUL TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922283235398009281#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:30:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922283235398009281#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ZELENSKIY SAYS &apos;WE INVITED&apos; TRUMP TO JOIN ISTANBUL TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US, SAUDI ARABIA TO SIGN AGREEMENT ON SPACE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922281023930249571#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:21:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922281023930249571#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US, SAUDI ARABIA TO SIGN AGREEMENT ON SPACE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US, SAUDI ARABIA SIGN ENERGY, DEFENCE, MINING AGREEMENTS - SAUDI STATE TV</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922280395040567469#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:18:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922280395040567469#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US, SAUDI ARABIA SIGN ENERGY, DEFENCE, MINING AGREEMENTS - SAUDI STATE TV&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WRIGHT TO SIGN AGREEMENT ON ENERGY, ANNOUNCER SAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922280030811398251#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:17:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922280030811398251#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WRIGHT TO SIGN AGREEMENT ON ENERGY, ANNOUNCER SAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP, MBS BEGIN SIGNING CEREMONY IN RIYADH</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922279415720935877#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:15:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922279415720935877#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP, MBS BEGIN SIGNING CEREMONY IN RIYADH&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Carney to unveil cabinet today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/mark-carney-to-unveil-cabinet-today-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:09:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/mark-carney-to-unveil-cabinet-today-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Mark Carney will unveil is cabinet today in a move that could move the Canadian dollar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market still isn&apos;t sure how Carney will govern and his plan to &apos;build, baby, build&apos; and counter US tariffs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ctvnews.ca/politics/article/sets-the-tone-more-than-half-of-pm-carneys-new-cabinet-will-be-fresh-faces/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;reporting &lt;/a&gt;said former Finance Minister and Trump-antagonist Chrystia Freeland would be left off the roster but that was quickly reversed and denied. It appears she will get a role and that&apos;s not a big surprise given that Carney is the godfather of her son and they&apos;ve long been close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carney is looking to build national bridges though and she&apos;s carrying much of Trudeau&apos;s baggage. It would be a poor sign if she had a high profile position like Finance Minister. I suspect that will go to former Laurentian Bank economist Carlos Leitao, who was previously Quebec&apos;s Minister of Finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another portfolio to watch is Environment. That portfolio has been a major drag on Canadian construction and investment. Eco-warrior Steven Guilbeault will &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nsnews.com/the-mix/steven-guilbeault-to-remain-in-cabinet-source-10648622&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;reportedly &lt;/a&gt;remain in cabinet but if it&apos;s in the environment file, it won&apos;t bode well for the loonie but early indications are that it&apos;s the Heritage file, which is also responsible for biodiversity, nature and Parks Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carney is expected to name 30 cabinet ministers overall but early reporting indicates it will be many of the same faces from the Trudeau regime, with about half being new cabinet ministers along with a roster of 10 &apos;secretaries of state&apos; who will have portfolios but won&apos;t participate in most cabinet meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After this, the market will be watching for the opening of parliament on May 27 and the throne speech.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD rebounds, but key levels loom ahead</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-rebounds-but-key-levels-loom-ahead-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:08:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-rebounds-but-key-levels-loom-ahead-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;158&quot; data-end=&quot;510&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The EURUSD is seeing a modest rebound today after sharp declines yesterday, driven in part by a stronger USD following news of US-China tariff reductions (set for a 90-day period at least). The move lower on Monday found buyers just ahead of the 38.2% retracement of the January–April rally at 1.10395 — a level that remains a critical support line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;512&quot; data-end=&quot;636&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A break below that 38.2% level would signal a deeper corrective move is underway, shifting the bias further to the downside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;512&quot; data-end=&quot;636&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The pair is moving higher helped by the CPI data which was more modest than expectations (0.2% vs 0.3% for the headline and the core measures).  There has been a modest move higher with the pair trading to a new high at 1.11349.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;638&quot; data-end=&quot;830&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the topside technically, the pair now eyes the April 3 swing high at 1.11452. A sustained move above this level would tilt the bias more bullish and target the next resistance zone, which includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;831&quot; data-end=&quot;914&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;831&quot; data-end=&quot;882&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;833&quot; data-end=&quot;882&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The 200-bar MA (4H) currently near 1.1200&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;883&quot; data-end=&quot;914&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;885&quot; data-end=&quot;914&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A swing area up to 1.1213&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;916&quot; data-end=&quot;1098&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For now, the bounce is corrective, but traders will be watching whether the pair can push through key resistance or fall back toward the retracement level to confirm trend direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1105&quot; data-end=&quot;1127&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Technical Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1128&quot; data-end=&quot;1329&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1128&quot; data-end=&quot;1180&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1130&quot; data-end=&quot;1180&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.10395 (38.2% retracement)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1181&quot; data-end=&quot;1253&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1183&quot; data-end=&quot;1253&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.11452 (Apr 3 swing), 1.1200–1.1213 (MA/swing zone and the 200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1254&quot; data-end=&quot;1329&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1256&quot; data-end=&quot;1329&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Neutral near-term; bearish below 1.10395, more bullish above 1.11452&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Lobbyists Turn Up the Heat in DC as August Regulation Buzz Grows</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/crypto-lobbyists-turn-up-the-heat-in-dc-as-august-regulation-buzz-grows-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:51:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/crypto-lobbyists-turn-up-the-heat-in-dc-as-august-regulation-buzz-grows-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Crypto mixing with DC politics? For the
longest time, that combination often spelled trouble—think friction, regulatory
fog, and sometimes, downright opposition from the powers that be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the ground seems to be shifting
rapidly in 2025. The once-chilly regulatory environment is showing signs of a
thaw, spurred by a new administration&apos;s different tune and a crypto industry
ready to make its voice heard loud and clear inside the Beltway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn&apos;t just quiet diplomacy; it&apos;s an
all-out push. Cryptocurrency advocates are flooding Washington, armed with
arguments, funding, and a sense of urgency. They see a window of opportunity
opening, especially with predictions floating around—even from major industry
players—that meaningful, pro-crypto regulations could start taking shape,
perhaps as soon as this August. It&apos;s a high-stakes moment, potentially setting
the stage for how digital assets integrate into the world&apos;s largest economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Binance CEO:
Pro-Crypto Regulations Could Come to the US by August&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most prominent voices adding
fuel to the August expectation fire is Binance CEO Richard Teng. Speaking
recently, Teng suggested the US&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thenationalnews.com/business/2025/04/30/binance-crypto-us-money/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt; could see new, supportive crypto legislation&lt;/a&gt;
emerge by late summer. Teng explained his optimistic view under the Trump
administration, “The new efforts and optimism is very real in the US. So, I
believe the US is going to come out with very enlightened, pro-industry and
smart regulations that support the industry but also manages the risk at the
same time. So you’re probably going to see some of the new legislation coming
through by August this year.” This positive view is contrasted starkly with
what many in the industry perceived as the &quot;Operation Choke Point 2.0&quot;
environment of the previous administration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teng sees the shift in the US potentiallyacting as a catalyst globally. As he noted at
the CONVERGE LIVE conference, when the world&apos;s biggest economy signals it wants
to embrace crypto, it prompts other governments to seriously consider their own
approaches. This perspective comes even as the administration&apos;saggressive
tariff policies introduced earlier in the year initially sent shockwaves
through global markets, including the cryptocurrency industry. It highlights a
potentially complex dynamic where trade protectionism coexists with a more
favorable stance on digital asset innovation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Binance itself is navigating this market
from a position of strength, bolstered by a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/mgx-backs-binance-in-landmark-investment-6242106085221073480&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;landmark $2 billion investment from Abu Dhabi&apos;s MGX&lt;/a&gt;—the
largest single investment into a crypto firm, paid entirely in stablecoins.
Furthermore, Teng has confirmed Binance isadvising
multiple governments and sovereign wealth funds on building their own national
digital asset reserves and regulatory frameworks, underlining the increasing
global trend towards state-level crypto engagement influenced partly by US
moves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crypto
Lobbyists Are Flooding the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Richard Teng&apos;s optimism isn&apos;t happening
in a vacuum; it&apos;s backed by an unprecedented level of activity from crypto
proponents on the ground in Washington. The industry isn&apos;t just knocking on
doors; it&apos;s practically setting up shop. We&apos;re talking aboutmore
than a dozen distinct groups—from established players like the Digital Chamber
of Commerce, the Blockchain Association, and the Crypto Council for Innovation
(CCI) to newer, more focused entities like the Solana Policy Institute and the
National Cryptocurrency Association (NCA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This surge reflects a feeling that now is
the time to influence policy. As Miller Whitehouse-Levine, now leading the
Solana Policy Institute, put it, there&apos;s an &quot;absolute torrent&quot; of
legislative and regulatory work happening, and the industry needs &quot;all the
help we could get.&quot; There&apos;s certainly plenty to tackle, with Congress
debating everything from market structure and stablecoin oversight to illicit
finance concerns and even government digital asset reserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, having so many players can
lead to challenges. Insiders privately admit the field is getting crowded,
potentially leading to duplicated efforts or diluted messages when engaging
with the finite number of key congressional staff and administration officials.
Funding and membership can also become competitive points. Still, the
prevailing view seems to be that a united front, even across multiple
organizations, is powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent wins, like the bipartisan pushback
against a potentially cripplingIRS
rule targeting DeFi, show that coordinated advocacy can yield results. On top
of the traditional lobbying, well-funded political action committees like
Fairshake and grassroots efforts like Coinbase&apos;s Stand With Crypto are flexing
their political muscle, aiming to ensure Congress remains crypto-friendly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next On the
Table: A US Stablecoin Bill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what&apos;s the most immediate focus of
all this activity? Eyes are firmly fixed on stablecoin regulation. These
digital dollars are seen as a critical bridge between traditional finance and
the crypto world, and getting the rules right is a top priority. Two bills, in
particular, are front and center: theSTABLE
Act in the House and the GENIUS Act in the Senate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What these two bills are really trying to
do is build a rulebook for stablecoins across the US. They get into the
nitty-gritty—like which companies can actually create stablecoins, demanding
they hold reliable reserves (think cash or safe government bonds), and setting
up oversight. The fact that both pieces of legislation actuallymade
it through their House and Senate committees this spring, and with lawmakers
from both parties agreeing, was a pretty big step.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regardless of the exact timing, the
momentum behind stablecoin legislation is undeniable. The GENIUS Act&apos;s proposed
dual-oversight structure—letting smaller issuers stick with state regulators
while larger ones fall under federal watch—seems designed to balance innovation
with stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a minute there, the buzz was that
Senate Majority Leader John Thunemight
push for a full Senate vote on the GENIUS Act before Memorial Day. That talk
has quieted down a bit, making the exact timing fuzzy now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, getting any stablecoin bill signed
into law would be huge for the cryptocurrency industry. It would signal that
the US is finally getting serious about fitting digital assets into the
financial picture and could be the first domino to fall, leading to clearer
rules for other parts of crypto later on.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US SPECIAL ENVOY KELLOGG: NOBODY WILL GET EVERYTHING IN TALKS TO END UKRAINE WAR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922273108330676498#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922273108330676498#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US SPECIAL ENVOY KELLOGG: NOBODY WILL GET EVERYTHING IN TALKS TO END UKRAINE WAR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PUTIN SAYS 50,000-60,000 PEOPLE SIGN MILITARY CONTRACTS MONTHLY: IFX</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922272455277580410#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:47:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922272455277580410#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PUTIN SAYS 50,000-60,000 PEOPLE SIGN MILITARY CONTRACTS MONTHLY: IFX&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EGGS WERE DOWN SOME 12.7% ON THE MONTH - THE BIGGEST TUMBLE SINCE 1984</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922271729717498128#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:44:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922271729717498128#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EGGS WERE DOWN SOME 12.7% ON THE MONTH - THE BIGGEST TUMBLE SINCE 1984&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRADERS CONTINUE TO BET ON 1ST FED RATE CUT IN SEPTEMBER, 2ND FED CUT IN OCTOBER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922269665335693741#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:36:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922269665335693741#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRADERS CONTINUE TO BET ON 1ST FED RATE CUT IN SEPTEMBER, 2ND FED CUT IN OCTOBER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRADERS KEEP WAGERS ON TWO FED RATE CUTS BY END-2025</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922269295943270854#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:34:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922269295943270854#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRADERS KEEP WAGERS ON TWO FED RATE CUTS BY END-2025&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US SHORT-TERM INTEREST-RATE FUTURES RISE AFTER CPI DATA AS TRADERS ADD TO FED RATE CUT BETS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922268728420385216#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:32:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922268728420385216#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US SHORT-TERM INTEREST-RATE FUTURES RISE AFTER CPI DATA AS TRADERS ADD TO FED RATE CUT BETS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US 10-YEAR TREASURY YIELDS FALL AFTER APRIL CPI, LAST AT 4.429%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922268601857331569#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:32:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922268601857331569#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US 10-YEAR TREASURY YIELDS FALL AFTER APRIL CPI, LAST AT 4.429%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US CPI Y/Y INCREASE IS SMALLEST SINCE FEB. 2021</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922268460375032057#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:31:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922268460375032057#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US CPI Y/Y INCREASE IS SMALLEST SINCE FEB. 2021&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US APRIL CONSUMER PRICES RISE 0.2% M/M; EST. +0.3% 
*US APRIL CONSUMER PRICES RISE 2.3% Y/Y; EST. +2.4% 

*US APRIL CORE CPI RISES 2.8% Y/Y; EST. +2.8%
*US APRIL CORE CPI RISES 0.2% M/M; EST. +0.3%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922268401654714874#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:31:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922268401654714874#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US APRIL CONSUMER PRICES RISE 0.2% M/M; EST. +0.3% &lt;br&gt;
*US APRIL CONSUMER PRICES RISE 2.3% Y/Y; EST. +2.4% &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*US APRIL CORE CPI RISES 2.8% Y/Y; EST. +2.8%&lt;br&gt;
*US APRIL CORE CPI RISES 0.2% M/M; EST. +0.3%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April core CPI +2.8% vs +2.8% y/y expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-core-cpi-28-vs-28-yy-expected-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-core-cpi-28-vs-28-yy-expected-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Headline CPI:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;CPI +2.3% vs +2.4% expected -- lowest since Feb 2021&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-march-core-cpi-28-vs-30-yy-expected-20250410/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior &lt;/a&gt;was +2.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;m/m reading at +0.2% vs +0.3% expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Month-over-month unrounded +0.221% vs -0.088% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core CPI:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI 2.8% vs +2.8% expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI m/m +0.2% vs +0.3% expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core unrounded +0.237% vs +0.116% m/m prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Real weekly earnings -0.1% vs +0.3% prior (revised to +0.6%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core goods prices +0.06% vs -0.09% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core services +0.317% vs +0.126% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core services ex shelter +0.287% vs +0.100% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core-CPI services ex-rent/OER +0.373% vs +0.095% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Services ex energy +0.317% vs +0.160% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was some modest US dollar selling on the headlines but it&apos;s mostly retraced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shelter rose 0.3%, accounting for more than half of the monthly increase while energy increased 0.7% as natural gas and electricity prices rose to offset a 0.1% decrease in gasoline. The food index fell 0.1%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core CPI was 2.1% annualized over the three months through April and 3.0% annualized in the six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the Fed would have an easy time teeing up a cut right now if not for the tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forget housing and insurance, we&apos;re onto tariff effects.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 AT LEAST FOUR CHINESE RARE EARTH MAGNET SUPPLIERS HAVE BEEN GRANTED EXPORT PERMITS BY BEIJING - SOURCES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922267694914478501#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:28:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922267694914478501#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 AT LEAST FOUR CHINESE RARE EARTH MAGNET SUPPLIERS HAVE BEEN GRANTED EXPORT PERMITS BY BEIJING - SOURCES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs now expects the ECB to reach terminal rate at 1.75% in July</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-now-expects-the-ecb-to-reach-terminal-rate-at-175-in-july-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:24:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/goldman-sachs-now-expects-the-ecb-to-reach-terminal-rate-at-175-in-july-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs has shifted closer to market pricing on the ECB. They now see a 25 bps cut in June and another July, which would get them to 1.75%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market is still skeptical on that timeline, seeing only an 80% chance of a cut in June and a lower likelihood of a cut at the July 24 meeting. The big event to watch for is July 9, which is the expiration of the reciprocal tariff exemption. So far progress on EU-US talks has been very slow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs also raised its GDP forecast for the Eurozone following the US-China deal and now sees +0.1% in Q3 and Q4 vs no growth prior. That&apos;s hardly inspiring stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 U.S. April CPI Due 8:30 a.m. ET; Seen +0.2%; Core +0.3%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922265090809532889#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:18:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922265090809532889#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 U.S. April CPI Due 8:30 a.m. ET; Seen +0.2%; Core +0.3%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back on inflation watch as US CPI set to drop</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/back-on-inflation-watch-as-us-cpi-set-to-drop-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:12:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/back-on-inflation-watch-as-us-cpi-set-to-drop-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;We will get a momentary break from the trade war today with US inflation data due at 8:30 am ET (1230 GMT). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s tough to say how the Fed is evaluating these data points because so much is happening so quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tariffs spiked in April but it takes some time for shipments to come through and turn into inflation. Then this week, the US dropped tariff rates on China. At the same time, OPEC production hikes and global economic gloom tanked oil prices in the month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add it all up and economists are forecasting both headline and core CPI up 0.3% m/m. The y/y readings are expected at +2.4% and +2.8%, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;d expect some dollar volatility on the release and I can see Fed implied probabilities bouncing around. Currently we&apos;re 40% priced for a July 30 rate cut and there are 81 bps priced in for the year ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP ENVOYS STEVE WITKOFF AND KEITH KELLOGG TO TRAVEL TO ISTANBUL FOR RUSSIA-UKRAINE TALKS —SOURCES FAMILIAR TELL REUTERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922262170751930720#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922262170751930720#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP ENVOYS STEVE WITKOFF AND KEITH KELLOGG TO TRAVEL TO ISTANBUL FOR RUSSIA-UKRAINE TALKS —SOURCES FAMILIAR TELL REUTERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *APPLE LOOKS TO ENABLE IPHONE CONTROL WITH NEURAL SIGNALS: WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922261426862686489#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922261426862686489#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*APPLE LOOKS TO ENABLE IPHONE CONTROL WITH NEURAL SIGNALS: WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive European FX news wrap: Encouraging improvement in soft data, US CPI next</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-encouraging-improvement-in-soft-data-us-cpi-next-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:38:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-encouraging-improvement-in-soft-data-us-cpi-next-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-nagel-its-important-to-be-cautious-and-not-overreact-20250513/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Nagel: It&apos;s important to be cautious and not overreact&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-nfib-small-business-optimism-index-958-vs-945-expected-20250513/&quot;&gt;US April NFIB small business optimism index 95.8 vs 94.5 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-pill-i-do-worry-about-upside-risks-to-inflation-in-upside-inflation-scenario-20250513/&quot;&gt;BoE&apos;s Pill: I do worry about upside risks to inflation in upside inflation scenario&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-zew-survey-current-conditions-820-vs-770-expected-20250513/&quot;&gt;Germany May ZEW survey current conditions -82.0 vs -77.0 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-is-the-distribution-of-forecasts-for-the-us-cpi-20250513/&quot;&gt;What is the distribution of forecasts for the US CPI?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-makhlouf-uncertainty-is-weighing-on-investment-20250513/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Makhlouf: Uncertainty is weighing on investment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-fund-manager-survey-fund-managers-most-underweight-us-dollars-since-2006-20250513/&quot;&gt;BofA Fund Manager Survey: Fund Managers most underweight US Dollars since 2006&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-fentanyl-issue-is-not-their-responsibility-20250513/&quot;&gt;China says fentanyl issue is not their responsibility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-lifts-ban-on-boeing-deliveries-amid-latest-trade-agreement-20250513/&quot;&gt;China lifts ban on Boeing deliveries amid latest trade agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-bessent-talks-in-geneva-with-china-resulted-in-a-mechanism-to-avoid-escalation-20250513/&quot;&gt;US Bessent: Talks in Geneva with China resulted in a mechanism to avoid escalation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-ilo-unemployment-rate-45-vs-45-expected-20250513/&quot;&gt;UK March ILO unemployment rate 4.5% vs 4.5% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariffs-policy-can-change-overnight-but-supply-chains-cannot-20250513/&quot;&gt;Tariffs policy can change overnight but supply chains cannot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-to-reduce-de-minimis-tariff-on-china-shipments-from-120-to-54-20250513/&quot;&gt;US to reduce de minimis tariff on China shipments from 120% to 54%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecb-reportedly-to-largely-endorse-past-policy-measures-in-strategy-review-20250513/&quot;&gt;ECB reportedly to largely endorse past policy measures in strategy review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-scale-back-on-fed-rate-cut-projections-amid-latest-tariff-developments-20250513/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs scale back on Fed rate cut projections amid latest tariff developments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-13-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250513/&quot;&gt;FX option expiries for 13 May 10am New York cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ubs-sees-better-growth-prospects-for-china-as-tariffs-impact-eases-20250513/&quot;&gt;UBS sees better growth prospects for China as tariffs impact eases&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-president-xi-jinping-says-that-tariff-and-trade-wars-produce-no-winners-20250513/&quot;&gt;China  President Xi Jinping says that tariff and trade wars produce no winners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been a pretty boring session as we haven&apos;t got any meaningful new information. The UK Employment data came out more or less in line with expectations although wage growth remains pretty high for the BoE. There&apos;s the usual trust issue with the UK employment data, so it didn&apos;t change anything in terms of market expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also got some promising signs in the soft data with the German ZEW and US NFIB surveys. Both improved as uncertainty and fears around tariffs and growth eased given the recent developments. We might see better and better data going forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank officials are now starting to sound more cautious on rate cuts as fears around global growth ease and risk of a surge in demand could increase inflationary pressures, especially given that some central banks cut rates amid the trade war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Trade Representative Greer said that they are moving as quickly as they can on trade deals and basically confirmed that the goal is a 10% global tariff rate. That should decrease general uncertainty and improve economic conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we have the US CPI report coming up. The focus will be on the Core figures with the Y/Y reading expected at 2.8% vs. 2.8% prior, while the M/M measure is seen at 0.3% vs. 0.1% prior. The economic data should start to gradually matter again going forward but bad data will likely be faded given the &quot;U-turn&quot; in trade policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, the focus will now switch from growth back to inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USTR Greer: We are moving as quickly as we can on trade deals</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ustr-greer-we-are-moving-as-quickly-as-we-can-on-trade-deals-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 11:22:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ustr-greer-we-are-moving-as-quickly-as-we-can-on-trade-deals-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;It will take time to end non-tariff barriers with China.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I will talk to the Indian commerce minister Tuesday, then flying to South Korea.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are discussing other deals in parallel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The US is not relying on any trade partner for critical goods.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Global 10% tariff is a strong incentive to reduce the deficit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump is to consider change if we see results on fentanyl.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It should now be pretty clear for everyone that the end goal is an average 10% global tariff rate. That should decrease general uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Nagel: It&apos;s important to be cautious and not overreact</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-nagel-its-important-to-be-cautious-and-not-overreact-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:30:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-nagel-its-important-to-be-cautious-and-not-overreact-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In monetary policy, it&apos;s important to be cautious and not overreact, giving undue weight to specific announcements that could change shortly afterwards.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will continue to apply a data-driven approach.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Decisions to be taken at each meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looks like the hawks at the ECB are starting to get uncomfortable with the pace of rate cuts and would prefer to get more information before adjusting further.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April NFIB small business optimism index 95.8 vs 94.5 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-nfib-small-business-optimism-index-958-vs-945-expected-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-nfib-small-business-optimism-index-958-vs-945-expected-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-march-nfib-small-business-optimism-index-974-vs-1013-expected-20250408/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Prior&lt;/a&gt; was 97.4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Uncertainty Index decreased four points from March to 92 but 
remained far above the historical average of 68. Seasonally adjusted, 
34% of business owners reported job openings they could not fill in 
April, down six points from March. The last time job openings were below
 this level was in January 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NFIB Chief Economist Bill Dunkelberg notes: &quot;Uncertainty continues to be a major impediment for small business owners
 in operating their business in April, affecting everything from hiring 
plans to investment decisions. While owners are still trying to fill a 
high number of current job openings, their outlook on business 
conditions is less supportive of future business investments.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoE&apos;s Pill: I do worry about upside risks to inflation in upside inflation scenario</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-pill-i-do-worry-about-upside-risks-to-inflation-in-upside-inflation-scenario-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:30:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/boes-pill-i-do-worry-about-upside-risks-to-inflation-in-upside-inflation-scenario-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Should not assume that latest MPR forecast is a direct endorsement of market interest rate curve.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I see risk of second round effects (for inflation).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I remain concerned we have seen a structural change in price and wage setting in UK.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Response of monetary policy to ensure we get CPI back to target may need to be more persistent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;MPR inflation forecast has become less relevant to MPC policy debate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pill, alongside Mann, voted for keeping the Bank Rate unchanged at the last policy decision. He is sounding hawkish because we haven&apos;t really seen a concrete progress in UK inflation and wage growth data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think the upside inflation scenario is already playing out as growth fears in the markets ease and the BoE cut interest rates even though they haven&apos;t made much progress on underyling inflation and especially on the wage growth side. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany May ZEW survey current conditions -82.0 vs -77.0 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-zew-survey-current-conditions-820-vs-770-expected-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:00:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-may-zew-survey-current-conditions-820-vs-770-expected-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -81.2&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economic sentiment 25.2 vs 11.9 expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -14.0&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The headline reading continues to underscore challenging conditions for the German economy but expectations are brightening, so that&apos;s a positive takeaway in all this. ZEW notes that with a new government in place and progress on trade disputes, there is a significant increase in optimism.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the distribution of forecasts for the US CPI?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-is-the-distribution-of-forecasts-for-the-us-cpi-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:30:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-is-the-distribution-of-forecasts-for-the-us-cpi-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The ranges of estimates are 
important in terms of market reaction because when the actual data deviates from the 
expectations, it creates a surprise effect. Another
 important input in market&apos;s reaction is the distribution of forecasts. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, although we can have a range of 
estimates, most forecasts might be clustered on the upper bound of the 
range, so even if the data comes out inside the range of estimates but 
on the lower bound of the range, it can still create a surprise effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CPI Y/Y &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.5% (6%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.4% (61%) - consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.3% (31%) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.2% (2%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;CPI M/M&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6% (1%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.4% (4%) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.3% (58%) - consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.2% (32%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.1% (4%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.0% (1%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core CPI Y/Y&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;3.0% (2%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.9% (18%) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.8% (62%) - consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2.7% (18%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core CPI M/M&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6% (1%) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.4% (6%) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.3% (66%) - consensus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.2% (24%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.1% (3%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that the expectations around an average 10% global tariff rate solidified and growth fears eased, the focus might switch back to inflation. The market might start to expect stronger economic activity ahead, therefore slower progress on inflation could deter the Fed from cutting rates and even lead to the market pricing in less rate cuts than previously expected. This should be supportive for the US Dollar in the short-term as Treasury yields rise.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Makhlouf: Uncertainty is weighing on investment</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-makhlouf-uncertainty-is-weighing-on-investment-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:11:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-makhlouf-uncertainty-is-weighing-on-investment-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty is weighing on investment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soft data pointing to a significant cooling in business and consumer sentiment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Global economic integretion is now stalled, if not reversing; last few weeks have seen an acceleration in pace and scale of change.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Even if a full-blown trade war turns out to be short-lived, uncertainty effects will persist for some time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monetary policy must adapt to the new nature of supply shocks generated by geoeconomic fragmentation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Given effects of size, scale and more persistent nature of fragmentation-induced shocks, and their impact on prices, monetary policy responses will need careful calibration.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Threats of inflation de-anchoring, from both above and below, warrant forceful and persistent responses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interest rates remains default policy lever in our toolbox; when constrained by lower bound, other tools such as targeted lending and balance sheet operations have their uses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He&apos;s suggesting a more careful approach to interest rates adjustments. I think the ECB now needs to pause for some time and see how things evolve in light of the recent news on the trade front. The market is now pricing 45 bps of easing by year-end compared to 56 bps before the US-China news.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar holds slightly lower so far on the session</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-holds-slightly-lower-so-far-on-the-session-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:10:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-holds-slightly-lower-so-far-on-the-session-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;After the strong gains yesterday, the dollar is catching a bit of a breather in trading today. This comes as US futures are also just down slightly after the surging gains in the day before. Market players are digesting the US-China trade truce and will have to wait to see if the optimism can be justified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;USD/JPY is down 0.4% to 147.85 but it doesn&apos;t take much away from the over 300 pips jump from yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Meanwhile, EUR/USD is up 0.2% to 1.1115 and GBP/USD up 0.3% to 1.3215 on the day. USD/CHF is also marked down by 0.7% to 0.8395 but is still well higher compared to the Friday close last week near 0.8300. The antipodes are also faring better with AUD/USD recovering a large chunk of its losses yesterday to 0.6405 - up 0.6% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Elsewhere, gold is also seen recovering back to $3,259 and holding the line near its 1 May low of $3,201 amid the drop yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Coming up later today, we&apos;ll have the US CPI report to add to the mix. We&apos;re not likely to see any major impact from tariffs show up though, so any kneejerk reaction to the numbers should be easily brushed aside.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BofA Fund Manager Survey: Fund Managers most underweight US Dollars since 2006</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-fund-manager-survey-fund-managers-most-underweight-us-dollars-since-2006-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:17:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-fund-manager-survey-fund-managers-most-underweight-us-dollars-since-2006-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fund Managers most underweight US Dollars since 2006.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US-China trade war ceasefire prevents recession/credit event.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior to US-China talks in Geneva, fund managers saw US tariffs on China goods at 37%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;61% of fund managers see soft landing for the economy versus 37% in April.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;26% see hard landing, down from 49% in April.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We can see here that the &quot;short US Dollar trade&quot; has been (and I think it&apos;s still is) a pretty overcrowded trade. I can see some more upside for the greenback in the next weeks but we might need strong economic data to make the market to price in an even less dovish path for interest rates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe an upside surprise in today&apos;s US CPI report might do it.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices lightly changed at the open today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-lightly-changed-at-the-open-today-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-lightly-changed-at-the-open-today-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy FTSE MIB flat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down slightly by 0.4% but that follows from the surging gains overnight as the index closed at the highs with over 3% gains.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDJPY Technical Analysis – The greenback is back</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-the-greenback-is-back-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 07:02:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdjpy-technical-analysis-the-greenback-is-back-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD got a boost across
the board yesterday as the US-China tariff relief was much better than
expected. The market is now looking at the more hawkish scenario where we get
an average 10% global tariff rate and economic activity picks up on an easing
in growth fears and general uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is leading to a
hawkish repricing in interest rates expectations with the market now seeing 56
bps of easing for the Fed by year-end compared to like 120 bps at the peak of
the fears in April. The short dollar trade was also pretty overcrowded so the
unwinding in positioning is giving the greenback even more strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the JPY side, the
currency has been driven mainly by global events rather than domestic
fundamentals. Alongside the Swiss Franc, it’s been the favoured safe haven in
the currencies space amid the swings in risk sentiment. The recent positive
mood in the markets weighed on the Japanese Yen which lost ground against all
the major currencies despite the market increasing the expectations for another
rate hike this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that USDJPY broke above the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt; yesterday following the much
better than expected US-China tariff relief. The buyers piled in on the
breakout and will now target the 151.00 handle. The sellers, on the other hand,
will want to see the price falling back below the trendline to position for a
drop into the 140.00 handle next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see that we have now an upward trendline defining the bullish momentum on this
timeframe. From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a better
risk to reward setup around the trendline, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into new lows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY Technical
Analysis – 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, there’s
not much else we can add here as the buyers will look for a bounce around the trendline,
while the sellers will look for a break lower. If the bullish momentum stays
strong, we can expect the buyers to increase the bullish bets on the break of
the recent high at 148.60. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we have the US CPI report. On Thursday, we get the
latest US Jobless Claims figures, the US PPI and the US Retail Sales data. On
Friday, we conclude the week with the Japanese Q1 GDP report and the University
of Michigan Consumer Sentiment survey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says fentanyl issue is not their responsibility</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-fentanyl-issue-is-not-their-responsibility-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:55:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-says-fentanyl-issue-is-not-their-responsibility-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, it was noted yesterday &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-is-the-china-camp-painting-the-trade-deal-situation-back-home-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; how China avoided mentioning the fentanyl issue in their communication/statement and now we&apos;re starting to see why. That comes despite the many comments by Bessent that China had supposedly come to understand the US&apos; position on the matter over the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The Chinese foreign ministry was asked today whether fentanyl would be discussed in trade talks moving forward. And their response is that fentanyl is a US issue and the responsibility for tackling that lies within the US itself. Adding that the 20% tariffs imposed on China due to the matter is &quot;unreasonable&quot;. Only one day gone and a chink in the armor already? Hmm.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China lifts ban on Boeing deliveries amid latest trade agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-lifts-ban-on-boeing-deliveries-amid-latest-trade-agreement-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-lifts-ban-on-boeing-deliveries-amid-latest-trade-agreement-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;From before: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-calls-for-its-airlines-to-halt-any-further-boeing-jet-deliveries-amid-trade-strife-20250415/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;China calls for its airlines to halt any further Boeing jet deliveries amid trade strife&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That helps to some extent but with the relative uncertainty of what might come next in the US-China trade war, I reckon Chinese airlines will continue to lean more and more towards Airbus - which already holds the dominant market share.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Bessent: Talks in Geneva with China resulted in a mechanism to avoid escalation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-bessent-talks-in-geneva-with-china-resulted-in-a-mechanism-to-avoid-escalation-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:25:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-bessent-talks-in-geneva-with-china-resulted-in-a-mechanism-to-avoid-escalation-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Talks in Geneva with China resulted in a mechanism to avoid escalation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;President Trump wants to rebalance the US economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China needs to rebalance towards consumption economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We do not want a generalised decoupling between the two largest economies in the world.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;United States will bring medicine, semiconductor and other strategic industries home.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Very productive discussions with Japan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Focused on Asia deals, Indonesia has been very forthcoming, Taiwan presented very good proposals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s nothing new here as he&apos;s just repeating what was said in the prior days and weeks. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +0.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:15:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;US stocks ended yesterday with a flourish, so that&apos;s helping to steady the ship on the week. Things are settling down now as we take a light breather to digest the US-China tariffs reduction and 90-day pause for talks to progress. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down 0.3% but that follows from 3.3% gains overnight, in which the index cleared both its 100 and 200-day moving averages comfortably.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:12:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;In the European session, we don&apos;t have much on the agenda other than the German ZEW survey and BoE&apos;s Pill speech. The ZEW index is expected to rebound on easing trade fears and BoE&apos;s Pill is unlikely to say anything new since he spoke just last week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the American session, we get the US CPI report where the Core Y/Y figure is expected at 2.8% vs. 2.8% prior, while the M/M measure is seen at 0.3% vs. 0.1% prior. I think the data will now start to get more and more important as the expectations around an average 10% global tariff rate solidify. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk going forward shouldn&apos;t be growth anymore. It will likely be inflation as economic activity picks up. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK March ILO unemployment rate 4.5% vs 4.5% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-ilo-unemployment-rate-45-vs-45-expected-20250513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 06:01:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-march-ilo-unemployment-rate-45-vs-45-expected-20250513/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 4.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Employment change 112k vs 115k expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior 206k&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Average weekly earnings +5.5% vs +5.2% 3m/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +5.6%; revised to +5.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Average weekly earnings ex bonus +5.6% vs +5.7% 3m/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +5.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;April payrolls change -33k&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -78k; revised to -47k&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The jobless continues to allude to added softness in the labour market with payrolls once again falling in April. ONS might still have some data inconsistencies on accuracy but the bigger picture trend has been playing out quite straightforward at least. As for wages, real earnings is at least continuing to come down a little but is still on the higher side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s hard to read too much into the data given the mix of things. But balancing this out with the BOE messaging, it won&apos;t press policymakers to desperately go with a rate cut next month.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
