<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: I COULD SEE A TRUMP-XI CALL HAPPENING IN COMING WEEKS OR MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921897547552977349#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921897547552977349#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: I COULD SEE A TRUMP-XI CALL HAPPENING IN COMING WEEKS OR MONTHS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 BESSENT: CAN ALWAYS GO BACK TO APRIL 2 LEVEL FOR CHINA TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921897364857458884#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:56:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921897364857458884#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 BESSENT: CAN ALWAYS GO BACK TO APRIL 2 LEVEL FOR CHINA TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *BESSENT SAYS IT IS `IMPLAUSIBLE&apos; CHINA TARIFFS GO BELOW 10%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921896410770751601#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:53:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921896410770751601#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*BESSENT SAYS IT IS `IMPLAUSIBLE&apos; CHINA TARIFFS GO BELOW 10%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: It is implausible that tariffs on China go below 10%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-it-is-implausible-that-tariffs-on-china-go-below-10-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:52:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-it-is-implausible-that-tariffs-on-china-go-below-10-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current tariffs level is a floor&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now, we have a process in place to avoid further escalation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This at least clears things up a bit on their current position at least. As a reminder, the US is now putting a 10% base level tariffs plus 20% tariffs due to the fentanyl issue (30% total) on China. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-deal-reportedly-does-not-cover-de-minimis-exemption-for-e-commerce-shipments-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;the de minimis exemption will not be restored&lt;/a&gt; as well even with the climb down. Meanwhile, China is putting a 10% base level tariffs on the US and have not pulled back on restricting rare earth exports from before &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-halts-rare-earth-exports-after-new-controls-raising-global-supply-concerns-20250413/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: APRIL 2ND LEVEL WOULD BE A CEILING FOR CHINA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921895793100792207#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:50:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921895793100792207#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: APRIL 2ND LEVEL WOULD BE A CEILING FOR CHINA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *BESSENT: CURRENT TARIFF LEVEL FOR CHINA IS A &apos;FLOOR&apos;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921895541895553138#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921895541895553138#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*BESSENT: CURRENT TARIFF LEVEL FOR CHINA IS A &apos;FLOOR&apos;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: PHASE ONE TRADE DEAL WITH CHINA OFFERED A TEMPLATE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921895407887454213#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:49:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921895407887454213#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: PHASE ONE TRADE DEAL WITH CHINA OFFERED A TEMPLATE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: AN UNFORTUNATE ESCALATION HAPPENED WITH CHINA.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921895224944599222#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:48:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921895224944599222#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: AN UNFORTUNATE ESCALATION HAPPENED WITH CHINA.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How is the China camp painting the trade deal situation back home?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-is-the-china-camp-painting-the-trade-deal-situation-back-home-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:47:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-is-the-china-camp-painting-the-trade-deal-situation-back-home-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;While China is also acknowledging the positive steps taken in seeking a trade deal, the nuance in how either the US or China is selling the narrative is also something important to be wary about. On paper, sure there are things to be optimistic as both sides seek de-escalation. However, the undertone is what will set the stage for further discussions and how fruitful that can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The US so far have pushed the narrative that both sides managed to see eye to eye in talks over the weekend. And that China has finally understood the US&apos; position on fentanyl and will do something about that. In the meantime, Bessent has been harping on the supposed mechanism for both sides to continue discussions moving forward. And he made sure markets know that with such a mechanism, retaliatory tariffs of the kind we saw last month will be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But how is China viewing all this instead?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;China&apos;s commerce ministry dubbed the deal as an &quot;important step&quot; in resolving the differences between the two countries via dialogue and consultation. Adding that it lays the groundwork for further cooperation. Note, there&apos;s no mention of fentanyl talks whatsoever here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And hours later, the message from the state media is making it clear how they see the situation as being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;&quot;This shows that China&apos;s firm countermeasures and resolute stance have been very effective. The countermeasures have had a material impact on the US and the US administration have reduced tariffs to the base level i.e. 10% after the talks.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Besides that, the commerce ministry also made sure to note that its restriction on rare earth exports will still be in place regardless of the agreement today. In case you missed it, this is related to the announcement last month &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-china-halts-rare-earth-exports-after-new-controls-raising-global-supply-concerns-20250413/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All this is not to say that there&apos;s two sides to the story though. At least this time around, the narratives from both sides are lining up much, much closer together than before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;However, it is evident that China is more reserved and cautiously optimistic. That said, optimistic is still optimistic especially after the height of tensions last month. And the joint statement today, which is a rarity on its own, reflects that as both sides are putting on a show to seek de-escalation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For just choosing to sit down and talk, China has definitely gotten a major concession from Trump. So, it&apos;s arguably clear who blinked first in this scenario. But at this point, it doesn&apos;t really matter who did. Egos aside, the development is a positive for markets and the global economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But in the bigger picture, can this be followed up by more positive correspondence and eventually an actual trade deal down the road? Or is this going to be the new normal with the US seeking sectoral tariffs/decoupling from China? We&apos;ll see in time.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT:   FOR THE FIRST TIME, CHINESE UNDERSTOOD U.S. CONCERNS ABOUT FENTANYL -MSNBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921892212125663686#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:36:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921892212125663686#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT:   FOR THE FIRST TIME, CHINESE UNDERSTOOD U.S. CONCERNS ABOUT FENTANYL -MSNBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT:  THERE IS A CHANCE TO REBALANCE TOGETHER; WE&apos;LL SEE IF IT&apos;S POSSIBLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921892167703806056#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:36:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921892167703806056#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT:  THERE IS A CHANCE TO REBALANCE TOGETHER; WE&apos;LL SEE IF IT&apos;S POSSIBLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: WE WANT CHINA TO REBALANCE ITS ECONOMY TOWARD MORE CONSUMPTION -MSNBC INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921892112229896662#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:36:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921892112229896662#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: WE WANT CHINA TO REBALANCE ITS ECONOMY TOWARD MORE CONSUMPTION -MSNBC INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) UKRAINE&apos;S FOREIGN MINISTER SAYS RUSSIA IS &apos;COMPLETELY IGNORING&apos; 30-DAY CEASEFIRE OFFER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921890880207679713#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:31:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921890880207679713#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UKRAINE&apos;S FOREIGN MINISTER SAYS RUSSIA IS &apos;COMPLETELY IGNORING&apos; 30-DAY CEASEFIRE OFFER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: WILL DISCUSS LABOR AND CAPITAL WITH CHINA IN FURTHER TALKS -MSNBC INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921890498895122741#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:29:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921890498895122741#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: WILL DISCUSS LABOR AND CAPITAL WITH CHINA IN FURTHER TALKS -MSNBC INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE SAYS QATARI GOVERNMENT HAS OFFERED TO DONATE A PLANE TO UNITED STATES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921890380418580984#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:29:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921890380418580984#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE SAYS QATARI GOVERNMENT HAS OFFERED TO DONATE A PLANE TO UNITED STATES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 CHINA&apos;S RARE EARTH EXPORT RESTRICTIONS CONTINUE: YUYUANTANTIAN, A WEIBO ACCOUNT WITH STATE TIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921890327964627438#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:28:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921890327964627438#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 CHINA&apos;S RARE EARTH EXPORT RESTRICTIONS CONTINUE: YUYUANTANTIAN, A WEIBO ACCOUNT WITH STATE TIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) LEAVITT: UNFREEZING RARE EARTH WAS PART OF US-CHINA DISCUSSIONS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921890245416472705#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:28:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921890245416472705#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LEAVITT: UNFREEZING RARE EARTH WAS PART OF US-CHINA DISCUSSIONS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: WE &quot;GOT A LOT DONE&quot; OVER TWO DAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921886253244452874#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:12:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921886253244452874#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: WE &quot;GOT A LOT DONE&quot; OVER TWO DAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT, ASKED IF WILL MEET WITH CHINA AGAIN: IMAGINE WE WILL MEET AGAIN IN NEXT FEW WEEKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921886178732646430#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:12:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921886178732646430#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT, ASKED IF WILL MEET WITH CHINA AGAIN: IMAGINE WE WILL MEET AGAIN IN NEXT FEW WEEKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: WE WANT AMERICAN BUSINESSES TO BE ABLE TO SELL INTO CHINA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921886055722106918#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921886055722106918#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: WE WANT AMERICAN BUSINESSES TO BE ABLE TO SELL INTO CHINA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: WILL SEE WHAT WE CAN DO TO WORK ON NON-TARIFF BARRIERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921885862347858309#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:11:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921885862347858309#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: WILL SEE WHAT WE CAN DO TO WORK ON NON-TARIFF BARRIERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: We want a decoupling with China for strategic necessities</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-want-a-decoupling-with-china-for-strategic-necessities-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:10:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-want-a-decoupling-with-china-for-strategic-necessities-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are going to protect our steel, semiconductor industries, selected medicines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Believe China is now serious about halting fentanyl flows into the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We have a mechanism in place to avoid upwards tariffs pressure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We want American businesses to be able to sell to China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I imagine we will meet (with China) again in the next few weeks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We got a lot done over two days&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will see what we can do on non-tariff barriers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, earlier in the day he said that neither side are interested in decoupling. So, yeah. In any case, any real intentions will be buried by the wave of optimism across markets right now as both sides seek de-escalation. But for China, they certainly got a lot out of it by just deciding to sit down for a chat. Either way, it&apos;s still a positive for markets and the global economy.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT:  BELIEVE CHINA IS NOW SERIOUS ABOUT HALTING FENTANYL FLOWS INTO U.S</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921885612186935568#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:10:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921885612186935568#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT:  BELIEVE CHINA IS NOW SERIOUS ABOUT HALTING FENTANYL FLOWS INTO U.S&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Sentiment Now (... and watch these prices)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/market-sentiment-now-and-watch-these-prices-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:08:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/market-sentiment-now-and-watch-these-prices-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-pm-slice=&quot;1 1 []&quot;&gt;Market Sentiment Snapshot for Traders and Investors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today’s financial markets are experiencing significant shifts driven primarily by the recent U.S.-China agreement on tariff reductions. Here is a detailed overview of the current sentiment across key financial instruments:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold (Bearish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold prices have dropped sharply, with futures plunging about 3%. This bearish momentum is largely a result of improved sentiment stemming from U.S.-China tariff cuts, reducing gold&apos;s attractiveness as a traditional safe-haven asset. Traders should monitor if uncertainties around these trade agreements resurface, potentially stabilizing or reversing gold&apos;s bearish trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GOLD HAS CROSSED DOWN 3320... But if it crosses above it, then we may have a dip in gold!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil (Bullish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil prices are strongly bullish, rising between 2% to over 3% today. Positive trade developments between the U.S. and China are fueling optimism for global economic growth and increased oil demand. However, the potential for higher crude oil oversupply due to increased OPEC production remains a notable risk that traders should watch closely, as it could temper current gains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 (Bullish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. equity markets are firmly bullish, with stock futures significantly higher. This positive sentiment is primarily due to easing U.S.-China tensions and expectations of improved trade conditions. Investors are cautiously optimistic, awaiting further details to assess the sustainability of this rally. Equity investors should maintain vigilance for any signs of stalled trade progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch ES 5882 today... If we get there, profit takers may stop in. TRADE AT YOUR OWN RISK ONLY.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US Dollar Index (Bullish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar has surged to a one-month high, driven by the improving global growth outlook linked to U.S.-China tariff relief. The bullish sentiment is strong, but the market acknowledges that maintaining this momentum depends on continued progress in trade negotiations. Currency traders should watch for developments closely, as any negative shifts could swiftly impact the dollar’s current strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese Yen (Bearish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The yen is notably bearish today, experiencing significant selling pressure as investors pivot away from safe-haven currencies in favor of riskier assets amid reduced geopolitical tensions. The positive U.S.-China tariff developments have significantly diminished the yen&apos;s attractiveness, placing additional downward pressure on the currency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Euro (Bearish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUR/USD has experienced considerable bearish pressure, breaking below key support and eyeing further declines towards the 1.09 handle. The euro’s weakness largely stems from the strengthened dollar. However, traders note that further downside may be limited, given the potential uplift in global economic sentiment from recent trade agreements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Euro futures CROSSED DOWN 1.1118... But if it crosses above it, then we may have a dip in Euro!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrencies (Bullish)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrencies, led notably by Ethereum (ETH), are seeing a strong bullish sentiment. ETH has gained approximately 42% in the past five days, driven by improved investor optimism from U.S.-China tariff cuts and an overall increase in risk appetite. The crypto market broadly reflects this positive sentiment, indicating confidence in continued bullish momentum in the near term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If bitcoin futures reaches 103,500 (retracing down to there), then bulls may buy again!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Correlations and Market Dynamics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-spread=&quot;false&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk-On Sentiment: The simultaneous rise in stocks, the US dollar, cryptocurrencies, and oil underscores strong &quot;risk-on&quot; market sentiment driven by U.S.-China trade optimism. This is negatively impacting traditional safe-haven assets like gold and yen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inverse Correlation (Gold vs. Stocks &amp;amp; Crypto): Gold’s bearishness directly corresponds with bullish equity and cryptocurrency sentiment, as traders shift away from defensive positions to riskier assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dollar Strength vs. Euro and Yen Weakness: The robust US dollar rally directly pressures the euro and yen, highlighting their inverse correlation with risk-positive developments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actionable Insights for traders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traders and investors should remain adaptive, closely tracking updates from ongoing U.S.-China negotiations. Immediate bullish or bearish biases can swiftly shift, depending on trade-related news. Keeping an eye on further details and potential reversals will be crucial in managing risk and capturing opportunities in the current dynamic market environment. Watch some of the tips above for possible hints for the end of the moves, and possible trades... at your own risk only.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How have interest rates expectations changed after the US-China news?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-us-china-news-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-us-china-news-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 54 bps (92% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 45 bps (79% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 50 bps (84% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 39 bps (58% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 78 bps (98% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 69 bps (69% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 30 bps (96% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 19 bps (96% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the US-UK deal last week, we had some &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-the-first-trade-deal-20250509/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;hawkish repricing &lt;/a&gt;as the expectations for a 10% baseline tariff for everyone started to solidify. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, following the very positive US-China news this morning, the market is taking an even more hawkish view on future rates as positive expectations about global growth and potentially a surge in economic activity in the short-term will likely lead central banks to slow down the pace further. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US-China deal reportedly does not cover de minimis exemption for e-commerce shipments</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-deal-reportedly-does-not-cover-de-minimis-exemption-for-e-commerce-shipments-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 10:51:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-china-deal-reportedly-does-not-cover-de-minimis-exemption-for-e-commerce-shipments-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The de minimis exemption is a rule which allowed for certain e-commerce shipments of goods at $800 or less to enter duty-free. The $800 is the threshold amount so to speak. Any shipments below that will not incur import charges basically. This allowed a supposed &quot;loophole&quot; for online retailers - particularly fast fashion from China - to have a stronger presence in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This exemption was removed by the White House last month &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/04/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-closes-de-minimis-exemptions-to-combat-chinas-role-in-americas-synthetic-opioid-crisis/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. And it looks like even with the trade deal announced today, that&apos;s not going to fall back into place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, in any case, online shopping from overseas will definitely be much more expensive for US consumers regardless of the deal today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;If you head over to the DHL sub-Reddit in the past two weeks, you can already see how much of a pain tariffs have become for US consumers. There&apos;s been countless cases of duties charged being much more than the entire item/product ordered itself. It goes to show where the pain really lies when it comes to tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More from BoE&apos;s Greene: Disinflation process in underway</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-greene-disinflation-process-in-underway-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 10:49:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-greene-disinflation-process-in-underway-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Disinflation process in underway.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some slack opened up in the labour market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Risks to UK productivity are to the downside.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FX rates could be disinflationary if the trend persists.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On net, I think tariffs will be disinflationary for the UK, this was a factor in my rate decision.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I came into this decision quite torn about whether to cut.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I wouldn&apos;t change my decision after this morning&apos;s US-China news.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don&apos;t yet have much clarity on EU tariffs, which are important for UK demand.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are focused more on domestic factors rather than trade.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the US-China news, the policymakers will start to adjust their views and look at the more hawkish scenario.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOE&apos;s Greene: Wage, inflation measures are moving in the right course but still too high</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-greene-wage-inflation-measures-are-moving-in-the-right-course-but-still-too-high-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 10:39:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-greene-wage-inflation-measures-are-moving-in-the-right-course-but-still-too-high-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inflation persistence indicators are still too high&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slightly worried that medium-term inflation expectations are starting to tick up&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The BOE might have managed to cut the rates last week but remarks such as these continue to highlight that there&apos;s certainly a strong debate of views within the ranks at the central bank.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equities, dollar hold gains ahead of US trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/equities-dollar-hold-gains-ahead-of-us-trading-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 10:37:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/equities-dollar-hold-gains-ahead-of-us-trading-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There was already the opening gap higher from early today as Trump floated &quot;a very good&quot; meeting with China over the weekend. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures were up 1.5% before doubling gains to be up by roughly 3% now. That comes after the joint statement by both sides, confirming the lowering of tariffs by 115% for 90 days as they seek further talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Since then, it&apos;s been quite straightforward trading on the session. There&apos;s not much let up in the optimism as equities continue to hold close to the highs. In Europe, the DAX is up 1.0% while the CAC 40 is up 1.4% as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As for FX, the dollar is also sitting at the highs for the day. EUR/USD is down 1.4% to 1.1090 while USD/JPY is up over 2% to 148.45 currently. Even AUD/USD has turned negative on the day with the pair down 0.4% to 0.6390 currently.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Drug prices to be cut by 59%, plus!</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-drug-prices-to-be-cut-by-59-plus-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 10:30:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-drug-prices-to-be-cut-by-59-plus-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;&quot;DRUG PRICES TO BE CUT BY 59%, PLUS! Gasoline, Energy, Groceries, and all other costs, DOWN. NO INFLATION!!! LOVE, DJT&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He still won&apos;t get the rate cuts he&apos;s pushing for &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD broke through the key support and it&apos;s now eyeing the 1.09 handle</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-broke-through-the-key-support-and-its-now-eyeing-the-109-handle-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 09:57:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-broke-through-the-key-support-and-its-now-eyeing-the-109-handle-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US Dollar has been taking it on the chin for a few months now and eventually it became one of the most crowded trades. In such instances, you should start to get wary and look for inflection points. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the last few weeks, I&apos;ve been highlighting that positive news on the trade front would have likely boosted the greenback in the short-term because of overstretched positioning. When you are at such overstretched levels, as soon as conditions change, the repricing can lead to meaningful corrections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the US Dollar is now driven by the hawkish repricing in interest rates expectations. At the peak of the trade war fears, the market went to price in as far as five rate cuts by the end of 2025, and now following the US-China news, we are down to just two rate cuts (which was the Fed&apos;s base case in December 2024).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the best case scenario I&apos;ve outlined &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-best-case-scenario-for-the-us-dollar-is-playing-out-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We should see further gains for the greenback as the market might even start to doubt the need for two rate cuts, but for that, stronger economic data might be needed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can see that we recently broke through the key support zone around the 1.1277 level where we had also the major trendline for confluence. We retested the breakout before opening lower today and then extending the move to the downside as the US-China news hit. The next key levels are the 1.10 and 1.09 handles, but I can see the swing low around the 1.09 being targeted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can see the strong move to the downside following the US-China news. That was the time to sell as we might not get a good pullback after such a surprising news. Remember that the market&apos;s reaction is stronger when it gets surprised. If we do get a pullback though, we should find sellers around the minor downward trendline near the 1.12 handle. If the price breaks higher, then the buyers could take the price to the next resistance around the 1.1277 level. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants lower interest rates but his strategy is likely to lead to higher rates</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-wants-lower-interest-rates-but-hes-strategy-is-likely-to-lead-to-higher-rates-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:56:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-wants-lower-interest-rates-but-hes-strategy-is-likely-to-lead-to-higher-rates-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;One of the main Trump&apos;s goals has been bringing long term interest rates down. The focus was on reducing the deficit because it impacted the long term premium.  We&apos;ve heard many times talks of the US being on an &quot;unsustainable path&quot; and in the long-run that leads to either higher taxes or higher &quot;money printing&quot;. For this reason, buyers of US debt could demand higher interest rates for the perceived future risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Short-term interest rates are determined by the central bank policy but long term rates are determined by the market. For long term interest rates, the market takes into account three main factors: future central bank policy, inflation expectations and future supply and demand of Treasury debt issuance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump&apos;s &quot;strategic uncertainty&quot; to negotiate trade barriers kind of halted the momentum in economic activity that we&apos;ve had before this whole tariffs saga begun. As we now price in better and better conditions for global growth (as the super high tariffs get brought down), the economic activity will likely start to accelerate and the higher demand could keep inflation higher for longer and take rate cuts off the table again. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This might keep the downside in long term yields limited and lead to higher rates in the second half of 2025 before seeing them rolling over and this time making a new low. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if you took the Trump trade quite literally?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-if-you-took-the-trump-trade-quite-literally-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:28:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-if-you-took-the-trump-trade-quite-literally-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Here&apos;s a graphical depiction of the S&amp;amp;P 500 and Trump&apos;s statements about buying stocks in the last few weeks:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And now, markets are rallying further as the US and China lower tariffs in favour of discussions - at least for the next 90 days. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up over 2.5% on the day, we&apos;re slated to open just above the 5,800 mark. If that holds, Trump&apos;s message from Thursday last week will again yield another positive follow through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And if you really took to his first message of it being &quot;THIS IS A GREAT TIME TO BUY!!!&quot; before the reciprocal tariffs pause announcement, the return would&apos;ve been roughly 16% as we get to the open later today.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More from BoE&apos;s Lombardelli: Latest US-China discussions are good news</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-lombardelli-latest-us-china-discussions-are-good-news-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-from-boes-lombardelli-latest-us-china-discussions-are-good-news-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Latest US-China discussions are good news, if reports are accurate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Progress on domestic inflation, not US tariffs, was the main factor behind my rate vote.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trade policy uncertainty will continue until there&apos;s a permanent solution.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK GDP data is volatile, makes it hard to gauge if weakness is due to demand or supply.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US-China news is without a doubt the news of the day and most likely of the week. They brought down tariffs by much more than expected, so that&apos;s a positive for global growth expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It could end up fuelling some inflation in the short-term, so that&apos;s going to be something to watch out for because it could force the central banks to take a longer pause on rate adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrimeXBT Introduces VIP Tiers with Up to 50% Trading Fee Discounts for Active Traders</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/primexbt-introduces-vip-tiers-with-up-to-50-trading-fee-discounts-for-active-traders-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:21:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/primexbt-introduces-vip-tiers-with-up-to-50-trading-fee-discounts-for-active-traders-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;PrimeXBT, a
regulated multi-asset broker, has announced the launch of its VIP Tiers, a
trading-based rewards system designed to lower trading costs for high-volume
traders. With discounts of up to 50% now available, the new system brings
enhanced flexibility and cost efficiency to trading across a wide range of
markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VIP Tiers are applied automatically based on a trader&apos;s
30-day cumulative trading volume across Crypto Futures, Forex, and CFDs on
Indices, Commodities, Stocks, and Crypto. Traders who reach the volume
milestone for VIP Tier 1 are instantly upgraded, unlocking a 25% discount on
Crypto Futures and CFD trading costs. The tier status remains locked for 30
days but can still be upgraded to VIP Tier 2, offering a 40% discount on Crypto
Futures and a 50% discount on CFD trading costs, once the trading volume criteria
is met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to PrimeXBT, the introduction of VIP Tiers gives
traders a clear and motivating way to lower trading costs the more they trade.
The tier system is designed to be accessible for active retail traders while
also catering to institutional participants across diverse markets. The broker
views this launch as a major step toward creating a more inclusive and
rewarding environment for high-volume traders of all kinds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This update reflects PrimeXBT’s ongoing commitment to
competitive conditions and long-term client trust. By providing full insight
into how trading fee discounts are calculated and when they apply, the company
strengthens its promise of fairness and clarity across its trading platforms. To
learn more, users can visit PrimeXBT website (https://primexbt.com).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About PrimeXBT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PrimeXBT is a
leading Crypto and CFD broker that offers an all-in-one trading platform to
buy, sell, and store Cryptocurrencies, and trade over 150 popular markets,
including Crypto Futures and CFDs on Crypto, Forex, Indices, Commodities, and
Stocks using both fiat and Crypto funds. Since its founding in 2018, PrimeXBT
has grown exponentially, serving 1,000,000+ traders in 150+ countries
worldwide. With an aim of making investing available to all, PrimeXBT lowers
the barriers to entry, providing easy and secure access to the financial
markets with industry-leading trading conditions and innovative tools. Clients
engage with a regulated financial services provider recognized for its
reliability and commitment to offering cost-efficient trading solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The content provided here is for informational purposes
only and is not intended as personal investment advice and does not constitute
a solicitation or invitation to engage in any financial transactions,
investments, or related activities. Past performance is not a reliable
indicator of future results. The financial products offered by the Company are
complex and come with a high risk of losing money rapidly due to leverage.
These products may not be suitable for all investors. Before engaging, you should
consider whether you understand how these leveraged products work and whether
you can afford the high risk of losing your money. The Company does not accept
clients from the Restricted Jurisdictions as indicated on its website. Some
products and services, including MT5, may not be available in your
jurisdiction. The applicable legal entity and its respective products and
services depend on the client’s country of residence and the entity with which
the client has established a contractual relationship during registration.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOE&apos;s Lombardelli: Caution remains appropriate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-lombardelli-caution-remains-appropriate-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:06:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-lombardelli-caution-remains-appropriate-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Evidence suggests that policy is still restrictive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wage growth is still too high for on target inflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wages is my main focus when looking for disinflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Further gradual disinflation progress and trade developments made 25 bps rate cut appropriate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just some token remarks here and ones that won&apos;t matter all too much as trade headlines are drowning out everything else at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNB total sight deposits w.e. 9 May CHF 453.2 bn vs CHF 454.1 bn prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-9-may-chf-4532-bn-vs-chf-4541-bn-prior-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-9-may-chf-4532-bn-vs-chf-4541-bn-prior-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Domestic sight deposits CHF 444.8 bn vs CHF 443.1 bn prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just some light changes in sight deposits in the past week. But the SNB can definitely take in some comfort now from the latest developments today surely.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best case scenario for the US Dollar is playing out</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-best-case-scenario-for-the-us-dollar-is-playing-out-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-best-case-scenario-for-the-us-dollar-is-playing-out-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Last week, I&apos;ve laid out a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-could-be-dead-wrong-on-rate-cuts-if-this-scenario-plays-out-20250507/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;case&lt;/a&gt; where the market could end up being &quot;dead wrong&quot; on interest rates expectations and that scenario is playing out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 10% baseline tariff rate on UK last week, kind of made me to turn up my nose, but the US-China announcement is much better than everyone expected and it will likely lead to positive global growth expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main point is that we&apos;ve been hearing and seeing from the economic reports that businesses 
are cautious due to tariff uncertainty and that&apos;s holding back activity.
 With such positive resolutions, economic activity will pick up fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fed could be even more constrained because there will be upward 
pressure on inflation and the economic data will start to show a strong 
rebound in activity justifying a cautious approach to rate adjustments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They will definitely deliver at least one rate cut, but they could end up with just that one cut in 2025. At the peak of the risk off sentiment last month, the market was pricing like 5 rate cuts by year-end and now we are back to 2 rate cuts (55 bps).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, we are back to where we were before the April 2 announcement and how the economy evolves from now on will determine if we indeed get just one cut or the two the Fed projected in December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this is of course a positive for the US Dollar in the short-term, especially since the USD short trade was one of the most crowded ones, but once we are done with the repricing in interest rates expectations, the focus will turn back to global growth and the positive sentiment could weigh on the greenback again.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: UK, Switzerland have moved to the front of the queue on trade deals</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-uk-switzerland-have-moved-to-the-front-of-the-queue-on-trade-deals-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:36:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-uk-switzerland-have-moved-to-the-front-of-the-queue-on-trade-deals-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s a chance if we can open up trade to China, we could have more fair trade towards the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China has not yet rebalanced towards a consumption-oriented economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And that&apos;s the end of the press conference. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are up 2.8% on the day, up from around 1.5% gains before the joint statement and briefing. Meanwhile, the dollar is much higher across the board with USD/JPY near 147.50 - up 1.5% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar surges higher as US, China bring down tariff levels for further talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-surges-higher-as-us-china-bring-down-tariff-levels-for-further-talks-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:33:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-surges-higher-as-us-china-bring-down-tariff-levels-for-further-talks-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;USD/JPY is now up nearly 1.5% on the day to 147.50 as the dollar is jumping higher across the board. EUR/USD is also marked down by over 1% now to 1.1120 with GBP/USD down 0.8% to test waters back under 1.3200 on the day. This comes with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures bordering on 3% gains while gold is down 2.9% on the day to $3,229 currently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The moves here are coming as the US and China issues a joint statement in confirming that both sides are reducing the reciprocal/retaliatory tariff levels by 115%. On the US side, they&apos;ll still be charging China with 30% tariffs overall. On the Chinese side, they&apos;ll be charging the US with 10% base level tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;All of this of course will be for 90 days, for now at least, as both sides seek to engage on further trade talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;I would say barring any major implosion in talks, that 90 days is subjective and can be kicked down the road unless one side loses patience with the other. And we all know who is more likely to be the one that does. So, just be wary of that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For now at least, it&apos;s all sunshine again in markets as the biggest known unknown sees a significant de-escalation. That being said, it&apos;s all about perception isn&apos;t it? Even with the tariffs reduction here, the effective tariff rate in the US is still going to be the highest since the 1940s. So, make what you will of that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;But for market sentiment, this market has been desperate for good news from US-China relations for quite a number of weeks now. And now that we finally get it, you can see the sort of elation in the immediate aftermath at least.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greer: We have a constructive path forward to have a positive conversation with China</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/greer-we-have-a-constructive-path-forward-to-have-a-positive-conversation-with-china-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/greer-we-have-a-constructive-path-forward-to-have-a-positive-conversation-with-china-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This agreement is about reciprocal tariffs, which are now at 10% each&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We ended up with a result that is very good for the US and China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There was no discussion on currency (Bessent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It is the first time that the Chinese understood the US&apos; position on fentanyl (Bessent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are leaving with a very good mechanism to avoid the kind of escalation we saw in the past weeks (Bessent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The dollar and risk trades are continuing to ramp higher on the headlines here as both Bessent and Greer are painting a very optimistic picture of what took place over the weekend and how things might pan out moving forward. USD/JPY is now up 1.3% to 147.20 while S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are nearing 3% gains on the day now.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: We have reached agreement with China on a 90-day pause, moving down tariff levels</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-have-reached-agreement-with-china-on-a-90-day-pause-moving-down-tariff-levels-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:09:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-we-have-reached-agreement-with-china-on-a-90-day-pause-moving-down-tariff-levels-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both sides will move reciprocal/retaliatory tariffs down by 115%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both sides very committed to 90-day pause period (Greer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An effective trade embargo was not sustainable practice for both sides (Greer)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Throughout the trade process, we have had a plan in place&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;And now, we have a mechanism for continued talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The consensus this weekend is that neither side wants a decoupling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We do want more balanced trade, would like to see China open to more US goods&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As negotiations move forward, think there is a possibility to see purchase agreements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Look forward to very good discussions now that there is the mechanism in place for talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It&apos;s a significant climb down from a trade embargo of course. But again, now all of this hinges on how talks will develop over the next 90 days. But unless things really go south, that timeline is one that I expect can be postponed time and time again. In the meantime though, Trump has done quite the job in hoodwinking the world into accepting the highest effective tariff levels in the US since the 1940s (even with this latest reduction) as being a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US to lower tariffs on China, to include a base 10% plus 20% fentanyl levy</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-to-lower-tariffs-on-china-to-include-a-base-10-plus-20-fentanyl-levy-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-to-lower-tariffs-on-china-to-include-a-base-10-plus-20-fentanyl-levy-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US to modify application of the rate of duty on articles of China&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This will be for an initial period of 90 days&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China will also suspend its tariffs on the US for an initial period of 90 days&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Only a 10% base tariffs rate will be applied&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A mechanism to continue discussions about economic and trade relations is established&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These discussions may be conducted alternately in China and the US, or in an agreed third country&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both sides may conduct working-level consultations on relevant economic and trade issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/articles/2025/05/joint-statement-on-u-s-china-economic-and-trade-meeting-in-geneva/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Full statement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Risk is ramping up on the headlines here with S&amp;amp;P 500 futures now up by 2.5% on the day. Essentially, the US to cut tariffs on China from 145% to 30%. Meanwhile, China is lowering theirs from 125% to 10%. This will apply for a period of 90 days for now as both sides look to discuss further on how to seek further progress in trade negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch: Bessent and Greer to brief on US-China talks in Geneva</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/watch-bessent-and-greer-to-brief-on-us-china-talks-in-switzerland-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:59:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/watch-bessent-and-greer-to-brief-on-us-china-talks-in-switzerland-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – Positive trade talks weigh on the precious metal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-positive-trade-talks-weigh-on-the-precious-metal-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 06:58:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-positive-trade-talks-weigh-on-the-precious-metal-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fundamental
Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold ended the last week
negatively, as first the positive expectations for the US-UK trade deal, and
then for the US-China talks over the weekend, weighed on the precious metal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the bigger picture, gold
remains in an uptrend as real yields will likely continue to fall amid Fed
easing. But in the short-term positive news on the trade front or a hawkish Fed
could trigger more downside for gold as the market prices out stagflationary
fears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold
Technical Analysis – Daily Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can
see that gold continues to pull back amid the positive news on the trade front.
From a risk management perspective, the buyers will have a better risk to
reward setup around the major &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-trendlines-20220406/&quot;&gt;trendline&lt;/a&gt;, while the sellers will look for a
break lower to increase the bearish bets into the 2957 level next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 4 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can
see the price fell all the way back to the key &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/technical-analysis-support-and-resistance-20220405/&quot;&gt;support&lt;/a&gt; around the 3258 level. This is where we can
expect the buyers to step in with a defined risk below the level to position
for a rally back into the 3367 resistance. The sellers, on the other hand, will
look for a break lower to increase the bearish bets into the major trendline
next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold Technical Analysis
– 1 hour Timeframe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can
see that we have a minor downward trendline now defining the current pullback. If
the price gets there, we can expect the sellers to lean on the trendline with a
defined risk above it to position for further downside. The buyers, on the
other hand, will look for a break higher to increase the bullish bets into new
highs. The red lines define the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-tip-know-the-average-daily-range-adr-20220207/&quot;&gt;average daily range&lt;/a&gt; for today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upcoming
Catalysts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar/&quot;&gt;Today&lt;/a&gt;, we get the US-China trade talks briefing. Tomorrow,
we have the US CPI report. On Thursday, we get the latest US Jobless Claims
figures, the US PPI and the US Retail Sales data. On Friday, we conclude the
week with the University of Michigan Consumer Sentiment report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
