<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 23 May: Pres. Trump is not partial to who he tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-23-may-pres-trump-is-not-partial-to-who-he-tariffs-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:59:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-23-may-pres-trump-is-not-partial-to-who-he-tariffs-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-appears-to-approve-the-nippon-takeover-of-us-steel-with-a-healthy-dose-of-spin-20250523/&quot;&gt;Trump appears to approve the Nippon takeover of US Steel -- with a healthy dose of spin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-settles-up-033-at-6153-20250523/&quot;&gt;Crude oil settles up $0.33 at $61.53&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-not-looking-for-a-deal-its-set-at-50-20250523/&quot;&gt;Trump: I&apos;m not looking for a deal with EU, it&apos;s set at 50%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/baker-hughes-oil-rig-count-8-to-465-20250523/&quot;&gt;Baker Hughes oil rig count -8  to 465&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-bessent-sovereign-wealth-fund-is-on-pause-20250523/&quot;&gt;More Bessent: Sovereign Wealth Fund is on pause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-cook-seeing-some-signs-of-stress-among-low-moderate-income-households-20250523/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Cook: Seeing some signs of stress among low-moderate income households&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-ultimately-sees-several-hundred-billion-per-year-in-tariff-revenue-20250523/&quot;&gt;Bessent ultimately sees &apos;several hundred billion&apos; per year in tariff revenue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-gdp-is-close-to-potential-20250523/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Musalem: GDP is close to potential&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bank-of-canada-rate-cut-odds-fall-further-after-retail-sales-data-20250523/&quot;&gt;Bank of Canada rate cut odds fall further after retail sales data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-new-home-sales-743k-vs-693k-expected-20250523/&quot;&gt;US April new home sales 743K vs 693K expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-do-not-want-short-term-inflation-expectations-to-bleed-into-longer-term-20250523/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Musalem: Do not want short-term inflation expectations to bleed into longer term&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-trump-move-is-in-response-to-eus-pace-on-tariffs-20250523/&quot;&gt;Bessent: Trump move is in response to EU&apos;s pace on tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/when-do-you-buy-the-tariff-dip-in-us-stocks-when-trump-tells-you-20250523/&quot;&gt;When do you buy the tariff dip in US stocks? When Trump tells you&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goosbee-businesses-want-some-consistency-20250523/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Goosbee: Businesses want some consistency in policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-retail-sales-08-vs-07-expected-20250523/&quot;&gt;Canada March retail sales +0.8% vs +0.7% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/welcome-to-trade-war-20-20250523/&quot;&gt;Welcome to Trade War 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-recommends-a-50-tariff-on-eu-starting-on-june-1-20250523/&quot;&gt;Trump recommends a 50% tariff on EU starting on June 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-hot-uk-retail-sales-weak-usd-trump-threatens-apple-20250523/&quot;&gt;Forexlive European FX news wrap: Hot UK retail sales, weak USD, Trump threatens Apple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-threatens-tariffs-on-apple-if-products-not-made-in-us-20250523/&quot;&gt;Trump threatens tariffs on Apple if products not made in US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-lane-confident-services-inflation-will-come-down-20250523/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Lane: Confident services inflation will come down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;149&quot; data-end=&quot;552&quot;&gt;The trading day began on a sour note—or a strong one, depending on your stance on tariffs—after former President Trump announced via social media that he would impose a 25% tariff on Apple products not manufactured in the U.S. The market responded swiftly: Apple shares declined for a seventh straight session, falling from a peak of $213.94 on May 14 to $195.27 today, a drop of -8.73%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;554&quot; data-end=&quot;913&quot;&gt;Trump didn’t stop there. In a follow-up post, he proposed a flat 50% tariff on the European Union, set to begin June 1. Later in the day, he reaffirmed his position, stating, “I’m not looking for a deal with the EU. It’s set at 50%.” The message is clear—Trump remains steadfast on tariffs, whether targeting foreign nations or U.S.-based companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;915&quot; data-end=&quot;1186&quot;&gt;If the EU retaliates, additional escalation could be on the horizon. This mirrors the pattern seen with China, where tariffs peaked at 145% before being temporarily reduced to 30% as of May 12, under a 90-day negotiation window. That clock is now ticking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1188&quot; data-end=&quot;1335&quot;&gt;Markets opened lower on the news. Although equities recovered somewhat intraday, they faded back toward the middle of the day’s range by the close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1342&quot; data-end=&quot;1383&quot;&gt;📉 Closing Numbers – May 23, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1384&quot; data-end=&quot;1545&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1384&quot; data-end=&quot;1436&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1386&quot; data-end=&quot;1436&quot;&gt;Dow Jones: -256.02 pts (-0.61%) at 41,603.07&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1437&quot; data-end=&quot;1485&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1439&quot; data-end=&quot;1485&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500: -39.29 pts (-0.67%) at 5,802.82&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1486&quot; data-end=&quot;1545&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1488&quot; data-end=&quot;1545&quot;&gt;Nasdaq Composite: -188.53 pts (-1.00%) at 18,737.21&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1547&quot; data-end=&quot;1576&quot;&gt;📉 Weekly Performance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1577&quot; data-end=&quot;1641&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1577&quot; data-end=&quot;1596&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1579&quot; data-end=&quot;1596&quot;&gt;Dow: -2.47%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1597&quot; data-end=&quot;1620&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1599&quot; data-end=&quot;1620&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500: -2.61%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1621&quot; data-end=&quot;1641&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1623&quot; data-end=&quot;1641&quot;&gt;Nasdaq: -2.47%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;US yield started the day lower and although ending the day lower, the US session saw some debt selling (yields moved higher). The final values near the end of week sees:&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 year yield 3.993%, -0.6 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.077%, -2.5 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year yield 4.509%, -4.4 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year yield 5.031%, -3.3 basis points.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the trading week, the yield curve is steep and with a&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield unchanged&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10 year yield is up 6.4 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 30 year yield rose sharply by 12.7 basis points (on it&apos;s way back above 5.0%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That policymakers speaking today gave a cautionary tone:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chicago Fed Pres. Austan Goolsbee, speaking on CNBC, emphasized that businesses are seeking consistency in policy amidst the uncertainty created by rapidly changing tariffs—particularly pointing to the proposed 50% EU tariff as a disruptive and alarming development for supply chains. He noted growing anxiety among firms about inflationary pressures stemming from ongoing tariff announcements and warned that such moves could have stagflationary consequences—the worst-case scenario for a central bank. Goolsbee stressed the importance of waiting for clearer data before acting, acknowledging that the effects of current policies may already be in motion but not yet visible in economic reports. While he still believes the U.S. economy is fundamentally strong, he indicated that his previous forecast for rate cuts by year-end may now be delayed by up to 16 months due to heightened uncertainty.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;St. Louis Fed Pres.Musalem warned that the Fed is closely monitoring signs that short-term inflation expectations could seep into long-term outlooks, a dynamic they are keen to avoid. He noted that businesses are already expecting higher input and output prices and are struggling to manage growing uncertainty. While GDP is currently close to its potential, inflation remains above target. Musalem also emphasized that the current environment is markedly different from the pandemic era, adding that the probability of a near-term Fed rate cut is low—estimated at just one in five.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Finally, Kansas City Federal Reserve Pres. Jeffrey Schmid emphasized that current uncertainty is largely being driven by ongoing tariff discussions. He stated that the Fed will place greater weight on hard data rather than forecasts when making interest rate decisions, cautioning against overreliance on soft data. Schmid also highlighted the need for the Fed to carefully consider its future use of the balance sheet. He acknowledged that markets have already priced in 83 basis points of rate cuts over the coming year.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fed - like businesses - are struggling with the uncertainty from the Trump administration and their policy actions.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar would lower versus all the major currency pairs with the biggest mover being against the NZD /1.44%) and the AUDUSD (-1.31%).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The greenback also fell close to 1% versus the JPY (-1.0%), CHF (-0.93%), and the CAD (-0.93%).  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the trading week, the dollar was weaker vs all the major currencies as well::&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;EUR: -1.81%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;JPY, -2.13%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;GBP, -1.99%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CHF -1.93%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CAD -1.69%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;AUD, -1.47%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NZD, -1.82%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at other markets: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil fell modestly this week by -0.29%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold rose by 4.82% with its largest weekly gain since April 7 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin rose from $106,520 to $108,234&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stock markets lower to end the week as Trump picks a fight with the EU</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stock-markets-lower-to-end-the-week-as-trump-picks-a-fight-with-the-eu-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:32:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stock-markets-lower-to-end-the-week-as-trump-picks-a-fight-with-the-eu-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Closing changes on the day:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 -0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq Comp -1.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DJIA -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russell 2000 -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Toronto TSX Comp +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the week:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 -2.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq -2.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DJIA -2.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;TSX -0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russell -3.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a week that began with a US debt downgrade and ended with a fresh trade war with the EU, a 2.6% decline is a surprisingly good result. US equities opened much lower on Friday but steadily recovered until some last-minute selling.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sefcovic: EU stands ready to defend its interests</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sefcovic-eu-stands-ready-to-defend-its-interests-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:10:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sefcovic-eu-stands-ready-to-defend-its-interests-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;It doesn&apos;t sound like the US and EU make a quick deal on trade that will drop the 50% tariffs that Trump recommended today and to go into effect on June 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The US is fully engaged and committed to securing a deal that works for both &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;EU commission remains ready to work in good faith&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;EU-US trade is unmatched and must be guided by mutual respect&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s tough to tell which way this is going to go but at least Sefcovic didn&apos;t go full-China style and announce immediate retaliatory tariffs -- though there&apos;s an argument that&apos;s the optimal strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump appears to approve the Nippon takeover of US Steel -- with a healthy dose of spin</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-appears-to-approve-the-nippon-takeover-of-us-steel-with-a-healthy-dose-of-spin-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 19:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-appears-to-approve-the-nippon-takeover-of-us-steel-with-a-healthy-dose-of-spin-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;US President Trump appears to have green-lighted the Nippon Steel takeover of US Steel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s a deal that he opposed on the campaign trail and was killed by President Biden after the election. However Nippon and US Steel sued to keep the deal alive and more-recently sweetened the pot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rejection of the deal was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/rejecting-the-us-steel-sale-to-nippon-steel-will-mark-the-end-of-an-era-in-us-capitalism-20241230/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;a low point for American capitalism &lt;/a&gt;and went against the idea that foreign companies should invest in the United States if they wanted to avoid tariffs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump wrote on Truth Social that was a &apos;planned partnership&apos; and that sparked some confusion but it looks like this is just spin as the $14 billion investment is exactly what Nippon &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/nippon-steel-invest-14-billion-us-steel-including-4-billion-new-mill-document-2025-05-19/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;dangled &lt;/a&gt;to close the deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares jumped 23% and are close to the deal price of $55/share. If approved the deal could close as soon as this weekend as both Nippon and US Steel have been ready to close for months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump wrote:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;I am proud to announce that, after much consideration and negotiation, 
US Steel will REMAIN in America, and keep its Headquarters in the Great 
City of Pittsburgh. For many years, the name, “United States Steel” was 
synonymous with Greatness, and now, it will be again. This will be a 
planned partnership between United States Steel and Nippon Steel, which 
will create at least 70,000 jobs, and add $14 Billion Dollars to the 
U.S. Economy. The bulk of that Investment will occur in the next 14 
months. This is the largest Investment in the History of the 
Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. My Tariff Policies will ensure that Steel 
will once again be, forever, MADE IN AMERICA. From Pennsylvania to 
Arkansas, and from Minnesota to Indiana, AMERICAN MADE is BACK. I will 
see you all at US Steel, in Pittsburgh, on Friday, May 30th, for a BIG 
Rally. CONGRATULATIONS TO ALL!&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite how this whole sad saga unfolded, it ultimately ends up in the good place for the US as Nippon will modernize a portion of the US steel industry and force it into a more-competitive place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The loser in this is Cleveland-Cliffs who lobbied hard to keep out foreign competition and investment. Shares of CLF are down 5.5%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil settles up $0.33 at $61.53</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-settles-up-033-at-6153-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 19:23:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-settles-up-033-at-6153-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Crude oil is settling the day up $0.33 on the day at $61.53. The high today reached $61.84. The low was at $60.06.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the trading week, the price is closing down marginally by about - $0.34 or -0.54%. The high for the week was at $64.14. The low was at $60.06.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decline this week was the first in 3 weeks as expectations of another OPEC+ production increase and concerns and uncertainty about growth given the tariffs environment weighs on price as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, the price action this week was above and below the 100/200 hour MA (blue and green lines). Those MAs come in near $61.66 (converged).  The price is closing below those MAs tilting the bias more to the downside at the end of the week. However, the MAs will be the barometer for buyers and sellers next week. Trade above is more bullish. Trade below is more bearish. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BofA: Yen faces summer weakness; we target USD/JPY at 155 by year-end</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-yen-faces-summer-weakness-we-target-usdjpy-at-155-by-year-end-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 19:22:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-yen-faces-summer-weakness-we-target-usdjpy-at-155-by-year-end-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;77&quot; data-end=&quot;369&quot;&gt;Bank of America maintains a bullish USD/JPY outlook, projecting the pair to rise to 155 by end-2025, citing a mix of domestic political, fiscal, and trade-related risks in Japan. They expect JPY and JGBs to weaken over the summer as structural pressures mount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;371&quot; data-end=&quot;386&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;388&quot; data-end=&quot;1297&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;388&quot; data-end=&quot;604&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;390&quot; data-end=&quot;604&quot;&gt;Japan-US Trade Talks Stalled:Lack of progress in bilateral trade negotiations reduces the appeal of Japanese assets, potentially delaying BoJ hikes and creating a twist-steepening in the JGB curve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;606&quot; data-end=&quot;875&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;608&quot; data-end=&quot;875&quot;&gt;Fiscal Concerns Grow:Calls for tax cuts from opposition parties and even some ruling coalition members threaten fiscal discipline. With PM Ishiba’s approval ratings under pressure, fiscal expansion may become unavoidable—bearish JPY and JGBs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;877&quot; data-end=&quot;1078&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;879&quot; data-end=&quot;1078&quot;&gt;Political Instability Risk:Upcoming Upper House elections could lead to leadership changes or a coalition shift, adding policy uncertainty and weakening investor confidence in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1080&quot; data-end=&quot;1297&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1082&quot; data-end=&quot;1297&quot;&gt;BoJ Policy Outlook:BofA continues to expect no additional BoJ rate hike until April 2026, leaving Japan at the mercy of structural capital outflows and a widening policy divergence with the Fed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1299&quot; data-end=&quot;1657&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1299&quot; data-end=&quot;1657&quot;&gt;BofA sees JPY vulnerability building into the summer, driven by political risk, stalled reforms, and widening fiscal concerns. Their base case remains USD/JPY at 155 by year-end, assuming a Fed on hold and no near-term BoJ hikes. Investors should prepare for continued JPY and JGB weakness amid these domestic pressures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1299&quot; data-end=&quot;1657&quot;&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1748114531705000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2hjHHLuIL-4PB-HPKdIiiP&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1748114531705000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2hjHHLuIL-4PB-HPKdIiiP&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: I DON&apos;T WANT THE CONSUMER TO PAY THE TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925981685629190237#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:26:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925981685629190237#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: I DON&apos;T WANT THE CONSUMER TO PAY THE TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: I&apos;m not looking for a deal with EU, it&apos;s set at 50%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-not-looking-for-a-deal-its-set-at-50-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:21:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-not-looking-for-a-deal-its-set-at-50-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Could talk about delays to EU tariffs if they start moving to the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Talks with EU are slow moving&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m not looking for a deal, it&apos;s set at 50%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Numerous other deals ready to be signed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Would also tariff Samsung and others who make iPhones&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cook said he would go to India but there would still be tariffs that way&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This has slowed the rebound in stocks. Obviously, he is looking for a deal with the EU but this is how he talks. Then again, who knows with Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WE NEED TREMENDOUS ELECTRICITY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925979480880767303#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:17:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925979480880767303#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WE NEED TREMENDOUS ELECTRICITY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP SIGNS FIRST OF NUCLEAR ENERGY ORDERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925979417127292940#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:17:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925979417127292940#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP SIGNS FIRST OF NUCLEAR ENERGY ORDERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credit Agricole: The return of USD &apos;frown&apos;; is a &apos;Truss Moment&apos; inevitable?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/credit-agricole-the-return-of-usd-frown-is-a-truss-moment-inevitable-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 18:01:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/credit-agricole-the-return-of-usd-frown-is-a-truss-moment-inevitable-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;92&quot; data-end=&quot;419&quot;&gt;Credit Agricole sees the return of the &quot;USD frown&quot;—the relationship between USD and US equity/FI performance—driving near-term USD weakness. But they dismiss fears of a full-blown crisis akin to the UK’s &quot;Truss moment,&quot; citing continued global demand for Treasuries and the USD’s reserve status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;421&quot; data-end=&quot;436&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;438&quot; data-end=&quot;1403&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;438&quot; data-end=&quot;656&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;440&quot; data-end=&quot;656&quot;&gt;USD Selling on Risk Aversion:Investors are selling USD as US equities weaken and Treasury yields rise, fearing capital outflows and fragility in US fixed income following Moody’s sovereign downgrade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;658&quot; data-end=&quot;893&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;660&quot; data-end=&quot;893&quot;&gt;Political and Policy Concerns:Stalled fiscal stimulus talks in Congress and Fed commentary on stagflation risks have amplified worries over the macro backdrop and reinforced the USD’s vulnerability to risk sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;895&quot; data-end=&quot;1157&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;897&quot; data-end=&quot;1157&quot;&gt;But No &apos;Truss Moment&apos;:Credit Agricole does not expect a disorderly selloff in US debt akin to the UK gilt crisis under PM Liz Truss. They argue long-end yields may stabilize, especially given the USD and USTs remain global reserve anchors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1159&quot; data-end=&quot;1403&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1161&quot; data-end=&quot;1403&quot;&gt;Structural USD Support Intact:Despite near-term volatility, global demand for USD assets remains resilient, which should cap USD downside, especially against currencies from economies with weaker fundamentals or lower yields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1405&quot; data-end=&quot;1737&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1405&quot; data-end=&quot;1737&quot;&gt;While the USD is under pressure from equity and bond market jitters, Credit Agricole sees this as a tactical adjustment rather than a structural shift. The market is not pricing in a systemic credibility shock like the UK faced in 2022, and the USD’s reserve status should limit sustained underperformance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1405&quot; data-end=&quot;1737&quot;&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1748109668311000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2_aSS5hMjY-wZdPWjIf093&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1748109668311000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2_aSS5hMjY-wZdPWjIf093&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD breaks to new highs for the week/new highs going back to May 14</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-breaks-to-new-highs-for-the-weeknew-highs-going-back-to-may-14-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:33:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-breaks-to-new-highs-for-the-weeknew-highs-going-back-to-may-14-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;140&quot; data-end=&quot;422&quot;&gt;The AUDUSD is pushing higher today, extending above Wednesday’s high of 0.6469 and reaching a session peak of 0.6494. The pair is up 1.26% on the day, with an 87-pip trading range, well above the 22-day average of 72 pips—highlighting strong momentum in favor of buyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;424&quot; data-end=&quot;718&quot;&gt;Technically, the rally began in the early Asian session as the pair found support at an upward-sloping trendline. That bounce encouraged buyers, and the bullish tone strengthened once price broke above the converged 100- and 200-hour moving averages (blue and green lines on the chart near 0.6434).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;720&quot; data-end=&quot;968&quot;&gt;A brief dip in the early U.S. session followed Trump-related headlines that sent equities lower, but importantly, the pullback stalled right at those same hourly MAs (again near 0.6434), reaffirming them as support and setting the stage for another upward leg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;970&quot; data-end=&quot;1002&quot;&gt;The latest move has seen AUDUSD:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1003&quot; data-end=&quot;1214&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1003&quot; data-end=&quot;1058&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1005&quot; data-end=&quot;1058&quot;&gt;Break above the 200-day moving average at 0.64526&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1059&quot; data-end=&quot;1127&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1061&quot; data-end=&quot;1127&quot;&gt;Push through a downward-sloping topside trendline near 0.64827&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1128&quot; data-end=&quot;1214&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1130&quot; data-end=&quot;1214&quot;&gt;Test resistance near recent swing highs (May 5 and May 14) around 0.6494–0.65005&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1216&quot; data-end=&quot;1261&quot;&gt;A break above those swing highs would target:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1262&quot; data-end=&quot;1406&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1262&quot; data-end=&quot;1324&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1264&quot; data-end=&quot;1324&quot;&gt;2025 high at 0.65135, the highest level since December 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1325&quot; data-end=&quot;1406&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1327&quot; data-end=&quot;1406&quot;&gt;61.8% retracement of the 2024 high–low move at 0.65489 (on the daily chart)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1408&quot; data-end=&quot;1624&quot;&gt;Conclusion:
Buyers remain firmly in control. Holding above the 100/200-hour MAs and 200-day MA keeps the bullish momentum intact. A break of 0.6500/0.6514 opens the door to broader upside targets toward 0.6549.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Hughes oil rig count -8  to 465</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/baker-hughes-oil-rig-count-8-to-465-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:07:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/baker-hughes-oil-rig-count-8-to-465-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul data-start=&quot;52&quot; data-end=&quot;167&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oil rig count: -8 to 465 (4th straight weekly decline)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Natural gas:-2 to 98&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Total rigs -10 to 566&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;169&quot; data-end=&quot;190&quot;&gt;Drill. Drill. Drill has not exactly been happening. Yet oil prices are still down on the year with the price down -14.51% or -$10.42 from the closing level at the end of 2024 ($71.81).  The current price is at $61.39. OPEC+ increased production and the expectations of slower growth is weighing on the price. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD bounces back higher</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-bounces-back-higher-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:38:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-bounces-back-higher-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The EURUSD moved lower on the back of the post from Pres.Trump at the start of the US session that he was proposing a 50% tariff on EU imports.  Later the administration started to walk that idea back as it &quot;just a suggestion&quot; (i.e. part of the art of the deal).  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, the price moved down to test the rising 100-hour MA on the headlines,  and got within 5-6 pips of the MA level. Buyers leaned and the dip as risk could be defined and limited against the level  The backtracking led to more buying as London/European traders exited for the week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The price has now moved back toward the highs from Wednesday at 1.1362.  Above that is a 61% retracement of the move down from the April high. That little comes in a 1.1378. The high prices from May 6 and May 7 also stalled near that retracement level increasing its importance (see green numbered circles).&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Bessent: Sovereign Wealth Fund is on pause</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-bessent-sovereign-wealth-fund-is-on-pause-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:11:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-bessent-sovereign-wealth-fund-is-on-pause-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;More from Treasury Secretary Bessent:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US Sovereign Wealth Fund is on pause.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I may be wrong but the idea stemmed from the receipts from the External Revenue Service and perhaps from the savings from DOGE.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN reality, if tariffs are too high, they won&apos;t provide any revenue as they become embargos instead.  Moreover, if the shakedown is to manufacture ALL goods in the US, that does not help tariff collections dreamed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOGE fell well short of savings expected. There will be no windfall there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drill baby drill?  Baker Hughes rig counts continue to move lower as the cost is too high and oil companies are shiifting to returning capital. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I guess there may be deals with China down the road.on commodities from farmers, but those types of promises are often broken. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trump has also touted a Strategic Bitcoin Reserve Fund. He met with the largest holders of his personal digital coin. We will probably hearing more above this type of fund as it becomes the idea du jour.  &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Cook: Seeing some signs of stress among low-moderate income households</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-cook-seeing-some-signs-of-stress-among-low-moderate-income-households-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-cook-seeing-some-signs-of-stress-among-low-moderate-income-households-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fed&apos;s Cook is out saying: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Seeing some signs of stress among low – moderate income households&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sufficiently large income shock could push up defaults, lead to losses for lenders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Treasury market function orderly during April volatility.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Watching commercial real estate market closely.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comments are not anything new&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COOK: SUFFICIENTLY LARGE INCOME SHOCK COULD PUSH UP DEFAULTS, LEAD TO LOSSES FOR LENDERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925944960827682830#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925944960827682830#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COOK: SUFFICIENTLY LARGE INCOME SHOCK COULD PUSH UP DEFAULTS, LEAD TO LOSSES FOR LENDERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent ultimately sees &apos;several hundred billion&apos; per year in tariff revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-ultimately-sees-several-hundred-billion-per-year-in-tariff-revenue-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:36:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-ultimately-sees-several-hundred-billion-per-year-in-tariff-revenue-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expect we will be negotiating with China in person again&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is a Laffer Curve for tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A lot of these non-tariff barriers are coming down&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don&apos;t know where &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sees &apos;several hundred billion&apos; per year in tariff revenue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;my sense is that int he next several weeks we will have several large deals announced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeats that the EU has a collective-action problem&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The German finance minister was very responsive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I think Merz will provide an opportunity for a US-German reset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All yields are up since the start of the year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The market could also be thinking the Congressional yield could create growth&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says he&apos;s not concerned about USD weakening alongside higher yields&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other currencies are strengthening, rather than USD weakening&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t see much to get excited about here. If anything, the comments about a US-Germany reset are positive.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD/CAD flirts with the lowest since October</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-flirts-with-the-lowest-since-october-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:34:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-flirts-with-the-lowest-since-october-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;I have a close eye on USD/CAD today  as the pair steadily slides as part of the broader US dollar selloff. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The loonie is so far underperforming the AUD and NZD today in percentage terms but it&apos;s also brushing up against an important level. Moreover, the market may be hesitant to push though with US and UK holidays coming on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key item on the agenda for the loonie in the week ahead is Thursday&apos;s Canadian GDP report. RBC expects it will show the Canadian economy grew by 1.8% annualized
in Q1. The caveat is that the quarter was front-loaded with strength in January that gradually faded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;We expect to see an increase in household consumption
in Q1 that was partially offset by a contraction in residential investment as
home resales cooled. Business investment likely inched higher, but is expected
to soften in the coming quarters as businesses freeze spending plans amid
disruptive trade policies,&quot; RBC writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My major worry about Canada relates to housing, which continues to crack. Listings are mounting quickly in the Toronto area and with 5-year rates rising, there is little hope for relief any time soon. The Bank of Canada is now less-likely to cut rates in June and the rising loonie will help to cool inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NZDUSD is extending to new session highs and highs for the week.What next technically?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-nzdusd-is-extending-to-new-session-highs-and-highs-for-the-weekwhat-next-technically-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:59:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-nzdusd-is-extending-to-new-session-highs-and-highs-for-the-weekwhat-next-technically-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The NZDUSD is stretching to new highs for the day and also new highs for the week (highest level since May 8). That move has taken the price above the 0.59664 from Wednesday, which also was near the high price going back to last week on May 14. Getting above that level is a bullish play and opens the door for further upside momentum for the NZDUSD..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With increased momentum, we could see the price ultimately reach the high prices from both April and May. Those levels came between 0.6018 and 0.6028 over time (see red numbered circles on the chart below). Getting above those levels would take the pair to the highest level since November 2024.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The moves to the upside, come after sellers had their shot over the last 8 or so days on breaks of the 200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart.  However, each time the price tried to extend below the 200 bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, sellers turned back to buyers fairly quickly (see green numbered circles outlining the tests of that 200 bar moving average).  That ultimately was the dominant play technically, that has moved the price higher this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video above, outlines the key levels in play and explains why.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Musalem: GDP is close to potential</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-gdp-is-close-to-potential-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:52:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-gdp-is-close-to-potential-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Musalem:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inflation is stills above target&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Today&apos;s world is very different from the pandemic, one in five chance at most that Fed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schmid:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will lean very much on hard data in making interest rates decisions, allows for less focus on forecasts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed needs to be careful how much emphasis it puts on soft data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Fed needs to think hard in future years about when and how it wants to use the balance sheet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market has priced in 83 bps in easing in the year ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech sector struggles, financial and healthcare remain resilient</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-struggles-financial-and-healthcare-remain-resilient-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:46:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-struggles-financial-and-healthcare-remain-resilient-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Today’s stock market reveals a challenging environment for technology stocks, with mixed outcomes across financial and healthcare sectors. Investors witness a dynamic trading landscape, highlighting the need for keen strategy and portfolio management. 🏛️&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;📉 Tech Sector: Widespread Declines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The technology sector is leading today’s downturn, with Microsoft (MSFT) experiencing a drop of 0.73% and Oracle (ORCL) down by 0.98%. Nvidia (NVDA), a major player in semiconductors, fell by 1.63%, continuing a challenging trend for chip manufacturers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This sector-wide decline highlights current investor hesitation amid industry-specific pressures.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;📈 Financial and Healthcare Sectors: Mixed Reactions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The financial sector shows resilience, despite a slight pullback in Visa (V) by 1.18% and JPMorgan Chase (JPM) by 0.66%. Interestingly, Intercontinental Exchange (ICE) shows strength with a 0.99% gain, indicating potential confidence in select financial services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The healthcare sector reflects steady performance with Johnson &amp; Johnson (JNJ) up by 0.14%, signaling modest investor interest in defensive stocks during market volatility.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 Consumer &amp; Communications: Mixed Signals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Amazon (AMZN) dropped by 0.94%, while Meta (META) fell 1.25%, contrasting with a better-than-expected performance in consumer cyclical sectors, indicating a cautious consumer sentiment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Google (GOOGL) and Netflix (NFLX) also experienced declines, hinting at investor wariness regarding future growth amid economic uncertainties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;📚 Market Mood and Strategies Forward&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overall, the market sentiment appears cautious, driven by adverse news in technology and muted recovery signals in other sectors.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Investors are advised to maintain a diversified portfolio to mitigate risks associated with specific sector declines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consider keeping an eye on the financial sector&apos;s potential for stability and exploring opportunities within healthcare stocks as safe havens in turbulent times.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay informed and adjust your strategies as needed by visiting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt; for comprehensive market analysis and news.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Canada rate cut odds fall further after retail sales data</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bank-of-canada-rate-cut-odds-fall-further-after-retail-sales-data-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bank-of-canada-rate-cut-odds-fall-further-after-retail-sales-data-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;USD/CAD is flirting with a break of the lows of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar is sliding broadly today but the Canadian dollar is getting an extra lift from March and April retail sales data. The numbers were solid and come on the heels of a hotter CPI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combined, that has the odds of a June 4 rate cut down to 28% from 65% before CPI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economists at CIBC were one group calling for cuts and now sound like they&apos;re just waiting for next week&apos;s GDP report to flip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Our forecast for a contraction in GDP in April and Q2 as a whole is driven more by expected
weakness in manufacturing and other sectors more directly impacted by US trade. Advance figures for those areas are
due to be released early next week, but if they also aren&apos;t as weak as anticipated then we will have to revise our forecast
for monthly GDP and likely our Bank of Canada rate cut call as well.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the report itself, they note that consumer spending has been holding up better than anticipated. The caveat is that auto sales were a big driver of stronger retail sales and that could have been a tariff front-run trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch for stops below the May low of 1.3748.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD technical analysis: Sellers stay in control as price targets key support</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-technical-analysis-sellers-stay-in-control-as-price-targets-key-support-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:12:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-technical-analysis-sellers-stay-in-control-as-price-targets-key-support-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;85&quot; data-end=&quot;383&quot;&gt;The USDCAD remains under selling pressure after failing to sustain gains above key resistance near 1.4009–1.4026 and the 200-day MA last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;85&quot; data-end=&quot;383&quot;&gt;This week, the price on Wednesday fell below a swing area between 1.38917 to 1.3904.  The break and hold below this zone gave sellers the green light to drive the pair even lower and they did on Wednesday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;85&quot; data-end=&quot;383&quot;&gt;Yesterday, the price corrected back toward the swing area again, with the high price reaching 1.3888 just short of the low of the swing area at 1.38917.  Sellers still in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;85&quot; data-end=&quot;383&quot;&gt;Today, the momentum lower continued with the pair now looking to test the lows of 2025 (and lowest levels since October 2024).  That level comes between 1.37497 to 1.37698 (see red numbered circles).  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;698&quot; data-end=&quot;829&quot;&gt;Do the buyers stall the fall at the lows for 2025?  Traders looking to buy a dip can lean with a stop below.  However, be aware that the 61.8% of the move up from the 2023 low comes in at 1.37415 - just below the low from 2025. So it might be wise for dip buyers to wait on a break of that retracement level.   &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April new home sales 743K vs 693K expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-new-home-sales-743k-vs-693k-expected-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-new-home-sales-743k-vs-693k-expected-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 724K (revised to 670K)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sales monthly change 10.9% vs +7.4% prior (revised to +2.6%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rising long-term yields and borrowing costs aren&apos;t helping the housing market. Shares of home builders have struggled badly this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a surprising number but it looks like some sales have simply been shifted by a month as the March number was revised far lower.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Musalem: Do not want short-term inflation expectations to bleed into longer term</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-do-not-want-short-term-inflation-expectations-to-bleed-into-longer-term-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:57:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-do-not-want-short-term-inflation-expectations-to-bleed-into-longer-term-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Musalem:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Businesses expect higher prices for inputs and outputs, Fed is watching that carefully&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business executives are trying to figure out how to manager uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schmid:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty is being driven by the tariff conversation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;ve heard similar comments from the Fed over and over. Nothing is changing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes now on today&apos;s previously-scheduled call between US and EU officials</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eyes-now-on-todays-previously-scheduled-call-between-us-and-eu-officials-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:47:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eyes-now-on-todays-previously-scheduled-call-between-us-and-eu-officials-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t think there is any secret on what&apos;s happening between the US and EU at the moment; Bessent spelled it out. He said the EU has been moving too slowly on trade and Trump wants to &apos;light a fire&apos; under the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The message was strategically timed ahead of a call today that was scheduled previously. At 12:30 pm ET, there is a call scheduled between EU trade boss Sefcovic and USA counterpart Greer will take place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market will be waiting for a read-out (or leak) from that call afterwards. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Update: One report says this call is at 11 am ET, so watch out for headlines earlier.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF technicals are doing their job. What does that mean? Watch this video and find out.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-technicals-are-doing-their-job-what-does-that-mean-watch-this-video-and-find-out-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:25:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-technicals-are-doing-their-job-what-does-that-mean-watch-this-video-and-find-out-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;75&quot; data-end=&quot;348&quot;&gt;The USDCHF continues to trade with a bearish tilt after a series of failed upside attempts near key technical levels. The 100-hour moving average (currently near 0.8284) served as strong resistance earlier this week, capping rallies yesterday most recently, and helping to turn buyers into sellers into the day close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;350&quot; data-end=&quot;682&quot;&gt;The recent decline seen today, initially found buyers near the 50% midpoint of the April-to-May range at 0.8257. However, EU tariff news triggered a decisive break below this level, adding downside momentum. The pair did not find support until reaching the next key swing area between 0.8193 and 0.8212—highlighted by past price reaction zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;886&quot;&gt;With price now below both the 100- and 200-hour moving averages and under key Fibonacci retracement levels, the bears remain in control unless buyers can push the pair back above 0.8257 (50%) and then 0.8284 (100 hour MA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;886&quot;&gt;Overall, howver, the technicals are doing their job. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;888&quot; data-end=&quot;913&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;914&quot; data-end=&quot;1129&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;914&quot; data-end=&quot;996&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;916&quot; data-end=&quot;996&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.8257 (50% retracement), 0.8284 (100-hour MA), 0.8300 (200-hour MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;997&quot; data-end=&quot;1050&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;999&quot; data-end=&quot;1050&quot;&gt;Support: 0.8212/0.8193 (swing area), 0.8163, 0.8139&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1051&quot; data-end=&quot;1129&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1053&quot; data-end=&quot;1129&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 0.8284, with further downside potential if 0.8193 breaks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: Trump move is in response to EU&apos;s pace on tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-trump-move-is-in-response-to-eus-pace-on-tariffs-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:25:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-trump-move-is-in-response-to-eus-pace-on-tariffs-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;If you missed it, Trump &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-recommends-a-50-tariff-on-eu-starting-on-june-1-20250523/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;earlier &lt;/a&gt;&apos;recommended&apos; a 50% tariff on the EU starting June 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump believes EU proposals have not been of good quality&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Would like to have Apple help US to make semiconductor supply chain better&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump trying to bring back precision manufacturing to the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says US is &apos;far along&apos; with India and Asian countries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most countries negotiating in good faith except EU&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These deals are moving quickly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will see more deals announced in 90-day period&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Separate comments are coming from the German foreign minister:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We support Commission to defend the European market&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both markets would suffer, that&apos;s why we want further negotiations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In hindsight, we should have been bracing for something. Trump took a break from the trade war to go to the Middle East and wouldn&apos;t have wanted to announce something like this during the G7 on Wed/Thurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, Trump will attend the G7 in Canada from June 15-17, so if he follows the pattern of lowering tensions during international visits, that leaves a three-week window.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
