<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Media reports that Iran is ready to sign an agreement for relief from sanctions</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/media-reports-that-iran-is-ready-to-sign-an-agreement-for-relief-from-sanctions-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:42:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/media-reports-that-iran-is-ready-to-sign-an-agreement-for-relief-from-sanctions-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;NBC citing an unnamed official&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More from Fed&apos;s Daly - can&apos;t give forward guidance now due to uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/more-from-feds-daly-cant-give-forward-guidance-now-due-to-uncertainty-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:32:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/more-from-feds-daly-cant-give-forward-guidance-now-due-to-uncertainty-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco President Mary Daly &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Any guidance on policy would be speculative and wrong, given uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-daly-business-is-cautious-amidst-the-economic-uncertainty-but-not-stalling-out-20250514/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Daly: Business is cautious amidst the economic uncertainty, but not &quot;stalling out&quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;--- &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t even know where to start with that comment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OK ... here goes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am not expressing an opinion on what I think the Federal Reserve should do right now. Cut or not cut. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More generally, given the level of uncertainty Daly is expressing here, what should a central bank do? here goes ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. There is always uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Right now its much higher than usual. Much higher, although since the tariff ceasefire between the US and China is dialled back a little. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. If it&apos;s a time of extreme uncertainty, its not just the central bank that&apos;d be feeling uncertain, but main street business and households probably even more so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. If uncertainty is so high as to lead to paralysis in giving forward guidance then I reckon the correct response is a rate cut. Or, if not that, then dovish talk, to ease concerns, at the margin. Ease financial conditions to give main street more room to move. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comments welcome. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point72&apos;s Steve Cohen says the US is not in recession ... yet. Fed will be slow to cut.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/point72s-steve-cohen-says-the-us-is-not-in-recession-yet-fed-will-be-slow-to-cut-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 22:07:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/point72s-steve-cohen-says-the-us-is-not-in-recession-yet-fed-will-be-slow-to-cut-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Point72&apos;s Steve Cohen:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We&apos;re not in a recession yet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I think we&apos;re going to have significant slowing growth&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We think it&apos;ll probably be a 45% chance of recession&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will be slowdown, Fed will be slow to respond&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stocks could retest their April lows&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cohen emphasized the volatility of the economic environment, saying his answers might have been different a week ago. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve Cohen is an American billionaire hedge fund manager and philanthropist, best known as the founder and CEO of Point72 Asset Management, a global multi-strategy investment firm. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He began his career at Gruntal &amp;amp; Co. before launching S.A.C. Capital Advisors in 1992, which became one of the most successful hedge funds of its time. Following a high-profile insider trading case that led to a $1.8 billion settlement and a two-year ban from managing outside capital, Cohen rebranded his firm as Point72 in 2014. The firm reopened to external investors in 2018 and now manages over $35 billion in assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sohn Investment Conference is an annual event held in New York city that brings together leading hedge fund managers and investors to share their market insights and investment ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;established in 1995&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; it raises funds for pediatric cancer research through the Sohn Conference Foundation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Daly: Business is cautious amidst the economic uncertainty, but not &quot;stalling out&quot;</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-daly-business-is-cautious-amidst-the-economic-uncertainty-but-not-stalling-out-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:51:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-daly-business-is-cautious-amidst-the-economic-uncertainty-but-not-stalling-out-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Federal Reserve&apos;s Daly:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monetary policy well-positioned, moderately restrictive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Businesses are cautious amid uncertainty, but not stalling out&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid growth, solid labor market, declining inflation, that’s where we want to be&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed policy can respond to whatever comes in the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Patience is the word of the day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Loan demand solid, credits are good&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco President Mary Daly is speaking in a fireside chat format before the California Bankers Association 25th Annual Conference and Directors Forum&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S DALY: MONETARY POLICY WELL-POSITIONED, MODERATELY RESTRICTIVE

DALY: BUSINESSES ARE CAUTIOUS AMID UNCERTAINTY, BUT NOT STALLING OUT

DALY: SOLID GROWTH, SOLID LABOR MARKET, DECLINING INFLATION

DALY: THAT&apos;S WHERE WE WANT TO BE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922771734987514101#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922771734987514101#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S DALY: MONETARY POLICY WELL-POSITIONED, MODERATELY RESTRICTIVE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
DALY: BUSINESSES ARE CAUTIOUS AMID UNCERTAINTY, BUT NOT STALLING OUT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
DALY: SOLID GROWTH, SOLID LABOR MARKET, DECLINING INFLATION&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
DALY: THAT&apos;S WHERE WE WANT TO BE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citi edge their 0 - 3 month Brent crude forecast slightly higher</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/citi-edge-their-0-3-month-brent-crude-forecast-slightly-higher-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:35:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/citi-edge-their-0-3-month-brent-crude-forecast-slightly-higher-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Citi have bumped up their 0-3 month price view to USD 60/bbl for Brent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;keeps Q2 and Q3 Brent averages at USD 62/bbl and USD 63/bbl respectively&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Info via Reuters headline. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foot Locker shares jump higher -  Dick’s Sporting Goods is close to acquiring</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/foot-locker-shares-jump-higher-dicks-sporting-goods-is-close-to-acquiring-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:32:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/foot-locker-shares-jump-higher-dicks-sporting-goods-is-close-to-acquiring-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Dick’s Sporting Goods is close to acquiring Foot Locker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wall Street Journal has the info:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;deal valued at approximately US$2.3 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;two sides are in discussion over a cash offer of $24 per share for Foot Locker&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;way above the most recent closing price of $12.87&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Since the announcement, Dick’s stock has fallen 7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Foot Locker shares have rocketed, to circa $21&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;One for the equity traders &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Bank says U.S. equities to maintain short-term outperformance amid tariff pause</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/deutsche-bank-says-us-equities-to-maintain-short-term-outperformance-amid-tariff-pause-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 21:17:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/deutsche-bank-says-us-equities-to-maintain-short-term-outperformance-amid-tariff-pause-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;153&quot; data-end=&quot;325&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;U.S. equities are likely to extend their recent outperformance in the near term, buoyed by easing trade tensions between Washington and Beijing, according to Deutsche Bank. From a note on Wednesday:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Looking forward, short-term, we expect the S&amp;amp;P 500’s recent outperformance to persist as US companies are the bigger beneficiary of the tariff cuts” &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;544&quot; data-end=&quot;855&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;However, analysts st DB tempered expectations for a sustained rally:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Although lower than feared for now, in our view, tariffs will still be a bigger burden for US companies than for European companies,” &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;broader underperformance could persist “until a substantial cut in tariffs would bring relief”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 update ... I stuck in a horizontal line I&apos;m eyeing for a period of work to be done:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive Americas FX news wrap 14 May: The USD rebounds from earlier declines. Gold lower</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-14-may-the-usd-rebounds-from-earlier-declines-gold-lower-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:45:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-14-may-the-usd-rebounds-from-earlier-declines-gold-lower-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/at-the-close-tech-leads-as-us-stocks-climb-again-20250514/&quot;&gt;At the close: Tech leads as US stocks climb again&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/david-einhorn-there-is-no-effort-to-reduce-the-deficit-buy-gold-20250514/&quot;&gt;David Einhorn: There is no effort to reduce the deficit, buy gold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6315-20250514/&quot;&gt;Crude oil futures settle at $63.15&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-april-us-retail-sales-likely-to-show-frontloading-boost-20250514/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs: April US retail sales likely to show frontloading boost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/putin-not-interested-in-one-on-one-meeting-with-zelensky-in-istanbul-report-20250514/&quot;&gt;Putin not interested in one-on-one meeting with Zelensky in Istanbul - report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/the-market-has-removed-60-basis-points-of-fed-easing-in-the-year-ahead-20250514/&quot;&gt;The market has removed 60 basis points of Fed easing in the year ahead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-price-breaks-below-200-bar-ma-as-momentum-shifts-lower-20250514/&quot;&gt;Gold Technical Analysis – Price breaks below 200-bar MA on 4H as momentum shifts lower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-markets-sag-late-spain-stocks-hit-16-year-high-20250514/&quot;&gt;European equity markets sag late, Spain stocks hit 16-year high&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/super-micro-computer-smci-bullish-break-above-200-day-ma-key-resistance-targets-ahead-20250514/&quot;&gt;Super Micro Computer (SMCI) – Bullish break above 200 day MA. Key resistance targets ahead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eia-weekly-us-crude-oil-inventories-3454k-vs-1078k-expected-20250514/&quot;&gt;EIA weekly US crude oil inventories +3454K vs -1078K expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-trade-deals-with-japan-and-south-korea-said-to-be-close-report-20250514/&quot;&gt;US trade deals with Japan and South Korea said to be close - report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-jefferson-current-policy-is-a-good-place-to-respond-to-economic-developments-20250514/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Jefferson: Current policy is a good place to respond to economic developments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-cracks-the-may-low-and-sinks-further-20250514/&quot;&gt;Gold cracks the May low and sinks further&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-dollar-struggles-continue-amid-mixed-markets-20250514/&quot;&gt;ForexLive European FX news wrap: Dollar struggles continue amid mixed markets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/germanys-chancellor-merz-were-committed-to-avoiding-protracted-trade-conflict-with-us-20250514/&quot;&gt;Germany&apos;s Chancellor Merz: We&apos;re committed to avoiding protracted trade conflict with US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-mba-mortgage-applications-we-9-may-11-vs-110-prior-20250514/&quot;&gt;US MBA mortgage applications w.e. 9 May +1.1% vs +11.0% prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-a-big-crypto-fan-20250514/&quot;&gt;Trump: I&apos;m a big crypto fan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolsbee-it-will-take-time-for-current-inflation-trends-to-show-up-in-the-data-20250514/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Goolsbee: It will take time for current inflation trends to show up in the data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was little in the way of news today with only the weekly crude oil inventory data (not a real market mover) as the only release in the US. Canada building permits fell -4.1%, erasing most of the 4.5% gain from last month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other than that, there were the aftermath of the deals made yesterday in the Middle East from Pres. Trump (and staff) with the tech/chip sector reaping most of the rewards.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;AMD closed up 4.68% and is up 19.37% since May 6. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NVIDIA rose 4.16%. Shares are up 34% since April 22&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Super Micro Computers (SMCI) surged nearly 15.69% after announcing a multi-year, $20 billion partnership with DataVolt, a Saudi Arabian data center developer.  Shares are up 40.64% since May 9th but is still down some 73% from the 2024 high closing level. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was some Fed commentary today with &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Federal Reserve Governor Philip Jefferson stating that the current &quot;moderately restrictive&quot; policy rate is well-positioned to respond to evolving economic conditions. He emphasized that the Fed is closely monitoring hard data for signs of slowing activity, though recent inflation figures suggest continued progress toward the 2% target. However, he warned that the path forward remains uncertain, particularly due to the potential inflationary impact of new tariffs. While the labor market remains solid, Jefferson noted that Q1 GDP figures likely overstated the slowdown in economic activity. He added that whether tariffs cause lasting inflation will depend on their implementation and how supply chains adjust. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier Fed&apos;s Goolsbee also spoke to the idea of patience saying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;He is emphasizing that some of the April inflation data likely reflects the lagged nature of how price trends appear in official statistics. He noted that the Fed remains in a wait-and-see mode, choosing to hold off on any policy shifts until clearer information emerges. Goolsbee cautioned against drawing conclusions about long-term inflation trends amid the current short-term volatility, stressing the importance of filtering out noise in the data. He reiterated that the Fed’s role is to act as a steady hand, not reacting to daily movements in markets or political headlines. His comments reinforce the Fed’s patient stance as it continues to assess evolving economic conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;113&quot; data-end=&quot;630&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Meanwhile, hedge fund manager David Einhorn, speaking to CNBC from the Sohn Conference, voiced serious concerns about the lack of any meaningful effort to address the U.S. fiscal deficit. He noted that &quot;there isn&apos;t even the beginning of a plan&quot; to confront the issue unless it escalates into a full-blown crisis. He also dismissed recent claims of finding $2 trillion in savings, suggesting the actual figure is closer to $150 billion, with tariffs potentially contributing an additional $100 billion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;632&quot; data-end=&quot;1078&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Einhorn expressed skepticism about the focus on the trade deficit, saying he doesn’t view it as a major problem. On gold, he stated he would be pleased to see it rise to $3,500 or $3,800, but not to $30,000, which he implied would reflect severe economic distress. He criticized the current administration for “building a retreat” and argued that the U.S. is not being perceived as a reliable negotiating partner by other nations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1080&quot; data-end=&quot;1500&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Looking ahead, Einhorn believes that the current market fixation on tariffs will likely fade, and other economic themes will take center stage. He also revealed a tactical position: he’s short leveraged MicroStrategy ETFs while holding a long position in MSTR stock. He explained that these leveraged ETFs are costly to operate, as they cannot use swaps and must instead rely on purchasing expensive options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the forex, the USD is ending mostly higher vs the major currencies with the exception vs the JPY (the USD was lower vs the JPY)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;EUR +0.15%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;JPY -0.45% &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;GBP +0.38%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CHF, +0.39%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CAD +0.30%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;AUD +0.63%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NZD +0.69%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USD did try to move lower into European morning session but reversed higher in the US session today.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;107&quot; data-end=&quot;517&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;EURUSD: The pair tested its 200-hour moving average at 1.1261 during the European morning session but failed to hold above it, rotating lower and breaking below the 100-hour moving average at 1.1183. As the session comes to a close, EURUSD is trading near 1.1169. Holding below the 100-hour MA in the new trading day would keep the bearish bias intact and sellers firmly in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;519&quot; data-end=&quot;1011&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;GBPUSD: GBPUSD climbed to test the lower boundary of a key swing area between 1.3362 and 1.33784, but sellers leaned against the level and pushed the price back down toward the 200-hour moving average at 1.32852. While there was modest buying at that level, the support ultimately gave way. The pair is now testing the 100-hour moving average at 1.32556 into the day’s close. A sustained break below that level would further shift momentum in favor of the sellers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USDJPY: The USDJPY was down over 1% earlier in the day but rebounded in the US session and is closing here in the rising 100 hour moving average at 146.777. That MA will be a short term barometer into the new trading day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NZDUSD: THe NZDUSD traded above its 100 bar moving average on the four hour chart at 0.59449, but could not sustain momentum. The subsequent fall to the price below the 200 hour moving average at 0.59368 and then the 100 hour moving average of 0.59049. The key 200 day moving average at 0.58828 is the next key target going into the new trading day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the closing levels in the US equities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average fell -89.37 points or -0.21% at 42051.06.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index closed higher on the year for the second consecutive day. Today the price rose modest 6.03 points or 0.10% at 5892.58. The index is up 0.19% for the year.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index rose 136.72 points or 0.72% at 19146.81.  For the year, the index is down -0.85%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market, yields are ending the day higher: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 year yield 4.057%, +4.0 basis points.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.170%, +4.9 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10 year yield 4.542%, +4.3 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30 year yield 4.975%, +3.3 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;in other markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil is trading down $0.76 at $62.91&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold is trading down $68 or -2.10% at $3181.30. Gold is down 7.8% from its most recent swing high on May 6 as flight to safety flows ease with hopes for more tariff deals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin is trading down $646 at $103,494.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI:China tightens full-chain control on strategic minerals to bolster national security</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymichina-tightens-full-chain-control-on-strategic-minerals-to-bolster-national-security-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:41:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymichina-tightens-full-chain-control-on-strategic-minerals-to-bolster-national-security-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;91&quot; data-end=&quot;503&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;While the Trump tariff war has entered a tentative ceasefire, China is not stepping back. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;91&quot; data-end=&quot;503&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China has announced a sweeping effort to enforce tighter export controls on strategic minerals, reinforcing national security through what officials describe as “full-chain management.” The Ministry of Commerce confirmed that the crackdown will span every stage of the supply chain—from mining and smelting to processing, transportation, manufacturing, and export—with an emphasis on preventing illegal outflows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;505&quot; data-end=&quot;949&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The move follows a national meeting in Changsha attended by senior officials from ten central government agencies and representatives from seven mineral-rich provinces, including Inner Mongolia and Jiangxi. The meeting highlighted the need for integrated supervision across all links of the supply chain, calling for robust traceability systems, stronger customs inspections, and routine management mechanisms to detect and address risks early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;951&quot; data-end=&quot;1350&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Authorities have pledged strict enforcement, with both central and local governments tasked with stepped-up oversight. Local jurisdictions are being directed to fast-track the registration and monitoring of businesses involved in strategic minerals, while companies are being urged to improve compliance awareness. Violators of the new measures will face severe penalties, according to the Ministry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;951&quot; data-end=&quot;1350&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Strategic minerals such as rare earths, lithium, graphite, and tungsten are critical for producing semiconductors, electric vehicle batteries, military hardware, and clean energy technologies. Tighter Chinese controls are likely to strain global supply chains, raise costs for manufacturers, and intensify competition among countries seeking to secure stable, non-Chinese sources of these vital materials.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic calendar in Asia Thursday, May 15, 2025 - Fed speaker, Australia jobs report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-thursday-may-15-2025-fed-speaker-australia-jobs-report-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-thursday-may-15-2025-fed-speaker-australia-jobs-report-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco President Mary Daly is speaking soon, at 2140 GMT / 1740 US Eastern time:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;participates in a fireside chat before the California Bankers Association 25th Annual Conference and Directors Forum&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later we&apos;ll get the Australian employment report for April. It feels early in the month for this, but the data is due on the third Thursday of each month and its rolled around quickly this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solid, but not spectacular, job growth is expected to continue. The jobless rate is expected to hold steady. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barring a surprise the AUD impact should be very limited. The Reserve Bank of Australia is expected to cut its cash rate by 25bp again next week. The Bank meets on May 19 and 20. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The times in the left-most column are GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The numbers in the right-most column are the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month/quarter as the case may be) result. The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade ideas thread - Thursday, 15 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-thursday-15-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:17:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-thursday-15-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Good morning, afternoon and evening all. Any charts, technical analysis, trade ideas, thoughts, views, ForexLive traders would like to share and discuss with fellow ForexLive traders, please do so:
 &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At the close: Tech leads as US stocks climb again</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/at-the-close-tech-leads-as-us-stocks-climb-again-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:06:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/at-the-close-tech-leads-as-us-stocks-climb-again-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;It was more of a battle today but the bulls came out ahead. Newsflow was quiet today -- one of the quietest days of the year -- and that allowed the momentum trade to continue to tick higher. Big winners were in megacap tech and the usual retail-driven tech stocks while some biotech stocks were hit by selling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq Comp +0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Russell 2000 -0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DJIA -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you can see there some divergence is creeping in but given the magnitude of recent moves, this was small potatoes. Tomorrow we get retail sales numbers and that could get things moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is a glance at some of the winners and losers on the Nasdaq.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Einhorn: There is no effort to reduce the deficit, buy gold</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/david-einhorn-there-is-no-effort-to-reduce-the-deficit-buy-gold-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:48:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/david-einhorn-there-is-no-effort-to-reduce-the-deficit-buy-gold-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Hedge fund manager David Einhorn is on CNBC:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There&apos;s not even the beginning of a plan to do anything about the deficit until it&apos;s a crisis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DOGE talked about $2 trillion in savings, it maybe found $150 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs might raise $100 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I don&apos;t understand why the trade deficit is a problem&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;ll be happy if gold goes to $3500, or $3800 but not if it goes to $30,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The administration is &apos;building a retreat&apos;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I don&apos;t see a great incentive for other countries to really negotiate with the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m pretty sure that in a few months we&apos;ll be talking about other things (than tariffs)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I don&apos;t think the USA is coming across as a reliable partner&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says he&apos;s short leveraged MSTR leveraged ETFs and hedged with a long MSTR. Explains it&apos;s a costly ETF to run because it can&apos;t use swaps and must buy high-priced options instead&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Einhorn pitcked LanXess, a German chemical company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today,
 I’m presenting a company where the management has made excellent 
strategic decisions, but the stock has suffered due to a lot of bad 
luck,” he said. “The
 opportunity today is to realize that the troubles have largely passed 
and that the company is likely to be on a successful path to realizing 
the benefits of its transformation.”&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The frontier: A trading algorithm that writes itself and evolves</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-frontier-a-trading-algorithm-that-writes-itself-and-evolves-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:17:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-frontier-a-trading-algorithm-that-writes-itself-and-evolves-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;For at least the past 25 years, human traders have been anxious about being replaced by machines and yet -- today -- there are more people trading than ever. I&apos;d argue that many of them shouldn&apos;t be trading and note that many of the human tasks in markets have been replaced but the future is hard to predict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a cottage industry around writing and (mostly) selling trading algos. Their success has been mixed at best and it&apos;s mostly been an avenue for grift in the retail space but Jim Simons made ungodly amounts of money quant trading and relatively simplistic methods (though we don&apos;t know the details).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In any case, could this be the next frontier in trading technology?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Google DeepMind today pulled the curtain back on AlphaEvolve,
 an artificial-intelligence agent that can invent brand-new computer 
algorithms — then put them straight to work inside the company’s vast 
computing empire.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;AlphaEvolve pairs Google’s Gemini
 large language models with an evolutionary approach that tests, 
refines, and improves algorithms automatically. The system has already 
been deployed across Google’s data centers, chip designs, and AI 
training systems — boosting efficiency and solving mathematical problems
 that have stumped researchers for decades.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;That description comes from a Venturebeat &lt;a href=&quot;https://venturebeat.com/ai/meet-alphaevolve-the-google-ai-that-writes-its-own-code-and-just-saved-millions-in-computing-costs/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;report &lt;/a&gt;on the DeepMind announcement today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea is that the model combines the creativity of a large language model with algorithms 
that can scrutinize the model’s suggestions to filter and improve 
solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can almost guarantee that there are people pouring money into this idea in markets. Unfortunately, the same technology is going to be put to military use and we&apos;ll be lucky to survive it.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WE WILL DO THINGS FOR QATAR THAT THEY WILL BE HAPPY ABOUT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922730546410471632#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:07:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922730546410471632#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WE WILL DO THINGS FOR QATAR THAT THEY WILL BE HAPPY ABOUT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TRUMP: WHEN BESSENT GOES ON TV, EVERYTHING GOES UP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922729313696145419#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:02:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922729313696145419#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TRUMP: WHEN BESSENT GOES ON TV, EVERYTHING GOES UP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil futures settle at $63.15</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6315-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:47:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6315-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The price of crude oil futures are settling at $63.15. That is up $0.52 or 0.82%. The high-priced today rates $63.64. The low price was at $62.78.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;129&quot; data-end=&quot;529&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The price has generally remained below the 50% retracement level of the trading range from the 2020 low, which stands at $64.71. For the bullish bias to gain traction, a sustained move above this midpoint is essential. On April 23, the price briefly climbed above this level, reaching a high of $64.83, before reversing lower—highlighting the importance of this technical barrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;531&quot; data-end=&quot;900&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Geopolitical developments may influence sentiment, with Ukraine and Russia set to hold talks on Thursday. Former President Trump has indicated he may attend, though it&apos;s unclear if President Putin will be present. Trump also reiterated his willingness to strike a deal with Iran, but only on the condition that Iran abandons its nuclear weapons program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;902&quot; data-end=&quot;1346&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Fundamentally, the market is drawing support from the growing view that recession fears may have been overstated. Meanwhile, the latest U.S. crude oil inventory report showed a surprise build of 3.454 million barrels, compared to expectations for a draw of 1.078 million. Gasoline inventories, however, fell by 1.022 million barrels, larger than the expected 561,000-barrel decline—a sign of continued strong demand.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: April US retail sales likely to show frontloading boost</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-april-us-retail-sales-likely-to-show-frontloading-boost-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-april-us-retail-sales-likely-to-show-frontloading-boost-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;87&quot; data-end=&quot;323&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs expects core retail sales to rise in April as consumers frontloaded purchases ahead of impending tariffs, while headline retail sales are likely to remain flat due to weak auto sales and falling gas prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;325&quot; data-end=&quot;340&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;342&quot; data-end=&quot;729&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;342&quot; data-end=&quot;469&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;344&quot; data-end=&quot;469&quot;&gt;Core retail sales forecast: +0.4% m/m, driven by precautionary spending ahead of expected tariff-related price increases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;471&quot; data-end=&quot;586&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;473&quot; data-end=&quot;586&quot;&gt;Headline retail sales forecast: Unchanged, as lower auto sales and gasoline prices offset strength elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;588&quot; data-end=&quot;729&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;590&quot; data-end=&quot;729&quot;&gt;Tariff impact emerging: Consumer behavior appears responsive to trade policy developments, with early signs of demand shifting forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;731&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;731&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot;&gt;Goldman sees the April retail sales report as an early reflection of tariff-driven consumer behavior, supporting resilient core demand but masking it under flat headline numbers due to sector-specific drags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;731&quot; data-end=&quot;956&quot;&gt;The US retail sales report is due out Thursday at 8:30 am ET.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747333787383000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw1CROAdlfLrUjx1-cj4kpSp&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747333787383000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw1CROAdlfLrUjx1-cj4kpSp&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD bounces off support target and trying to extend above and toward MA targets</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-bounces-off-support-target-and-trying-to-extend-above-and-toward-ma-targets-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:30:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-bounces-off-support-target-and-trying-to-extend-above-and-toward-ma-targets-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;115&quot; data-end=&quot;367&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCAD moved lower in early trading today but found support near a familiar swing area between 1.38917 and 1.3904. Buyers leaned against that zone, which has acted as a floor in recent sessions, and the price responded with a bounce higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;369&quot; data-end=&quot;596&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The recovery has taken the pair back above the 100-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, currently at 1.39656. That’s a constructive technical step for buyers, as it shifts short-term momentum back in their favor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;598&quot; data-end=&quot;871&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;However, the pair still trades comfortably below the 200-day moving average, which comes in at 1.40115. That longer-term trend indicator is located within a key resistance zone between 1.40097 and 1.40208, making it a critical hurdle for any further upside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;873&quot; data-end=&quot;1078&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Above that, the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement of the March 2025 high-to-low move comes in at 1.40525. That level represents a more meaningful target for buyers looking to gain firmer control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1080&quot; data-end=&quot;1404&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In summary, buyers stepped in at key support and have completed the first step by reclaiming the 100-bar MA. But to turn today’s bounce into something more substantial, they’ll need to push through the 200-day MA and break above the 1.40525 retracement level. Until then, upside confidence remains tentative.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin not interested in one-on-one meeting with Zelensky in Istanbul - report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/putin-not-interested-in-one-on-one-meeting-with-zelensky-in-istanbul-report-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:18:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/putin-not-interested-in-one-on-one-meeting-with-zelensky-in-istanbul-report-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Moscow Times reports that Putin has no intention of meeting directly with Zelensky in Istanbul.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This war has gone on for far too long but it&apos;s hard to say if we&apos;re really in the endgame.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SocGen: We don&apos;t recommend USD shorts here; prefer long AUD and short CHF exposures</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/socgen-we-dont-recommend-usd-shorts-here-prefer-long-aud-and-short-chf-exposures-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:50:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/socgen-we-dont-recommend-usd-shorts-here-prefer-long-aud-and-short-chf-exposures-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;77&quot; data-end=&quot;355&quot;&gt;Société Générale refrains from recommending explicit short USD positions for now, citing policy-driven disruption in FX markets. Instead, they favor tactical long AUD and short CHF exposure, anticipating benefits from trade thaw and reduced geopolitical tension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;357&quot; data-end=&quot;372&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;374&quot; data-end=&quot;975&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;374&quot; data-end=&quot;554&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;376&quot; data-end=&quot;554&quot;&gt;USD view neutral for now: Despite President Trump’s desire for a weaker dollar and rising US yields, SocGen expects EUR/USD and USD/JPY to stay range-bound until late summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;556&quot; data-end=&quot;732&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;558&quot; data-end=&quot;732&quot;&gt;Market uncertainty: Disconnected relationships between FX and rate differentials—similar to 2022—suggest traders are reacting more to political signals than fundamentals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;734&quot; data-end=&quot;835&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;736&quot; data-end=&quot;835&quot;&gt;AUD bullish bias: SocGen favors being long AUD amid signs of improving US-China trade dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;837&quot; data-end=&quot;975&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;839&quot; data-end=&quot;975&quot;&gt;CHF bearish bias: Recommends short CHF positioning, expecting a decline in safe-haven demand as geopolitical risk potentially eases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot;&gt;SocGen avoids a direct USD short stance but sees selective opportunities: long AUD as trade tensions ease and short CHF as geopolitical risk subsides. Broader USD weakness is more likely after the summer once clearer policy and data signals emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1243&quot;&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747331392560000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0RYlIf4wI_OcP4iut4d04j&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747331392560000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0RYlIf4wI_OcP4iut4d04j&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The market has removed 60 basis points of Fed easing in the year ahead</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/the-market-has-removed-60-basis-points-of-fed-easing-in-the-year-ahead-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 17:21:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/the-market-has-removed-60-basis-points-of-fed-easing-in-the-year-ahead-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fed pricing has substantially shifted since the peak of angst about growth, tariffs and inflation two weeks ago. At the time, the market was pricing in 131 bps in easing through the April 29, 2026 scheduled FOMC meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, that has dropped to 71 bps as the market cheers the sharp drop in US-China tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even in the past day, the move has continued as a Sept cut has gone from fully priced in (and a tad more) to now at 91%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think for risk assets this is ultimately a good thing as provides for a large Fed put on top of what&apos;s a seeming re-emergence of the Trump put. For the US dollar it&apos;s more complicated as any weakness in the US economy now leaves it vulnerable to a rapid repricing lower in rates.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 📊 MARKETS NOW EXPECT 2 RATE CUTS IN 2025

Kalshi’s latest forecast shows 2 rate cuts priced in for 2025, a sharp reset from the 4–5 cuts expected earlier this year. Sticky inflation, tight labor markets, and cautious Fed guidance are forcing traders to rethink the easing cycle.

Is the market underestimating recession risks — or is the Fed done cutting?
https://kalshi.com/markets/kxratecutcount/number-of-rate-cuts</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922697283037970660#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:55:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922697283037970660#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;📊 MARKETS NOW EXPECT 2 RATE CUTS IN 2025&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Kalshi’s latest forecast shows 2 rate cuts priced in for 2025, a sharp reset from the 4–5 cuts expected earlier this year. Sticky inflation, tight labor markets, and cautious Fed guidance are forcing traders to rethink the easing cycle.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Is the market underestimating recession risks — or is the Fed done cutting?&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://kalshi.com/markets/kxratecutcount/number-of-rate-cuts&quot;&gt;kalshi.com/markets/kxratecut…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:8080/pic/media%2FGq7K-FSWUAARJ5T.png&quot; style=&quot;max-width:250px;&quot; /&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Technical Analysis – Price breaks below 200-bar MA on 4H as momentum shifts lower</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-price-breaks-below-200-bar-ma-as-momentum-shifts-lower-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:44:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-technical-analysis-price-breaks-below-200-bar-ma-as-momentum-shifts-lower-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;86&quot; data-end=&quot;357&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Gold has broken below the 200-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, signaling a potential shift in momentum following its recent highs.The last few attempts of that rising MA (see green line on the chart above) found sellers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;86&quot; data-end=&quot;357&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A close - and staying below this key trend-defining level - would confirm weakening bullish control and open the door for deeper corrective movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;359&quot; data-end=&quot;393&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The next downside targets include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;394&quot; data-end=&quot;598&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;394&quot; data-end=&quot;438&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;396&quot; data-end=&quot;438&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;$3167.74 – the swing high from April 3&amp;gt; The low has reached $3173.85 so far&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;439&quot; data-end=&quot;508&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;441&quot; data-end=&quot;508&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;$3139 – the underside of the broken ascending channel trendline&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;509&quot; data-end=&quot;598&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;511&quot; data-end=&quot;598&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;$3129.26 – the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement of the rally from the November swing low&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;600&quot; data-end=&quot;843&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;These levels represent key technical checkpoints where buyers may attempt to regroup. However, failure to hold those supports could lead to an extended pullback, especially if broader risk sentiment or interest rate expectations shift further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;845&quot; data-end=&quot;976&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For bulls to regain control, a move back above the 200-bar MA near $3,249 would be needed to neutralize the immediate bearish bias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;978&quot; data-end=&quot;1003&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1004&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1004&quot; data-end=&quot;1074&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1006&quot; data-end=&quot;1074&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: $3,249 (200-bar MA), $3,306 (recent swing high zone)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1075&quot; data-end=&quot;1118&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1077&quot; data-end=&quot;1118&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: $3,167.74, $3,139, $3,129.26&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1119&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1121&quot; data-end=&quot;1187&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 200-bar MA; neutralizing only above $3,249&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US NOT SEEKING TO WEAKEN DOLLAR AS PART OF TRADE DEALS: SOURCE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922693791418298414#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:41:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922693791418298414#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US NOT SEEKING TO WEAKEN DOLLAR AS PART OF TRADE DEALS: SOURCE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD Technical Analysis – Sellers lean at resistance, bias bearish below support zone</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-technical-analysis-sellers-lean-at-resistance-bias-bearish-below-support-zone-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:08:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-technical-analysis-sellers-lean-at-resistance-bias-bearish-below-support-zone-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;99&quot; data-end=&quot;427&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;EURUSD failed to sustain earlier gains as price action today stalled just ahead of the 200-hour moving average (green line on the chart above) and the lower boundary of a key swing zone between 1.12657 and 1.1275. Sellers leaned into the level and have since pushed the pair back toward the 100-hour moving averages&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;429&quot; data-end=&quot;741&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The current focus is on the swing area between 1.1193 and 1.1213, which previously marked key highs from 2024 (not shown). A confirmed break below this zone - and the 100 hour MA at 1.11876 - would be technically significant and likely accelerate selling momentum. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;743&quot; data-end=&quot;1028&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, immediate targets include the 1.1145 support area followed by the weekly low near 1.10648. These levels could attract additional sellers if the current pressure persists. To shift momentum back to the upside, EURUSD would need to reclaim 1.1213 and the 200 hour MA (and stay above) at 1.12578.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1030&quot; data-end=&quot;1055&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1056&quot; data-end=&quot;1264&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1056&quot; data-end=&quot;1122&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1058&quot; data-end=&quot;1122&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.1213,  200-hour MA at 1.12578, 1.12657–1.1275 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1123&quot; data-end=&quot;1204&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1125&quot; data-end=&quot;1204&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.1193–1.1213 (swing zone), 1.11876 (100-hour MA), 1.1145, 1.10648&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1205&quot; data-end=&quot;1264&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1207&quot; data-end=&quot;1264&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 1.1213; intensifies under 1.11876&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1266&quot; data-end=&quot;1416&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The sellers remain in control as long as price stays capped below 1.1213. Watch for follow-through below key supports to confirm bearish continuation.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE BANS US AGENCIES FROM G-20 WORK IN http://S.AFRICA:WAPO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922679354821075403#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:44:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922679354821075403#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE BANS US AGENCIES FROM G-20 WORK IN &lt;a href=&quot;http://S.AFRICA&quot;&gt;S.AFRICA&lt;/a&gt;:WAPO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - TESLA SHARES EXTEND GAINS, LAST UP 4%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922678753945067597#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:41:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922678753945067597#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - TESLA SHARES EXTEND GAINS, LAST UP 4%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equity markets sag late, Spain stocks hit 16-year high</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-markets-sag-late-spain-stocks-hit-16-year-high-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:36:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-markets-sag-late-spain-stocks-hit-16-year-high-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Closing changes on the day:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stoxx 600 -0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC -0.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE 100 -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.3% -- highest close since 2008&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB +0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spanish stocks have been in an impressive bull market and are making new highs after the tariff rout.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP SECURES HISTORIC $1.2 TRILLION ECONOMIC COMMITMENT IN QATAR -FACT SHEET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922676409668960446#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922676409668960446#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP SECURES HISTORIC $1.2 TRILLION ECONOMIC COMMITMENT IN QATAR -FACT SHEET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) NISSAN WEIGHS MOVING SENTRA PRODUCTION FROM MEXICO TO U.S. TO AVOID TARIFFS - AUTOMOTIVE NEWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922675711673852194#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:29:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922675711673852194#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NISSAN WEIGHS MOVING SENTRA PRODUCTION FROM MEXICO TO U.S. TO AVOID TARIFFS - AUTOMOTIVE NEWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HOTLINE CONNECTING PENTAGON AND FAA AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLERS AT WASHINGTON REAGAN AIRPORT HAS BEEN INOPERABLE SINCE 2022 -- FAA OFFICIAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922674286122164547#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:24:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922674286122164547#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HOTLINE CONNECTING PENTAGON AND FAA AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLERS AT WASHINGTON REAGAN AIRPORT HAS BEEN INOPERABLE SINCE 2022 -- FAA OFFICIAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian dollar dips to the lows of the day as S&amp;P 500 falls flat</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-dollar-dips-to-the-lows-of-the-day-as-sp-500-falls-flat-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:17:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-dollar-dips-to-the-lows-of-the-day-as-sp-500-falls-flat-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Australian dollar stalled out today at 0.6500 and is now coming under broad pressure. The dip takes place as the US dollar rebounds in a choppy market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The move looks like it was driven by profit taking in stock markets and a rise in 10-year yields to 4.50%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - ELON MUSK MEETS WITH QATAR INVESTMENT AUTHORITY CHAIRMAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922672142539165960#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:15:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922672142539165960#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - ELON MUSK MEETS WITH QATAR INVESTMENT AUTHORITY CHAIRMAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Micro Computer (SMCI) – Bullish break above 200 day MA. Key resistance targets ahead</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/super-micro-computer-smci-bullish-break-above-200-day-ma-key-resistance-targets-ahead-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:14:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/super-micro-computer-smci-bullish-break-above-200-day-ma-key-resistance-targets-ahead-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;88&quot; data-end=&quot;661&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Super Micro Computer (SMCI) shares are currently up around 17.14% at $45.57 , extending yesterday’s 16% rally. The sharp move comes on the heels of a major catalyst: a multi-year, $20 billion partnership with Saudi data-center developer DataVolt. As part of the deal, Super Micro will accelerate delivery of ultra-dense GPU platforms and rack systems for DataVolt’s hyperscale AI campuses in both Saudi Arabia and the U.S. CEO Charles Liang highlighted the partnership’s strategic value in expanding U.S. manufacturing and advancing Saudi Arabia’s ambition to become a global tech hub.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;663&quot; data-end=&quot;926&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;This agreement is embedded in a broader U.S.-Saudi commercial initiative totaling $600 billion—the largest such package ever—of which $80 billion in AI and tech infrastructure is being backed by major players including Alphabet, Oracle, Salesforce, AMD, and Uber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;928&quot; data-end=&quot;1502&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For SMCI, the rebound comes after a volatile stretch. Shares had surged to a post-split high of $122.90 in 2024 (following a 10:1 split in October), only to plunge to $17.25 in November amid concerns over accounting irregularities and a delayed earnings release that nearly cost the company its NASDAQ listing. Though the most recent earnings report on May 6 fell short—EPS of $0.31 vs. $0.41 expected, and revenue of $4.6 billion vs. $5.01 billion—the new partnership, coupled with renewed AI enthusiasm and improved transparency, has sparked a sharp reversal in sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1504&quot; data-end=&quot;1582&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;So with the worst potentially behind them, what are the technicals saying now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;91&quot; data-end=&quot;437&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Super Micro Computer (SMCI) is showing renewed bullish momentum after rebounding from a near-collapse late last year. The recent rally has pushed the stock above the 200-day moving average (green line on the chart above), now at $39.87—a level that buyers must defend to maintain control. Holding above this moving average would help solidify a base for further upside traction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;439&quot; data-end=&quot;780&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The next hurdle lies in a key swing area between $47.86 and $51.35. This zone has repeatedly acted as both support and resistance, making it a pivotal battle zone. A sustained break above this region opens the door toward trendline resistance near $53.20, followed by the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement level of the 2024–2025 decline at $57.61.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;782&quot; data-end=&quot;973&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The high of the year at $66.44 came before a post-earnings collapse, but the market now appears to be regaining confidence. If buyers can keep the momentum going, there’s room to roam higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;975&quot; data-end=&quot;1106&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, failure to hold above the 200-day MA could signal a fading recovery and refocus attention on lower support levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1108&quot; data-end=&quot;1133&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1134&quot; data-end=&quot;1389&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1134&quot; data-end=&quot;1190&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1136&quot; data-end=&quot;1190&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Immediate support: $39.87 (200-day moving average)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1191&quot; data-end=&quot;1240&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1193&quot; data-end=&quot;1240&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance zone: $47.86–$51.35 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1241&quot; data-end=&quot;1318&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1243&quot; data-end=&quot;1318&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Next upside targets: $53.20 (trendline), $57.61 (38.2% Fib retracement)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1319&quot; data-end=&quot;1389&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1321&quot; data-end=&quot;1389&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bullish above $39.87 with momentum building; caution below&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another stock that was hit hard is also trying to make a comeback.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMD shares are up 5.02% after rising 5.13%,and 4.01% over the prior two days.  The price moved above the 100 aday MA on Monday at $107.48 (now a risk level for buyers looking for more upside). The 200 day MA is above at $127.30 and would need to be broken to increase the bullish bias. The 38.2% of the move down from the 2024 high is at $134.09&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares from the peak in 2024 fell -66%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the bottom is in and the tech/AI momentum reignites, staying above the 100 day MA is now the risk at $107.48.  More confidence comes on a break of the 200 day MA at $127.29. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUSSIA&apos;S LAVROV WILL NOT TAKE PART IN TALKS IN ISTANBUL - KOMMERSANT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922665257815703673#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:48:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922665257815703673#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUSSIA&apos;S LAVROV WILL NOT TAKE PART IN TALKS IN ISTANBUL - KOMMERSANT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KENNEDY SAYS HIS OPINIONS ABOUT VACCINES ARE IRRELEVANT, DOES NOT THINK PEOPLE SHOULD TAKE MEDICAL ADVICE FROM HIM</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922662579475714503#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:37:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922662579475714503#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KENNEDY SAYS HIS OPINIONS ABOUT VACCINES ARE IRRELEVANT, DOES NOT THINK PEOPLE SHOULD TAKE MEDICAL ADVICE FROM HIM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CHINA SUSPENDS, SCRAPS UNRELIABLE LIST POLICIES ON SOME US COS.

*CHINA SUSPENDS EXPORTS CONTROL OVER 28 US ENTITIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922658190602219793#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:20:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922658190602219793#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CHINA SUSPENDS, SCRAPS UNRELIABLE LIST POLICIES ON SOME US COS.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*CHINA SUSPENDS EXPORTS CONTROL OVER 28 US ENTITIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *WITKOFF SAYS HE, RUBIO TO TRAVEL TO ISTANBUL ON FRIDAY: RTRS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922657903158173812#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922657903158173812#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*WITKOFF SAYS HE, RUBIO TO TRAVEL TO ISTANBUL ON FRIDAY: RTRS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRADE-TARIFF DEALS WITH JAPAN AND SOUTH KOREA SAID TO BE “CLOSE”: SOURCES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922657301279682846#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:16:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922657301279682846#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRADE-TARIFF DEALS WITH JAPAN AND SOUTH KOREA SAID TO BE “CLOSE”: SOURCES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) QATAR AGREES TO BUY 160 BOEING AIRCRAFT: WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922656057886642672#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:11:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922656057886642672#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;QATAR AGREES TO BUY 160 BOEING AIRCRAFT: WHITE HOUSE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA PAUSES EXPORT CONTROL MEASURES AGAINST 28 US ENTITIES FOR 90 DAYS FROM MAY 14-COMMERCE MINISTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922655347472282066#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:08:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922655347472282066#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA PAUSES EXPORT CONTROL MEASURES AGAINST 28 US ENTITIES FOR 90 DAYS FROM MAY 14-COMMERCE MINISTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA PAUSES UNRELIABLE ENTITY LIST MEASURE ON 17 US ENTITIES-COMMERCE MINISTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922655109307056431#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:07:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922655109307056431#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA PAUSES UNRELIABLE ENTITY LIST MEASURE ON 17 US ENTITIES-COMMERCE MINISTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $BA - TRUMP: BOEING AGREEMENT IS FOR OVER $200 BLN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922654805232640396#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:06:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922654805232640396#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23BA&quot;&gt;$BA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP: BOEING AGREEMENT IS FOR OVER $200 BLN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
