<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Cook: Seeing some signs of stress among low-moderate income households</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-cook-seeing-some-signs-of-stress-among-low-moderate-income-households-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:03:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-cook-seeing-some-signs-of-stress-among-low-moderate-income-households-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Fed&apos;s Cook is out saying: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Seeing some signs of stress among low – moderate income households&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sufficiently large income shock could push up defaults, lead to losses for lenders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Treasury market function orderly during April volatility.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Watching commercial real estate market closely.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comments are not anything new&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COOK: SUFFICIENTLY LARGE INCOME SHOCK COULD PUSH UP DEFAULTS, LEAD TO LOSSES FOR LENDERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925944960827682830#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:00:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925944960827682830#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COOK: SUFFICIENTLY LARGE INCOME SHOCK COULD PUSH UP DEFAULTS, LEAD TO LOSSES FOR LENDERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S COOK: SEEING SOME SIGNS OF STRESS AMONG LOW-, MODERATE-INCOME HOUSEHOLDS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925944874173366378#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:00:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925944874173366378#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S COOK: SEEING SOME SIGNS OF STRESS AMONG LOW-, MODERATE-INCOME HOUSEHOLDS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: TRUMP&apos;S AGENDA RISKS BEING SLOWED BY COURTS, DEMOCRATS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925944809224540437#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925944809224540437#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: TRUMP&apos;S AGENDA RISKS BEING SLOWED BY COURTS, DEMOCRATS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: SOVEREIGN WEALTH FUND ON PAUSE UNTIL WE DEAL WITH EVERYTHING ELSE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925944692845236685#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:59:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925944692845236685#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: SOVEREIGN WEALTH FUND ON PAUSE UNTIL WE DEAL WITH EVERYTHING ELSE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) WHITE HOUSE AI CZAR: RESTRICTING THE SALE OF EUV LITHOGRAPHY EQUIPMENT TO CHINA IS THE SINGLE MOST IMPORTANT EXPORT CONTROL THAT WE HAVE IN THE AREA OF SEMICONDUCTORS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925944627288244546#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:59:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925944627288244546#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WHITE HOUSE AI CZAR: RESTRICTING THE SALE OF EUV LITHOGRAPHY EQUIPMENT TO CHINA IS THE SINGLE MOST IMPORTANT EXPORT CONTROL THAT WE HAVE IN THE AREA OF SEMICONDUCTORS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: HARVARD IS A GIANT HEDGE FUND</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925942422162296891#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:50:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925942422162296891#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: HARVARD IS A GIANT HEDGE FUND&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SENIOR COGNAC INDUSTRY OFFICIAL SAYS TRUMP&apos;S LATEST TARIFF PROPOSAL WOULD MEAN WE CAN NO LONGER SELL OUR PRODUCTS IN UNITED STATES, OUR BIGGEST MARKET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925942205874688164#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925942205874688164#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SENIOR COGNAC INDUSTRY OFFICIAL SAYS TRUMP&apos;S LATEST TARIFF PROPOSAL WOULD MEAN WE CAN NO LONGER SELL OUR PRODUCTS IN UNITED STATES, OUR BIGGEST MARKET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *BESSENT: COULD CHANGE SUPPLEMENTARY LEVERAGE RATIO OVER SUMMER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925941418528260275#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:46:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925941418528260275#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*BESSENT: COULD CHANGE SUPPLEMENTARY LEVERAGE RATIO OVER SUMMER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. JUDGE BLOCKS TRUMP FROM REVOKING HARVARD UNIVERSITY&apos;S ABILITY TO ENROLL FOREIGN STUDENTS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925941361032765773#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:46:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925941361032765773#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. JUDGE BLOCKS TRUMP FROM REVOKING HARVARD UNIVERSITY&apos;S ABILITY TO ENROLL FOREIGN STUDENTS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *BESSENT: WAS JUST IN MIDEAST, TRILLIONS OF DOLLARS COMING TO US</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925941250470859117#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925941250470859117#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*BESSENT: WAS JUST IN MIDEAST, TRILLIONS OF DOLLARS COMING TO US&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUSSIA WILL GIVE APPROPRIATE RESPONSE TO MASSIVE UKRAINIAN ATTACKS ON ITS TERRITORY - FOREIGN MINISTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925940115827732909#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:41:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925940115827732909#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUSSIA WILL GIVE APPROPRIATE RESPONSE TO MASSIVE UKRAINIAN ATTACKS ON ITS TERRITORY - FOREIGN MINISTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: OTHER COUNTRIES&apos; CURRENCIES RISING, NOT DOLLAR FALLING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925939595167900103#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:39:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925939595167900103#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: OTHER COUNTRIES&apos; CURRENCIES RISING, NOT DOLLAR FALLING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: WOULDN&apos;T NECESSARILY CATEGORIZE IT AS WEAK DOLLAR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925939541229064463#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:39:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925939541229064463#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: WOULDN&apos;T NECESSARILY CATEGORIZE IT AS WEAK DOLLAR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: NOT WORRIED ABOUT US DEBT DYNAMICS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925939296323739847#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:38:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925939296323739847#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: NOT WORRIED ABOUT US DEBT DYNAMICS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: NOT PARTICULARLY WORRIED ABOUT WHAT MARKET&apos;S THINKING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925939262714790082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:37:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925939262714790082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: NOT PARTICULARLY WORRIED ABOUT WHAT MARKET&apos;S THINKING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent ultimately sees &apos;several hundred billion&apos; per year in tariff revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-ultimately-sees-several-hundred-billion-per-year-in-tariff-revenue-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:36:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-ultimately-sees-several-hundred-billion-per-year-in-tariff-revenue-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expect we will be negotiating with China in person again&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is a Laffer Curve for tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A lot of these non-tariff barriers are coming down&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don&apos;t know where &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sees &apos;several hundred billion&apos; per year in tariff revenue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;my sense is that int he next several weeks we will have several large deals announced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeats that the EU has a collective-action problem&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The German finance minister was very responsive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I think Merz will provide an opportunity for a US-German reset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All yields are up since the start of the year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The market could also be thinking the Congressional yield could create growth&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says he&apos;s not concerned about USD weakening alongside higher yields&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other currencies are strengthening, rather than USD weakening&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t see much to get excited about here. If anything, the comments about a US-Germany reset are positive.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: WRONG TO THINK BONDS ARE MOVING ON US CONGRESS ACTION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925938961643397359#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:36:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925938961643397359#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: WRONG TO THINK BONDS ARE MOVING ON US CONGRESS ACTION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: MAY SEE A US-GERMANY RESET UNDER CHANCELLOR MERZ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925938877086204013#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:36:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925938877086204013#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: MAY SEE A US-GERMANY RESET UNDER CHANCELLOR MERZ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 BESSENT: WILL BE NEGOTIATING AGAIN IN PERSON WITH CHINA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925938577323479260#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:35:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925938577323479260#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 BESSENT: WILL BE NEGOTIATING AGAIN IN PERSON WITH CHINA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 BESSENT: OVER THE NEXT COUPLE WEEKS WE&apos;RE GOING TO HAVE SEVERAL LARGE DEALS ANNOUNCED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925938522889826404#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925938522889826404#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 BESSENT: OVER THE NEXT COUPLE WEEKS WE&apos;RE GOING TO HAVE SEVERAL LARGE DEALS ANNOUNCED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: SEVERAL HUNDRED BLN DOLLARS A YR. TO COME FROM TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925938435015016486#m</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:34:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925938435015016486#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: SEVERAL HUNDRED BLN DOLLARS A YR. TO COME FROM TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USD/CAD flirts with the lowest since October</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-flirts-with-the-lowest-since-october-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:34:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdcad-flirts-with-the-lowest-since-october-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;I have a close eye on USD/CAD today  as the pair steadily slides as part of the broader US dollar selloff. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The loonie is so far underperforming the AUD and NZD today in percentage terms but it&apos;s also brushing up against an important level. Moreover, the market may be hesitant to push though with US and UK holidays coming on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key item on the agenda for the loonie in the week ahead is Thursday&apos;s Canadian GDP report. RBC expects it will show the Canadian economy grew by 1.8% annualized
in Q1. The caveat is that the quarter was front-loaded with strength in January that gradually faded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;We expect to see an increase in household consumption
in Q1 that was partially offset by a contraction in residential investment as
home resales cooled. Business investment likely inched higher, but is expected
to soften in the coming quarters as businesses freeze spending plans amid
disruptive trade policies,&quot; RBC writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My major worry about Canada relates to housing, which continues to crack. Listings are mounting quickly in the Toronto area and with 5-year rates rising, there is little hope for relief any time soon. The Bank of Canada is now less-likely to cut rates in June and the rising loonie will help to cool inflation.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NZDUSD is extending to new session highs and highs for the week.What next technically?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-nzdusd-is-extending-to-new-session-highs-and-highs-for-the-weekwhat-next-technically-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:59:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-nzdusd-is-extending-to-new-session-highs-and-highs-for-the-weekwhat-next-technically-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The NZDUSD is stretching to new highs for the day and also new highs for the week (highest level since May 8). That move has taken the price above the 0.59664 from Wednesday, which also was near the high price going back to last week on May 14. Getting above that level is a bullish play and opens the door for further upside momentum for the NZDUSD..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With increased momentum, we could see the price ultimately reach the high prices from both April and May. Those levels came between 0.6018 and 0.6028 over time (see red numbered circles on the chart below). Getting above those levels would take the pair to the highest level since November 2024.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The moves to the upside, come after sellers had their shot over the last 8 or so days on breaks of the 200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart.  However, each time the price tried to extend below the 200 bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, sellers turned back to buyers fairly quickly (see green numbered circles outlining the tests of that 200 bar moving average).  That ultimately was the dominant play technically, that has moved the price higher this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video above, outlines the key levels in play and explains why.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Musalem: GDP is close to potential</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-gdp-is-close-to-potential-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:52:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-gdp-is-close-to-potential-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Musalem:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inflation is stills above target&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Today&apos;s world is very different from the pandemic, one in five chance at most that Fed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schmid:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will lean very much on hard data in making interest rates decisions, allows for less focus on forecasts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed needs to be careful how much emphasis it puts on soft data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Fed needs to think hard in future years about when and how it wants to use the balance sheet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market has priced in 83 bps in easing in the year ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech sector struggles, financial and healthcare remain resilient</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-struggles-financial-and-healthcare-remain-resilient-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:46:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-struggles-financial-and-healthcare-remain-resilient-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Today’s stock market reveals a challenging environment for technology stocks, with mixed outcomes across financial and healthcare sectors. Investors witness a dynamic trading landscape, highlighting the need for keen strategy and portfolio management. 🏛️&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;📉 Tech Sector: Widespread Declines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The technology sector is leading today’s downturn, with Microsoft (MSFT) experiencing a drop of 0.73% and Oracle (ORCL) down by 0.98%. Nvidia (NVDA), a major player in semiconductors, fell by 1.63%, continuing a challenging trend for chip manufacturers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This sector-wide decline highlights current investor hesitation amid industry-specific pressures.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;📈 Financial and Healthcare Sectors: Mixed Reactions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The financial sector shows resilience, despite a slight pullback in Visa (V) by 1.18% and JPMorgan Chase (JPM) by 0.66%. Interestingly, Intercontinental Exchange (ICE) shows strength with a 0.99% gain, indicating potential confidence in select financial services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The healthcare sector reflects steady performance with Johnson &amp; Johnson (JNJ) up by 0.14%, signaling modest investor interest in defensive stocks during market volatility.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 Consumer &amp; Communications: Mixed Signals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Amazon (AMZN) dropped by 0.94%, while Meta (META) fell 1.25%, contrasting with a better-than-expected performance in consumer cyclical sectors, indicating a cautious consumer sentiment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Google (GOOGL) and Netflix (NFLX) also experienced declines, hinting at investor wariness regarding future growth amid economic uncertainties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;📚 Market Mood and Strategies Forward&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overall, the market sentiment appears cautious, driven by adverse news in technology and muted recovery signals in other sectors.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Investors are advised to maintain a diversified portfolio to mitigate risks associated with specific sector declines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consider keeping an eye on the financial sector&apos;s potential for stability and exploring opportunities within healthcare stocks as safe havens in turbulent times.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay informed and adjust your strategies as needed by visiting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt; for comprehensive market analysis and news.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Canada rate cut odds fall further after retail sales data</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bank-of-canada-rate-cut-odds-fall-further-after-retail-sales-data-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bank-of-canada-rate-cut-odds-fall-further-after-retail-sales-data-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;USD/CAD is flirting with a break of the lows of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar is sliding broadly today but the Canadian dollar is getting an extra lift from March and April retail sales data. The numbers were solid and come on the heels of a hotter CPI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combined, that has the odds of a June 4 rate cut down to 28% from 65% before CPI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economists at CIBC were one group calling for cuts and now sound like they&apos;re just waiting for next week&apos;s GDP report to flip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Our forecast for a contraction in GDP in April and Q2 as a whole is driven more by expected
weakness in manufacturing and other sectors more directly impacted by US trade. Advance figures for those areas are
due to be released early next week, but if they also aren&apos;t as weak as anticipated then we will have to revise our forecast
for monthly GDP and likely our Bank of Canada rate cut call as well.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the report itself, they note that consumer spending has been holding up better than anticipated. The caveat is that auto sales were a big driver of stronger retail sales and that could have been a tariff front-run trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch for stops below the May low of 1.3748.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD technical analysis: Sellers stay in control as price targets key support</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-technical-analysis-sellers-stay-in-control-as-price-targets-key-support-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:12:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-technical-analysis-sellers-stay-in-control-as-price-targets-key-support-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;85&quot; data-end=&quot;383&quot;&gt;The USDCAD remains under selling pressure after failing to sustain gains above key resistance near 1.4009–1.4026 and the 200-day MA last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;85&quot; data-end=&quot;383&quot;&gt;This week, the price on Wednesday fell below a swing area between 1.38917 to 1.3904.  The break and hold below this zone gave sellers the green light to drive the pair even lower and they did on Wednesday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;85&quot; data-end=&quot;383&quot;&gt;Yesterday, the price corrected back toward the swing area again, with the high price reaching 1.3888 just short of the low of the swing area at 1.38917.  Sellers still in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;85&quot; data-end=&quot;383&quot;&gt;Today, the momentum lower continued with the pair now looking to test the lows of 2025 (and lowest levels since October 2024).  That level comes between 1.37497 to 1.37698 (see red numbered circles).  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;698&quot; data-end=&quot;829&quot;&gt;Do the buyers stall the fall at the lows for 2025?  Traders looking to buy a dip can lean with a stop below.  However, be aware that the 61.8% of the move up from the 2023 low comes in at 1.37415 - just below the low from 2025. So it might be wise for dip buyers to wait on a break of that retracement level.   &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April new home sales 743K vs 693K expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-new-home-sales-743k-vs-693k-expected-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-new-home-sales-743k-vs-693k-expected-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 724K (revised to 670K)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sales monthly change 10.9% vs +7.4% prior (revised to +2.6%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rising long-term yields and borrowing costs aren&apos;t helping the housing market. Shares of home builders have struggled badly this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a surprising number but it looks like some sales have simply been shifted by a month as the March number was revised far lower.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Musalem: Do not want short-term inflation expectations to bleed into longer term</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-do-not-want-short-term-inflation-expectations-to-bleed-into-longer-term-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:57:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-do-not-want-short-term-inflation-expectations-to-bleed-into-longer-term-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Musalem:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Businesses expect higher prices for inputs and outputs, Fed is watching that carefully&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business executives are trying to figure out how to manager uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schmid:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uncertainty is being driven by the tariff conversation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;ve heard similar comments from the Fed over and over. Nothing is changing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes now on today&apos;s previously-scheduled call between US and EU officials</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eyes-now-on-todays-previously-scheduled-call-between-us-and-eu-officials-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:47:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eyes-now-on-todays-previously-scheduled-call-between-us-and-eu-officials-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t think there is any secret on what&apos;s happening between the US and EU at the moment; Bessent spelled it out. He said the EU has been moving too slowly on trade and Trump wants to &apos;light a fire&apos; under the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The message was strategically timed ahead of a call today that was scheduled previously. At 12:30 pm ET, there is a call scheduled between EU trade boss Sefcovic and USA counterpart Greer will take place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market will be waiting for a read-out (or leak) from that call afterwards. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Update: One report says this call is at 11 am ET, so watch out for headlines earlier.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF technicals are doing their job. What does that mean? Watch this video and find out.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-technicals-are-doing-their-job-what-does-that-mean-watch-this-video-and-find-out-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:25:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-technicals-are-doing-their-job-what-does-that-mean-watch-this-video-and-find-out-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;75&quot; data-end=&quot;348&quot;&gt;The USDCHF continues to trade with a bearish tilt after a series of failed upside attempts near key technical levels. The 100-hour moving average (currently near 0.8284) served as strong resistance earlier this week, capping rallies yesterday most recently, and helping to turn buyers into sellers into the day close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;350&quot; data-end=&quot;682&quot;&gt;The recent decline seen today, initially found buyers near the 50% midpoint of the April-to-May range at 0.8257. However, EU tariff news triggered a decisive break below this level, adding downside momentum. The pair did not find support until reaching the next key swing area between 0.8193 and 0.8212—highlighted by past price reaction zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;886&quot;&gt;With price now below both the 100- and 200-hour moving averages and under key Fibonacci retracement levels, the bears remain in control unless buyers can push the pair back above 0.8257 (50%) and then 0.8284 (100 hour MA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;886&quot;&gt;Overall, howver, the technicals are doing their job. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;888&quot; data-end=&quot;913&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;914&quot; data-end=&quot;1129&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;914&quot; data-end=&quot;996&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;916&quot; data-end=&quot;996&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.8257 (50% retracement), 0.8284 (100-hour MA), 0.8300 (200-hour MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;997&quot; data-end=&quot;1050&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;999&quot; data-end=&quot;1050&quot;&gt;Support: 0.8212/0.8193 (swing area), 0.8163, 0.8139&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1051&quot; data-end=&quot;1129&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1053&quot; data-end=&quot;1129&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 0.8284, with further downside potential if 0.8193 breaks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bessent: Trump move is in response to EU&apos;s pace on tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-trump-move-is-in-response-to-eus-pace-on-tariffs-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:25:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bessent-trump-move-is-in-response-to-eus-pace-on-tariffs-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;If you missed it, Trump &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-recommends-a-50-tariff-on-eu-starting-on-june-1-20250523/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;earlier &lt;/a&gt;&apos;recommended&apos; a 50% tariff on the EU starting June 1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump believes EU proposals have not been of good quality&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Would like to have Apple help US to make semiconductor supply chain better&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump trying to bring back precision manufacturing to the US&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says US is &apos;far along&apos; with India and Asian countries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most countries negotiating in good faith except EU&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These deals are moving quickly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will see more deals announced in 90-day period&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Separate comments are coming from the German foreign minister:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We support Commission to defend the European market&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both markets would suffer, that&apos;s why we want further negotiations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In hindsight, we should have been bracing for something. Trump took a break from the trade war to go to the Middle East and wouldn&apos;t have wanted to announce something like this during the G7 on Wed/Thurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, Trump will attend the G7 in Canada from June 15-17, so if he follows the pattern of lowering tensions during international visits, that leaves a three-week window.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When do you buy the tariff dip in US stocks? When Trump tells you</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/when-do-you-buy-the-tariff-dip-in-us-stocks-when-trump-tells-you-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:15:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/when-do-you-buy-the-tariff-dip-in-us-stocks-when-trump-tells-you-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are down 1.5% shortly before the open while Nasdaq futures are down 1.8% as Apple falls 3.5% on Trump tariff threats on iPhones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s a long weekend in the US so trade could taper off into the weekend but a big question will be: When to buy the dip? The lesson of the China trade war round is that Trump doesn&apos;t have the appetite to really hurt the stock market, so the trade is to buy the dip. The question is: when?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s a much tougher one to answer. We&apos;re at the end of another week and there haven&apos;t been any trade deals this week, despite Hassett saying they were coming again. The July 9 deadline for tariffs is fast approaching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For me, there is no edge in guessing at the timing of when to buy. At best, you can buy it when Trump tells you to.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The market is figuring out that it&apos;s better to sell the US dollar in the trade war</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-figuring-out-that-its-better-to-sell-the-us-dollar-in-the-trade-war-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:04:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-figuring-out-that-its-better-to-sell-the-us-dollar-in-the-trade-war-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The knee-jerk reaction to Trump threatening tariffs on the EU was to buy the US dollar on a number of fronts but that&apos;s quickly faded. Cable is now trading near the highs, AUD has bounced all the way back and the loonie is at its best levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the euro -- which is the target of the tariffs -- has rebounded 35 pips and is still up a half-cent on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trend so far this year has been to sell the US dollar as the US breaks the global consensus on trade. That should be the result of this round of tariffs as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, some people will be looking to buy the dip but that&apos;s tough to time. It&apos;s certainly early at the moment but if you believe Trump will ultimately back down then it&apos;s never too early. He left himself an out by waiting until June 1 and it&apos;s notable that there is a call scheduled today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EU doesn&apos;t have the backbone for a fight in the way that China does so this could go badly for them if they roll over. That said, it&apos;s tough with so many voices in Europe. If they do fight, it could embolden the Chinese, Japanese and others as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again, these are all risks for the US economy and US dollar. I don&apos;t see how the Fed gets any closer to cutting rates now and I don&apos;t see how US businesses will be more-willing to invest or hire in light of this development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, the clearest trades are buying the yen, Swiss franc and gold.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Goosbee: Businesses want some consistency in policy</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goosbee-businesses-want-some-consistency-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:35:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goosbee-businesses-want-some-consistency-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Companies want some consistency&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leaders have to put pencils down because of so much change&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A 50% EU tariff is an order of magnitude different from current situation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariff rates that high would be scary for the suppl;y chain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is anxiety among firms that continued tariff announcements would disrupt the supply chain and lead to rising price environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In the short run the Fed needs to wait for the dust to clear, the bar for action is higher until that happens.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If tariffs have a stagflationary impact then that is the central banks worse situation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;My fear is the data comes out with a lag, so something may have already happened. Upcoming reports may show a more serious impact from actions already taken.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The market determines the long end of yields. We should take into consideration the impact from that impact on the economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our job is to look at anything that affects prices and employment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interest rates are still within historical ranges, if there is a crisis over US fiscal stability they would be moving higher.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ON April 2, I thought rates could come down by the end of the year.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;That might be extended out 10-16 months from now. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Still feel that underneath the volatility, the economy remains strong, if tariffs and uncertainty were not a threat to inflation, rates would eventually fall.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is the Fed to do, but wait given the fiscal side of the equation is easing and tightening on a daily basis.  Yes trade policy is 11% of the economy but the impact can be a multiple of that 11% if the apple cart is more than wobbling and it has ancillary impacts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk managers look to define and limit risk, and then accept risk.  That does not mean not take risk, it just says they define and limit it as much as possible.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What Goolsbee and the Fed members are saying is risk to inflation and employment can not be defined. It cannot be limited.  So sit tight until the dust settles.  &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada March retail sales +0.8% vs +0.7% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-retail-sales-08-vs-07-expected-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:30:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-retail-sales-08-vs-07-expected-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The advanced March &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-retail-sales-for-february-04-versus-04-estimate-20250425/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;report &lt;/a&gt;was +0.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was -0.4% (revised to -0.5%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ex-autos -0.7% vs 0.0% expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior ex-autos +0.5% (revised to +0.6%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advance April report +0.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RBC &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.rbc.com/en/thought-leadership/economics/featured-insights/rbc-consumer-spending-tracker/?nocache&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;survey &lt;/a&gt;on Canadian consumers last week hinted at a resilient consumer in April and that&apos;s what the advance number shows. On the flipside, that core number in March is poor.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EURUSD moves lower after Trump imposed 50% tariff on EU goods</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-eurusd-moves-lower-after-trump-imposed-50-tariff-on-eu-goods-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:20:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-eurusd-moves-lower-after-trump-imposed-50-tariff-on-eu-goods-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The EURUSD is moving to the downside reversing the gains from earlier today after Pres. Trump said he would impose a 50% tariff on EU imports into the US starting June 1.  He also said he would impose a 25% tariff on Apple iPhones not manufactured in the US. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The climb down the mountain restarts(and things seemed so bright in the Middle East last week). Yields are lower. Stocks are sharply lower. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video above, I take a look at the three major currency pairs - the EURUSD, USDJPY and GBPUSD - from a technical perspective. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the US yields:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield 3.932%, -6.5 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.027%, -8.5 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10 year yield 4.473%, -8.0basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30 yar yield 4.997%, -6.3  basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the US stock indices, the earlier pre-market gains are being eroded fast with the Nasdaq moving from about +40 points to down -92 points over just the last hour of trading&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow dow -577 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P down -88 points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq -390 points.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Trade War 2.0</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/welcome-to-trade-war-20-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/welcome-to-trade-war-20-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The trade war was never going to be one-and-done. Trump loves tariffs too much and has too long of a list of grievances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of progress on trade deals over the past two weeks was a red flag and the 90-day deadline was ticking ever closer. He&apos;s left himself an &apos;out&apos; here by delaying this to June 1 but at the same time, I think he&apos;s handing some leverage to China here in negotiations. How many fronts does the US want to fight at once?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The past two weeks have been a wonderful, placid moment and a glimpse into what could be, but until Congress takes away Trump&apos;s ability to impose tariffs, then this dance will continue.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump recommends a 50% tariff on EU starting on June 1</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-recommends-a-50-tariff-on-eu-starting-on-june-1-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:46:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-recommends-a-50-tariff-on-eu-starting-on-june-1-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump recommends a 50% tariff on EU.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says EU has been hard to deal with.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariff would start on June 1st.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No tariff if product is built or manufactured in US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our discussion with them going nowhere.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s not been a secret that the EU would have been harder to deal with and Trump seems to get tired of it.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive European FX news wrap: Hot UK retail sales, weak USD, Trump threatens Apple</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-hot-uk-retail-sales-weak-usd-trump-threatens-apple-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-hot-uk-retail-sales-weak-usd-trump-threatens-apple-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article__title&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-threatens-tariffs-on-apple-if-products-not-made-in-us-20250523/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Trump threatens tariffs on Apple if products not made in US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-lane-confident-services-inflation-will-come-down-20250523/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Lane: Confident services inflation will come down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-this-weeks-data-20250523/&quot;&gt;How have interest rates expectations changed after this week&apos;s data?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/bulgaria-advances-toward-euro-adoption-20250523/&quot;&gt;Bulgaria Advances Toward Euro Adoption&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecb-q1-2025-negotiated-wage-indicator-238-vs-412-in-q4-2024-20250523/&quot;&gt;ECB Q1 2025 negotiated wage indicator +2.38% vs +4.12% in Q4 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-rehn-june-cut-appropriate-if-data-confirm-stabilisation-of-inflation-20250523/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Rehn: June cut &apos;appropriate&apos; if data confirm stabilisation of inflation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/france-may-consumer-confidence-88-vs-93-expected-20250523/&quot;&gt;France May consumer confidence 88 vs 93 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-q1-final-gdp-04-vs-02-qq-expected-20250523/&quot;&gt;Germany Q1 final GDP 0.4% vs 0.2% q/q expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-retail-sales-12-vs-02-mm-expected-20250523/&quot;&gt;UK April retail sales +1.2% vs +0.2% m/m expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-stournaras-i-see-a-june-rate-cut-and-then-pause-20250523/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Stournaras: I see a June rate cut and then pause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-23-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250523/&quot;&gt;FX option expiries for 23 May 10am New York cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-pushes-eu-to-cut-tariffs-or-face-extra-duties-ft-20250523/&quot;&gt;Trump pushes EU to cut tariffs or face extra duties - FT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been a pretty boring session in terms of newsflow. The UK retail sales report was the only highlight. The data beat expectations by a huge margin with good weather cited as the main reason. Nonetheless, there&apos;s been a strong positive trend in retail sales for several months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the markets, the most notable mover has been the US Dollar which extended the overnight losses. There was no catalyst since yesterday&apos;s strong US PMIs, but the fact that the market has already repriced interest rates expectations in line with the Fed&apos;s baseline for 2025 gives the greenback little support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will need more to trim the rate cuts bets further and give the USD a boost. That could come with the data in June when we get ISM PMIs, NFP and CPI before the FOMC Policy Decision. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, we could either range here or see more losses for the greenback. For today, we are already at the daily average range limit, so there shouldn&apos;t be much follow through in the American session and chances of a pullback are higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late in the session, Trump posted on Truth Social that he would impose 25% tariffs on Apple if the iPhones were not made in the US. That saw the AAPL stock dropping more than 3% in pre-market trading.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens tariffs on Apple if products not made in US</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-threatens-tariffs-on-apple-if-products-not-made-in-us-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 11:24:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-threatens-tariffs-on-apple-if-products-not-made-in-us-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;iPhone&apos;s that will be sold in the US will be manufactured and built in US, not India or anyplace else.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If that&apos;s not the case, a tariff of at least 25% must be paid by Apple to the US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AAPL stock is down on the news.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Lane: Confident services inflation will come down</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-lane-confident-services-inflation-will-come-down-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:12:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-lane-confident-services-inflation-will-come-down-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confident services inflation will come down.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Services inflation in the Eurozone has been stuck around 4% for well over a year. You can see it in the chart below.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How have interest rates expectations changed after this week&apos;s data?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-this-weeks-data-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:05:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/how-have-interest-rates-expectations-changed-after-this-weeks-data-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed: 51 bps (95% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB: 52 bps (94% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoE: 39 bps (94% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoC: 34 bps (70% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA: 68 bps (57% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBNZ: 60 bps (90% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SNB: 50 bps (81% probability of rate cut at the upcoming meeting)
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;*for the SNB, the rest of the probability is for a 50 bps cut&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rate hikes by year-end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BoJ: 15 bps (98% probability of no change at the upcoming meeting)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key events that weighed on the market pricing this week were:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;RBA&apos;s Bullock mentioning that they did discuss a 50 bps cut. That saw the market increasing the rate cut bets for the RBA from 54 bps to 68 bps by year-end. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Canadian Core inflation data surprising to the upside. That caused the market to price out immediately a rate cut in June that was expected before the CPI release.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hot UK CPI data. The market took a less dovish view and favoured just one rate cut in 2025.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulgaria Advances Toward Euro Adoption</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bulgaria-advances-toward-euro-adoption-20250523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bulgaria-advances-toward-euro-adoption-20250523/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;106&quot;&gt;Investor Update: Bulgaria Advances Toward Euro Adoption – Symbolic but Limited Impact on Euro Currency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;108&quot; data-end=&quot;590&quot;&gt;Core News:
Bulgaria is making steady progress toward adopting the euro by January 1, 2026. The country has met most Maastricht criteria, including public debt limits, fiscal discipline, and exchange rate stability. The main remaining challenge is elevated inflation, while political stability is also seen as critical for ensuring a successful transition. Despite recent debate—including a proposed national referendum—the trajectory remains broadly on course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;592&quot; data-end=&quot;631&quot;&gt;Implications for the Euro Currency:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;633&quot; data-end=&quot;1544&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;633&quot; data-end=&quot;857&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;635&quot; data-end=&quot;857&quot;&gt;Marginal Economic Impact: Bulgaria&apos;s economy is relatively small compared to the broader eurozone. As such, its inclusion is unlikely to significantly shift the euro&apos;s macro fundamentals or valuation in FX markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;859&quot; data-end=&quot;1060&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;861&quot; data-end=&quot;1060&quot;&gt;Already Pegged: Since 1999, the Bulgarian lev has been pegged to the euro via a currency board, meaning the transition to full euro adoption will likely have minimal exchange rate volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1062&quot; data-end=&quot;1321&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1064&quot; data-end=&quot;1321&quot;&gt;Symbolic Significance: Bulgaria&apos;s accession reinforces confidence in the euro project. In an environment where some countries have questioned deeper integration, Bulgaria’s move is a political signal of continued EU cohesion and currency appeal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1323&quot; data-end=&quot;1544&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1325&quot; data-end=&quot;1544&quot;&gt;Banking System Already Integrated: Bulgaria has participated in the ECB’s banking union and supervision mechanisms for several years. This lowers systemic risk and supports a smoother monetary policy transition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1546&quot; data-end=&quot;1589&quot;&gt;Potential Risks and Internal Frictions:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1590&quot; data-end=&quot;1972&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1590&quot; data-end=&quot;1778&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1592&quot; data-end=&quot;1778&quot;&gt;Catch-Up Inflation: Price level convergence with eurozone averages could trigger a one-time inflationary jump in Bulgaria, a common concern in smaller economies joining the bloc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1779&quot; data-end=&quot;1972&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1781&quot; data-end=&quot;1972&quot;&gt;Implementation Risks: BNB official Iliya Lingorski warned of logistical hurdles, including software upgrades and infrastructure overhauls. These could complicate the rollout timeline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1974&quot; data-end=&quot;2424&quot;&gt;Investor Takeaway:
Bulgaria’s euro adoption will not materially impact the euro’s strength or stability, but it does offer a symbolic boost to EU integration and policy credibility. For investors, the transition reduces currency risk in Bulgaria, supports long-term capital inflows, and confirms eurozone resilience. However, watch for short-term volatility tied to political developments and inflation dynamics within Bulgaria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2426&quot; data-end=&quot;2666&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;This article was generated at ForexLive.com (evolving to be investingLive.com at the end of this year)
with the assistance of AI and may contain factual or contextual inaccuracies. It should not be solely relied upon without verification.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
