<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $BABA - U.S.-LISTED SHARES OF ALIBABA DOWN 1.9% PREMARKET AFTER REPORT OF US SCRUTINY OF COMPANY&apos;S AI DEAL WITH APPLE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924407705466175997#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 10:12:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924407705466175997#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23BABA&quot;&gt;$BABA&lt;/a&gt; - U.S.-LISTED SHARES OF ALIBABA DOWN 1.9% PREMARKET AFTER REPORT OF US SCRUTINY OF COMPANY&apos;S AI DEAL WITH APPLE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SENATE TAKES ITS SECOND STAB AT ADVANCING STABLECOIN LEGISLATION: SEMAFOR

Senators expect to vote again tonight on advancing legislation to create rules for stablecoins — a type of cryptocurrency pegged to assets like the dollar — after a previous attempt imploded, a person familiar with the plans said.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924402991056007457#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:53:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924402991056007457#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SENATE TAKES ITS SECOND STAB AT ADVANCING STABLECOIN LEGISLATION: SEMAFOR&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Senators expect to vote again tonight on advancing legislation to create rules for stablecoins — a type of cryptocurrency pegged to assets like the dollar — after a previous attempt imploded, a person familiar with the plans said.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BITCOIN RETREATS FROM RECENT HIGHS AFTER MOODY&apos;S DOWNGRADES U.S. CREDIT RATING 

Bitcoin falls, retreating from multi-month highs, as investors sell risky assets. This comes after Moody&apos;s Ratings downgraded U.S. sovereign debt to Aa1 from Aaa, citing spiraling government debt. The cryptocurrency had a strong week last week, recording its highest-ever weekly close near $106,500, Saxo says in a note. Bitcoin falls 0.8% to $103,298, having hit a peak of $107,060 in overnight trade, its highest in nearly four months, LSEG data show</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924401435686449362#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924401435686449362#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BITCOIN RETREATS FROM RECENT HIGHS AFTER MOODY&apos;S DOWNGRADES U.S. CREDIT RATING &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Bitcoin falls, retreating from multi-month highs, as investors sell risky assets. This comes after Moody&apos;s Ratings downgraded U.S. sovereign debt to Aa1 from Aaa, citing spiraling government debt. The cryptocurrency had a strong week last week, recording its highest-ever weekly close near $106,500, Saxo says in a note. Bitcoin falls 0.8% to $103,298, having hit a peak of $107,060 in overnight trade, its highest in nearly four months, LSEG data show&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD is back at the key resistance but unlikely to break through today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-is-back-at-the-key-resistance-but-unlikely-to-break-through-today-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-is-back-at-the-key-resistance-but-unlikely-to-break-through-today-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been a rough day for the US Dollar so far. This is just the daily trend that was set &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-dollar-under-pressure-again-to-start-the-session-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;earlier in the morning&lt;/a&gt;. The &quot;good news&quot; for the greenback is that we might have reached the peak in the bearish momentum today. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the EURUSD chart below, we can see that the price is now near the top of the average daily range (red line), which stands right at the key 1.1278 resistance zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is where we can expect the sellers to step in with a defined risk above the resistance to position for a drop into the 1.10 handle. The buyers, on the other hand, will look for a break higher to start targeting new highs, but from a risk management perspective, entering at the highs would be pretty bad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s not much on the agenda today that could help the greenback, but Fed speakers might give it a boost if we get some more hawkish comments, especially from Fed&apos;s Williams.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) DXY DOLLAR INDEX FALLS TO 10-DAY LOW OF 100.186</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924395271292686388#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:22:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924395271292686388#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DXY DOLLAR INDEX FALLS TO 10-DAY LOW OF 100.186&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EURO EXTENDS GAINS, RISES 1% VERSUS DOLLAR TO $1.1274</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924393021090529544#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:13:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924393021090529544#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EURO EXTENDS GAINS, RISES 1% VERSUS DOLLAR TO $1.1274&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) KREMLIN SAYS ROMANIAN ELECTION WAS &apos;AT THE VERY LEAST, STRANGE&apos; -TASS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924392990203691314#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:13:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924392990203691314#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KREMLIN SAYS ROMANIAN ELECTION WAS &apos;AT THE VERY LEAST, STRANGE&apos; -TASS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin: Putin, Trump to hold phone call at 17:00 Moscow time on Monday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/kremlin-putin-trump-to-hold-phone-call-at-1700-moscow-time-on-monday-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:11:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/kremlin-putin-trump-to-hold-phone-call-at-1700-moscow-time-on-monday-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kremlin: Putin, Trump to hold phone call at 17:00 Moscow time on Monday.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is at 14:00 GMT or 10:00 ET. Trump will likely push for a ceasefire until they get a peace deal but the Russians don&apos;t seem on the same page.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 KREMLIN: PUTIN, TRUMP TO HOLD PHONE CALL AT 17.00 MOSCOW TIME ON MONDAY - RIA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924391468916932765#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:07:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924391468916932765#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 KREMLIN: PUTIN, TRUMP TO HOLD PHONE CALL AT 17.00 MOSCOW TIME ON MONDAY - RIA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $NFLX: JPMORGAN DOWNGRADES NETFLIX TO NEUTRAL FROM OVERWEIGHT - PT $1,220 (FROM $1,150)

We remain bullish on Netflix’s long-term leadership in streaming and its potential to become global TV. However, in the near term, after strong stock gains, the risk/reward looks more balanced. Three key points:

🔸 The stock is at an all-time high, trading at 39x 2026E EPS and 44x 2026E FCF, likely pricing in 2025 upside.

🔸 NFLX has been a defensive play, but easing macro/tariff concerns could lead investors to rotate into other beaten-down tech names.

🔸 Summer is a seasonally slower period for Netflix, and after last week’s Upfront, the near-term catalyst path looks quieter, despite strong Q3 content.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924391319314526407#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:06:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924391319314526407#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NFLX&quot;&gt;$NFLX&lt;/a&gt;: JPMORGAN DOWNGRADES NETFLIX TO NEUTRAL FROM OVERWEIGHT - PT $1,220 (FROM $1,150)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
We remain bullish on Netflix’s long-term leadership in streaming and its potential to become global TV. However, in the near term, after strong stock gains, the risk/reward looks more balanced. Three key points:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 The stock is at an all-time high, trading at 39x 2026E EPS and 44x 2026E FCF, likely pricing in 2025 upside.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 NFLX has been a defensive play, but easing macro/tariff concerns could lead investors to rotate into other beaten-down tech names.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Summer is a seasonally slower period for Netflix, and after last week’s Upfront, the near-term catalyst path looks quieter, despite strong Q3 content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurozone April final CPI +2.2% vs +2.2% y/y prelim</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-cpi-22-vs-22-yy-prelim-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-april-final-cpi-22-vs-22-yy-prelim-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI +2.7% vs +2.7% y/y prelim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.5%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;No changes to the initial estimates. The market is pricing 91% chance of another 25 bps cut at the June ECB meeting and a total of 51 bps of easing by year-end. The June cut might be hard to avoid, but it might also be the last one for 2025. Data will tell.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 *US 30-YEAR TREASURY YIELD RISES TO 5.02%, HIGHEST SINCE NOV. 2023</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924384916248121718#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:41:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924384916248121718#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 *US 30-YEAR TREASURY YIELD RISES TO 5.02%, HIGHEST SINCE NOV. 2023&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNB total sight deposits w.e. 16 May CHF 443.18 bn vs CHF 453.24 bn prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-16-may-chf-44318-bn-vs-chf-45324-bn-prior-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 08:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/snb-total-sight-deposits-we-16-may-chf-44318-bn-vs-chf-45324-bn-prior-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Domestic sight deposits CHF 434.8 bn vs CHF 444.8 bn prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The SNB publishes these figures weekly, and they can show whether the SNB is intervening in currency markets or adjusting liquidity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;885&quot; data-end=&quot;1131&quot;&gt;An increase in total sight deposits usually indicates that the SNB is injecting liquidity into the system, possibly through foreign exchange interventions (buying foreign currencies to weaken the CHF) or other forms of quantitative easing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1134&quot; data-end=&quot;1249&quot;&gt;A decrease may suggest tightening monetary policy, withdrawing liquidity, or not intervening in FX markets.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US Dollar under pressure again to start the session</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-dollar-under-pressure-again-to-start-the-session-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:33:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-dollar-under-pressure-again-to-start-the-session-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US Dollar opened lower today and after a bit of a consolidation during the Asian session, started to depreciate again in the European session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Moody&apos;s downgrade is cited as the culprit although there are also other drivers. One above all is that the market has repriced interest rates expectations for the Fed to reflect the central bank&apos;s base case of two cuts in 2025. Therefore, we would need stronger reasons to price out the remaining cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had some upside in the greenback following the higher inflation expectations in the UMich survey last Friday but those gains didn&apos;t last for long. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only bullish scenario for the dollar now is that we get strong economic data or more hawkish Fed comments, so that the remaining rate cuts get priced out and give the greenback another short-term boost. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As long as better global growth remains the main driver, the USD should keep on depreciating against its peers, but if inflation starts to become a concern, then we will likely see more upside for the dollar.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Outlook for the week of 19th - 23rd May</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-19th-23rd-may-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:14:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/market-outlook-for-the-week-of-19th-23rd-may-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;On Monday, Canada has a bank holiday for Victoria Day, and in the U.S., several FOMC members are expected to deliver remarks.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, the focus will be on the RBA monetary policy announcement, followed later in the day by Canadian inflation data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; On Wednesday, the U.K. will release its inflation data and on Thursday, flash manufacturing and services PMIs will be released for the eurozone, the U.K., and the U.S.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, on Friday, Japan will publish its national core CPI y/y, while the U.K. and Canada will release their retail sales data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this week&apos;s meeting, the RBA is widely expected to deliver a 25 bps rate cut, lowering the cash rate from 4.10% to 3.85%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, inflation data in Australia has softened, with the trimmed mean CPI dipping to 2.9%, now within the RBA&apos;s target range. Headline inflation held steady at 2.4%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wages rose 3.4% y/y, driven by public sector agreements, while private sector wage growth remained stable. April’s jobs report surprised to the upside, adding 89,000 positions, and the unemployment rate held at 4.1%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The RBA is expected to continue cutting rates through the end of the year. However, Wells Fargo analysts argue that solid domestic data and easing China-U.S. trade tensions reduce the likelihood of further policy easing.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consensus for the CPI m/m is 0.5%, up from the prior 0.3%. The median CPI y/y is expected to remain unchanged at 2.9%, while the trimmed CPI y/y is projected to rise from 2.8% to 2.9%, and the common CPI y/y is likely to increase from 2.3% to 2.4%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Analysts from RBC argue that Canada’s April CPI is likely to reflect a drop in headline inflation, primarily due to the removal of the consumer carbon tax on energy products at the beginning of the month. They emphasize that the distortion stems from a temporary federal tax relief measure, which included the GST rebate and ended in February. As a result, annual inflation is forecast to fall sharply from 2.3% in March to 1.6%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Analysts do not expect the effects of tariffs to be reflected in this month’s data just yet. Retaliatory tariffs are anticipated to have a limited impact on consumer prices, as businesses pivot to alternative import sources and consumers shift toward non-tariffed goods.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canadian food price growth is expected to remain elevated at 3.2% y/y in April, with core inflation rising to 2.6%. March retail sales, due this week, are expected to have rebounded to 0.7% from a February decline, driven by pre-tariff auto purchases. While auto sales likely dipped in April, broader consumer spending appears resilient despite weaker sentiment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the U.K., the consensus for CPI y/y is 3.3%, up from the prior 2.6%. Core CPI y/y is likely to rise from 3.4% to 3.6%, while services inflation is expected to come in below the BoE’s forecast of 5%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysts at ING emphasized that April’s inflation data carries extra weight, as it is typically the month when a wide range of services prices are reset for the year. Both April 2023 and 2024 delivered surprises that jolted markets, often with stronger-than-expected prints.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of monetary policy, the BoE is not finished with rate cuts just yet, with another reduction expected at either the June or August meeting.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week&apos;s PMI data for the eurozone will offer a clearer picture of how the economy is holding up. Last month, the services sector declined to 50.1, while manufacturing remained in contractionary territory at 49, and the composite PMI slipped from 50.9 to 50.4.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, conditions in the euro area appear to have stabilized, supported by easing E.U.–U.S. trade tensions, political stability in Germany, and softening inflation data, all of which point to a modest pickup in activity.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Japan, the consensus for the national core CPI y/y is for an increase from 3.2% to 3.5%. This rise is largely attributed to the effects of reduced energy subsidies and new price hikes in sectors such as food and education. Tokyo CPI, often viewed as a bellwether, surprised to the upside earlier this month, climbing to 3.4% y/y, while the core print excluding fresh food and energy surged to 3.1%, its highest level in over a year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; As a reminder, the BoJ left rates unchanged at its May meeting but signaled openness to further hikes if inflation remains persistent. Uncertainty surrounding U.S. tariffs and signs of weakening global demand complicate the outlook.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Gina Constantin at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equities slightly lower at the open</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-slightly-lower-at-the-open-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 07:07:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equities-slightly-lower-at-the-open-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s been a bit of a risk-off mood throughout the Asian session with the Moody&apos;s downgrade cited as the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Price Prediction for End of May 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-price-prediction-for-end-of-may-2025-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 06:24:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-price-prediction-for-end-of-may-2025-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;What Price Will Bitcoin Hit in May? Polymarket Bets Provide Insight&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As investors and traders navigate the volatile crypto market, many ask, &quot;What price will Bitcoin hit in May?&quot; Prediction markets such as Polymarket have gained popularity by offering speculative insight through aggregated bets, potentially indicating the market&apos;s collective sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, Polymarket’s betting data for Bitcoin&apos;s price by the end of May shows significant predictions:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below $80k: 2% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$85k: 5% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$90k: 11% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$110k: 38% probability (highest probability)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$115k: 15% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$125k: 2% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$150k: 1% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;$200k: less than 1% probability&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the strongest sentiment among bettors anticipates Bitcoin will reach around $110,000 by the month&apos;s end, reflected in a notable 38% likelihood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is Polymarket Accurate in Predicting Bitcoin Prices?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polymarket&apos;s accuracy has been the subject of research. A recent study from CoinDesk (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/03/21/polymarket-is-94-accurate-in-predicting-world-events-research&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;www.coindesk.com/markets/2025/03/21/polymarket-is-94-accurate-in-predicting-world-events-research&lt;/a&gt;) suggests Polymarket is approximately 94% accurate when predicting outcomes within hours of resolution. Even one month in advance, its accuracy remains impressively high, above 90%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, the predictive strength varies significantly with longer-term forecasts. CoinCodex (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coincodex.com/article/65963/is-polymarket-accurate&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;https://www.coincodex.com/article/65963/is-polymarket-accurate&lt;/a&gt;) highlights that accuracy diminishes as the prediction timeframe extends, due to increased unpredictability and market volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cautions for Investors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its strengths, bettors should be aware that Polymarket reflects sentiment rather than guaranteed outcomes. Additionally, a Medium article (medium.com/@balajibal/why-are-polymarket-betters-losing-money-af3cc506fd9a) highlights that the majority of bettors typically experience losses, underscoring the speculative nature of these bets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using Polymarket as a Sentiment Gauge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While not a crystal ball, Polymarket provides a useful barometer of market expectations. Traders and investors can combine Polymarket insights with technical and fundamental analysis for a comprehensive approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As May progresses, Bitcoin watchers can continue monitoring Polymarket&apos;s evolving probabilities to better understand where collective market sentiment might push prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Price Forecast for the End of May 2025 is Apx. $110k (... but do not take any of this as a guarantee!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what price will Bitcoin hit in May? While no method guarantees results, Polymarket’s current sentiment strongly suggests a target near $110,000. Investors are encouraged to use this insight prudently alongside broader market analysis.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU and UK said to reach outline deal to strengthen ties</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-and-uk-said-to-reach-outline-deal-to-strengthen-ties-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 05:58:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eu-and-uk-said-to-reach-outline-deal-to-strengthen-ties-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;EU and UK said to reach outline deal to strengthen ties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;EU-UK deal agreed by negotiators, needs political sign off.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EU and UK will meet today in London for the first official summit since Brexit. The meeting is to pave the way for closer ties between both sides. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-pm-starmer-expected-to-announce-brexit-reset-deal-on-monday-is-brexin-the-word-20250518/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; you can find earlier news.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *EU AND UK SAID TO REACH OUTLINE DEAL TO STRENGTHEN TIES

*EU-UK DEAL AGREED BY NEGOTIATORS, NEEDS POLITICAL SIGN OFF</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924342522437910578#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 05:53:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924342522437910578#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*EU AND UK SAID TO REACH OUTLINE DEAL TO STRENGTHEN TIES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*EU-UK DEAL AGREED BY NEGOTIATORS, NEEDS POLITICAL SIGN OFF&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US 30 year Treasury yield rises to 5% for the first time since April</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-30-year-treasury-yield-rises-to-5-for-the-first-time-since-april-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 05:26:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-30-year-treasury-yield-rises-to-5-for-the-first-time-since-april-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Everyone is talking about the Moody&apos;s downgrade and there are of course the usual doomsday-like opinions spreading. In my opinion, this is no big deal. It&apos;s more of a symbolic thing. The S&amp;amp;P Global Ratings downgraded the US in 2011 and Fitch did so in 2023. Why should we care now about Moody&apos;s downgrade?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some say that the context is different because of the deficits and the recent trade war, and I can get behind that idea, but the biggest drivers of advanced economies long term yields is future central bank policy and inflation expectations. As you can see from the chart below, long term Treasury yields have been ranging between 4% and 5% mainly because of pro-growth fiscal policies and the Fed keeping rates higher for longer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the Fed were to hike now and trigger a recession, the long term yields would drop below 4% pretty quickly and nobody would care about the Moody&apos;s downgrade. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-wants-lower-interest-rates-but-hes-strategy-is-likely-to-lead-to-higher-rates-20250512/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, there&apos;s limited downside at the moment for yields and the path of least resistance remains to the upside as inflation risk increases. In fact, as we now price in better and better conditions for growth, the economic activity will 
likely start to accelerate and that could lead to inflationary pressures. The Fed is also in a difficult position because rate cuts now could exacerbate inflation fears and drive long term yields even higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s also the thing about consumer inflation expectations continuing to increase in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/umich-may-prelim-consumer-sentiment-508-vs-534-expected-20250516/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;UMich survey&lt;/a&gt; released on Friday, which by the way, was the catalyst for the increase in yields before the Moody&apos;s downgrade. Now, one can trash the UMich survey for the political bias and so on, but the Fed hasn&apos;t met the target for almost 5 years and at some point the time factor could pose a risk for a de-anchoring of inflation expectations, so one cannot dismiss it. Better to be open-minded. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 19 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-19-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:58:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-19-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;EUR/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.1150
(EUR375mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
145.00
(US$474mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
145.55
(US$510mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;146.50 (US$1.16bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;147.00 (US$1.50bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;GBP/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3300 (GBP559mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CHF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8420 (CHF159mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.3985
(US$587mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.3675
(US$529mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6525 (AUD563mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6480 (AUD310mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6355
(AUD595mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;NZD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.5915 (NZD1.06bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Tertiary Industry Index for March 15.8% vs -0.9% prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-tertiary-industry-index-for-march-158-vs-09-prior-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:32:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-tertiary-industry-index-for-march-158-vs-09-prior-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior -0.9% (revised to -0.3%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This indicator measures the change in output in the service (tertiary) sector of the Japanese economy. It&apos;s not a market moving release.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the main events for today?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 04:17:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;It&apos;s kind of a synthetic Sunday today on the data front given the empty calendar. There&apos;s just the final Eurozone CPI reading in the European session but it won&apos;t be market moving unless we see big deviations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fed speakers will be the main highlight today. It will be interesting to hear from them about consumer inflation expectations in the UMich report which rose further despite the easing in trade tensions. At the moment, there&apos;s also some angst about the Moody&apos;s downgrade, although in my opinion it&apos;s not a big deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, it&apos;s said that Trump and Putin will speak on the phone today to push for a ceasefire and get the peace deal done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Central bank speakers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:30 GMT/08:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Bostic (hawk - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:45 GMT/08:45 ET - Fed&apos;s Williams (neutral - voter) --- the most important one&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;12:45 GMT/08:45 ET - Fed&apos;s Bostic (hawk - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;17:15 GMT/13:15 ET - Fed&apos;s Logan (neutral - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;17:30 GMT/13:30 ET - Fed&apos;s Kashkari (hawk - non voter)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays expects the ECB to cut rates by 25bp in June, September and December</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/barclays-expects-the-ecb-to-cut-rates-by-25bp-in-june-september-and-december-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/barclays-expects-the-ecb-to-cut-rates-by-25bp-in-june-september-and-december-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;European Central Bank forecast from Barclays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ECB&apos;s next monetary policy meeting is scheduled for June 5, 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market expectations suggest a high probability of another 25 basis point cut, potentially bringing the deposit rate down to 2.00%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This outlook is influenced by concerns over global trade tensions and their impact on eurozone inflation and growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Barclays suggest the June cut is on, with another 25bp cut at each of the September and December meetings. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: USD opened week lower as Moody’s US downgrade weighs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-usd-opened-week-lower-as-moodys-us-downgrade-weighs-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-usd-opened-week-lower-as-moodys-us-downgrade-weighs-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-speaks-monday-on-economic-outlook-bostic-logan-and-kashkari-speak-also-20250519/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Williams speaks Monday on economic outlook. Bostic, Logan and Kashkari speak also,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-will-strengthen-policy-coordination-20250519/&quot;&gt;China NBS spokesman (more): Will strengthen policy coordination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-foreigntradeovercamedifficulties-maintainedsteadygrowth-20250519/&quot;&gt;China NBS spokesman (more): Foreign trade overcame difficulties, maintained steady growth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-fin-min-kato-says-japan-not-facing-problem-getting-funds-via-debt-issuance-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan fin min Kato says Japan not facing problem getting funds via debt issuance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/centrist-victory-in-romania-defeats-far-right-candidate-a-democratic-signal-20250519/&quot;&gt;Centrist Victory in Romania Defeats Far-Right Candidate: A Democratic Signal?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-panel-approve-trump-tax-cut-bill-setting-up-a-possible-vote-on-passage-this-week-20250519/&quot;&gt;US House panel approve Trump tax cut bill, setting up a possible vote on passage this week&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-prime-minister-ishiba-japan-financial-situation-worse-than-greece-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan Prime Minister Ishiba: Japan financial situation worse than Greece&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-stats-spokesman-contribution-of-consumptiontoecogrowthwillcontinuetoincrease-20250519/&quot;&gt;China Stats spokesman: contribution of consumption to eco growth will continue to increase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/&quot;&gt;Chinese officials say the economy is growing steadily in the face of pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/sp-500-analysis-for-today-by-tradecompass-20250519/&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 Analysis for Today by tradeCompass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-industrial-output-april-2025-61-yy-expected-55-prior-77-20250519/&quot;&gt;China Industrial Output April 2025 +6.1% y/y (expected 5.5%, prior +7.7%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boj-depgov-uchida-will-keep-raising-interest-rates-if-economy-prices-improve-as-forecast-20250519/&quot;&gt;BOJ DepGov Uchida  Will keep raising interest rates if economy, prices improve as forecast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-new-home-prices-unchanged-mm-in-april-4-yy-20250519/&quot;&gt;China new home prices unchanged m/m in April, -4% y/y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71916-vs-estimate-at-72057-20250519/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1916 (vs. estimate at 7.2057)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-agriculture-ministry-suspended-imports-of-poultry-from-parts-of-brazil-bird-flu-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan’s Agriculture Ministry  suspended imports of poultry from parts of Brazil - bird flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-pm-ishiba-says-again-cant-accept-us-tariffs-on-autos-20250519/&quot;&gt;Japan PM Ishiba says again can&apos;t accept US tariffs on autos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/bitcoin-hitting-its-highest-since-the-end-of-january-circa-usd106400-20250519/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin hitting its highest since the end of January, circa USD106,400+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/icymi-goldman-sachs-us-tariffs-may-weaken-the-dollar-as-growth-slows-20250518/&quot;&gt;ICYMI - Goldman Sachs: US tariffs may weaken the dollar as growth slows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-house-price-indicator-shows-smallest-springtime-rise-since-2016-20250518/&quot;&gt;UK house price indicator shows smallest Springtime rise since 2016&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-q1-ppi-inputs-and-outputs-both-higher-qq-20250518/&quot;&gt;New Zealand Q1 PPI inputs and outputs both higher q/q&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-data-april-services-pmi-drops-deeper-into-contraction-at-485-prior-491-20250518/&quot;&gt;New Zealand data: April Services PMI drops deeper into contraction at 48.5 (prior 49.1)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/globex-is-open-us-equity-index-futures-drop-sp500-es-down-07-nasdaq-nq-down-09-20250518/&quot;&gt;Globex is open! US equity index futures drop. S&amp;amp;P500 (ES) down 0.7%. NASDAQ (NQ) down 0.9%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-19-may-2025-chinese-economic-activity-data-for-april-20250518/&quot;&gt;Economic calendar in Asia 19 May 2025 - Chinese economic activity data for April&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-monday-19-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250518/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Monday, 19 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/binance-and-kraken-said-to-have-been-targets-of-coinbase-like-hack-attacks-20250518/&quot;&gt;Binance and Kraken said to have been targets of Coinbase-like hack attacks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/monday-morning-forex-rates-update-jpy-and-eur-higher-20250518/&quot;&gt;Monday morning forex rates update - JPY and EUR higher&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/romanian-centrist-presidential-candidate-ahead-with-543-after-97-of-votes-counted-20250518/&quot;&gt;Romanian centrist Presidential candidate ahead with 54.3% after 97% of votes counted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/weekend-bessent-threatens-tariff-rates-to-return-to-reciprocal-levels-if-no-trade-deal-20250518/&quot;&gt;Weekend: Bessent threatens tariff rates to return to ‘reciprocal’ levels if no trade deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/former-president-joe-biden-was-diagnosed-with-an-aggressive-form-of-prostate-cancer-20250518/&quot;&gt;Former President Joe Biden was diagnosed with an &quot;aggressive form&quot; of prostate cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eyes-on-euro-politics-romania-centrist-dan-appears-on-course-to-win-romanian-presidency-20250518/&quot;&gt;Eyes on Euro politics - Romania centrist Dan appears on course to win Romanian presidency&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/monday-open-levels-indicative-fx-prices-19-may-2025-20250518/&quot;&gt;Monday open levels, indicative FX prices, 19 May 2025&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weekend:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-weekend-news-hasnt-been-great-for-market-confidence-20250518/&quot;&gt;The weekend news hasn&apos;t been great for market confidence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-pm-starmer-expected-to-announce-brexit-reset-deal-on-monday-is-brexin-the-word-20250518/&quot;&gt;UK PM Starmer expected to announce Brexit ­&quot;reset&quot; deal on Monday. (Is Brexin the word?)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-pm-albanese-says-hes-up-for-a-deal-with-europe-on-free-trade-20250518/&quot;&gt;Australian PM Albanese says he&apos;s &quot;up for a deal&quot; with Europe on free trade&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-lagardeeurusd-up-justified-by-the-uncertainty-loss-of-confidence-in-us-policies-20250518/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Lagarde:EUR/USD up justified by the uncertainty &amp;amp; loss of confidence in US policies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-central-bank-board-member-schnabel-cautious-on-a-june-ecb-rate-cut-20250517/&quot;&gt;European Central Bank Board Member Schnabel cautious on a June ECB rate cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-kazaks-rate-cuts-may-be-nearing-end-but-outlook-still-uncertain-20250517/&quot;&gt;ECB’s Kazaks: Rate cuts may be nearing end, but outlook still uncertain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/newsquawk-week-ahead-uk-eu-summit-rba-china-activity-data-global-pmi-data-canada-cpi-20250517/&quot;&gt;Newsquawk Week Ahead: UK-EU Summit, RBA, China Activity Data, Global PMI Data, Canada CPI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/friday-bombshell-moodys-downgrades-the-us-credit-rating-20250516/&quot;&gt;Friday bombshell: Moody&apos;s downgrades US credit rating&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-hot-umich-inflation-expectations-cool-fed-rate-cut-talk-20250516/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Hot UMich inflation expectations cool Fed rate cut talk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;225&quot; data-end=&quot;450&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Markets reopened for the new week digesting the late-Friday US credit rating downgrade by Moody’s. The agency announced the move after US markets had closed, a decision some have called oddly timed—perhaps even irresponsible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;452&quot; data-end=&quot;867&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Opening FX trade saw a generally weaker US dollar, with the most notable move in USD/JPY, which fell more than 60 points from Friday’s close. EUR/USD also edged higher, with gains extending after Romania’s presidential election results came in. Pro-EU and pro-NATO candidate Dan won, defeating a far-right challenger. The outcome was interpreted as a win for EU political stability, lending the euro a modest boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;869&quot; data-end=&quot;970&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;As the session wore on, the dollar continued to soften a touch, the move was far from a rout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;972&quot; data-end=&quot;1108&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;US equity index futures gapped lower on the Globex open, as did US Treasury futures. As of writing, equity futures have slipped further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1110&quot; data-end=&quot;1163&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;China&apos;s April data was the key focus for the session:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1165&quot; data-end=&quot;1477&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1165&quot; data-end=&quot;1236&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1167&quot; data-end=&quot;1236&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Industrial output rose 6.1% y/y (vs. 5.5% expected, prior 7.7%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1237&quot; data-end=&quot;1303&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1239&quot; data-end=&quot;1303&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Retail sales grew 5.1% y/y (vs. 5.5% expected, prior 5.9%)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1304&quot; data-end=&quot;1380&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1306&quot; data-end=&quot;1380&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Fixed asset investment was up 4.0% YTD (vs. 4.2% expected and prior)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1381&quot; data-end=&quot;1444&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1383&quot; data-end=&quot;1444&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Surveyed jobless rate dipped to 5.1% from 5.2% in March&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1445&quot; data-end=&quot;1477&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1447&quot; data-end=&quot;1477&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;House prices remained soft&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1479&quot; data-end=&quot;1772&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Overall, the data were mixed. Industrial activity held up well, even as signs of weaker consumption and ongoing deflationary pressures linger. Trump’s tariffs have yet to cause significant damage, though slowing exports and falling bank lending suggest headwinds are mounting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1774&quot; data-end=&quot;2158&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In Japan, Prime Minister Ishiba ruled out tax cuts funded by new debt, acknowledging that with market interest rates now positive, the country’s fiscal health is &quot;worse than Greece.&quot; Finance Minister Kato added that Japan is not facing problems issuing debt but warned that a loss of market trust could weaken the yen and trigger inflationary stress. JPY barely moved on the comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2160&quot; data-end=&quot;2468&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In the US, a House committee narrowly advanced President Trump’s tax cut package in a 17–16 vote on Sunday evening. Interestingly, four GOP “hardliners” who had opposed it earlier shifted their &quot;no&quot; stance to “present.” Hardliners? That label seems generous if they caved so easily—perhaps just political theatre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2470&quot; data-end=&quot;2546&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin has continued its ascent, climbing to fresh highs above USD 106,500.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former US President Joe Biden has been diagnosed with an &apos;aggressive form&apos; of prostate cancer that has metastasized to the bone, his office said in a statement, adding that &apos;the cancer appears to be hormone-sensitive which allows for effective management&apos; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We wish him well. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Williams speaks Monday on economic outlook. Bostic, Logan and Kashkari speak also,</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-speaks-monday-on-economic-outlook-bostic-logan-and-kashkari-speak-also-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:35:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-williams-speaks-monday-on-economic-outlook-bostic-logan-and-kashkari-speak-also-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The times listed below are GMT/US Eastern time:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1230/0830		Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic gives welcome remarks before the 2025 Financial Markets Conference - &quot;Financial Intermediation In Transition: How Will Policy Adapt?&quot; hosted by the Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1245/0845		Federal Reserve Bank of New York President John Williams speaks on the economic outlook before the Mortgage Bankers Association Secondary and Capital Markets Conference, in New York&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1245/0845		Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic moderates a discussion before the 2025 Financial Markets Conference - &quot;Financial Intermediation In Transition: How Will Policy Adapt?&quot; hosted by the Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1715/1315	 Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas President Lorie Logan is a panel moderator at the &quot;Policy Session 2: The Increasing Role of Nonbank Institutions in the Treasury and Money Markets&quot; before the 2025 Financial Markets Conference&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1730/1330		Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis President Neel Kashkari participates in conversation before the Minnesota Young American Leaders Program (MYALP) at the University of Minnesota, in Minneapolis, Minn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Williams speech would seem the most pertinent for traders. Doubly so as Williams, being NY Fed chief, has a permanent vote on the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC), and indeed is vice-chair of the committee. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China NBS spokesman (more): Will strengthen policy coordination</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-will-strengthen-policy-coordination-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 03:11:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-will-strengthen-policy-coordination-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;China National Bureau of Statistics (NBS) spokesman:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability of foreign trade enterprises to develop market has increased, have strong adjustment capabilities during trade friction and fluctuations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China has the conditions, ability and confidence to deal with various challenges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Necessary to see that the current overall low prices will increase the pressure on enterprises and affect the income growth of residents&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Structural contradiction of employment is still prominent, and employment pressure on youth group is great.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will strengthen policy coordination and promote urban renewal and affordable housing construction, for stable and healthy development of real estate market&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-foreigntradeovercamedifficulties-maintainedsteadygrowth-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China NBS spokesman (more): Foreign trade overcame difficulties, maintained steady growth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-stats-spokesman-contribution-of-consumptiontoecogrowthwillcontinuetoincrease-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;China Stats spokesman: contribution of consumption to eco growth will continue to increase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-industrial-output-april-2025-61-yy-expected-55-prior-77-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;China Industrial Output April 2025 +6.1% y/y (expected 5.5%, prior +7.7%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link&quot;&gt;Chinese officials say the economy is growing steadily in the face of pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China NBS spokesman (more): Foreign trade overcame difficulties, maintained steady growth</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-foreigntradeovercamedifficulties-maintainedsteadygrowth-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:45:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-nbs-spokesman-more-foreigntradeovercamedifficulties-maintainedsteadygrowth-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt; China National Bureau of Statistics (NBS) spokesman:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We need to recognize that the internal driving force for investment growth is ‘obviously insufficient’&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We need to improve the efficiency of investment and continue to optimize the structure of investment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Foreign trade overcame difficulties and maintained steady growth in April, demonstrated strong resilience and international competitiveness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The reduction of tariffs by China and the United States in the next stage is conducive to the growth of bilateral trade and the recovery of the world economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Against increased external shocks, China’s foreign trade has been able to withstand pressure and continue to grow &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article-slot__title title top&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-stats-spokesman-contribution-of-consumptiontoecogrowthwillcontinuetoincrease-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;China Stats spokesman: contribution of consumption to eco growth will continue to increase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-industrial-output-april-2025-61-yy-expected-55-prior-77-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;China Industrial Output April 2025 +6.1% y/y (expected 5.5%, prior +7.7%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Chinese officials say the economy is growing steadily in the face of pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan fin min Kato says Japan not facing problem getting funds via debt issuance</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-fin-min-kato-says-japan-not-facing-problem-getting-funds-via-debt-issuance-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-fin-min-kato-says-japan-not-facing-problem-getting-funds-via-debt-issuance-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan finance minister Kato:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan not facing problem procuring funds from market via debt issuance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If Japan loses market trust in its finances, it may face rise in interest rates that could affect debt redemption&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Losing market trust in Japan’s finances could trigger weak yen, excessive inflation that would have severe impact on economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY has not moved too much on these comments from Kato. At face value Kato&apos;s assurances are fine. But, in answering such questions its indicative of concerns rising over Japan&apos;s fiscal troubles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PM Ishiba remarks also, a bit of a worry this!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-prime-minister-ishiba-japan-financial-situation-worse-than-greece-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan Prime Minister Ishiba: Japan financial situation worse than Greece&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrist Victory in Romania Defeats Far-Right Candidate: A Democratic Signal?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/centrist-victory-in-romania-defeats-far-right-candidate-a-democratic-signal-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:42:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/centrist-victory-in-romania-defeats-far-right-candidate-a-democratic-signal-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;138&quot; data-end=&quot;224&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Centrist Victory in Romania: A Democratic Signal Amid Europe’s Rightward Drift&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;226&quot; data-end=&quot;278&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Global News Update – Romania Presidential Runoff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;280&quot; data-end=&quot;708&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Independent centrist and Bucharest mayor Dikurser Dan has defeated far-right candidate George Simeon in Romania’s presidential runoff, securing over 54% of the vote. This win came amid the highest voter turnout in 25 years, showing a rare moment of political engagement in the region. Simeon, known for nationalist rhetoric and anti-EU sentiment, was viewed by many as part of the wider European far-right surge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;710&quot; data-end=&quot;986&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;This result may act as a political counterweight to recent developments in Europe, where populist and far-right parties have gained traction (e.g., the Netherlands, France, Germany). Romania&apos;s election instead showcased a public defense of centrist, pro-democratic values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;993&quot; data-end=&quot;1030&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Interpretation for Investors:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1032&quot; data-end=&quot;1948&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1032&quot; data-end=&quot;1196&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1034&quot; data-end=&quot;1196&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Investor Confidence: While Romania is not a major global market mover, the election result adds a marginal boost to political stability in Eastern Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1197&quot; data-end=&quot;1448&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1199&quot; data-end=&quot;1448&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Broader Sentiment: The outcome may soften the perceived momentum of far-right forces in Europe. That’s mildly reassuring for risk sentiment in European markets, especially as the region approaches the 2025 EU Parliamentary elections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1449&quot; data-end=&quot;1638&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1451&quot; data-end=&quot;1638&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Euro Stock Market Reaction? Likely neutral to slightly supportive. The result affirms continued EU alignment from Romania, avoiding friction or fragmentation narratives that can weigh on the euro. The European stock market should be more influenced by what the US stock market futures are doing today. You are welcome to check our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/sp-500-analysis-for-today-by-tradecompass-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 analysis for today with tradeCompass by ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt; (evolving to become &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investinglive.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;investingLive.com&lt;/a&gt; later this year).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1639&quot; data-end=&quot;1948&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1641&quot; data-end=&quot;1948&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Equities Outlook: No direct significant impact is expected from the Romanian Centerist win, but contributes to a mosaic of global stability, which—when paired with dovish central banks or easing inflation—can enhance risk-on appetite in equities. But on its own, this is a low-signal event unless further shifts occur in Central or Eastern Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1955&quot; data-end=&quot;2368&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bottom Line for Traders:
This election result is more symbolic than catalytic. It does not directly move markets, but it’s worth noting for those watching political risk in Europe. The key takeaway is that voters pushed back against extremism, suggesting that centrism still holds resilience—a theme that may calm some nerves among global investors tracking political volatility across the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2370&quot; data-end=&quot;2470&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Stay tuned for any ripple effects in the eurozone narrative as we head into summer political cycles.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House panel approve Trump tax cut bill, setting up a possible vote on passage this week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-panel-approve-trump-tax-cut-bill-setting-up-a-possible-vote-on-passage-this-week-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:42:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-panel-approve-trump-tax-cut-bill-setting-up-a-possible-vote-on-passage-this-week-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;US House panel approve Trump tax cut bill, setting up a possible vote on passage this week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note, this isn&apos;t the vote, that&apos;s yet to come as the headline says. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Prime Minister Ishiba: Japan financial situation worse than Greece</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-prime-minister-ishiba-japan-financial-situation-worse-than-greece-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:39:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-prime-minister-ishiba-japan-financial-situation-worse-than-greece-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Ishiba drops a big comment!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan financial situation worse than Greece&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Against funding tax cuts with JGBs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY update, not a lot moved on the &apos;worse than Greece&apos; remark:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Stats spokesman: contribution of consumption to eco growth will continue to increase</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-stats-spokesman-contribution-of-consumptiontoecogrowthwillcontinuetoincrease-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:34:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-stats-spokesman-contribution-of-consumptiontoecogrowthwillcontinuetoincrease-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;International environment now still complex and severe, domestic cyclical and structural contradictions are intertwined&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;But there are many favorable conditions for sustained economic recovery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Although external impact increased in April, the trend of economic recovery did not change&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gradual implementation of policies will be conducive to the sustained recovery and improvement of the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As the effect of policies continues to show, contribution from consumption to economic growth will continue to increase&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-industrial-output-april-2025-61-yy-expected-55-prior-77-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China Industrial Output April 2025 +6.1% y/y (expected 5.5%, prior +7.7%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Chinese officials say the economy is growing steadily in the face of pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese officials say the economy is growing steadily in the face of pressure</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:14:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/chinese-officials-say-the-economy-is-growing-steadily-in-the-face-of-pressure-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Comments from an official at China&apos;s National Bureau of Statistics (NBS) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Productivity demand grew steadily&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;employment situation generally stable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;economy grew steadily in face of pressure, continues developing in an upward trend&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China actively diversifying, expanding trade with Belt and Road initiative nations &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The comments follow the April economic data release, a mixed bag:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-industrial-output-april-2025-61-yy-expected-55-prior-77-20250519/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;China Industrial Output April 2025 +6.1% y/y (expected 5.5%, prior +7.7%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an aside, from the data something that might interest oil traders:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China’s April apparent oil demand falls 5.6% y/y&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 Analysis for Today by tradeCompass</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/sp-500-analysis-for-today-by-tradecompass-20250519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/sp-500-analysis-for-today-by-tradecompass-20250519/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;114&quot; data-end=&quot;178&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 E-mini Futures Analysis for Today – May 19, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;180&quot; data-end=&quot;259&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Current Price: 5931.00
Change from Friday Close: Approximately -0.75%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;261&quot; data-end=&quot;604&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;At the time of this analysis, S&amp;amp;P 500 E-mini futures (ES) are already trading below a critical bearish threshold, as defined by today’s tradeCompass. Price action under 5947.0 confirms we are currently in bearish territory, with 5944.5 aligning precisely with Thursday’s Value Area High — reinforcing the downward bias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;611&quot; data-end=&quot;656&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bearish Bias &amp;amp; tradeCompass Threshold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;658&quot; data-end=&quot;948&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;658&quot; data-end=&quot;711&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;660&quot; data-end=&quot;711&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bearish threshold: Any price below 5947.0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;712&quot; data-end=&quot;796&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;714&quot; data-end=&quot;796&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;We are now trading below that level, meaning bearish setups are in play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;797&quot; data-end=&quot;948&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;799&quot; data-end=&quot;948&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Short Entry Zone: Around 5933–5934, where today’s VWAP sits — offering a practical entry point for short trades depending on your method.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;955&quot; data-end=&quot;988&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bearish Targets for Today for S&amp;amp;P 500 Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;990&quot; data-end=&quot;1116&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;These downside targets are derived from volume profile and VWAP zones — key liquidity levels that attract institutional flows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-start=&quot;1118&quot; data-end=&quot;1364&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1118&quot; data-end=&quot;1164&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1121&quot; data-end=&quot;1164&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5916.0 – Just above Friday’s VWAP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1165&quot; data-end=&quot;1208&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1168&quot; data-end=&quot;1208&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5908.5 – Just above May 14 POC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1209&quot; data-end=&quot;1277&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1212&quot; data-end=&quot;1277&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5900.0 – Psychological round number &amp;amp; near Friday’s VAL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1278&quot; data-end=&quot;1321&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1281&quot; data-end=&quot;1321&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5864.0 – Just above May 12 VAH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1322&quot; data-end=&quot;1364&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1325&quot; data-end=&quot;1364&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5838.0 – Just above May 12 VWAP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1366&quot; data-end=&quot;1527&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Use these as partial profit targets — a core tradeCompass tactic to help you lock in gains progressively rather than aiming for a single, uncertain exit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1534&quot; data-end=&quot;1773&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;📣 Rebranding Note: ForexLive.com will be evolving to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investinglive.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;investingLive.com&lt;/a&gt; later this year, bringing investors and traders more decision support tools, advanced analysis, real-time news, and enhanced platform features we’re rolling out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1780&quot; data-end=&quot;1823&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bullish Threshold &amp;amp; Reversal Levels for S&amp;amp;P 500 Futures Today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1825&quot; data-end=&quot;1990&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;If the market reverses and breaks above 5953.5 (above Friday’s VWAP), this would invalidate the current bearish map. In that case, potential bullish targets are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-start=&quot;1992&quot; data-end=&quot;2203&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1992&quot; data-end=&quot;2046&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1995&quot; data-end=&quot;2046&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5966.0 – 1st upper VWAP deviation from Friday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2047&quot; data-end=&quot;2092&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2050&quot; data-end=&quot;2092&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5974.0 – Just below Friday’s POC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2093&quot; data-end=&quot;2127&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2096&quot; data-end=&quot;2127&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5977.0 – Friday’s VAH&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2128&quot; data-end=&quot;2203&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2131&quot; data-end=&quot;2203&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;5994.0 – Just under the 6000 round number and 3rd VWAP deviation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2205&quot; data-end=&quot;2335&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;These targets, while not far apart, represent real liquidity pools where large participants may act — not random price points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2342&quot; data-end=&quot;2387&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For Stock Market Swing Traders &amp;amp; Portfolio Viewers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2389&quot; data-end=&quot;2636&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;You don’t need to trade ES futures directly to benefit. If the market reaches 5838 and bounces, it could signal that the selloff has hit exhaustion — offering a potential setup or timing clue for equity portfolios or correlated assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2638&quot; data-end=&quot;2685&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Look for how price behaves at that level:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;2686&quot; data-end=&quot;2807&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2686&quot; data-end=&quot;2740&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2688&quot; data-end=&quot;2740&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Reversal: May hint at buyer strength returning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;2741&quot; data-end=&quot;2807&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2743&quot; data-end=&quot;2807&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Failure or stall: Suggests further downside remains possible&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2814&quot; data-end=&quot;2855&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Final Note: Your S&amp;amp;P 500 Map for Today, Your Method&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2857&quot; data-end=&quot;3114&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;tradeCompass provides the map, but your entries, stops, and size are up to your system. This tool supports multiple styles — day traders, swing traders, or macro observers — by pinpointing where institutional moves are more likely to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3116&quot; data-end=&quot;3180&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Use it as a decision support layer, not a prediction engine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;3187&quot; data-end=&quot;3276&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Stay sharp. Trade with confidence. Trade at your own risk only.
— tradeCompass, powered by investingLive.com&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BIDEN DIAGNOSED WITH PROSTATE CANCER- STATEMENT FROM HIS OFFICE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924197777413697694#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 20:17:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924197777413697694#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BIDEN DIAGNOSED WITH PROSTATE CANCER- STATEMENT FROM HIS OFFICE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ROMANIAN CENTRIST CANDIDATE DAN IN FIRST PLACE WITH 53.68%, HARD RIGHT SIMION IN SECOND PLACE AFTER 90% OF VOTES COUNTED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924185830467231844#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 19:30:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924185830467231844#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ROMANIAN CENTRIST CANDIDATE DAN IN FIRST PLACE WITH 53.68%, HARD RIGHT SIMION IN SECOND PLACE AFTER 90% OF VOTES COUNTED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ROMANIAN HARD RIGHT CANDIDATE SIMION IN FIRST PLACE, CENTRIST DAN IN SECOND PLACE AFTER 30% OF VOTES COUNTED</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924172395192926329#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 18:37:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924172395192926329#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ROMANIAN HARD RIGHT CANDIDATE SIMION IN FIRST PLACE, CENTRIST DAN IN SECOND PLACE AFTER 30% OF VOTES COUNTED&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT PLANS TO ATTEND G7 FINANCE MINISTERS, CENTRAL BANK GOVERNORS MEETING IN CANADA MAY 20-22 -TREASURY SPOKESPERSON</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924135942287220909#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 16:12:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924135942287220909#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT PLANS TO ATTEND G7 FINANCE MINISTERS, CENTRAL BANK GOVERNORS MEETING IN CANADA MAY 20-22 -TREASURY SPOKESPERSON&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE SAYS EUROPE IS AN IMPORTANT ALLY OF USA, BUT WE HAVE DISAGREEMENTS ON TRADE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924100406935695676#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:50:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924100406935695676#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. VICE PRESIDENT VANCE SAYS EUROPE IS AN IMPORTANT ALLY OF USA, BUT WE HAVE DISAGREEMENTS ON TRADE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. TREASURY SECRETARY BESSENT: IF COUNTRIES ARE NOT NEGOTIATING IN GOOD FAITH, THEY WILL GET A LETTER WITH U.S. TARIFF RATE -NBC INTERVIEW

U.S. TREASURY SECRETARY BESSENT: I THINK THAT RATE WOULD BE THE APRIL 2 LEVEL -NBC</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924096662852497649#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:36:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924096662852497649#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. TREASURY SECRETARY BESSENT: IF COUNTRIES ARE NOT NEGOTIATING IN GOOD FAITH, THEY WILL GET A LETTER WITH U.S. TARIFF RATE -NBC INTERVIEW&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
U.S. TREASURY SECRETARY BESSENT: I THINK THAT RATE WOULD BE THE APRIL 2 LEVEL -NBC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT, AFTER CALL WITH WALMART CEO: WALMART IS GOING TO &apos;EAT&apos; SOME OF THE TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924096418924347563#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:35:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924096418924347563#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT, AFTER CALL WITH WALMART CEO: WALMART IS GOING TO &apos;EAT&apos; SOME OF THE TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: WE ARE DETERMINED TO BRING SPENDING DOWN, GROW U.S. ECONOMY -NBC INTERVIEW</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924096317678100640#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:34:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924096317678100640#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: WE ARE DETERMINED TO BRING SPENDING DOWN, GROW U.S. ECONOMY -NBC INTERVIEW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT ON WALMART AND TARIFFS: DID SPEAK WITH WALMART CEO ON SATURDAY -CNN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924096149507506199#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:34:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924096149507506199#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT ON WALMART AND TARIFFS: DID SPEAK WITH WALMART CEO ON SATURDAY -CNN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BESSENT: THINK WE WILL DO A LOT OF REGIONAL DEALS -CNN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924096031911801187#m</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:33:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924096031911801187#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BESSENT: THINK WE WILL DO A LOT OF REGIONAL DEALS -CNN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
