<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>The gold bulls are fighting back today, but it&apos;s uphill</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-gold-bulls-are-fighting-back-today-but-its-uphill-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-gold-bulls-are-fighting-back-today-but-its-uphill-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Gold is up $40 today to $3219 in an impressive $110 intraday turnaround after falling as low as $3120 in Asia-Pacific trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a growing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-losing-its-appetite-to-fund-us-twin-deficits-deutsche-bank-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;conversation &lt;/a&gt;about US fiscal sustainability and its erratic trade war. Trade tensions have fallen and gold has fallen at the same time but we&apos;re still not clear on where the end goal is or how to get there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only trade deal so far is between the US and UK. It was a win for the US but trade between the military allies is surprisingly small and limited, with the major categories of trade getting exemptions. Will other countries offer anything in order to get 10% tariff rates in the US?  That&apos;s hard to believe until we see it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With that, the fear (and what&apos;s boosting gold) is the possibility that we&apos;re just in an ebb in trade negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe the bigger question is how all these events are seen abroad. Certainly, this is at least a nudge towards some level of de-dollarization or de-integration. Trust in US trade and military treaties is certainly stretched.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, we&apos;re watching the US fiscal package unfold and it looks like there won&apos;t be much austerity, with +6% deficits-to-GDP ratios forever.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $NVDA - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $COIN - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt; - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The market is losing its appetite to fund US twin deficits - Deutsche Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-losing-its-appetite-to-fund-us-twin-deficits-deutsche-bank-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-losing-its-appetite-to-fund-us-twin-deficits-deutsche-bank-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;George Saravelos is Global Head of FX Research at
Deutsche Bank is out with a striking note today, highlighting the problems with the US dollar, deficits and government policy. The note certainly resonates with US 30-year yields touching off 5% today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He highlights the emerging consensus around the fiscal budget bill that&apos;s working its way though Congress and the growing likelihood of higher deficits. That&apos;s working against the White House&apos;s stated aim of lowering the trade deficit because it gooses consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They see the current account deficit continuing to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The significance of
this conclusion cannot be over-estimated. We have been arguing over the last
few months that the market is reducing its willingness to fund US twin deficits,&quot; Saravelos writes. &quot;We worry this is
brewing a major problem for the dollar and potentially the US bond market too.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding to the vulnerability is a backdrop of larger foreign ownership of US assets and &quot;extreme&quot; valuation of dollar-denominated assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s tough to call a tipping point in this relationship but at some point the US will face a reckoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;For foreigners to
continue financing US debt one thing needs to happen: the non-dollar price of
US Treasuries needs to decline, either via currency depreciation or a drop in
the price of the bonds. The problem for the latter is that it makes US debt
dynamics even worse so is not sustainable. We are ultimately left with the only
solution to this problem being dollar weakness.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saravelos believes this is already unfolding as inflows to the US are slowing and that there is an emerging breakdown in the dynamic between USD/JPY and yields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;To sum it all up, as Secretary Bessent alluded to
himself, the US cannot be asking of the rest of the world to reduce its
imbalance with America if the US is not willing to reduce its own. The risk is
the rest of the world forces the correction upon the US in a disorderly way.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada&apos;s S&amp;P/TSX index rises to a new record high</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/canadas-sptsx-index-rises-to-a-new-record-high-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:05:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/canadas-sptsx-index-rises-to-a-new-record-high-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Canada&apos;s S&amp;amp;P TSX stuck in the city is stretching to a new all-time high. The high price today reach two 589.46. The current prices at 25882.41 of 190 points or 0.74% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new high extended above the prior hi going back to June January 30 at 25875.61. The high price for the index was reached on January 30 at 25808.25.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The index moved down -14.10% from its January high. That move to the downside retraced around 50% midpoint of the move up from the October 2023 low price, before starting the bounce back to the new highs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the trading year, the index is up 4.69% after rising 17.99% in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the US major indices are now positive on the day:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average is up 215 points or 0.51% at 42266.78&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index is up 28.23 points or 0.48% at 5921. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index is up 44.47 points or 0.23% in 19191.71&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the 2025 trading year, the Dow and NASDAQ indices are still negative, but the S&amp;amp;P is now positive for 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average -0.70%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index +0.65%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index -0.63%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2024 the:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average rose 12.88%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index rose 23.31%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index rose 28.64%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade

🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:54:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) UAE PRESIDENT SAYS UAE TO INVEST $1.4T IN U.S OVER NEXT 10 YEARS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923058732037972351#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:51:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923058732037972351#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UAE PRESIDENT SAYS UAE TO INVEST $1.4T IN U.S OVER NEXT 10 YEARS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ATLANTA FED GDPNOW MAY 15: 2.5% (PREV 2.3%)</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923057857517216056#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:48:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923057857517216056#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ATLANTA FED GDPNOW MAY 15: 2.5% (PREV 2.3%)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed GDPNow Q2 rises to 2.5% from 2.3% prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-q2-rises-to-25-from-23-prior-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:48:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-q2-rises-to-25-from-23-prior-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Q2 estimate for GDP from the Atlanta Fed is up to 2.5% from 2.3% on May 8. In their own words: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The GDPNow model estimate for real GDP growth (seasonally adjusted annual rate) in the second quarter of 2025 is 2.5 percent on May 15, up from 2.3 percent on May 8. After recent releases from the US Census Bureau, the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, and the Federal Reserve Board of Governors, the nowcasts of second-quarter real personal consumption expenditures growth and second-quarter real gross private domestic investment growth increased from 3.3 percent and 1.2 percent, respectively, to 3.7 percent and 1.5 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next GDPNow update is Friday, May 16. Please see the &quot;Release Dates&quot; tab below for a list of upcoming releases.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHATGPT NOW HAS MORE MONTHLY USERS THAN WIKIPEDIA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923054809801687353#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:36:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923054809801687353#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHATGPT NOW HAS MORE MONTHLY USERS THAN WIKIPEDIA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qatar wealth fund plans to invest $500B in US over the next 10 years</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/qatar-wealth-fund-plans-to-invest-500b-in-us-over-the-next-10-years-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:25:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/qatar-wealth-fund-plans-to-invest-500b-in-us-over-the-next-10-years-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Qatar wealth fund plans to invest $500B in US over the next 10 years.  This is according to Bloomberg.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the week, during talks in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia pledged a historic $600 billion in future investments across U.S. energy, technology, defense, and infrastructure sectors, a commitment announced jointly by the White House and Saudi leadership. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complementing that headline figure, Saudi Aramco also signed 34 preliminary agreements with American companies valued at up to $90 billion, underscoring the kingdom’s push to deepen commercial ties with the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FBI SAYS MALICIOUS ACTORS ARE USING TEXT MESSAGES AND AI-GENERATED VOICE MESSAGES TO IMPERSONATE SENIOR US OFFICIALS TO TARGET OTHER STATE AND FEDERAL GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923051177366651003#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:21:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923051177366651003#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FBI SAYS MALICIOUS ACTORS ARE USING TEXT MESSAGES AND AI-GENERATED VOICE MESSAGES TO IMPERSONATE SENIOR US OFFICIALS TO TARGET OTHER STATE AND FEDERAL GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freddie Mac 30 year mortgage rate 6.81% up from 6.76% last week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/freddie-mac-30-year-mortgage-rate-681-up-from-676-last-week-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:18:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/freddie-mac-30-year-mortgage-rate-681-up-from-676-last-week-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Freddie Mac 30 year mortgage rate for the current week rises to 6.81% from 6.76%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;633&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;U.S. housing data continue to paint a mixed picture. New‑home sales rose solidly in March, climbing to a seasonally‑adjusted annual rate (SAAR) of 724 000 units, a 7.4 % jump from February and 6 % above year‑earlier levels. Builders are attracting buyers with incentives: the median price of a newly built home slipped to $403 600, down 7.5 % from a year earlier, while inventory edged up to 503 000 units (an 8.3‑month supply). These figures suggest that new construction remains the brightest spot in residential real estate as builders fill the gap left by a thin resale market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;635&quot; data-end=&quot;1088&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Meanwhile, the existing‑home market remains subdued. March resale transactions fell 5.9 % on the month to an annual pace of 4.02 million—2.4 % below the same period last year—confirming that high borrowing costs and limited listings continue to dampen turnover. Yet tight supply is supporting prices: the median existing‑home price reached $403 700, up 2.7 % year on year and the highest ever recorded for March. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1090&quot; data-end=&quot;1680&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Financing conditions are steady but still historically expensive. Freddie Mac’s latest Primary Mortgage Market Survey shows the 30‑year fixed rate at 6.81 % (week ended 15 May), up modestly from 6.76 % the prior week. Rates have hovered in a 6.7 – 6.9 % corridor for nearly four months and sit roughly 30 basis points below the level of a year ago. That range has been tight enough to limit refinancing but stable enough to coax some buyers off the sidelines—purchase‑application volume is running about 18 % above last year’s depressed levels.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *CANADA&apos;S S&amp;P/TSX COMPOSITE INDEX RISES 0.7% TO HIT RECORD</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923050320579420378#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:18:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923050320579420378#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*CANADA&apos;S S&amp;amp;P/TSX COMPOSITE INDEX RISES 0.7% TO HIT RECORD&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *SPEAKER JOHNSON: STILL ON PATH TO PASS TRUMP TAX BILL NEXT WEEK</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923050035781959995#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:17:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923050035781959995#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*SPEAKER JOHNSON: STILL ON PATH TO PASS TRUMP TAX BILL NEXT WEEK&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *QATAR WEALTH FUND PLANS TO INVEST $500 BLN IN US OVER 10 YEARS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923049930102276156#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:16:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923049930102276156#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*QATAR WEALTH FUND PLANS TO INVEST $500 BLN IN US OVER 10 YEARS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major European indices close higher on the day</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/major-european-indices-close-higher-on-the-day-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/major-european-indices-close-higher-on-the-day-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;2&quot; data-end=&quot;29&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The major European indices are closing the session with gains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The German DAX is closing at a new record high level of 23680.03.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Spain&apos;s Ibex April 2008. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB closed at its highest level going back to 2007&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A snapshot of the closing levels shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX (Germany): +0.65%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;30&quot; data-end=&quot;59&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;32&quot; data-end=&quot;59&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;UK&apos;s FTSE 100 (UK): +0.57%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;60&quot; data-end=&quot;91&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;62&quot; data-end=&quot;91&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;France CAC 40 (France): +0.21%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;92&quot; data-end=&quot;132&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;94&quot; data-end=&quot;132&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Euro Stoxx 50 (Eurozone): +0.12%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;133&quot; data-end=&quot;166&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;135&quot; data-end=&quot;166&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Spain&apos;s IBEX 35 (Spain): +0.65%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;199&quot; data-end=&quot;231&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;201&quot; data-end=&quot;231&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Italy FTSE MIB (Italy): +0.15%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BYD ESTABLISHES EUROPEAN HEADQUARTERS IN HUNGARY: WANG CHUAN-FU</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923037317343687136#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:26:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923037317343687136#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BYD ESTABLISHES EUROPEAN HEADQUARTERS IN HUNGARY: WANG CHUAN-FU&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NZDUSD testing 200-bar MA on 4-hour chart and swing area down ot 0.5852 area</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nzdusd-testing-200-bar-ma-on-4-hour-chart-and-swing-area-down-ot-05852-area-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:20:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nzdusd-testing-200-bar-ma-on-4-hour-chart-and-swing-area-down-ot-05852-area-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;200&quot; data-end=&quot;536&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The NZDUSD continues to trade within a broad sideways range, with buyers and sellers battling around key technical levels. Earlier this week, buyers made an attempt to push the pair above the 100-bar MA on the 4-hour chart, but the move stalled and ultimately failed. That MA, currently near 0.5939, now serves as a topside target and high of of a cluster of MAs that would need to be broken, for the buyers to take back more control.  Included in that cluster are the:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;200 day MA at 0.5882&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;100 hour MA at 0.59036&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;200 hour MA at 0.5930, and&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;100 bar MA on 4-hour chart at 0.59399&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;538&quot; data-end=&quot;825&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, the price is now testing the 200 bar MA at 0.5863, on the 4-hour chart between 0.5852 to 0.5860. Earlier this week, sellers briefly pushed the pair below the swing area between 0.5852 and 0.5860, but the rising 200-bar MA on the 4-hour chart (currently at 0.5863 but lower earlier this week) helped attract dip buyers. The price bounced off that area, confirming it as a critical support zone in the current range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;975&quot; data-end=&quot;1257&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;As long as NZDUSD remains trapped between the cluster of MAs and well-defined horizontal levels, short-term momentum will hinge on breakouts. A move back above the series of MA peaking at 0.5939 would revive upside potential, while a break below 0.5863 and then 0.5852 (and staying below) would shift the bias more firmly to the downside.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks rebound from lows for the day</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-rebound-from-lows-for-the-day-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:09:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-rebound-from-lows-for-the-day-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The major US stock indices are recovering from Lowe&apos;s. The S&amp;amp;P index is now down around -5 points or -0.08% at 5888. The low price reached 5865.16 down -27.42 point at session lows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NASDAQ index is still down -92 points are -0.49% at 19053. But reached a low of 18967.78 down -179 point at session lows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Dow industrial average as down nine points or -0.02% at 42042.06. At session lows the index was down -267.02 points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although indices are still down, the levels are sharply off the intraday lows.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The road ahead for the consumer is going to be rough - CIBC</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-road-ahead-for-the-consumer-is-going-to-be-rough-cibc-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-road-ahead-for-the-consumer-is-going-to-be-rough-cibc-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;CIBC is out with a note on today&apos;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-retail-sales-01-vs-00-expected-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US retail sales report &lt;/a&gt;and they&apos;re not impressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They note the soft &apos;control group&apos; reading and possible pull-forward spending as a mirage. Later in the year, slower population growth could lead to weakness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The road ahead for the consumer is going to be rough,&quot; CIBC writes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They note that liberation day has been somewhat walked back but rates are still much higher at around 15% compared to 3% tariffs before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Many businesses have been managing these first few months through inventories and
absorbing some of the tariffs, but that is starting to change. Major retailers are starting to report price hikes for May
and the summer,&quot; they write.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That echos what Walmart said today, as it plans to raise prices in May, as tariff-affected merchandise arrives.

“The magnitude and speed at which these prices are coming to us is somewhat unprecedented in history,” said CFO John David Rainey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CIBC sees some paths to a boost in consumer sentiment but they&apos;re narrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;The mood is more cautious, sentiment is low and markets are on edge with an administration seeking
to make drastic changes to international trade and finance even if more methodically now. Fiscal policy could turn
more supportive and lift spirits, but the rates market might cut into some of that benefit if it does come. All in all, we
expect tariffs and the sentiment shock to bring consumption growth to slow to around 1-1.5% in the second half of this
year.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did the stock go down? Why did gold go up? We will never fully know.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/why-did-the-stock-go-down-why-did-the-gold-go-up-we-will-never-fully-know-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:03:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/why-did-the-stock-go-down-why-did-the-gold-go-up-we-will-never-fully-know-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Why Markets Move: Stop Obsessing Over &quot;Why&quot; and Start Mastering the &quot;How&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think I&apos;ve been getting this question about once a week for over 10 years. &quot;Why is the stock going down?&quot;, &quot;Why is the stock going up?&quot; and just less than an hour ago on one of our channels:  &quot;What reasons pushing gold up again ???&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most frequent questions traders and investors repeatedly ask is deceptively simple. It seems straightforward—there must be a clear and simple reason behind every price movement. Yet, if you&apos;ve spent time actively trading or investing, you&apos;ll have discovered the frustrating reality: markets rarely move for just one clear reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&apos;s dive deeply into understanding why obsessing over the &quot;why&quot; is often less useful than learning &quot;how&quot; to successfully participate and profit from market movements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Myth of Single-Cause Market Moves&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It happens consistently, especially during earnings seasons or major economic events:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A company reports impressive revenue growth, beats analyst expectations on earnings per share (EPS), issues strong guidance—yet the stock drops 7%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold prices, after soaring to new all-time highs, suddenly plunge by 11% within a few weeks—then abruptly reverse course and rise sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This seemingly paradoxical behavior puzzles many market participants, leading them to repeatedly ask: &quot;Why?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The truth is complex: Financial markets are dynamic systems driven by myriad interconnected forces. It&apos;s essential to internalize that no single reason typically dictates price action, and even experienced market professionals rarely fully grasp all contributing factors. Wait, that was an understatement because there is no one alive that fully  knows the entire, complete, fully weighted, precise resolution of the why markets move. It is impossible to know all the why&apos;s and that will probably never change. And, no, I am not talking about the reason being that there are X buy orders vs Y sell orders, etc. I am also talking about why those orders were set in the 1st place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding Complexity and Embracing Uncertainty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s human nature to crave simplicity and direct causation. Our brains seek easily digestible answers, but markets resist such simplification. Several critical factors consistently influence asset prices:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fundamental Catalysts: Earnings announcements, economic data, interest rate decisions, geopolitical developments, commodity cycles, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical Levels: Volume-weighted average price (VWAP), key levels from volume profile analysis (Value Area High/Low, Point of Control), opening prices for the year/month/day, Fibonacci retracements, and psychological round-number levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Positioning and Order Flow: Institutional order placement, hedge fund risk management rules, algorithmic trading strategies, short covering, and large-scale profit-taking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hidden Factors and Dark Pools: Off-exchange transactions and institutional trading activities that aren&apos;t immediately transparent but significantly influence price action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critically, even when a major news item appears clearly bullish or bearish, its real market impact depends heavily on pre-existing market expectations, positioning, and broader sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Real-World Example: Gold Futures&apos; Recent Movement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider recent price action in Gold Futures (GC). After touching an all-time high at 3,509.9, prices dropped by approximately 11% over 17 trading sessions, bottoming at 3,123.3. Yet, shortly afterward, the market rebounded sharply, trading back up toward 3,210.5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the surface, the immediate question might be, &quot;What caused gold to suddenly bounce back?&quot; But digging deeper, the move may reflect multiple simultaneous factors:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Short Position Profit-Taking: Institutional traders and hedge funds often set risk thresholds, necessitating periodic profit-taking and position size adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Algorithmic Buying at Technical Levels: Sophisticated algorithms automatically activate buy orders around certain technical levels like VWAP, monthly opens, or high-volume nodes (POC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Broader Market Sentiment Shifts: Perhaps investors interpreted weaker economic data or geopolitical tensions as reasons to increase allocations to safe-haven assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critically, none of these factors alone fully explain the complexity of market behavior—but all likely contributed simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Limits of &quot;Knowing Why&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assume, hypothetically, you know precisely why gold bounced—say, investors flocking to safe havens amid economic fears. Even if correct, this information alone provides limited actionable trading guidance. It does not:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Determine the optimal entry and exit points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inform you about how significant resistance or support levels may influence future price moves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reveal the ideal position sizing and risk management strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simply knowing the reason doesn&apos;t automatically translate into profitable decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transitioning from &quot;Why&quot; to &quot;How&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Successful traders and investors shift their emphasis from endlessly dissecting why markets move to skillfully determining how to exploit these movements. Here&apos;s how to practically adopt this crucial mindset shift:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify Key Levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understand where institutional and algorithmic orders cluster (VWAP, POC, Value Areas, Fibonacci levels).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch Price Action Closely:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Observe how price behaves at these critical levels—absorption, rejection, breakout, or retest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Risk Management and Position Sizing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearly define entry and exit points, profit-taking areas, and stop-loss placements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adaptability:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be ready to adjust your trading plan based on actual market responses rather than theoretical reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;By focusing on these strategies, you develop a proactive trading framework centered on actionable data rather than elusive causes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ForexLive.com Evolves: Introducing investingLive.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recognizing the broader needs and interests of investors and traders, ForexLive.com will evolve later this year into &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investinglive.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;investingLive.com&lt;/a&gt;. This transition aims to provide comprehensive coverage beyond currencies, including stocks, commodities, cryptocurrencies, and alternative investments. The new platform will deliver enhanced market insights, decision-support tools, educational resources, and actionable strategies tailored to today&apos;s dynamic investing environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Practical Takeaway: Master the Art of Riding the Wave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, successful investing isn&apos;t about having perfect explanations for every market move—it&apos;s about successfully navigating those moves. Rather than fixating on explanations, traders should prioritize:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actionable Preparation: Have structured plans that anticipate multiple scenarios at key price levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Real-Time Responsiveness: Quickly adapt your positions based on market feedback, not your biases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consistent Risk Discipline: Adhere strictly to planned risk management protocols.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The legendary trader Jesse Livermore famously advised:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Markets are never wrong; opinions often are.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Internalize this wisdom. Accept uncertainty. Master the art of positioning yourself to profitably &quot;ride the wave,&quot; rather than fruitlessly trying to pinpoint precisely &quot;why&quot; the wave formed or where it will ultimately break.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By adopting this disciplined approach, traders and investors will experience sustained success, improved confidence, and less anxiety about market mysteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned as we continue evolving into investingLive.com, bringing you an even richer suite of tools and insights to navigate financial markets effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUSSIA-UKRAINE TALKS IN ISTANBUL CAN BE DELAYED TO TMRW: TASS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923031070535975168#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:01:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923031070535975168#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUSSIA-UKRAINE TALKS IN ISTANBUL CAN BE DELAYED TO TMRW: TASS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD capped by resistance at the 200 hour MA, presses back to key support at 100-hour MA</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-capped-by-resistance-at-the-200-hour-ma-presses-back-to-key-support-at-100-hour-ma-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:57:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-capped-by-resistance-at-the-200-hour-ma-presses-back-to-key-support-at-100-hour-ma-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;178&quot; data-end=&quot;476&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The EURUSD remains under pressure after yesterday’s rally was capped by the 200-hour moving average and a swing area that extended up to 1.1275. That area remains a key upside hurdle for buyers looking to regain control, although the MA has drifted lower and currently sits near 1.1243.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;478&quot; data-end=&quot;746&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Today’s price action has been contained, with highs limited near 1.1227, adding to the bearish tone. The pair has rotated back lower and is now retesting the 100-hour moving average at 1.11764—a level that already provided some support earlier in the today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;748&quot; data-end=&quot;978&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A break and hold below 1.1176 would tilt the bias further to the downside and expose the pair to a deeper retracement, with potential targets at 1.1145, the low for the week at 1.1064 and the 38.2% retracement of the 2025 trading range (from the Januayr low) at 1.10395. Getting below the 38.2% will ultimately need to be broken for the sellers to take more control.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;980&quot; data-end=&quot;1135&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Buyers will need to push back above 1.1213, then ultimately challenge the 200-hour MA at 1.12429 and swing area resistance between 1.12657 and 1.12754, to shift momentum back in their favor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1137&quot; data-end=&quot;1154&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1155&quot; data-end=&quot;1329&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1155&quot; data-end=&quot;1242&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1157&quot; data-end=&quot;1242&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.11764 (100-hour MA), 1.1145 (swing low), 1.1064 (low for the week), 1.10395 (38.2% retracement of 2025 trading range)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1243&quot; data-end=&quot;1329&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1245&quot; data-end=&quot;1329&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.1227 (intraday high), 1.1243 (200-hour MA), 1.1275 (swing area top)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *COREWEAVE SIGNED UP TO $4B ADDITIONAL DEAL WITH OPENAI

$CRWV $MSFT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923028385040617728#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:51:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923028385040617728#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*COREWEAVE SIGNED UP TO $4B ADDITIONAL DEAL WITH OPENAI&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23CRWV&quot;&gt;$CRWV&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23MSFT&quot;&gt;$MSFT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants waver as financials lead market rally</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-giants-waver-as-financials-lead-market-rally-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:46:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-giants-waver-as-financials-lead-market-rally-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stock market heatmap today reveals a dynamic landscape of performance across various sectors. While the technology sector struggled to find footing, the financials surged ahead, providing a significant anchor for the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;📉 Technology Sector: Notable tech giants like Apple (AAPL) and Oracle (ORCL) faced challenges, slipping by 0.93% and 1.37% respectively. The overall sentiment in technology seemed cautious, partly due to continued pressure on semiconductors.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;📈 Financial Sector: This sector shone brightly today, with financial heavyweights such as Visa (V) and BlackRock (BLK) posting gains of 1.41% and 1.10% respectively. Investor confidence appears to be buoyed by optimism surrounding interest rate trends and economic recovery.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🔺 Consumer Defensive Sector: Companies like Coca-Cola (KO) and Walmart (WMT) had varied performances, with KO enjoying a 2.02% rise, suggesting strong consumer staples support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;🔻 Consumer Cyclical Sector: Interestingly, the likes of Amazon (AMZN) and Tesla (TSLA) saw declines of 2.89% and 2.84% respectively, indicating investor hesitation in the cyclical domain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market&apos;s mood reflected a mixed bag of emotions today. While technology grappled with uncertainties, financials boosted overall market morale. The shifting dynamics likely stem from the latest financial earnings releases and macroeconomic updates, with investors keeping a keen eye on inflationary pressures and the Fed&apos;s next moves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the current sector analysis and trend evaluation, it is advisable for investors to consider a diversified approach. Focusing on financially robust sectors like the Financials can offer stability while awaiting clearer signals from the technology sector, which remains a challenge amidst semiconductor struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the market navigates through these fluctuating dynamics, consider re-evaluating positions in high-beta sectors and focusing on defensive plays like consumer staples. Stay informed with real-time updates and market data, and do visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt; for a deeper dive into market movements and strategies.📊&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FAA SAYS IT COULD BAN PENTAGON FROM TRANSPORTING VIPS ON ROUTINE MISSIONS AROUND DC AIRPORT: &quot;EVERYTHING IS ON THE TABLE&quot; -- HOUSE HEARING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923026939633184849#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:45:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923026939633184849#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FAA SAYS IT COULD BAN PENTAGON FROM TRANSPORTING VIPS ON ROUTINE MISSIONS AROUND DC AIRPORT: &quot;EVERYTHING IS ON THE TABLE&quot; -- HOUSE HEARING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP TARGETS BILLIONS IN ENERGY GRANTS FOR NEW ROUND OF AUDITS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923023349996765605#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:31:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923023349996765605#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP TARGETS BILLIONS IN ENERGY GRANTS FOR NEW ROUND OF AUDITS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDUSD stalls at 200-day MA for second time this week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-stalls-at-200-day-ma-for-second-time-this-week-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:29:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/audusd-stalls-at-200-day-ma-for-second-time-this-week-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;86&quot; data-end=&quot;361&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The AUDUSD continues to face strong resistance at the 200-day moving average, which capped rallies both on Monday and again today at the session high of 0.6457. Sellers leaned into that level, keeping upside momentum in check and maintaining the bearish pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;363&quot; data-end=&quot;537&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, a cluster of moving averages, all broken on the move lower, sits between 0.6419 and 0.6437 and now acts as a key resistance zone. This area includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;538&quot; data-end=&quot;660&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;538&quot; data-end=&quot;572&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;540&quot; data-end=&quot;572&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The 200-hour MA at 0.64376&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;573&quot; data-end=&quot;607&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;575&quot; data-end=&quot;607&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The 100-hour MA at 0.64254&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;608&quot; data-end=&quot;660&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;610&quot; data-end=&quot;660&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The 100-bar MA on the 4-hour chart at 0.6419&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;662&quot; data-end=&quot;927&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;After the fall, the low price reached 0.6401, just above the psychological 0.6400 level, where support buyers emerged. However, the rebound stalled at 0.6422, unable to reclaim the broken MAs—giving sellers a short-term advantage below this cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;929&quot; data-end=&quot;1137&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;To shift the bias back to the upside, the pair needs to sustain a move above 0.6437, and then break through the 200-day MA at 0.6457. That would open the door toward 0.6513, the high for the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1139&quot; data-end=&quot;1350&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Conversely, a break below 0.6400 could see further downside toward the next support at 0.6388, followed by the broader swing area between 0.6321 and 0.63437. Beyond that, key support targets include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1351&quot; data-end=&quot;1444&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1351&quot; data-end=&quot;1384&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1353&quot; data-end=&quot;1384&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The 100-day MA at 0.62951&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1385&quot; data-end=&quot;1444&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1387&quot; data-end=&quot;1444&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The 38.2% retracement of the April rally at 0.62844&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MEXICO PRESIDENT CALLS U.S. REPUBLICANS&apos; PROPOSAL TO TAX REMITTANCES &apos;UNACCEPTABLE&apos;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923020807074115722#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:21:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923020807074115722#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MEXICO PRESIDENT CALLS U.S. REPUBLICANS&apos; PROPOSAL TO TAX REMITTANCES &apos;UNACCEPTABLE&apos;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU&apos;s Sefcovic agreed with US Commerce Secretary Lutnick to accelerate trade talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eus-sefcovic-agreed-with-us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-to-accelerate-trade-talks-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:18:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eus-sefcovic-agreed-with-us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-to-accelerate-trade-talks-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The toughest negotiation of all for the US administration is with the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just don&apos;t see any world where the EU can accept a 10% floor on tariffs. But there is also a significant trade surplus with the US so I don&apos;t see how Trump&apos;s team can back down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if the EU gets sub-10% tariffs then what about other trade partners? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a perfect world maybe all tariffs end up back at zero and the US gets some trade concessions that open up some markets. There&apos;s a decent chance of that but that sort of &apos;win&apos; is hardly worth the political cost the US has already paid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US business inventories for March 0.1% vs 0.2% estimate</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-business-inventories-for-march-01-vs-02-estimate-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:00:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-business-inventories-for-march-01-vs-02-estimate-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior month business inventories 0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business inventories for March 0.1% vs 0.2% estimate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Retail inventories ex-Autos 0.4% vs 0.1% last month&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Details from the Census Bureau:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;94&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2&quot; data-end=&quot;94&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Total sales (March): $1,919.9B, up 0.7% from February 2025 and up 4.5% from March 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;95&quot; data-end=&quot;195&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;97&quot; data-end=&quot;195&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Total inventories (March): $2,578.1B, up 0.1% from February 2025 and up 2.5% from March 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;196&quot; data-end=&quot;269&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;198&quot; data-end=&quot;269&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Inventories/sales ratio (March): 1.34, down from 1.37 in March 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sales are outpacing the inventory build which could be a problem if tariffs impact supplies going forward. That is still TBD but it seems that at a minimum, tariffs will rise by 10%. What does that do to prices, demand, and inventories?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US May NAHB housing market index 34 vs 40 expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-may-nahb-housing-market-index-34-vs-40-expected-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:00:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-may-nahb-housing-market-index-34-vs-40-expected-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 40&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Details:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Single family 37 vs 45 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prospective buyers 23 vs 25 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sales expectations 42 vs 43 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This matches the lowest since 2022 and -- outside of the pandemic period -- is the worst since 2012. The west region is particularly soft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can&apos;t imagine that today&apos;s touch of 5% in US 30-year yields is going to help the sentiment in the housing market. That said, spending on home-related goods was strong in today&apos;s retail sales report.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trading Amid Turbulence: Octa Broker Explores How to Trade During News-Driven Volatility</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-amid-turbulence-octa-broker-explores-how-to-trade-during-news-driven-volatility-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:50:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/trading-amid-turbulence-octa-broker-explores-how-to-trade-during-news-driven-volatility-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Today, financial markets no longer dance
solely to the rhythm of macroeconomic data releases. Instead, they often lurch
or rally in response to an offhand remark from a political leader or an abrupt
policy tweet. Nowhere is this more evident than in recent weeks, where
headlines—not spreadsheets—have dominated market momentum. Traditional
indicators like inflation figures or Purchasing Managers Indices (PMIs) still
carry weight, but traders should also read between the headlines and act on the
fly. Octa Broker provides examples of how news affects the market and what
events are worth monitoring. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Historical
Impact of News on Markets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market-shocking news is nothing new. Arguably,
one of the most infamous examples occurred on 15 January 2015, when the Swiss
National Bank unexpectedly eliminated its currency ceiling against the euro.
Within seconds, the EUR/CHF pair &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/business-30829917&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;plummeted
by nearly 30%&lt;/a&gt;, wiping billions from the forex markets and sending
shockwaves around global financial institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This historical context matters. It
reminds that both scheduled and unscheduled news can have outsized impacts on
market pricing, especially when market participants are caught off guard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scheduled vs.
Unscheduled News Events&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scheduled news events, by their nature,
offer predictability. Reports such as the Consumer Price Index (CPI), labour
market data, PMIs, and central bank meetings are calendar fixtures. Their
importance, however, varies depending on the issuing country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States is a leader in terms of
influence. As the issuer of the global reserve currency, U.S. economic data has
global ramifications. An example is the U.S. CPI reading, which not only shifts
USD pairs but, often, equity indexes and commodities. The Bureau of Labor
Statistics releases these &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bls.gov/schedule/2025/05_sched.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt;
monthly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pmi.spglobal.com/Public/Release/ReleaseDates&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;PMI reports&lt;/a&gt;, often early indicators of
economic health, are published by S&amp;amp;P Global on a harmonised schedule
across major economies. Central bank meeting dates, while known in advance,
still generate high volatility due to surprise rate decisions or hawkish/dovish
commentary. Federal Reserve (Fed) meetings can be tracked &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/monetarypolicy/fomccalendars.htm&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and the European Central Bank’s (ECB)
schedule is also available on the institution’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecb.europa.eu/press/calendars/mgcgc/html/index.en.html&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, unscheduled news events are
unpredictable and often far more dramatic in terms of market impact. These
include geopolitical tensions, unexpected policy announcements, or political
rhetoric. On 1 February 2025, President Trump&apos;s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/trump-readies-order-steep-tariffs-goods-mexico-canada-china-2025-02-01&quot;&gt;sudden announcement&lt;/a&gt; of comprehensive tariffs
on Canadian imports pushed USD/CAD to record multi-decade highs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Surge of
Unscheduled News in Recent Times&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;April 2025 exemplified how chaotic
unscheduled news can become.  In early
April, shifting U.S. tariff policies caused &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/02/business/stock-market-recovery-trump-tariffs.html&quot;&gt;sharp moves in equity markets&lt;/a&gt;. Major indices
dropped into correction territory but later recovered after revised statements.
Then, in early May, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/sustainable-finance-reporting/us-job-growth-slows-marginally-april-unemployment-rate-steady-42-2025-05-02&quot;&gt;mixed job data&lt;/a&gt; added to the uncertainty,
offering little clarity on what to expect next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current News
Events Influencing the Markets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several unscheduled narratives are
currently steering sentiment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
Trade negotiations between the
U.S. and China are ongoing, with some progress achieved, but uncertainty
continues to linger as to whether an acceptable and long-lasting agreement can
be achieved within a 90-day deadline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
President Trump’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-wont-remove-fed-chair-powell-before-term-ends-2026-tv-interview-2025-05-04&quot;&gt;public critique&lt;/a&gt; of Fed Chair Jerome Powell
continues to inject uncertainty into the monetary policy outlook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
Meanwhile, the U.S. remains
involved—&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.euronews.com/my-europe/2025/05/02/us-will-not-fly-around-the-world-to-mediate-ukraine-russia-meetings-washington-says&quot;&gt;albeit hesitantly&lt;/a&gt;—in peace talks between
Ukraine and Russia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
Trade discussions with Japan have
also become strained, with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/business/us-cedes-little-ground-key-tariffs-talks-with-japan-nikkei-says-2025-05-02&quot;&gt;little progress &lt;/a&gt;reported thus far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategies for
Traders During High-Volatility News Cycles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this news-saturated environment,
adaptability is key. Traders can navigate volatility with the following
strategies:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
Use smaller position sizes to
limit exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
Apply tighter stop-loss orders to
protect against sudden swings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
Opt for short-term trades to
reduce the risk of overnight event surprises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;●     
Avoid overly volatile assets
unless accompanied by clear signals or hedges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kar Yong Ang, a financial market analyst at
Octa Broker, notes: ‘With news-driven and
unexpected volatilities driving trading in our current setting, traders must
become more reactive and less anticipatory in their strategies. Do not try to
front-run and second-guess the outcome of this or that event. Instead, wait for
the dust to settle and then enter the market. Position sizing should reflect
the current volatility regime, ideally calculated through dynamic risk metrics
like ATR (Average True Range). Most importantly, traders should maintain a
structured news-monitoring routine and understand the second-order effects of
headlines—for example, how a tariff announcement may ripple through
commodities, currencies, and interest rate expectations simultaneously.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About Octa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scheduled economic releases still matter,
but unscheduled news—particularly in the current politically charged global
climate—has emerged as the primary driver of market sentiment. The line between
economic and political news continues to blur, and with it, the predictability
of price action. For traders, this means one thing above all: stay flexible,
stay informed, and adjust strategies to match the new reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compliance
reminder: trading
Contracts for Difference (CFDs) carries a high level of risk and may not be
suitable for all investors. Emotional trading can increase this risk. Always
trade within your means and understand the risks involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.octafx.com?utm_source=media&amp;amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;amp;utm_campaign=%20How_to_Trade_During_NewsDriven_Volatility&amp;amp;utm_content=ww_fx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Octa &lt;/a&gt;is an international broker that has been providing online
trading services worldwide since 2011. It offers commission-free access to
financial markets and various services used by clients from 180 countries who
have opened more than 52 million trading accounts. To help its clients reach
their investment goals, Octa offers free educational webinars, articles, and
analytical tools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company is involved in a
comprehensive network of charitable and humanitarian initiatives, including the
improvement of educational infrastructure and short-notice relief projects
supporting local communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its foundation, Octa has won
more than 100 awards, including the &apos;Most Reliable Broker Global 2024&apos; award
from Global Forex Awards and the &apos;Best Mobile Trading Platform 2024&apos; award from
Global Brand Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian delegation said it is ready to discuss compromises at talks with Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russian-delegation-said-it-is-ready-to-discuss-compromises-at-talks-with-ukraine-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/russian-delegation-said-it-is-ready-to-discuss-compromises-at-talks-with-ukraine-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There are so many conflicting signals on this war at the moment. It&apos;s impossible to make sense of where it really stands.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD holds above 200-bar MA on 4-hour chart, eyes key resistance cluster</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-holds-above-200-bar-ma-on-4-hour-chart-eyes-key-resistance-cluster-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:36:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-holds-above-200-bar-ma-on-4-hour-chart-eyes-key-resistance-cluster-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;149&quot; data-end=&quot;409&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCAD moved back above the 200-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart (currently at 1.3957) yeasteray, and found support against it during today’s pullback. That level now serves as immediate support, and holding above it keeps the near-term bullish bias intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;411&quot; data-end=&quot;655&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the topside, the 200-day moving average at 1.40126 remains a key upside target, reinforced by a swing area resistance between 1.40097 and 1.40268. Earlier this week, the high price stalled within this zone, just above the 200-day MA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;657&quot; data-end=&quot;855&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A break above that resistance area would open the door toward the 38.2% retracement of the March decline at 1.40525, which is the next critical hurdle for buyers aiming to regain firmer control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;857&quot; data-end=&quot;1050&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, a move back below 1.3957 could trigger a rotation toward the next key support swing area between 1.38917 and 1.3904, which held the low yesterday and earlier this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;857&quot; data-end=&quot;1050&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The battle is on between the dip buyers and the rally sellers.  Traders wait for the next break. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1052&quot; data-end=&quot;1069&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1070&quot; data-end=&quot;1239&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1070&quot; data-end=&quot;1141&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1072&quot; data-end=&quot;1141&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.3957 (200-bar MA on H4), 1.38917–1.3904 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1142&quot; data-end=&quot;1239&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1144&quot; data-end=&quot;1239&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.40126 (200-day MA), 1.40097–1.40268 (swing area), 1.40525 (38.2% retracement)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard to find any sign of weakness in the US consumer</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/hard-to-find-any-sign-of-weakness-in-the-us-consumer-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:29:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/hard-to-find-any-sign-of-weakness-in-the-us-consumer-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s US retail sales report was mostly positive news. The control group was the lone exception but that was on softer grocery store spending while economically-sensitive spots showed some real strength, like food services and drinking places up 0.8%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CFO of the world&apos;s biggest retailer had this to say on the call today:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; February was softer than expected, March was back to normal and April was very strong&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within the report there were some signs of consumers stretching dollars toward essentials and value. Comp sales rose 4.5% though with transactions up 1.6%. Again, much of that was in groceries and essentials as general merchandise slipped slightly but it&apos;s not a big red flag. Some could be higher end consumers trading down but you really have to squint to see a soft consumer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Internationally, they also saw steady but slower spending in Mexico and Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another sign came from Comcast today, which owns theme parks in the US and around the world. At a conference, the company CFO said there has been no sign of impact from economic uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of WMT are down 2.3% pre-market.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April industrial production 0.0% vs +0.2% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-industrial-production-00-vs-02-expected-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:15:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-industrial-production-00-vs-02-expected-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manufacturing output -0.4% vs -0.2% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior output +0.3% (revised to +0.4%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is some major uncertainty on the industrial side of the economy right now. I&apos;m not sure this offers any clarity.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF stays between key support and key resistance targets</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-stays-between-key-support-and-key-resistance-targets-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:07:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-stays-between-key-support-and-key-resistance-targets-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;64&quot; data-end=&quot;324&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCHF continues to find sellers near familiar technical levels, with the 38.2% retracement of the March–April decline at 0.8482 acting as firm resistance earlier this week. The inability to push above that level has resulted in a retracement lower as sellers remain in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;326&quot; data-end=&quot;382&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The swing area halted yesterday&apos;s fall between 0.8318 and 0.8333 (the low reached 0.83233), which previously served as resistance and now acts as support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;554&quot; data-end=&quot;754&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Buyers will want to see price remain above that 0.8318–0.8333 zone to maintain short-term bullish hopes. A move below would weaken the technical picture and open the door for further downside probing. Also in play above that is the falling 200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart at 0.8342 (see green line on the chart above). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;756&quot; data-end=&quot;954&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the topside, the 38.2% retracement at 0.8482 remains the key level to break to shift control more decisively to the buyers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;956&quot; data-end=&quot;971&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;972&quot; data-end=&quot;1097&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;972&quot; data-end=&quot;1034&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;974&quot; data-end=&quot;1034&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 0.8344 (200-bar MA on 4-hour chart), 0.8318–0.8333 (key swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1035&quot; data-end=&quot;1097&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1037&quot; data-end=&quot;1097&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.8473. (This is the high of swing area going back January 2015 - not shown), 0.8482 (38.2% Fib of move down from 2025 high), 0.8619 (50% retracement)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Iranian official says haven&apos;t received fresh proposal from the US - report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/senior-iranian-official-says-havent-received-fresh-proposal-from-the-us-report-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:06:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/senior-iranian-official-says-havent-received-fresh-proposal-from-the-us-report-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Oil prices sank today after a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/more-on-iran-is-ready-to-sign-a-nuclear-deal-if-sanctions-lifted-20250514/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;report &lt;/a&gt;said Iran is ready to sign a nuclear deal if all economic sanctions are lifted. Trump &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-were-getting-close-to-doing-a-deal-with-iran-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;added &lt;/a&gt;to that by saying Iran had agreed to terms and that &quot;we&apos;re getting close to doing a deal with Iran.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This pushes back on that a bit but there is some serious smoke around a deal. Oil prices have come about $1 off the bottom but that was before this headline.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Powell discusses mon pol framework, doesn&apos;t comment on the outlook for rates</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-powell-discusses-mon-pol-framework-doesnt-comment-on-the-outlook-for-rates-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 12:41:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-powell-discusses-mon-pol-framework-doesnt-comment-on-the-outlook-for-rates-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;April PCE will likely come in around 2.2% y/y&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Officials agree that strategic language around both short falls of employment and average inflation need to be reconsidered&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Framework needs to be robust&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Revisions to Fed communication are also being considered&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&apos;s nothing to take away here for markets, at least in the short term.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
