<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Japan finance minister Kato says will discuss FX with Bessent</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-says-will-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:46:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-says-will-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan finance minister Kato &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;will discuss FX with Bessent in line with points agreed in prior talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FX should be determined by market&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;excessive FX moves damage economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FT: Trump administration split on timing of adding Chinese chipmakers to export blacklist</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ft-trump-administration-split-on-timing-of-adding-chinese-chipmakers-to-export-blacklist-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:10:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ft-trump-administration-split-on-timing-of-adding-chinese-chipmakers-to-export-blacklist-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Financial Times is gated, but in brief:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trump administration plans to put a number of Chinese chipmaking companies on an export blacklist (the “entity list”)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;timing of the move has been complicated by the trade deal agreed by China and the US in Geneva at the weekend&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;some Trump administration officials have argued that putting export controls on critical Chinese groups now could jeopardise the trade negotiations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand April Manufacturing PMI shows an uptick in expansion to 53.9 vs. prior 53.2</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-april-manufacturing-pmi-shows-an-uptick-in-expansion-to-539-vs-prior-532-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 23:03:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-april-manufacturing-pmi-shows-an-uptick-in-expansion-to-539-vs-prior-532-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;BNZ – BusinessNZ Performance of Manufacturing Index (PMI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;April comes in at 53.9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;up from 53.2 in March&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; fourth month in a row showing expansion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; above the average of 52.5 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;BusinessNZ’s Director, Advocacy Catherine Beard:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“All of the sub-index values were in expansion during April.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;BNZ’s Senior Economist Doug Steel:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“activity is not surging, but a manufacturing recovery seems to be underway with the PMI having improved substantially from its low of 41.4 last June. That said, there remain questions around how sustainable it is given uncertainty stemming from offshore”.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSBC modelling sees USD/JPY trading a 141 - 149 range (there&apos;s a but)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/hsbc-modelling-sees-usdjpy-trading-a-141-149-range-theres-a-but-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:42:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/hsbc-modelling-sees-usdjpy-trading-a-141-149-range-theres-a-but-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;HSBC argue for further yen recovery vs the USD citing &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;heightened U.S. policy uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;resumption of pessimism toward the U.S. economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;renewed expectations of Fed easing soon&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;HSBC are tracking trade developments, noting market sensitivity &quot;to headlines about U.S.-Japan trade talks, especially regarding FX discussions” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HSBC’s modelling indicates 141-149 range for USD/JPY, though analysts do recognise risks for both overshooting and undershooting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I stuck in lines around 141 and 149, just using eyeballing ... it looks like we don&apos;t have to worry about over and undershooting those levels for a while to come yet. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia financial media reports that “Australia won’t join Trump trade war on China”</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-financial-media-reports-that-australia-wont-join-trump-trade-war-on-china-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:12:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-financial-media-reports-that-australia-wont-join-trump-trade-war-on-china-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;A piece in today&apos;s Australian Financial Review on Australia not joining in on Trump&apos;s trade attack on China. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade Minister Don Farrell spoke in an interview with the AFR (gated): &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;reluctant to be part of a US campaign
against China on trade, given that Australian exports to China are worth almost 10 times that to the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“China is our
largest trading partner. Chinese trade is almost 10 times more
valuable to Australia”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We don’t want to do less business
with China, we want to do more business with China.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;

We’ll make
decisions about how we continue to engage with China based on our
national interests and not on what the Americans may or may not
want.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AFR is gated, here is the link if you can access it for much more. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Deputy Treasury Secretary says not concerned about persistent increases in prices</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-deputy-treasury-secretary-says-not-concerned-about-persistent-increases-in-prices-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:30:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-deputy-treasury-secretary-says-not-concerned-about-persistent-increases-in-prices-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;U.S. Deputy Treasury Secretary Faulkender spoke in an interview with Bloomberg TV:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;not concerned about persistent increases in prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;expects inflation will return to target level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US economy building foundation to accelerate in H2 this year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;confident that August timeline is earliest we have to worry about X date&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan, US to resume tariff talks after G7 summit as Akazawa plans Washington visit</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-us-to-resume-tariff-talks-after-g7-summit-as-akazawa-plans-washington-visit-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:09:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-us-to-resume-tariff-talks-after-g7-summit-as-akazawa-plans-washington-visit-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan, US to resume tariff talks after G7 summit as Akazawa plans Washington visit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan and the United States are preparing for a third round of negotiations over trade tariffs, aiming to resume talks later this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The discussions are part of ongoing efforts to ease tensions following recent U.S. tariff hikes under the Trump administration. Japan’s chief negotiator, Ryosei Akazawa, is expected to travel to the U.S. for the talks shortly after attending the upcoming Group of Seven (G7) meeting of finance ministers and central bank governors. That summit, set to be held next week, is likely to feature prominently in setting the tone for bilateral discussions, with both sides under pressure to find common ground on trade imbalances and tariff rollbacks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Akazawa will attend the summit for finance ministers and central bankers being held Banff, Alberta, Canada on  May 20 -22. This is being held ahead of the 2025 G7 Leaders’ Summit, which will be in Kananaskis, Alberta, Canada from June 15 to 17.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s Akazawa in the hat!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea April export prices have shown their slowest rise y/y since December 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/south-koreaapril-exportpriceshave-shown-their-slowestriseyysincedecember-2023-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 21:07:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/south-koreaapril-exportpriceshave-shown-their-slowestriseyysincedecember-2023-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;South Korea April data, comes via the Bank of Korea:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Export prices in won terms +0.7% y/y vs revised +6.4% in March, export prices slowest rise y/y since December 2023&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Import prices in won terms -2.3% y/y vs revised +3.4% in March, import prices fastest drop y/y since October 2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Korea says April Foreign net investment in local stocks -13.59 trln won vs -1.64 trln won in March
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;says April Foreign net investment in local bonds +11.26 trln won vs +5.87 trln won in March&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;KRW update:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Dip in PPI pulls down USD/JPY</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-dip-in-ppi-pulls-down-usdjpy-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:41:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-dip-in-ppi-pulls-down-usdjpy-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-retail-sales-01-vs-00-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;US April retail sales +0.1% vs 0.0% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-ppi-24-vs-25-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;US April PPI +2.4% vs +2.5% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-initial-jobless-claims-229k-versus-229k-estimate-20250515/&quot;&gt;US initial jobless claims 229K versus 229K estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/philadelphia-fed-business-index-for-may-40-vs-110-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;Philadelphia Fed Business index for May -4.0 vs -11.0 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-may-nahb-housing-market-index-34-vs-40-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;US May NAHB housing market index 34 vs 40 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-industrial-production-00-vs-02-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;US April industrial production 0.0% vs +0.2% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/empire-manufacturing-index-for-may-92-vs-100-estimate-20250515/&quot;&gt;Empire manufacturing index for May -9.2 vs -10.0 estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-q2-rises-to-25-from-23-prior-20250515/&quot;&gt;Atlanta Fed GDPNow Q2 rises to 2.5% from 2.3% prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eus-sefcovic-agreed-with-us-commerce-secretary-lutnick-to-accelerate-trade-talks-20250515/&quot;&gt;EU&apos;s Sefcovic agreed with US Commerce Secretary Lutnick to accelerate trade talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-business-inventories-for-march-01-vs-02-estimate-20250515/&quot;&gt;US business inventories for March 0.1% vs 0.2% estimate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-mexico-cuts-benchmark-interest-rate-to-85-from-90-20250515/&quot;&gt;Bank of Mexico cuts benchmark interest rate to 8.5% from 9.0%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-says-economy-is-on-a-solid-footing-trade-clouds-the-outlook-20250515/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Barr says economy is on a solid footing, trade clouds the outlook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-powell-discusses-mon-pol-framework-doesnt-comment-on-the-outlook-for-rates-20250515/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Powell discusses mon pol framework, doesn&apos;t comment on the outlook for rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-wholesale-trade-02-vs-03-expected-20250515/&quot;&gt;Canada March wholesale trade 0.2% vs -0.3% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/walmart-offers-a-major-warning-on-prices-20250515/&quot;&gt;Walmart offers a major warning on prices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude oil down $1.42 to $61.77&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields down 9 bps to 4.43%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold up $60 to $3234&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CHF leads, NZD lags&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 up 0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We got a full slate of data today and most of the numbers were close to estimates but PPI stood out as a softer indication and that led to Fed rate cut odds ticking higher, especially further out the curve. It also lent some relief in bonds as yields fell 7-11 bps across the curve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar continues to differ in its reaction function to yield moves, suggesting that fiscal policy is increasingly seen as off-base. Despite falling yields, the US dollar rose and it&apos;s been the opposite on days when yields have risen. That&apos;s something Deutsche Bank &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-losing-its-appetite-to-fund-us-twin-deficits-deutsche-bank-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;raised the alarm &lt;/a&gt;on today and a critical dynamic to watch as the US budget drama plays out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US retail sales data was somewhat comforting as it showed strong spending in bars and restaurants, which is typically one of the first things to go. Walmart did offer a stark warning about price rises though so that should keep the Fed in watch-and-wait mode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Canadian dollar was something of an outperformer in North American as oil and commodity prices rebounded from the earlier lows. Part of that was a bounce in oil prices after Iran said it hadn&apos;t received an deal offers from the United States. The risk picture also lent some support, though that wasn&apos;t seen in the other commodity currencies.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Chance To Nominate Your Candidate for the Industry’s Most Creditable Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/last-chance-to-nominate-your-candidate-for-the-industrys-most-creditable-awards-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:38:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/last-chance-to-nominate-your-candidate-for-the-industrys-most-creditable-awards-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The nomination period for the UF AWARDS Global 2025 is coming to an end on 30th of May, which means your window for recommending your brand as a nominee is quickly closing!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The UF AWARDS and their recipients receive an incredible level of coverage within the industry. Meaning that even brands that don’t win still receive an unprecedented boost to their profiles, and it can help bolster their reputation, since the stringent selection process only allows the most competitive companies to progress to the next stage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Prove your brand is a market leader&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Distinguishing yourself in such a densely populated and competitive market can be extremely challenging. Modern consumers are discerning and often immune to catchy marketing taglines and slogans, even more so if they are industry insiders. So, how do you convince them to work with you? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;With proof. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://uf-awards.com/cyprus2025/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;UF AWARDS&lt;/a&gt; are not only one of the market&apos;s most credible and covered awards events, but they can also help brands establish or expand their footprint in existing regions or when entering a new market through increased global brand exposure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;As one of the industry’s most well-established awards, the UF AWARDS bring an unparalleled level of recognition to brands that innovate, disrupt the status quo, and propel the industry forward. The nominees include some of the financial service industry’s and FinTech world’s biggest and boldest. Past winners have included agile start-ups, FinTech firms that offer industry-critical software, and companies that are household names. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Winning a UF AWARD Global title shows that your company can stand shoulder to shoulder with some of the leading B2B and B2C brands in its sector and head and shoulders above the rest on the global stage. It lends credibility to a brand, increases a company&apos;s visibility, and can be used on marketing creatives to prove to potential clients that they offer leading products and services. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Multiple award categories&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://uf-awards.com/cyprus2025/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;UF AWARDS Global&lt;/a&gt; offer multiple award categories that top-tier financial service and FinTech companies can be nominated for. This means that B2C and B2B companies can be enlisted for outstanding features, products, and services they offer, facing direct competitors, instead of competing against companies and firms that may not even share the same segment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Additionally, nominees can be recommended for multiple awards if their offerings align with the respective requirements.. For example, a brand may be nominated as “Best Trading Platform” as well as “Best Customer Support”. The category winners are decided on by a public vote, which ensures impartiality, credibility, and that they are awarded based purely on merit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;How to nominate your favorite brand&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Your last chance to nominate a brand for the UF AWARDS Global is the 30th of May 2025. Here’s how to &lt;a href=&quot;https://uf-awards.com/cyprus2025/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;submit a nomination&lt;/a&gt; or recommend a brand as a nominee:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Register on the Awards website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Once registered and logged in, select the category of your brand you wish to nominate from the dropdown - Broker Awards or B2B Awards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Next, click on the Award title that best describes the scope of your business, and nominate the company worthy of the title. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Once the nominees are submitted, the voting will open on the 3rd and close on the 11th of June. The awards will be announced during the Award ceremony taking place on the 18th of June. For more information about the award categories and to submit nominations, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://uf-awards.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;uf-awards.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Good luck to all nominees, and we look forward to seeing you at the award ceremony!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP Morgan CEO Dimon says US recession risks remain high amid deficits and inflation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-ceo-dimon-says-us-recession-risks-remain-high-amid-deficits-and-inflation-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:36:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-ceo-dimon-says-us-recession-risks-remain-high-amid-deficits-and-inflation-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;462&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Equity markets seem to have shaken off the risk, Jamie Dimon with a caution, ICYMI.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;462&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Dimon says a U.S. recession is still a live risk. The JPMorgan Chase CEO told Bloomberg that surging federal deficits, persistent inflation and the prospect of higher long-term interest rates could yet tip the economy into contraction. “I wouldn’t take it off the table at this point,” he said, adding that he relies on his bank’s economists for precise forecasts and cannot predict “how big it will be or how long it will last” if a downturn materialises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;464&quot; data-end=&quot;862&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;JPMorgan’s research team this week trimmed its recession probability to “below 50 percent,” having previously expected a slump soon after the Trump administration’s early-April tariff blitz. Chief U.S. economist Michael Feroli acknowledged that risks remain “elevated,” but Dimon cautioned that even the current uncertainty is enough to make businesses hesitate before committing to new investment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *NVIDIA REPORTS 7% STAKE IN COREWEAVE IN 13G</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923114324479869131#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:32:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923114324479869131#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*NVIDIA REPORTS 7% STAKE IN COREWEAVE IN 13G&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *ACKMANS PERSHING EXITS NKE IN Q1:13F

$NKE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923108871356166577#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:10:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923108871356166577#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*ACKMANS PERSHING EXITS NKE IN Q1:13F&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NKE&quot;&gt;$NKE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major indices close mixed. NASDAQ lower as Meta-reverses course on AI problems</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/major-indices-close-mixed-nasdaq-lower-as-meta-reverses-course-on-ai-problems-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:09:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/major-indices-close-mixed-nasdaq-lower-as-meta-reverses-course-on-ai-problems-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The WSJ reported that Meta has delayed the release of its flagship large language model, Llama 4 “Behemoth,” citing internal concerns about its performance and whether it offers meaningful improvements over previous versions. That news sent shares of Meta lower with the price closing at $643.88, down $-15.48 for -2.35%. At session highs, the stock was up $3.89.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decline also helped to reverse the rising NASDAQ index into negative territory. It is closing down -34.49 points or -0.18% at 19112.32. At session highs, the index was up 60.41 points. The other side is that at session lows, the price was down -179.03 points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A look at the closing levels shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average +271.69 points toward 0.65% at 42322.75. For the week going into the last day of the week, the index is up 2.60%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index is up 24.35.2 or 0.41% at 5916.92. For the week the index is up 4.54%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index fell -34.49 points or -0.18% at 19112.32. For the week, the index is up 6.60%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *S&amp;P 500 CLOSES UP 0.3%, NASDAQ FALLS 0.2%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923106366782079010#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923106366782079010#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*S&amp;amp;P 500 CLOSES UP 0.3%, NASDAQ FALLS 0.2%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic calendar in Asia 16 May 2025: Japan Q1 GDP prelim. &amp; RBNZ inflation expectations</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-16-may-2025-japan-q1-gdp-prelim-rbnz-inflation-expectations-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:58:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-16-may-2025-japan-q1-gdp-prelim-rbnz-inflation-expectations-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The focal points on the data agenda are the economic growth data from Japan for the January - March quarter and the Reserve Bank of New Zealand Survey of Expectations for inflation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan preliminary Q1 GDP:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most economists expect Japan’s economy shrank in the first quarter, primarily due to soft consumer spending at home and lacklustre overseas demand. GDP is forecast to contract by 0.1% quarter-on-quarter for January–March, after a 0.6% expansion at the end of 2024. While private consumption is set to rise, supported by steady household spending and a boost from inbound tourism, weak exports are likely to weigh heavily. There was only limited front-loading of shipments to avoid tariffs, unlike in other major exporting countries, and imports have picked up. This subdued growth outlook suggests the Bank of Japan may delay further interest rate hikes for now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reserve Bank of New Zealand Survey of Expectations:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RBNZ conducts quarterly surveys to gauge inflation expectations among business leaders and professional forecasters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past three quarters, the surveys indicate a general decline in both 1-year and 2-year ahead inflation expectations, suggesting that inflation is expected to move closer to the RBNZ&apos;s target band of 1–3%. The slight uptick in the 1-year expectation in Q1 2025 may reflect short-term factors, but the 2-year expectation continued its downward trend, indicating confidence in medium-term price stability. It&apos;s the two-year period that the RBNZ focuses on most in the survey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q1 2025 (Survey conducted in January 2025)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;306&quot; data-end=&quot;548&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;306&quot; data-end=&quot;387&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;308&quot; data-end=&quot;387&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1-year ahead inflation expectation: Increased to 2.15% from 2.05% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;388&quot; data-end=&quot;548&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;390&quot; data-end=&quot;548&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;2-year ahead inflation expectation: Decreased to 2.06% from 2.12% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q4 2024 (Survey conducted in October 2024)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;602&quot; data-end=&quot;844&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;602&quot; data-end=&quot;683&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;604&quot; data-end=&quot;683&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1-year ahead inflation expectation: Decreased to 2.05% from 2.40% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;844&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;686&quot; data-end=&quot;844&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;2-year ahead inflation expectation: Increased to 2.12% from 2.03% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q3 2024 (Survey conducted in July 2024)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;895&quot; data-end=&quot;1137&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;895&quot; data-end=&quot;976&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;897&quot; data-end=&quot;976&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1-year ahead inflation expectation: Decreased to 2.40% from 2.73% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1137&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;979&quot; data-end=&quot;1137&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;2-year ahead inflation expectation: Decreased to 2.03% from 2.33% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RBNZ closely monitors these expectations to inform its monetary policy stance. The decline in medium-term expectations aligns with the central bank&apos;s goal of maintaining inflation within its target range, potentially allowing for more accommodative monetary policy if the trend continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An upside move for the two-year should support the NZD, at the margin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The times in the left-most column are GMT.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The numbers in the right-most column are the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month/quarter as the case may be) result. The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade ideas thread - Friday, 16 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-friday-16-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:58:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-friday-16-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Good morning, afternoon and evening all, welcome to Friday! Any charts, technical analysis, trade ideas, thoughts, views, ForexLive traders would like to share and discuss with fellow ForexLive traders, please do so:
 &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HHS TO STOP RECOMMENDING ROUTINE COVID SHOTS FOR CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923103658792616242#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:50:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923103658792616242#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HHS TO STOP RECOMMENDING ROUTINE COVID SHOTS FOR CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta delays rollout of flagship AI model amid internal performance concerns</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/meta-delays-rollout-of-flagship-ai-model-amid-internal-performance-concerns-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:37:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/meta-delays-rollout-of-flagship-ai-model-amid-internal-performance-concerns-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The WSJ is reporting that Meta has delayed the release of its flagship large language model, Llama 4 “Behemoth,” citing internal concerns about its performance and whether it offers meaningful improvements over previous versions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;649&quot; data-end=&quot;761&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;651&quot; data-end=&quot;761&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Delayed Release: Behemoth, originally targeted for an April release, has now been pushed to fall or later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;762&quot; data-end=&quot;910&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;764&quot; data-end=&quot;910&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Performance Issues: Engineers say Behemoth shows minimal gains over prior models, sparking debate about whether it’s ready for public release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;911&quot; data-end=&quot;1044&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;913&quot; data-end=&quot;1044&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Internal Frustration: Meta executives are frustrated with the Llama 4 team’s progress and may restructure the AI product group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1045&quot; data-end=&quot;1212&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1047&quot; data-end=&quot;1212&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Mismatch with Public Claims: Behemoth has been publicly touted as outperforming rivals, but insiders say training issues are limiting its real-world performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1213&quot; data-end=&quot;1404&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1215&quot; data-end=&quot;1404&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Earlier Releases Questioned: Two Llama models released in April performed well on AI leaderboards, but Meta later admitted it had optimized those submissions specifically for the tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1405&quot; data-end=&quot;1520&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1407&quot; data-end=&quot;1520&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Research Team Turnover: 11 of the 14 researchers behind the original Llama model have since left the company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1521&quot; data-end=&quot;1693&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1523&quot; data-end=&quot;1693&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Industry Trend: Meta’s delays reflect broader challenges in the AI space—OpenAI’s GPT-5 and Anthropic’s Claude 3.5 Opus have also missed initial release expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1694&quot; data-end=&quot;1832&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1696&quot; data-end=&quot;1832&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Meta’s AI Spending: The company plans up to $72 billion in capital expenditures this year, much of it devoted to AI development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shares of Meta are trading down -$14.12 or -2.16% 15 $645.15, after trading as high as +$3.89 on the day. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *META TO DELAY ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP: WSJ

*META&apos;S &apos;BEHEMOTH&apos; WAS INTERNALLY SLATED FOR APRIL RELEASE: WSJ

*META ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP AI MODEL DELAYED TO FALL OR LATER: WSJ

$META</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923096475015274849#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:21:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923096475015274849#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*META TO DELAY ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*META&apos;S &apos;BEHEMOTH&apos; WAS INTERNALLY SLATED FOR APRIL RELEASE: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*META ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP AI MODEL DELAYED TO FALL OR LATER: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23META&quot;&gt;$META&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Mexico cuts benchmark interest rate to 8.5% from 9.0%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-mexico-cuts-benchmark-interest-rate-to-85-from-90-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:11:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-mexico-cuts-benchmark-interest-rate-to-85-from-90-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;158&quot; data-end=&quot;225&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;160&quot; data-end=&quot;225&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bank of Mexico lowers benchmark interest rate to 8.50% from 9.00%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;226&quot; data-end=&quot;263&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;228&quot; data-end=&quot;263&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Board says decision was unanimous&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;264&quot; data-end=&quot;409&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;266&quot; data-end=&quot;409&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Board estimates that looking forward it could continue calibrating the monetary policy stance and consider adjusting it in similar magnitudes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;410&quot; data-end=&quot;552&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;412&quot; data-end=&quot;552&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Board anticipates that the inflationary environment will allow to continue the rate cutting cycle, albeit maintaining a restrictive stance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;553&quot; data-end=&quot;624&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;555&quot; data-end=&quot;624&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Headline inflation is projected to converge to target in Q3 of 2026&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;625&quot; data-end=&quot;730&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;627&quot; data-end=&quot;730&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Balance of risks for trajectory of inflation within the forecast horizon remains biased to the upside&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;731&quot; data-end=&quot;792&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;733&quot; data-end=&quot;792&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Balance of risks for trajectory of inflation has improved&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;793&quot; data-end=&quot;892&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;795&quot; data-end=&quot;892&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Changes in economic policy by the new US administration have added uncertainty to the forecasts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;893&quot; data-end=&quot;1067&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;895&quot; data-end=&quot;1067&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Board will take into account the effects of the country’s weak economic activity and the incidence of both the restrictive monetary policy stance that has been maintained&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1068&quot; data-end=&quot;1164&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1070&quot; data-end=&quot;1164&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Forecasts Q4 2026 average annual headline inflation at 3.3% versus previous forecast of 3.0%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1165&quot; data-end=&quot;1257&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1167&quot; data-end=&quot;1257&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Forecasts Q4 2026 average annual core inflation at 3.0% versus previous forecast of 3.0%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1258&quot; data-end=&quot;1354&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1260&quot; data-end=&quot;1354&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Forecasts Q4 2025 average annual headline inflation at 3.3% versus previous forecast of 3.3%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1355&quot; data-end=&quot;1445&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1357&quot; data-end=&quot;1445&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Forecasts Q4 2025 average annual core inflation at 3.4% versus previous forecast of 3.3%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1355&quot; data-end=&quot;1445&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1357&quot; data-end=&quot;1445&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The board took into account the behavior of the exchange rate, the weakness of the economic activity and the possible impact of changes in trade policies worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1355&quot; data-end=&quot;1445&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1357&quot; data-end=&quot;1445&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The environment of uncertainty and trade tensions poses significant downward risks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;91&quot; data-end=&quot;408&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Technically, the USDMXN is rebounding after hitting its lowest level since October in yesterday’s trade, with a session low of 19.3006. Today’s decline found support just above that mark at 19.3230, and the pair has since moved higher, breaking above the 100-hour moving average, currently at 19.4639.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;410&quot; data-end=&quot;673&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Holding above this level gives buyers a bit more short-term control. The next key upside target is the 200-hour moving average at 19.5375—a break above which would further strengthen the bullish bias and suggest a more meaningful recovery off the recent lows.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *COINBASE HACKERS HAD ACCESS TO CUSTOMER DATA SINCE JANUARY

$COIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923092251049177096#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923092251049177096#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*COINBASE HACKERS HAD ACCESS TO CUSTOMER DATA SINCE JANUARY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *STATE OF WISCONSIN INVESTMENT BOARD EXITS BITCOIN ETF POSITION: SEC FILING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923090409468711385#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923090409468711385#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*STATE OF WISCONSIN INVESTMENT BOARD EXITS BITCOIN ETF POSITION: SEC FILING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil settles at $61.62</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-settles-at-6162-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-settles-at-6162-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The price of crude oil move down $1.53 or 2.42% settling at $61.62. Contributing to the downward bias includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;140&quot; data-end=&quot;735&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;140&quot; data-end=&quot;266&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;142&quot; data-end=&quot;266&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Potential U.S.–Iran nuclear deal: May lead to lifting of sanctions on Iranian oil exports, increasing global supply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;267&quot; data-end=&quot;384&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;269&quot; data-end=&quot;384&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;OPEC+ production increases: Scheduled to add 411,000 bpd as part of the continued rollback of earlier cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;385&quot; data-end=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;387&quot; data-end=&quot;512&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;IEA demand outlook: Sees global demand growth slowing from 0.99M bpd in Q1 to 0.65M bpd for the rest of 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;513&quot; data-end=&quot;622&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;515&quot; data-end=&quot;622&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;IEA supply outlook: Revised 2025 global supply growth upward to 1.6M bpd, from 1.2M bpd previously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;623&quot; data-end=&quot;735&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;625&quot; data-end=&quot;735&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Macroeconomic headwinds: Ongoing tariff tensions and slowing global growth are weighing on oil demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, the price of oil moved down to test the 200-hour MA today at session lows. The price did extend below that MA but could not sustain momentum. The price is back below the 100 and 200-hour MAs. The higher 100 hour MA is at $62.12. The 200-hour MA is at $60.41.  THose MAs will be barometers for more bullish or more bearish bias on a break higher or lower. .  &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US-UAE AI CAMPUS WILL PARTNER WITH &apos;SEVERAL&apos; US COMPANIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085920363831532#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:39:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085920363831532#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US-UAE AI CAMPUS WILL PARTNER WITH &apos;SEVERAL&apos; US COMPANIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *DOJ PROBING IF HARVARD ADMISSIONS DEFRAUDED GOVERNMENT: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085187870576740#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085187870576740#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*DOJ PROBING IF HARVARD ADMISSIONS DEFRAUDED GOVERNMENT: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *STATE DEPARTMENT IS LEADING CAMPAIGN ACCUSING EUROPE OF LIMITING FREE SPEECH AND PROMOTING CENSORSHIP -- WSJ

*ADMINISTRATION SEES EU AS PART OF ‘GLOBAL CENSORSHIP-INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX’ HURTING U.S. TECH -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085085919641778#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085085919641778#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*STATE DEPARTMENT IS LEADING CAMPAIGN ACCUSING EUROPE OF LIMITING FREE SPEECH AND PROMOTING CENSORSHIP -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*ADMINISTRATION SEES EU AS PART OF ‘GLOBAL CENSORSHIP-INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX’ HURTING U.S. TECH -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GBPUSD remains range bound but with a bullish tilt</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gbpusd-remains-range-bound-but-with-a-bullish-tilt-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gbpusd-remains-range-bound-but-with-a-bullish-tilt-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;159&quot; data-end=&quot;549&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The GBPUSD remains confined to a 68-pip trading range today, narrower than the 22-day average range of 102 pips (about a month of trading). Price action has been choppy, but the 100-hour moving average (currently at 1.32614) has consistently provided support during intraday dips. This level also aligns with recent swing lows (see red numbered circles), reinforcing its importance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;551&quot; data-end=&quot;914&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Staying above the 100-hour MA has kept buyers in play, and with the pair now trading above the 200-hour MA (green line), those buyers are looking to gain more control. However, attempts to build upside momentum have repeatedly stalled. The most recent rally reached a session high of 1.3319, just shy of the May 9 high at 1.33227, before pulling back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;916&quot; data-end=&quot;1361&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A sustained break above 1.33227 would open the door toward the weekly high at 1.33597, followed by resistance at 1.3379. Beyond that, the market would look to challenge the 2025 highs at 1.3423, 1.3433, and 1.3441, with 1.3430 also representing the high from 2024 (see daily chart below). Notably, the brief April breakout above that level marked the highest price since March 2022—but it lacked follow-through, and sellers quickly regained control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1363&quot; data-end=&quot;1483&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For now, staying above the 200-hour MA remains key for buyers to maintain momentum and press for a topside breakout.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Barr says economy is on a solid footing, trade clouds the outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-says-economy-is-on-a-solid-footing-trade-clouds-the-outlook-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:06:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-barr-says-economy-is-on-a-solid-footing-trade-clouds-the-outlook-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trade shock could be particularly hard on small businesses and trigger price increases if supply chains are affected or firms fail&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There isn&apos;t much of a nod here but after today&apos;s PPI data, the market is back to fully pricing in 25 bps in September.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *RUSSIA DEPLOYS 640,000 TROOPS IN WAR AGAINST UKRAINE: MILITARY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923074660993835285#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:55:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923074660993835285#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*RUSSIA DEPLOYS 640,000 TROOPS IN WAR AGAINST UKRAINE: MILITARY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE LEGAL HEAD CALLS SEC INVESTIGATION A RELIC OF PAST ADMINISTRATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923072444299915747#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:46:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923072444299915747#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE LEGAL HEAD CALLS SEC INVESTIGATION A RELIC OF PAST ADMINISTRATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE CHIEF LEGAL OFFICER: REPORTED SEC INVESTIGATION IS A HOLD-OVER FROM PRIOR ADMINISTRATION ABOUT A METRIC WE STOPPED REPORTING 2.5 YEARS AGO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923072369427354065#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923072369427354065#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE CHIEF LEGAL OFFICER: REPORTED SEC INVESTIGATION IS A HOLD-OVER FROM PRIOR ADMINISTRATION ABOUT A METRIC WE STOPPED REPORTING 2.5 YEARS AGO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The gold bulls are fighting back today, but it&apos;s uphill</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-gold-bulls-are-fighting-back-today-but-its-uphill-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-gold-bulls-are-fighting-back-today-but-its-uphill-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Gold is up $40 today to $3219 in an impressive $110 intraday turnaround after falling as low as $3120 in Asia-Pacific trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a growing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-losing-its-appetite-to-fund-us-twin-deficits-deutsche-bank-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;conversation &lt;/a&gt;about US fiscal sustainability and its erratic trade war. Trade tensions have fallen and gold has fallen at the same time but we&apos;re still not clear on where the end goal is or how to get there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only trade deal so far is between the US and UK. It was a win for the US but trade between the military allies is surprisingly small and limited, with the major categories of trade getting exemptions. Will other countries offer anything in order to get 10% tariff rates in the US?  That&apos;s hard to believe until we see it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With that, the fear (and what&apos;s boosting gold) is the possibility that we&apos;re just in an ebb in trade negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe the bigger question is how all these events are seen abroad. Certainly, this is at least a nudge towards some level of de-dollarization or de-integration. Trust in US trade and military treaties is certainly stretched.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, we&apos;re watching the US fiscal package unfold and it looks like there won&apos;t be much austerity, with +6% deficits-to-GDP ratios forever.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $NVDA - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $COIN - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt; - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The market is losing its appetite to fund US twin deficits - Deutsche Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-losing-its-appetite-to-fund-us-twin-deficits-deutsche-bank-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-market-is-losing-its-appetite-to-fund-us-twin-deficits-deutsche-bank-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;George Saravelos is Global Head of FX Research at
Deutsche Bank is out with a striking note today, highlighting the problems with the US dollar, deficits and government policy. The note certainly resonates with US 30-year yields touching off 5% today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He highlights the emerging consensus around the fiscal budget bill that&apos;s working its way though Congress and the growing likelihood of higher deficits. That&apos;s working against the White House&apos;s stated aim of lowering the trade deficit because it gooses consumer demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They see the current account deficit continuing to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;The significance of
this conclusion cannot be over-estimated. We have been arguing over the last
few months that the market is reducing its willingness to fund US twin deficits,&quot; Saravelos writes. &quot;We worry this is
brewing a major problem for the dollar and potentially the US bond market too.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding to the vulnerability is a backdrop of larger foreign ownership of US assets and &quot;extreme&quot; valuation of dollar-denominated assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s tough to call a tipping point in this relationship but at some point the US will face a reckoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;For foreigners to
continue financing US debt one thing needs to happen: the non-dollar price of
US Treasuries needs to decline, either via currency depreciation or a drop in
the price of the bonds. The problem for the latter is that it makes US debt
dynamics even worse so is not sustainable. We are ultimately left with the only
solution to this problem being dollar weakness.&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saravelos believes this is already unfolding as inflows to the US are slowing and that there is an emerging breakdown in the dynamic between USD/JPY and yields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;To sum it all up, as Secretary Bessent alluded to
himself, the US cannot be asking of the rest of the world to reduce its
imbalance with America if the US is not willing to reduce its own. The risk is
the rest of the world forces the correction upon the US in a disorderly way.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada&apos;s S&amp;P/TSX index rises to a new record high</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/canadas-sptsx-index-rises-to-a-new-record-high-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:05:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/canadas-sptsx-index-rises-to-a-new-record-high-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Canada&apos;s S&amp;amp;P TSX stuck in the city is stretching to a new all-time high. The high price today reach two 589.46. The current prices at 25882.41 of 190 points or 0.74% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new high extended above the prior hi going back to June January 30 at 25875.61. The high price for the index was reached on January 30 at 25808.25.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The index moved down -14.10% from its January high. That move to the downside retraced around 50% midpoint of the move up from the October 2023 low price, before starting the bounce back to the new highs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the trading year, the index is up 4.69% after rising 17.99% in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the US major indices are now positive on the day:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average is up 215 points or 0.51% at 42266.78&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index is up 28.23 points or 0.48% at 5921. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index is up 44.47 points or 0.23% in 19191.71&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the 2025 trading year, the Dow and NASDAQ indices are still negative, but the S&amp;amp;P is now positive for 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average -0.70%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index +0.65%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index -0.63%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2024 the:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average rose 12.88%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index rose 23.31%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index rose 28.64%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade

🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:54:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed GDPNow Q2 rises to 2.5% from 2.3% prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-q2-rises-to-25-from-23-prior-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:48:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/atlanta-fed-gdpnow-q2-rises-to-25-from-23-prior-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Q2 estimate for GDP from the Atlanta Fed is up to 2.5% from 2.3% on May 8. In their own words: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The GDPNow model estimate for real GDP growth (seasonally adjusted annual rate) in the second quarter of 2025 is 2.5 percent on May 15, up from 2.3 percent on May 8. After recent releases from the US Census Bureau, the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, and the Federal Reserve Board of Governors, the nowcasts of second-quarter real personal consumption expenditures growth and second-quarter real gross private domestic investment growth increased from 3.3 percent and 1.2 percent, respectively, to 3.7 percent and 1.5 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next GDPNow update is Friday, May 16. Please see the &quot;Release Dates&quot; tab below for a list of upcoming releases.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qatar wealth fund plans to invest $500B in US over the next 10 years</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/qatar-wealth-fund-plans-to-invest-500b-in-us-over-the-next-10-years-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:25:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/qatar-wealth-fund-plans-to-invest-500b-in-us-over-the-next-10-years-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Qatar wealth fund plans to invest $500B in US over the next 10 years.  This is according to Bloomberg.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier in the week, during talks in Riyadh, Saudi Arabia pledged a historic $600 billion in future investments across U.S. energy, technology, defense, and infrastructure sectors, a commitment announced jointly by the White House and Saudi leadership. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complementing that headline figure, Saudi Aramco also signed 34 preliminary agreements with American companies valued at up to $90 billion, underscoring the kingdom’s push to deepen commercial ties with the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freddie Mac 30 year mortgage rate 6.81% up from 6.76% last week</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/freddie-mac-30-year-mortgage-rate-681-up-from-676-last-week-20250515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:18:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/freddie-mac-30-year-mortgage-rate-681-up-from-676-last-week-20250515/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Freddie Mac 30 year mortgage rate for the current week rises to 6.81% from 6.76%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;633&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;U.S. housing data continue to paint a mixed picture. New‑home sales rose solidly in March, climbing to a seasonally‑adjusted annual rate (SAAR) of 724 000 units, a 7.4 % jump from February and 6 % above year‑earlier levels. Builders are attracting buyers with incentives: the median price of a newly built home slipped to $403 600, down 7.5 % from a year earlier, while inventory edged up to 503 000 units (an 8.3‑month supply). These figures suggest that new construction remains the brightest spot in residential real estate as builders fill the gap left by a thin resale market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;635&quot; data-end=&quot;1088&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Meanwhile, the existing‑home market remains subdued. March resale transactions fell 5.9 % on the month to an annual pace of 4.02 million—2.4 % below the same period last year—confirming that high borrowing costs and limited listings continue to dampen turnover. Yet tight supply is supporting prices: the median existing‑home price reached $403 700, up 2.7 % year on year and the highest ever recorded for March. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1090&quot; data-end=&quot;1680&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Financing conditions are steady but still historically expensive. Freddie Mac’s latest Primary Mortgage Market Survey shows the 30‑year fixed rate at 6.81 % (week ended 15 May), up modestly from 6.76 % the prior week. Rates have hovered in a 6.7 – 6.9 % corridor for nearly four months and sit roughly 30 basis points below the level of a year ago. That range has been tight enough to limit refinancing but stable enough to coax some buyers off the sidelines—purchase‑application volume is running about 18 % above last year’s depressed levels.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
