<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Shares of Target fall 7% as the company highlights consumer weakness</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/shares-of-target-fall-7-as-the-company-highlights-consumer-weakness-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:39:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/shares-of-target-fall-7-as-the-company-highlights-consumer-weakness-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;What is happening with the US consumer?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, the market breathed a sigh of relief after Walmart maintained its annual sales forecast. The CFO &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/hard-to-find-any-sign-of-weakness-in-the-us-consumer-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;said &lt;/a&gt;February was softer than expected, March was back to normal and April was very strong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But could the signal have been that higher-end consumers who usually shop at Target trading down?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TGT is down 7% after missing Q1 revenue estimates. The company also cut its full-year sales outlook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of that may be because of the DEI dance the company is doing but I find it hard to believe that consumers actually care. The company blamed most of the decline on the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Sales were down nearly 3% compared to a year ago. The company now expects a low-single digit decline in sales this 
fiscal year, compared to a previous forecast of net sales growth of 
about 1%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; CEO Brian Cornell  said that “ongoing pressure in our discretionary business, plus five consecutive 
months of declining consumer confidence, tariff uncertainty and the 
reaction to the updates we shared on belonging in January.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also remember that consumers haven&apos;t even been hit by tariff price hikes yet. The company said that price hikes are a &quot;last resort&quot; but didn&apos;t rule them out.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD trades to new lows.  Eyes support at 1.38607</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-trades-to-new-lows-eyes-support-at-138607-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:32:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-trades-to-new-lows-eyes-support-at-138607-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;93&quot; data-end=&quot;396&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCAD remains under pressure, continuing its slide that began last week after the pair tested and failed at the 200-day moving average on two occasions (higher green line currently at 1.4016). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;93&quot; data-end=&quot;396&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The price traded above and below the 100 and 200 hour MAs over the last two trading days, with the 100 hour MA stalling the last rally yesterday before rotating lower.  When the price fell below the lows from Monday and Tuesday near 1.3917 in the Asian session today, the sellers pushed lower.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;398&quot; data-end=&quot;728&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Price is now trading to new lows and is testing a key swing level near 1.38607. A break below this level would put the price in the lower extreme area for 2025 which bottomed at 1.37497.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;398&quot; data-end=&quot;728&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance now comes in between 1.3891 and 1.3904, which must be cleared to ease the bearish bias and shift near-term control back toward buyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;730&quot; data-end=&quot;846&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Looking at the daily chart below, the low price for 2025 stalled just ahead of the 61.8% of the move up from the 2023 low at 1.37415 (the low reached 1.37497 within 8 pips of that target).  Swing levels toward that low would eye 1.3646 and below that the low from April at 1.3780.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;730&quot; data-end=&quot;846&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Sellers are in control.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;848&quot; data-end=&quot;863&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;864&quot; data-end=&quot;1073&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;864&quot; data-end=&quot;921&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;866&quot; data-end=&quot;921&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.38607, 1.3825, 1.3749 (2025 low extreme), 1.37415 (61.8% off daily)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;922&quot; data-end=&quot;996&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;924&quot; data-end=&quot;996&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 1.3891–1.3904, 1.3917 (swing level) 1.3949 (100-hour MA), 1.4016 (200-day MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;997&quot; data-end=&quot;1073&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;999&quot; data-end=&quot;1073&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 1.3904, downside risks increase on break of 1.3860&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INVESTORS WORRY ABOUT FISCAL BALANCE BEYOND THE U.S. 

The U.S. isn&apos;t the only country spurring fiscal concerns, Deutsche Bank&apos;s Jim Reid writes. A 20-year bond auction in Japan yesterday had the lowest demand in a decade, he says. Reid points out that the current debt-to-GDP ratio is 100% in the U.S. and the U.K., and 250% in Japan, compared to 41%, 42% and 113%, respectively, in 1999, when Japan introduced its 30-year sovereign bond. &quot;We&apos;ve never had a 30yr plus global bond market before when debt has been this high,&quot; Reid says, adding that &quot;this is uncharted territory.&quot; He says supply will increase in coming years, &quot;so the long-end desperately needs inflation to be controlled.&quot;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925181177133940782#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:25:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925181177133940782#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INVESTORS WORRY ABOUT FISCAL BALANCE BEYOND THE U.S. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The U.S. isn&apos;t the only country spurring fiscal concerns, Deutsche Bank&apos;s Jim Reid writes. A 20-year bond auction in Japan yesterday had the lowest demand in a decade, he says. Reid points out that the current debt-to-GDP ratio is 100% in the U.S. and the U.K., and 250% in Japan, compared to 41%, 42% and 113%, respectively, in 1999, when Japan introduced its 30-year sovereign bond. &quot;We&apos;ve never had a 30yr plus global bond market before when debt has been this high,&quot; Reid says, adding that &quot;this is uncharted territory.&quot; He says supply will increase in coming years, &quot;so the long-end desperately needs inflation to be controlled.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HASSETT: WE&apos;RE GOING TO GET MORE THAN 3% GROWTH</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925180465767452873#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:22:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925180465767452873#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HASSETT: WE&apos;RE GOING TO GET MORE THAN 3% GROWTH&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HASSETT: IF WE GET 3% GROWTH, TRUMP&apos;S TAX BILL PAYS FOR ITSELF</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925180404467630213#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:22:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925180404467630213#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HASSETT: IF WE GET 3% GROWTH, TRUMP&apos;S TAX BILL PAYS FOR ITSELF&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economies.com Launches VIP Subscription and Offers Free Trading Signals</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/economiescom-launches-vip-subscription-and-offers-free-trading-signals-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:14:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/economiescom-launches-vip-subscription-and-offers-free-trading-signals-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Elevate your trading
strategy with precise insights and reliable analysis. Economies.com&apos;s VIP
Subscription stands as a beacon for serious traders seeking a competitive edge.
Embrace the power of accurate forecasts and expert guidance to navigate volatile
markets with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the dynamic world of
forex trading, having access to timely and reliable information is crucial. As
a serious trader, you understand the importance of leveraging trading signals
to make informed decisions. Economies.com VIP emerges as the ultimate solution,
offering an array of services designed to optimize your trading endeavors. With
features like exclusive market analysis and daily price forecasts, this
subscription service ensures you are well-equipped to tackle the challenges of
the trading arena. Additionally, it provides insights into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economies.com/best-brokers&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Best Trading Platform&lt;/a&gt; to
enhance your trading experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benefits of the VIP
subscription&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Economies.com VIP
subscription offers unparalleled benefits tailored for discerning traders. This
service provides exclusive market analysis that goes beyond surface-level
insights, delving into nuanced forex trading insights that guide strategic decision-making.
Subscribers gain access to daily price forecasts, empowering them to anticipate
market movements with remarkable accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a focus on
delivering expert trading insights, Economies.com equips you with the knowledge
needed to identify profitable opportunities and mitigate risks. The integration
of cryptocurrency trading analysis adds an additional layer of depth, catering
to traders who diversify their portfolios with digital assets. By subscribing
to Economies.com VIP, you position yourself at the forefront of market
intelligence, ready to capitalize on emerging trends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Economies.com
has been a trusted resource for many years, with its Arabic version,
fxnewstoday.ae, also offering a VIP subscription service. Feedback from users
highlights the value that traders derive from this service. Users commend its
comprehensive analysis and user-friendly platform, emphasizing how it enhances
their trading experience. Whether you&apos;re a seasoned trader or new to the
market, Economies.com VIP offers tools that cater to various expertise levels,
ensuring you remain competitive in an ever-evolving landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free trading signals
offer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those eager to
maximize their trading potential, the early bird trading offer presents an
enticing opportunity. BestTradingSignal partners with Economies.com to provide
free trading signals exclusively for early subscribers. These signals serve as
a strategic advantage, offering real-time insights into potential market shifts
and lucrative trades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trading signals for
forex are essential for staying ahead of sudden market changes, allowing you to
seize opportunities as they arise. This limited-time offer not only amplifies
your trading toolkit but also underscores Economies.com&apos;s commitment to supporting
its community of traders. By signing up now, you gain access to actionable
insights that can transform your trading outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The synergy between
BestTradingSignal and Economies.com ensures that you&apos;re not just reacting to
market movements but proactively positioning yourself for success. As you
explore these free trading signals, you&apos;ll discover how they complement the
broader range of services offered by Economies.com VIP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choosing the best
trading brokers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selecting the right
broker is paramount in achieving trading success. Economies.com assists
subscribers in comparing top-tier brokers by offering detailed analyses and
reviews. These insights guide you in choosing the best trading brokers that
align with your specific needs and goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A comprehensive broker
comparison can significantly impact your trading journey by ensuring you work
with regulated entities that prioritize transparency and security. Through
Economies.com subscription services, you gain access to a curated list of reputable
brokers renowned for their reliability and competitive offerings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This feature empowers
you to make informed decisions without sifting through overwhelming options
alone. As part of the VIP subscription for traders, this resource facilitates
seamless integration between your trading strategy and execution platform—a crucial
step toward optimizing your performance in the forex market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Encouraging immediate
action&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To capitalize on these
benefits and more, take immediate action by subscribing today. The call is
clear: sign up now for VIP access and free signals! Embrace this opportunity to
enhance your trading capabilities with tools that deliver precision and insight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decision-making
process should consider how Economies.com&apos;s offerings can elevate your approach
within trading strategies. By committing to this subscription service, you&apos;re
not only investing in current market knowledge but also securing your future
success through continuous support and expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, integrating
diverse considerations into your broader investment strategy further
diversifies your portfolio while aligning with current financial trends. This
holistic approach positions you for sustained growth in both forex and broader
financial markets. For those interested in diversifying further, exploring &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economies.com/best-brokers/commodities/gold&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;How to invest in
gold&lt;/a&gt; could be a valuable addition to your strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Forex Market Trend Analysis with Advanced Trading Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/enhancing-forex-market-trend-analysis-with-advanced-trading-tools-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:11:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/enhancing-forex-market-trend-analysis-with-advanced-trading-tools-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Analyzing forex market
trends is critical for traders aiming to capitalize on currency movements.
Accurate data analysis and the use of advanced trading tools empower traders to
make informed decisions. Understanding key data sources and trading signals enhances
trend analysis, providing a competitive edge in the forex market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the dynamic world of
forex trading, staying ahead of market trends can significantly impact your
success. Market trends in forex are patterns or directions that currency values
tend to follow over a period. By understanding these trends, you can better
anticipate future movements and make strategic trading decisions. Utilizing
effective &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economies.com/best-brokers&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;best trading software&lt;/a&gt; can further enhance
your ability to analyze these trends effectively. This article explores the
essential components of forex market trend analysis and the role of advanced
tools in optimizing trading strategies.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding forex market trends &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forex market trends
refer to the general direction in which a currency pair&apos;s value is moving.
Recognizing these trends is vital for traders as it informs their buying and
selling strategies. Trends can be bullish, bearish, or sideways, each offering
unique opportunities and challenges. Bullish trends indicate rising prices,
while bearish trends suggest falling prices. Sideways trends show a lack of
strong directional movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traders often rely on
technical analysis to identify these trends, using chart patterns and
indicators to predict future price actions. Understanding the nature of forex
trends allows traders to align their strategies with prevailing market
conditions. By analyzing historical price data, traders can determine potential
entry and exit points that maximize profits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Successful trend
analysis involves more than just recognizing patterns; it requires interpreting
these patterns within the context of broader economic events. Economic
indicators, geopolitical developments, and monetary policies all influence
currency movements. Being aware of these factors helps you understand why a
trend is occurring, enabling you to anticipate changes and adjust your
strategies accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key data sources for trend analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Accurate trend analysis
in the forex market relies heavily on robust data sources. Traders frequently
turn to economic calendars to track upcoming events that could impact currency
valuations. These calendars provide information on interest rate announcements,
employment reports, and other economic indicators that influence forex markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another critical data
source is historical price charts, which offer insights into past market
behaviors. By studying these charts, traders can identify recurring patterns
and use them to forecast future movements. Technical indicators such as moving
averages, RSI (Relative Strength Index), and MACD (Moving Average Convergence
Divergence) are invaluable tools for analyzing price data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, real-time
news feeds provide up-to-the-minute information on political events and
economic developments worldwide. Staying informed about global events helps
traders understand market sentiment and potential impacts on currency values.
Combining these data sources creates a comprehensive picture of market
conditions, enabling more precise trend predictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Utilizing trading signals for decision-making&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trading signals play a
crucial role in interpreting forex market trends and guiding trading decisions.
These signals are generated by analyzing technical indicators and identifying
potential buy or sell opportunities based on specific criteria. They help you
pinpoint optimal times to enter or exit trades, maximizing profit potential
while minimizing risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are different
types of trading signals, including manual signals provided by experienced
analysts and automated signals generated by algorithms. Manual signals rely on
human expertise to interpret market data and suggest actions. In contrast,
automated signals use pre-set criteria within trading software to generate
alerts when conditions align with predefined parameters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effectiveness of
trading signals depends on their accuracy and timeliness. To ensure reliable
outcomes, it&apos;s essential to evaluate the credibility of signal providers or the
algorithms used in generating them. Reliable signals enhance your decision-making
process by providing clear guidance amid volatile market conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The role of advanced trading tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economies.com/best-brokers/forex&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt; best
forex trading platform&lt;/a&gt; will offer a wide range of tools for
traders. Advanced trading tools have revolutionized how traders analyze forex
market trends. These sophisticated platforms offer features such as real-time
analytics, customizable charts, and automated strategies that streamline the
trading process. They enable you to quickly assess large volumes of data and
make informed decisions with greater precision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One significant
advantage of advanced trading tools is their ability to integrate various data
sources seamlessly. By consolidating information from different channels into a
single interface, they provide a holistic view of the market landscape. This integration
simplifies trend analysis by presenting comprehensive insights at your
fingertips.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The use of automation
within these tools also enhances efficiency by executing trades based on
predetermined criteria without manual intervention. This capability allows you
to capitalize on opportunities instantly while reducing emotional bias in
decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF Technical Outlook: Price bounces off swing area target.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-technical-outlook-price-bounces-off-swing-area-target-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:07:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdchf-technical-outlook-price-bounces-off-swing-area-target-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;93&quot; data-end=&quot;345&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCHF has rotated lower today, continuing the decline over the last 6 or so trading days..  The price has returned to a familiar swing area between 0.8193 and 0.8212, which has previously acted as the low of an up-and-down trading range (see Red Box). The pair found buyers on the initial test, with price bouncing modestly toward another swing area between 0.8272 and 0.82803.  This area is now close resistance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;347&quot; data-end=&quot;607&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A break above this zone would shift focus toward the falling 100-hour moving average at 0.83316, followed by the 200-hour MA at 0.83591, both of which represent key upside hurdles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;609&quot; data-end=&quot;844&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Until then, the bearish bias remains in place with the descending trendline and moving averages acting as a ceiling. A break back below the lower end of the swing area at 0.8193 would open the door for further downside probing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;846&quot; data-end=&quot;861&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;862&quot; data-end=&quot;1034&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;862&quot; data-end=&quot;891&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;864&quot; data-end=&quot;891&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 0.8212, 0.8193&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;892&quot; data-end=&quot;969&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;894&quot; data-end=&quot;969&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.8272–0.8280, 0.8332 (100-hour MA), 0.8359 (200-hour MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;970&quot; data-end=&quot;1034&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;972&quot; data-end=&quot;1034&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Bearish below 0.8280, bullish potential above 0.8332&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will the buyers defend 5% yields once again? The red flags are flying</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/will-the-buyers-defend-5-yields-once-again-the-red-flags-are-flying-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/will-the-buyers-defend-5-yields-once-again-the-red-flags-are-flying-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There are plenty of things going on in the economy, trade and politics at the moment that are worth watching closely but I believe the confluence of them all -- and the single most important metric to watch -- is the yield on long bonds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year we&apos;ve seen three tests of 5% and they were all met by buyers, including early this week after the debt downgrade. But this time the buying momentum faded quickly and yields are up 5.5 bps to 5.02%. If we can close above 5% (especially on the weekly), that&apos;s a good sign that the buyers are exhausted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that case, we could very quickly be talking about the 2023 high of 5.17%. That came at a time when Liz Truss was blowing up the UK economy and US inflation was out of control. It was also in a much stronger (at least nominally) economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, this is a worrisome signal that&apos;s a problem for risk assets and it&apos;s a red flag that the US dollar is down today even as yields rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One caveat is that 10-year yields are still within the 2025 range and have some decent breathing room ahead of the January high of 4.81%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Centeno: We made need rates below neutral rate to prevent inflation sub-2%</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-centeno-we-made-need-rates-below-neutral-rate-to-prevent-inflation-sub-2-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-centeno-we-made-need-rates-below-neutral-rate-to-prevent-inflation-sub-2-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interest rate to prevent inflation from falling under 2% may have to come below the neutral rate between 1.50-2.00%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market is pricing 1.64% as the low for ECB rates which is a bit more than 50 bps fully priced in. Getting helow his neutral range would mean at least one more cut on top of that.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada April new housing price index -0.4% vs 0.0% prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-new-housing-price-index-04-vs-00-prior-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:34:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-new-housing-price-index-04-vs-00-prior-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was 0.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cracks in the Canadian housing market are growing and help isn&apos;t coming. The latest CPI number drastically cut the odds of a BOC rate cut in June (odds now just 31%) and Canadian yields are following the global trend higher.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ELON MUSK TO ATTEND WHITE HOUSE MEETING WITH RAMAPHOSA, TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925167497906409688#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:31:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925167497906409688#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ELON MUSK TO ATTEND WHITE HOUSE MEETING WITH RAMAPHOSA, TRUMP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GBPUSD moved up-and-down after stronger CPI. What are the charts telling traders?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-gbpusd-moved-up-and-down-after-stronger-cpi-what-are-the-charts-telling-traders-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:12:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-gbpusd-moved-up-and-down-after-stronger-cpi-what-are-the-charts-telling-traders-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The GBPUSD moved higher to a new high going back to 2022 after hotter than expected CPI data, but has reversed lower.  The pair is back below the 2024 hgh at 1.3433, and the 2025 high from April at 1.3441 after spiking to 1.34695.  Staying below those levels will keep the sellers in play. Move above and we should resume the upside momentum to new highs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EUR and JPY are also higher vs the USD (the USD is lower) to start the US trading day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video above, I take a look at the price action and the technicals that are driving the price action to start the US trading session.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regarding the UK inflation, it surprised to the upside in April, with headline CPI rising by 3.5% year-over-year (vs 3.3% expected, prior 2.6%). Core CPI climbed to 3.8% (vs 3.6% expected), and services inflation surged to 5.4% (vs 4.8% expected), pointing to persistent underlying pressures. The stronger-than-expected data significantly dents hopes for aggressive rate cuts from the Bank of England, with markets now pricing in just one 25 bp cut by year-end—if that. The report reinforces the view that inflation, not weak growth, is the dominant risk facing central banks, aligning with similar concerns for the ECB and the Fed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ECB&apos;s Centeno said the interest rate to prevent inflation from falling under 2%, may have to come below the neutral rate between 1.5% and 2.0%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Late yesterday, Cleveland Fed President Beth Hammack spoke and expressed concern over recent sentiment data, noting it reflects unease about the economic outlook. She emphasized that the Fed faces a tough balancing act if both inflation and unemployment become problematic. Hammack stressed the importance of monitoring how business decisions are affected by trade policies, and for now, believes the Fed’s best course is to “sit on its hands” and evaluate data closely while engaging with communities. She added that inflation expectations remain well-anchored, but any shift in those expectations could prompt the Fed to take action. &quot;Uncertainty&quot; is the key theme for Fed officials.  The undercurrent is the fear of inflation but the economy matters too. So eyes are pealed to the data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US MBA mortgage applications fell sharply by 5.1% in the week ending May 16, reversing the prior week’s 1.1% gain - and then some. The decline was broad-based, with the market index dropping to 238.5 (from 251.2), the purchase index down to 157.8 (from 166.5), and the refinance index slipping to 682.5 (from 718.1). Meanwhile, the average 30-year mortgage rate rose slightly to 6.92% from 6.86%, likely contributing to the pullback in activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The economic calendar only shows Canada new housing price index for April and the weekly EIA crude oil inventory data. Late yesterday the private data showed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks are lower with the futures implying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow Industrial average futures are down -325 points after falling -114.83 points or -0.27% yesterday&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index futures are implying a decline of -35 points after yesterday&apos;s -23.14 points or -0.39% decline&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq futures are implying a decline of -131 points after falling -72.75 points or -0.38%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the European markets, the major indices are lower at the start of the US session:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German Dax, -0.21%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC, -0.66% &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE 100, -0.02%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex, -0.36%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB, -0.24%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market, yields higher with the yield curve steepening. The two-year yield to his back of 4%. The 30-year yield is back above 5%:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield 4.002%, +3.2 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.119%, +5.2 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year yield 4.544%, +6.4 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year yield 5.035%, +6.8 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil up $0.65 at $62.86&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold is up $20.44 or 0.62% at $3310.34&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin is trading down $353 at $106,502. Intraday high price reached $108,035&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive European FX news wrap: UK inflation surprises to the upside</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-uk-inflation-surprises-to-the-upside-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:41:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-uk-inflation-surprises-to-the-upside-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;article__title&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-speaker-johnson-we-came-to-40000-salt-deduction-cap-agreement-20250521/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;US House Speaker Johnson: We came to $40,000 SALT deduction cap agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-de-guindos-2-price-goal-to-be-reached-sooner-than-later-20250521/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s de Guindos: 2% price goal to be reached sooner than later&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-mba-mortgage-applications-we-16-may-51-vs-11-prior-20250521/&quot;&gt;US MBA mortgage applications w.e. 16 May -5.1% vs +1.1% prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-kazaks-the-ecb-will-soon-reach-terminal-rate-if-baseline-holds-20250521/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Kazaks: The ECB will soon reach terminal rate if baseline holds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-de-guindos-equity-valuations-are-high-credit-spreads-out-of-sync-with-risk-20250521/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s de Guindos: Equity valuations are high, credit spreads out of sync with risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/traders-trim-bets-on-boe-easing-favouring-just-one-rate-cut-in-2025-20250521/&quot;&gt;Traders trim bets on BoE easing favouring just one rate cut in 2025&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-cpi-35-vs-33-yy-expected-20250521/&quot;&gt;UK April CPI +3.5% vs +3.3% y/y expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/fx-option-expiries-for-21-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250521/&quot;&gt;FX option expiries for 21 May 10am New York cut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japans-super-long-bond-yields-continue-to-surge-to-record-highs-20250521/&quot;&gt;Japan&apos;s super-long bond yields continue to surge to record highs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/what-are-the-main-events-for-today-20250521/&quot;&gt;What are the main events for today?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calling today&apos;s session boring would be an euphemism. The newsflow was extremely limited and we got no data other than the UK CPI report. The UK inflation figures beat expectations by a big margin and triggered a repricing in interest rates expectations with the market now favouring just one rate cut in 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global long term yields remain elevated as bond traders might not only worry about debts now but also about inflation as central banks continue to downplay inflation risks and focus more on the growth part. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the final part of the session we also got the news that Republicans have reached an agreement to increase the state and local tax (SALT) deduction to $40,000, which was one of the final hurdles holding up Trump&apos;s &quot;big, beautiful bill&quot;. The House Speaker has also said that they could vote on the bill tonight. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA SAYS US TRADE TALKS ARE AN IMPORTANT STEP TO BRIDGE GAPS BUT MULTILATERALISM IS NEEDED TO FIND A WAY OUT FROM THE GLOBAL TRADE TURMOIL - CHINA STATEMENT TO WTO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925150020598170056#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:21:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925150020598170056#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA SAYS US TRADE TALKS ARE AN IMPORTANT STEP TO BRIDGE GAPS BUT MULTILATERALISM IS NEEDED TO FIND A WAY OUT FROM THE GLOBAL TRADE TURMOIL - CHINA STATEMENT TO WTO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US House Speaker Johnson: We came to $40,000 SALT deduction cap agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-speaker-johnson-we-came-to-40000-salt-deduction-cap-agreement-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:20:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-house-speaker-johnson-we-came-to-40000-salt-deduction-cap-agreement-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;US House Speaker Johnson said that they reached an agreement on the $40,000 SALT deduction cap. Hardline conservatives have been resistant to a significant hike to the deduction cap. This should be a big step forward in passing the party’s “big, beautiful bill.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A congressional correspondent with CNN posted on X that the House Speaker said they will try to vote tonight.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US STATE REP. HARRIS SAYS IN HIS OPINION, TAX BILL GOT WORSE OVERNIGHT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925147619443032212#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:12:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925147619443032212#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US STATE REP. HARRIS SAYS IN HIS OPINION, TAX BILL GOT WORSE OVERNIGHT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s de Guindos: 2% price goal to be reached sooner than later</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-de-guindos-2-price-goal-to-be-reached-sooner-than-later-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:10:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-de-guindos-2-price-goal-to-be-reached-sooner-than-later-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2% price goal to be reached sooner than later.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We can&apos;t be complacent on fiscal risks for markets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Energy costs and the Euro to push inflation down.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some one-offs boosted Q1 GDP in Eurozone.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New projections to go in &apos;same direction&apos; as EU&apos;s.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Many risks we&apos;ve flagged have become reality.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t have the same conviction on the ECB reaching the 2% goal sooner than later, unless he&apos;s talking about headline CPI which could be affected by lower energy prices. Services inflation has been running above 4% since 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $TSLA - BYD EUROPE: BY THE END OF 2025, WILL HAVE MORE THAN 1000 SALES LOCATIONS IN EUROPE

BYD EUROPE: THIS YEAR WE WILL ENTER 12 NEW MARKETS IN EUROPE

BYD EUROPE: WITHIN FIVE YEARS WE WANT CUSTOMERS TO SAY BYD IS A EUROPEAN CARMAKE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925144895854952562#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925144895854952562#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TSLA&quot;&gt;$TSLA&lt;/a&gt; - BYD EUROPE: BY THE END OF 2025, WILL HAVE MORE THAN 1000 SALES LOCATIONS IN EUROPE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
BYD EUROPE: THIS YEAR WE WILL ENTER 12 NEW MARKETS IN EUROPE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
BYD EUROPE: WITHIN FIVE YEARS WE WANT CUSTOMERS TO SAY BYD IS A EUROPEAN CARMAKE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US AVERAGE 30-YEAR MORTGAGE RATE RISES 6 BPS TO 6.92 PCT IN MAY 16 WEEK - MBA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925144741840081154#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:00:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925144741840081154#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US AVERAGE 30-YEAR MORTGAGE RATE RISES 6 BPS TO 6.92 PCT IN MAY 16 WEEK - MBA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US MBA mortgage applications w.e. 16 May -5.1% vs +1.1% prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-mba-mortgage-applications-we-16-may-51-vs-11-prior-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 11:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-mba-mortgage-applications-we-16-may-51-vs-11-prior-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +1.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Market index 238.5 vs 251.2 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Purchase index 157.8 vs 166.5 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refinance index 682.5 vs 718.1 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year mortgage rate 6.92% vs 6.86% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is never a market moving release. Of course, as long term interest 
rates rise, mortgage applications fall. The mortgage market index and 
the US30Y yield are inversely correlated. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BLOOMBERG SPOX: SYSTEMS ARE RETURNING TO NORMAL OPERATIONS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925140320099987877#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:43:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925140320099987877#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BLOOMBERG SPOX: SYSTEMS ARE RETURNING TO NORMAL OPERATIONS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. 30-YEAR TREASURY YIELD TOPS 5% AGAIN AMID GLOBAL BOND SELLOFF

🔸 This marks only the second time since 2007 that 30-year yields have topped 5%.
🔸 U.S. 30-year yield rose to 5.026%, the highest since October 2023, as global bond markets declined.
🔸 Rise driven by U.S. fiscal concerns and broader selloff in global bonds.
🔸 UK yields surged on stronger inflation data; Japanese yields jumped after a weak bond auction.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925139378466152745#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925139378466152745#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. 30-YEAR TREASURY YIELD TOPS 5% AGAIN AMID GLOBAL BOND SELLOFF&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 This marks only the second time since 2007 that 30-year yields have topped 5%.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 U.S. 30-year yield rose to 5.026%, the highest since October 2023, as global bond markets declined.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Rise driven by U.S. fiscal concerns and broader selloff in global bonds.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 UK yields surged on stronger inflation data; Japanese yields jumped after a weak bond auction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CANTOR FITZGERALD ON NVIDIA ( $NVDA): STILL A TOP PICK

🔸 Analyst C.J. Muse reiterates Overweight rating and $200 price target.

🔸 Despite a $15B hit to 2025 data center revenue from China restrictions, Q2 guidance is expected to be stronger than feared ($46B revenue vs. $46.3B consensus).

🔸 Blackwell chip ramp and improving shipment visibility support bullish outlook.

🔸 2025 data center revenue forecast: $200B (vs. $175B consensus), even with China impact.

🔸 Management likely to express confidence in AI spending through 2026 and reiterate mid-70% gross margins in 2H 2025.

🔸 EPS estimates: $5.00 for 2025 (vs. $4.37 consensus), $6.50–$7.00 for 2026 (vs. $5.59 consensus).

🔸 Shares still seen as undervalued at 26.8x/19.9x expected 2025/2026 EPS.

🔸 Earnings call on May 28 expected to be a key positive catalyst.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925138636984516912#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:36:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925138636984516912#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CANTOR FITZGERALD ON NVIDIA ( &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt;): STILL A TOP PICK&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Analyst C.J. Muse reiterates Overweight rating and $200 price target.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Despite a $15B hit to 2025 data center revenue from China restrictions, Q2 guidance is expected to be stronger than feared ($46B revenue vs. $46.3B consensus).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Blackwell chip ramp and improving shipment visibility support bullish outlook.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 2025 data center revenue forecast: $200B (vs. $175B consensus), even with China impact.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Management likely to express confidence in AI spending through 2026 and reiterate mid-70% gross margins in 2H 2025.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 EPS estimates: $5.00 for 2025 (vs. $4.37 consensus), $6.50–$7.00 for 2026 (vs. $5.59 consensus).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Shares still seen as undervalued at 26.8x/19.9x expected 2025/2026 EPS.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Earnings call on May 28 expected to be a key positive catalyst.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TARGET CORP ( $TGT) Q1 EARNINGS SUMMARY:

🔸 Q1 Net Sales: $23.85B (vs. $24.27B expected)
🔸 Q1 Adjusted EPS: $1.30 (vs. $1.61 expected)
🔸 Q1 Comparable Sales: -3.8% (vs. -1.08% expected)

2025 Outlook:

🔸 Sales: Expected to decline in low single digits (vs. +0.27% expected)
🔸 Adjusted EPS: $7.00–$9.00 (vs. $8.40 expected)

Other Updates:

🔸 Launched &quot;acceleration office&quot; led by Michael Fiddelke
🔸 Amy Tu, Chief Legal &amp; Compliance Officer, is departing</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925137500848198055#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:32:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925137500848198055#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TARGET CORP ( &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23TGT&quot;&gt;$TGT&lt;/a&gt;) Q1 EARNINGS SUMMARY:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Q1 Net Sales: $23.85B (vs. $24.27B expected)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Q1 Adjusted EPS: $1.30 (vs. $1.61 expected)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Q1 Comparable Sales: -3.8% (vs. -1.08% expected)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
2025 Outlook:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Sales: Expected to decline in low single digits (vs. +0.27% expected)&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Adjusted EPS: $7.00–$9.00 (vs. $8.40 expected)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Other Updates:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Launched &quot;acceleration office&quot; led by Michael Fiddelke&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Amy Tu, Chief Legal &amp; Compliance Officer, is departing&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BLOOMBERG TERMINAL OUTAGE HITS TRADERS

Bloomberg, the markets data and media service, suffered widespread disruption on Wednesday morning that prevented traders from accessing live pricing and delayed an auction of UK government debt.

Users complained that the $28,000-a-year Bloomberg terminal service was running with significant delays and that the absence of live pricing prevented them from carrying out trades.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925136660951404736#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:28:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925136660951404736#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BLOOMBERG TERMINAL OUTAGE HITS TRADERS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Bloomberg, the markets data and media service, suffered widespread disruption on Wednesday morning that prevented traders from accessing live pricing and delayed an auction of UK government debt.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Users complained that the $28,000-a-year Bloomberg terminal service was running with significant delays and that the absence of live pricing prevented them from carrying out trades.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MOSCOW MAYOR SOBYANIN SAYS AIR DEFENCE SYSTEMS DOWNED THREE DRONES EN ROUTE TO MOSCOW

OPERATIONS AT MOSCOW SHEREMETYEVO AIRPORT RESTRICTED - REGULATOR</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925136418084430200#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:27:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925136418084430200#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MOSCOW MAYOR SOBYANIN SAYS AIR DEFENCE SYSTEMS DOWNED THREE DRONES EN ROUTE TO MOSCOW&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
OPERATIONS AT MOSCOW SHEREMETYEVO AIRPORT RESTRICTED - REGULATOR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) EU INDUSTRY CHIEF PUSHES ‘BUY EUROPEAN’ IN RESPONSE TO DONALD TRUMP 

The EU plans to prioritize European companies in public procurement, aiming to reduce reliance on foreign suppliers amid global trade tensions, particularly with the US and China.

Prompted by former US President Trump&apos;s tariffs and NATO threats, the EU is pushing for greater self-sufficiency in key sectors like tech, defense, and raw materials. Stéphane Séjourné, EU executive vice-president, unveiled a plan to streamline internal market rules and introduce a “Buy European Act” that would allow governments to exclude foreign bidders from public contracts—currently restricted by EU and WTO rules.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925136313428148610#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:27:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925136313428148610#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EU INDUSTRY CHIEF PUSHES ‘BUY EUROPEAN’ IN RESPONSE TO DONALD TRUMP &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The EU plans to prioritize European companies in public procurement, aiming to reduce reliance on foreign suppliers amid global trade tensions, particularly with the US and China.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Prompted by former US President Trump&apos;s tariffs and NATO threats, the EU is pushing for greater self-sufficiency in key sectors like tech, defense, and raw materials. Stéphane Séjourné, EU executive vice-president, unveiled a plan to streamline internal market rules and introduce a “Buy European Act” that would allow governments to exclude foreign bidders from public contracts—currently restricted by EU and WTO rules.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. S&amp;P 500 E-MINI FUTURES, NASDAQ 100 AND DOW FUTURES EXTEND DECLINES; LAST DOWN 0.8% EACH</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925135036568735761#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:22:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925135036568735761#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. S&amp;amp;P 500 E-MINI FUTURES, NASDAQ 100 AND DOW FUTURES EXTEND DECLINES; LAST DOWN 0.8% EACH&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Market Guides Introduces New Scanner Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/stock-market-guides-introduces-new-scanner-technology-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 10:01:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/stock-market-guides-introduces-new-scanner-technology-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Stock Market Guides, a company that offers stock market
scanning software, has announced the latest improvement to its proprietary
stock scanner technology. Their stock scanner not only finds trade setups in
real time that are popular among active traders, but it also now shows how each
of those trade setups performed historically according to backtest research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Andy Yuda, a Senior Consultant at Stock Market
Guides, &quot;One example of a scan we offer is for oversold stocks based on
their RSI indicator. It&apos;s a popular trade setup for many active stock traders.
Before you pull the trigger on buying a stock that&apos;s oversold, wouldn’t you
want to know how that stock has performed historically when it’s been oversold?
If that stock doesn&apos;t have a track record of success historically for that
trade setup, why buy it now? That historical performance is the information our
scanner brings to light.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This new technology is available not only for active stock
traders, but also for buy-and-hold investors as well as option traders. The
scanner at Stock Market Guides caters to trade setups based on technical
analysis, like chart patterns and stock indicators, as well as investments
based on fundamental analysis, like price-to-earnings ratios and earnings
growth.Customers
can also enable the scanner to pick trades for them. This is offered for both
stocks and stock options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This scanner technology upgrade is the latest feature that
Stock Market Guides has made available to retail investors.  They also
offer free educational guides that cover everything from how to buy stocks all
the way to how to calculate advanced stock market indicator values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About Stock Market Guides&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stock Market Guides
is based in Altadena, California, and has been offering stock scanning services
to the public since 2023. Prior to that, its founders did years of research and
development that led to the creation of the business and its offerings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information about Stock Market Guides and its
range of educational content and services, users can visit
https://www.stockmarketguides.com. Stock Market Guides continues to provide
educational content aimed at supporting informed financial decision-making for
its readership.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Kazaks: The ECB will soon reach terminal rate if baseline holds</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-kazaks-the-ecb-will-soon-reach-terminal-rate-if-baseline-holds-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:32:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-kazaks-the-ecb-will-soon-reach-terminal-rate-if-baseline-holds-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ECB will soon reach terminal rate if baseline holds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interest rate cuts are nearing an end assuming inflation stabilises at 2% over the coming months.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s important to analise alternative scenarios amid the trade uncertainty.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If either inflationary or deflationary risk scenario materialises, monetary policy will react accordingly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market sees the terminal rate for the ECB around 1.75%, which is equivalent to two more 25 bps cuts.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google&apos;s VEO 3 AI Video Generation is Insane. Hollywood (and Related) Stocks to Short?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/googles-veo-3-ai-video-generation-is-insane-hollywood-and-related-stocks-to-short-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:29:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/googles-veo-3-ai-video-generation-is-insane-hollywood-and-related-stocks-to-short-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;1:1-1:164&quot;&gt;Prepare to be astonished. Google DeepMind just unveiled Veo 3, a video generation model that is, quite literally, mind-blowing. We&apos;ve never seen anything like it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;3:1-3:325&quot;&gt;Veo can generate high-definition, 8-second videos complete with incredibly realistic and perfectly synchronized audio. Forget heavily curated demos – here  Dr. Furkan Gözükara, a PhD Computer Engineer, gathered 60 un-cherry-picked examples from users on Twitter. Because let&apos;s be real, seeing what people are actually creating is the true test of any hyped-up release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&quot;6:1-6:95&quot;&gt;🔗 Official website: &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; externallink=&quot;&quot; jslog=&quot;197247;track:generic_click,impression;BardVeMetadataKey:[[r_907bc73730036066,c_2b1c4b68ac1a3bad,null,rc_b10ecef143cda07c,null,null,en,null,1,null,null,1,0]]&quot; href=&quot;https://deepmind.google/models/veo/&quot; class=&quot;ng-star-inserted&quot;&gt;https://deepmind.google/models/veo/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stocks to Short as Hollywood Film Making Might Be Disrupted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Always do your own research, we at ForexLive.com do not provide financial advice but our experts continue to give you wonderful &apos;heads up&apos;, early in the game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AI Disruption in Hollywood: Top Stocks to Short Amid Google&apos;s Veo3 Launch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence continues to disrupt major industries, and Hollywood is no exception. Recent advancements, especially Google&apos;s unveiling of Veo3 and its Flow filmmaking tool, mark a significant turning point in movie production economics. High-quality filmmaking capabilities that previously required substantial financial investments are becoming widely accessible, posing severe threats to traditional film studios and entertainment stocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google&apos;s Veo3 and Flow: Revolutionizing Film Production&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During Google I/O 2025, the technology giant introduced Veo3, an advanced AI-powered video creation tool developed by DeepMind. Veo3 allows users—including independent creators, filmmakers, and businesses—to generate professional-grade videos simply through text or image prompts. Its ability to integrate realistic sound effects, dialogue, and accurate lip-sync and movements significantly surpasses previous AI models, bringing professional filmmaking capabilities into the hands of everyday users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complementing Veo3, Google also launched Flow, an intuitive filmmaking platform designed specifically for creatives. Flow empowers storytellers to effortlessly produce cinematic-quality scenes and short films. The tool, supported by Google&apos;s Gemini AI models, translates everyday language prompts into stunningly realistic visual outputs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stocks to Short Due to AI Disruption&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The democratization of film production brought on by Veo3 and similar AI tools threatens several legacy media and entertainment companies, making their stocks potential targets for short sellers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Paramount Global (NASDAQ: PARA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paramount is highly reliant on conventional TV channels and traditional film production methods. Its slower transition to digital-first streaming, combined with limited financial adaptability, makes it particularly susceptible to rapid market share loss driven by AI-enhanced competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. AMC Entertainment Holdings (NYSE: AMC)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMC depends heavily on theatrical movie releases. The proliferation of high-quality AI-generated home entertainment could significantly decrease theater attendance, exacerbating AMC&apos;s already tenuous financial stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. Lions Gate Entertainment (NYSE: LGF.A)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lions Gate, as a smaller, independent film studio without strong digital distribution channels, is especially vulnerable. The company&apos;s reliance on expensive, conventional filmmaking methods places it directly at risk from AI-driven video creation technologies, potentially undermining its entire business model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netflix Could Gain from AI Advancements?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, Netflix (NASDAQ: NFLX) appears well-positioned to benefit from the AI-driven disruption. With its robust digital-first approach, Netflix can leverage AI tools like Veo3 to significantly reduce production costs. The future of filmmaking may shift substantially toward lower-cost AI-assisted productions managed by skilled prompt engineers and compelling storytelling teams, offering Netflix a substantial competitive edge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical Analysis: Lions Gate Stock at Critical Juncture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So here is one example you can check out. From a technical standpoint, Lions Gate&apos;s stock currently shows a downward-sloping channel, which could traditionally signal a bullish flag. However, caution is warranted. A decisive break below the critical support range of $6.40-$6.50 could trigger significant bearish momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market sentiment toward Lions Gate has already turned increasingly negative following Google&apos;s Veo3 announcement. The stock has recently struggled around mid-channel resistance levels, making it an attractive candidate for short sellers monitoring technical indicators closely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Orientation for Investors Associated With AI-powered Video&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors should pay close attention to both technical setups and fundamental vulnerabilities. Lions Gate provides an illustrative example of the kind of stock vulnerable to short selling in response to AI disruption in Hollywood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the AI landscape evolves, investors and traders must adapt quickly, conducting thorough due diligence into companies&apos; strategic resilience or vulnerability to AI-driven shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reminder: ForexLive.com is evolving into &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investinglive.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;investingLive.com&lt;/a&gt; later this year, expanding its market coverage and offering enhanced decision support tools, market insights, and live financial analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: Always invest and trade at your own risk. This article does not constitute financial advice.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How trading different asset classes can increase your chances of success</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/how-trading-different-asset-classes-can-increase-your-chances-of-success-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 09:13:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/how-trading-different-asset-classes-can-increase-your-chances-of-success-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;tweet mt-2 ng-binding&quot; ng-bind-html=&quot;secure(th.tweet, tweet)&quot;&gt;Different asset classes respond in different ways to various fundamental developments. You can have bonds selling-off because the central bank is tightening monetary policy or you can have an FX pair in an uptrend because the central bank of the currency that is appreciating is raising interest rates, while the central bank of the currency that is depreciating is cutting rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;tweet mt-2 ng-binding&quot; ng-bind-html=&quot;secure(th.tweet, tweet)&quot;&gt;You can also have various equity sectors responding in different ways to economic events with cyclical stocks falling during hard times and defensive stocks rising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;tweet mt-2 ng-binding&quot; ng-bind-html=&quot;secure(th.tweet, tweet)&quot;&gt;When you build your trading idea you should find a market where your idea can be expressed in the best possible way giving you the highest return for the risk taken. This process will also keep you disciplined as you will look only for the highest conviction trades and refrain from taking trades just out of boredom. Remember that your job is not to trade but to make money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stanley Druckenmiller once said that one of the reasons for his success was that he was lucky to travel across asset classes. He traded commodities, currencies, bonds and equities and it gave him the discipline to trade only what he had the highest conviction in. If he didn&apos;t have a good idea in equities, he was happy to have no equities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;tweet mt-2 ng-binding&quot; ng-bind-html=&quot;secure(th.tweet, tweet)&quot;&gt;Imagine you have two central banks beginning to tighten their monetary policy and the risk sentiment picture is murky. Given that, you may have the corresponding FX pair just ranging and not giving you any high probability trade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;tweet mt-2 ng-binding&quot; ng-bind-html=&quot;secure(th.tweet, tweet)&quot;&gt;What you can do though is to trade the country&apos;s government bonds as a tighter policy will cause a drop in those securities. In this way you reduce your risk and increase your chances of success. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;tweet mt-2 ng-binding&quot; ng-bind-html=&quot;secure(th.tweet, tweet)&quot;&gt;With more experience you’ll start to notice that when you have high conviction in your trade, because you clearly see the reasons for taking a position, your psychological pressure will be much lower compared to the times when you force trades trying to outsmart the market.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) DONALD TRUMP JR WHEN ASKED IF HE WOULD RUN FOR PRESIDENT: &quot;YOU NEVER KNOW&quot;</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1925113551691084121#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:56:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1925113551691084121#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DONALD TRUMP JR WHEN ASKED IF HE WOULD RUN FOR PRESIDENT: &quot;YOU NEVER KNOW&quot;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Traders Redefines Prop Trader Success</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/ultimate-traders-redefines-prop-trader-success-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:43:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/ultimate-traders-redefines-prop-trader-success-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;In prop trading, factors like developing a strong psychology and mindset are as important in reaching financial goals as a successful strategy. Award-winning firm &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ultimatetraders.com/?utm_source=publishers&amp;amp;utm_medium=media&amp;amp;utm_content=homepage&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Ultimate Traders&lt;/a&gt; recognises this and prioritises this within its growing community by providing the education, tools, and technology for each challenge participant to trade at their own pace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;This is not the only way the company is innovative in its relationship with its clients. As a younger, tech-savvy group, it not only wants to get funded to trade, it also believes in genuine partnership. In its funded trader program, the firm supports freedom of trading styles while focusing on reliable resources for traders that enable them to exchange ideas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The shift in broker-trader relations led by the prop company is rippling across the industry, moving the focus away from isolated, high-pressure environments to platforms that foster trading groups, ongoing education, and shared experiences of the ups and downs in the markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Prop firm challenge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;To take on a market challenge, Ultimate Traders sees educational resources as a priority, not an afterthought. As one of the best prop trading firms, it offers structured learning which is tailored to individual needs, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Strategy guides and psychological performance modules&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Real-time trade analysis and video walkthroughs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Access to experienced mentors for performance reviews and risk management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Regularly updated materials driven by feedback&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;This approach ensures traders are equipped not just to participate, but to excel and adapt as markets evolve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Mentoring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Group solidarity is recognised as a catalyst for trader growth. The prop firm has invested in interactive spaces such as its dedicated, private Discord servers where traders at all levels can share insights, discuss strategies, and support one another. Whether someone is looking for prop trading for beginners or is an experienced trader, the resources for improvement and growth are all in one place. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Weekly sessions, trade recaps, and mental resilience discussions help to build a culture of collaboration. Mentorship teams, often composed of experienced traders, provide hands-on guidance, clarify rules, and celebrate milestones - going far beyond traditional customer service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;There are also plans to explore in-person meet-ups and build a trader advisory panel with active traders. By sharing daily trading experience, they could offer valuable feedback to boost an even more dynamic evolution in the prop trading industry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Awards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;In pursuing its goal to identify talented traders, Ultimate Traders has won several awards, including Most Transparent Prop Firm (2024) and Best Prop Trading Firm (2024).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Ultimate Traders review&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The company’s testimonials on Trustpilot often have five stars, highlighting fast payouts, fair pricing, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ultimatetraders.com/?utm_source=publishers&amp;amp;utm_medium=media&amp;amp;utm_content=homepage&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;a smooth, organised challenge process, and the clarity of trading rules&lt;/a&gt;. Endorsements like the following reinforce the value of a transparent experience. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;“I am pretty new to prop trading and I appreciate their effort in making the rules as clear as possible. There is nothing that is left behind, just navigate to the Trading Rules page on their website and here everything you need to know is displayed.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Jamala A.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Instant funding prop firm&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;There are no ongoing membership fees - just a one-time, refundable fee for challenge participation. This model removes barriers and allows traders to focus on developing their skills and strategies in their own time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;“Legit prop firm that actually paid out. First, I passed the 50k challenge and got funded. Then, I got a successful streak of trades and applied for a payout. They processed it fast.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Lillian H.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;“I didn’t expect to see prices for all those funded accounts so cheap. I thought it would cost me a fortune. Obviously, I chose a classic challenge and bought a funded account with a balance of $25,000 for $169. I would have never thought that it’s possible to buy a funded account for such a low price. The transaction was through a bank card and everything went pretty smoothly.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Jose R.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Flexible and inclusive &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The new trading landscape is defined by flexibility and inclusivity. The company offers a range of challenges and funding opportunities. These fit diverse styles, from scalping and day trading to swing and algorithmic strategies, and are available to traders from around the world. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Profit-sharing arrangements are also evolving, with some enabling retention of up to 90% of gains, and the chance to scale up to substantially funded accounts. This alignment of interests encourages long-term commitment and performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Technology and market access&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;State-of-the-art platforms, such as MetaTrader 4, provide advanced charting, algorithmic trading capabilities, and access across devices. Those who trade with firm capital can engage with hundreds of instruments, including forex, commodities, metals, indices, and shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Today, the forex prop firm redefines a successful partnership with traders as dynamic mutual personal and professional growth. By combining transparency, robust education, flexible opportunities, and a strong sense of community, they are setting new standards for what participants can expect. On Ultimate Traders’ platform, sustainable strategies are built on continuous learning and genuine support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Join the challenge on their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ultimatetraders.com/?utm_source=publishers&amp;amp;utm_medium=media&amp;amp;utm_content=homepage&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s de Guindos: Equity valuations are high, credit spreads out of sync with risk</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-de-guindos-equity-valuations-are-high-credit-spreads-out-of-sync-with-risk-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:06:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecbs-de-guindos-equity-valuations-are-high-credit-spreads-out-of-sync-with-risk-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Equity valuations are high, credit spreads out of sync with risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US downgrade was discounted by markets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurozone bond yields have decoupled from US, spread contained.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Markets are complacent but that can change.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Credit spreads widened a bit recently but it didn&apos;t trigger any notable pullback in European equities. There might be some complacency for sure. For example, the market got too much fixated on growth risk which is now fine, but the inflation risk is being underestimated. And no one is paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq Futures Analysis Now with orderFlow Intel at ForexLive.com</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nasdaq-futures-analysis-now-with-orderflow-intel-at-forexlivecom-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nasdaq-futures-analysis-now-with-orderflow-intel-at-forexlivecom-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Nasdaq Futures Analysis Now - Early Signs of a Possible Bullish Reversal, Using AI and Deep Order Flow Analysis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;orderFlow Intel Trader Update&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prediction Score: +4 (Bullish Bias Confirmed, Increasing Confidence)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, price action has consolidated firmly near the psychologically significant level of 21,300. Round numbers like this typically attract substantial liquidity, as market makers frequently look to trigger stop orders from both buyers and sellers around these levels. Over the past 30 minutes, bullish momentum has notably increased, with buyers actively absorbing selling pressure at recent lows—a positive sign reinforcing bullish expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quick Reminder: ForexLive.com will become investingLive.com later this year, significantly expanding our offering for investors and traders with more powerful decision-support tools, in-depth analysis, live market news, and additional advanced features. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Price Levels to Monitor:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potential Resistance at ~21,350 (Value Area Low):
Traders should watch closely here—if price reclaims and sustains above this critical level, it would substantially enhance the bullish case by moving price back within today&apos;s value area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;VWAP (~21,370):
Successfully breaking and holding above today&apos;s Volume-Weighted Average Price would strongly confirm buyers have regained market control, significantly boosting bullish confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immediate Support at ~21,286:
This historically relevant price level currently acts as important support. Its defense by buyers has thus far been encouraging. If breached, monitor the next key support at 21,260, a level identified through our advanced liquidity, volume profile, and order flow analysis methodology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding the Prediction Scale (-10 to +10):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our prediction scores range from -10 (Extremely Bearish) to +10 (Extremely Bullish). The midpoint, 0, indicates a neutral or indecisive stance. As the scores move further away from zero, the confidence and strength of our directional bias grow accordingly. Today&apos;s score of +4 signals a confirmed bullish bias with increasing confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is orderFlow Intel?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;orderFlow Intel is our specialized proprietary methodology at ForexLive.com (soon to become &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investinglive.com/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;investingLive.com&lt;/a&gt;). It integrates advanced order flow data, volumetric analytics, liquidity pools, VWAP deviations, and critical volume-profile-based price levels to give traders and investors unique insights into market moves before they fully materialize on price charts. Our approach tracks real-time buyer and seller dominance, market absorption, and hidden liquidity shifts, providing you with actionable insights to make well-informed trading decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay agile, informed, and watchful around these key price points as market conditions evolve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade Nasdaq Futures or any other financial instrument at your own risk only.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices open slightly lower with hot UK inflation likely weighing</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-open-slightly-lower-with-hot-uk-inflation-likely-weighing-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 07:14:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-indices-open-slightly-lower-with-hot-uk-inflation-likely-weighing-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eurostoxx -0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Germany DAX -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France CAC 40 -0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE -0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain IBEX +0.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;ve seen some downside in stock indices triggered by the hot UK inflation data. European indices have been on an incredible rally since Trump&apos;s tariffs pause on April 9 but inflation concerns could trigger a correction as the market would price out the rate cuts expected for the ECB. The next Eurozone CPI report will likely be key.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EC Markets Takes Centre Stage at iFX EXPO International 2025 in Limassol</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/ec-markets-takes-centre-stage-at-ifx-expo-international-2025-in-limassol-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 07:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/ec-markets-takes-centre-stage-at-ifx-expo-international-2025-in-limassol-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;In June, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecmarkets.com/ec/fwkicv&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;EC Markets&lt;/a&gt; will undertake initiatives that mark new, decisive steps in its worldwide expansion and consolidation within the financial sector. The company will play a leading role at the now established iFX Expo International 2025, which will be held from 17 to 19 June at the City of Dreams Mediterranean Resort in Limassol. This year’s iFX Expo is expected to be far more than a conventional exhibition: the gathering of thousands of financial-services professionals—representing more than 120 countries—aims to confirm its reputation as the pre-eminent forum for foreign-exchange markets, fintech and payment services both in Europe and globally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;For EC Markets, Cyprus constitutes a significant strategic hub for regional and international development, and the iFX Expo provides a timely opportunity not only to showcase corporate excellence but also to demonstrate its guiding philosophy of transparency, technological superiority and meaningful human dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Official Sponsor of the Welcome Party at Columbia Beach&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The exhibition formally opens on the evening of 17 June, and EC Markets, as exclusive sponsor of the Welcome Party, will host all participants at Columbia Beach, one of Limassol’s most iconic seafront venues. Against the backdrop of the Mediterranean and in an atmosphere that epitomises the city’s cosmopolitan character, guests will enjoy the occasion while initiating dialogue in a relaxed manner before the two demanding days that follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;For EC Markets, the Welcome Party offers an excellent opportunity to highlight a central element of its ethos: the role of the host who respects everyone active in the sector, viewing them not as competitors but as fellow travellers in the worlds of economics, innovation and entrepreneurial development. Participants in iFX Expo International 2025 will be welcomed by the CEO and Chairman, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sherwan-zeybo-1a3541b4&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Mr &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/matthew-smith-6b130b8/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Matthew Smith&lt;/a&gt;, the Group Marketing Director, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/nick-xydas/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Mr Nick Xydas&lt;/a&gt;, the Global Head of Business Development, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sherwan-zeybo-1a3541b4/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Mr Sherwan Zeybo&lt;/a&gt;, and the entire company team, in a space designed for productive and substantive discussions. Finally, the Welcome Party promises impressive surprises and a spectacular display that attendees will long remember.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;EC Markets at Booth 72 of iFX Expo Limassol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The following day, EC Markets will be at Booth 72, where our dynamic team will be available for face-to-face meetings. Visitors will have the opportunity to converse with specialist professionals and to learn about the company’s vision, as outlined by Mr Matthew Smith in early April at iFX LATAM 2025. Concurrently, EC Markets will sponsor the exhibition’s Beer Bar, providing a welcoming space in which attendees may relax and engage in informal discussions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Summer Updates: A Season of Developmental Change for EC Markets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;The upward trajectory of EC Markets continues with further tangible developments. The company will officially launch its completely redesigned corporate website, which offers an optimised registration experience, multilingual educational content, analyses and updates, as well as advanced, innovative high-level tools. The new site reflects the company’s transition towards a digitally focused, data-centric operating models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Inauguration of New Offices in Limassol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;In parallel with the website launch, EC Markets will inaugurate new offices in a modern, architecturally refined building overlooking Limassol’s Old Port. The premises will accommodate a creative, productive and diverse team, together with a content-production studio for educational and analytical material and will above all provide a secure space for dialogue in which diversity is embraced as a vital asset. This project underscores the company’s long-term commitment to investment in infrastructure and human capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;EC Markets Places Transparency, Technology and Education at the Centre of Its Strategy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;By integrating hospitality, technological advancement and an educational approach, EC Markets seeks to redefine the contemporary profile of a global broker. Its participation in iFX Expo International 2025, together with the forthcoming website launch and the new offices, exemplifies a mature strategy that, step by step, places transparency, education and regional specialisation at its core.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Those interested in following developments may visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ecmarkets.com/ec/fwkicv&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;ecmarkets.com&lt;/a&gt; or follow EC Markets on its official social-media channels for continuous updates on all initiatives and activities.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traders trim bets on BoE easing favouring just one rate cut in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/traders-trim-bets-on-boe-easing-favouring-just-one-rate-cut-in-2025-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:38:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/traders-trim-bets-on-boe-easing-favouring-just-one-rate-cut-in-2025-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The market pricing now sees 34 bps of easing in 2025 compared to 41 bps before the UK CPI release. The next cut is fully priced in for November. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is still a bit high in my opinion and I would expect some more hawkish repricing in the next weeks and months for the BoE and for other major central banks.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK April CPI +3.5% vs +3.3% y/y expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-cpi-35-vs-33-yy-expected-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 06:00:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/uk-april-cpi-35-vs-33-yy-expected-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +2.6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Core CPI +3.8% vs +3.6% y/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +3.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Services CPI +5.4% vs +4.8% y/y expected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +4.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big upside surprise for UK inflation. The market will certainly reprice the rate cut expectations to something like 25-28 bps of easing by year-end (one rate cut) and even then I&apos;m skeptical the BoE will be able to cut again in 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the risk I&apos;ve been talking about in the last few weeks. It&apos;s not growth, it&apos;s inflation now. And that will likely be the same for the ECB and the Fed. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 21 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/fx-option-expiries-for-21-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 05:23:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/fx-option-expiries-for-21-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250521/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;EUR/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1400 (EUR 1.09bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1390
(EUR 1.83bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1305 (EUR 1.23bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1270 (EUR 1.11bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.1250 (EUR 2.02 bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
144.50
(US$ 940mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
142.00 (US$ 878mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;GBP/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3500 (GBP 432mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3420 (GBP 387mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3400 (GBP 537mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1.3265 (GBP 459mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CHF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8300 (CHF 545mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8250 (CHF 1.10bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8200 (CHF 425mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.8100 (CHF 430mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
1.4270
(US$ 1.12bn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6400 (AUD 303mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.6380 (AUD 321mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;NZD/USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0.5875 (NZD 349mn)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;article-link article-link article-link&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MUSK SAYS HE PLANS TO BE AT THE WHITE HOUSE COUPLE OF DAYS EVERY FEW WEEKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924924085617750135#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:24:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924924085617750135#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MUSK SAYS HE PLANS TO BE AT THE WHITE HOUSE COUPLE OF DAYS EVERY FEW WEEKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MUSK SAYS MERGING TESLA AND XAI NOT OUT OF THE QUESTION, WOULD NEED SHAREHOLDER APPROVAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924924014130004309#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:23:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924924014130004309#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MUSK SAYS MERGING TESLA AND XAI NOT OUT OF THE QUESTION, WOULD NEED SHAREHOLDER APPROVAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ELON MUSK SAYS WILL DEPLOY A MILLION NVIDIA BLACKWELL AI CHIPS AT NEW XAI FACILITY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924923940264157608#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:23:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924923940264157608#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ELON MUSK SAYS WILL DEPLOY A MILLION NVIDIA BLACKWELL AI CHIPS AT NEW XAI FACILITY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
