<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>JP Morgan sees modest USD depreciation ahead amid rebalancing, hedging flows.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-sees-modest-usd-depreciation-ahead-amid-rebalancing-hedging-flows-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 21:37:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-sees-modest-usd-depreciation-ahead-amid-rebalancing-hedging-flows-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;220&quot; data-end=&quot;446&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;JP Morgan’s FX strategy team expects the US dollar to face mild downward pressure in the near term, driven by portfolio rebalancing and increased currency hedging—particularly from countries with large exposure to US equities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;448&quot; data-end=&quot;804&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;In a research note, the bank identified Norway, Switzerland, Canada, Sweden, the UK, Australia, and Israel as having the largest US equity holdings relative to their own GDP. “Capital repatriation could be most consequential for their currencies,” the team said, flagging these economies as potentially more sensitive to shifts in global asset allocations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;806&quot; data-end=&quot;1053&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;While the bank does not anticipate large-scale capital outflows from the US, it sees “a modest USD depreciation” as the most likely outcome in the near term, partly due to rebalancing activity and a shift toward more active FX hedging strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1055&quot; data-end=&quot;1394&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;An equal-weighted real exchange rate index of the dollar against other G10 currencies suggests the USD remains elevated on a historical basis. “In the medium to long run, currencies have generally mean-reverted in real terms,” JP Morgan noted, though it cautioned that such adjustments typically unfold over several years or even a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1396&quot; data-end=&quot;1548&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;“Even if capital outflows from the US are quite modest, a cyclical moderation in the USD still warrants a rebalancing of FX hedges,” the note concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1396&quot; data-end=&quot;1548&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1396&quot; data-end=&quot;1548&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;DXY (a USD index) update:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1396&quot; data-end=&quot;1548&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;I didn&apos;t draw in anything, but a quick eyeball suggests to me the drop has work to do around here. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US FAA issued an order reducing the flight arrival and departure rate at Newark Airport</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-faa-issued-an-order-reducing-the-flight-arrival-and-departure-rate-at-newark-airport-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 21:22:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-faa-issued-an-order-reducing-the-flight-arrival-and-departure-rate-at-newark-airport-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The airport has been beset by issues that haverve raised safety concerns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; From the US Federal Aviation Administration statement:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The FAA issued an interim order reducing the flight arrival and departure rate at Newark Liberty International Airport.Under the interim order issued Tuesday, the maximum hourly rate will be:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;28 arrivals and 28 departures until construction of Runway 4-Left/22-Right is complete. Daily construction will end on June 15, 2025, but will continue on Saturdays until the end of the year. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Outside of the construction period, 34 arrivals and departures until Oct. 25, 2025. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our goal is to relieve the substantial inconvenience to the traveling public from excessive flight delays due to construction, staffing challenges, and recent equipment issues, which magnify as they spread through the National Airspace System,” said Acting FAA Administrator Chris Rocheleau.The new limits take effect on May 20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;** &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay safe out there folks!&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Kugler speaking - does not comment on monetary policy nor on her economic outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kugler-speaking-does-not-comment-on-monetary-policy-nor-on-her-economic-outlook-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 21:01:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-kugler-speaking-does-not-comment-on-monetary-policy-nor-on-her-economic-outlook-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Federal Reserve Board Governor Adriana Kugler gives commencement address before the Spring 2025 Berkeley Economics Commencement Ceremony&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Old pic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-bostic-more-busiinesses-say-they-can-no-longer-delay-tariff-price-hikes-or-job-cuts-20250520/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Bostic: More businesses say they can no longer delay tariff price hikes or job cuts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-hearing-that-businesses-and-households-are-holding-back-from-decisions-20250520/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Musalem: Hearing that businesses and households are holding back from decisions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-monetary-policy-is-currently-is-well-positioned-20250520/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot; class=&quot;article-link&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Musalem: Monetary policy currently is well positioned&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUD: CBA brings forward RBA rate cut forecast, flags risk of earlier and deeper easing</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/aud-cba-brings-forward-rba-rate-cut-forecast-flags-risk-of-earlier-and-deeper-easing-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/aud-cba-brings-forward-rba-rate-cut-forecast-flags-risk-of-earlier-and-deeper-easing-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;206&quot; data-end=&quot;477&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Commonwealth Bank of Australia has brought forward its rate cut expectations, now pencilling in reductions in both August and September, as moderating inflation and softening wage growth increase the likelihood of earlier monetary easing by the Reserve Bank of Australia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“We continue to expect two further rate cuts this year, but now favour August and September,” CBA economists said in a note. “The catalyst for the shift has been the RBA’s change in tone on inflation.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;682&quot; data-end=&quot;883&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;CBA has retained its base case of four cuts for the current easing cycle—first outlined in October 2023—which would take the cash rate from 4.35% to 3.35%, a level the bank says is “closer to neutral.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;885&quot; data-end=&quot;1178&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;However, the bank warned that downside risks are building. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“Inflation has moderated relatively quickly and wages growth is slowing, even as the unemployment rate holds steady at 4.1%,” the note said, highlighting a sluggish consumer recovery and heightened global uncertainty as key headwinds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1180&quot; data-end=&quot;1428&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;While CBA still sees August as the more likely starting point for renewed easing, it did not rule out a July cut. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;“The risk lies with additional and quicker easing,” the bank noted. “But the RBA would have to see hard data for this to materialise.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1430&quot; data-end=&quot;1589&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;CBA also flagged the possibility of the RBA having to move the cash rate into “slightly stimulatory territory” should global conditions worsen more materially.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1430&quot; data-end=&quot;1589&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The dates ahead to be aware of. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil: private survey of inventory shows headline crude oil build vs. draw expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-private-survey-of-inventory-shows-headline-crude-oil-build-vs-draw-expected-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:33:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-private-survey-of-inventory-shows-headline-crude-oil-build-vs-draw-expected-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Via oilprice.com on Twitter:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expectations I had seen centred on:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;Headline crude -1.3mn barrels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;Distillates -1.4mn bbls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;Gasoline -0.5 mn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;This data point is from a privately-conducted survey by the American Petroleum Institute (API).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;It&apos;s a survey of oil storage facilities and companies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The official report is due Wednesday morning US time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two reports are quite different.The official government data comes from the US Energy Information Administration (EIA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Its based on data from the Department of Energy and other government agencies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;Whereas information on total crude oil storage levels and variations from the previous week&apos;s levels are both provided by the API report, the EIA report also provides statistics on inputs and outputs from refineries, as well as other significant indicators of the status of the oil market, and storage levels for various grades of crude oil, such as light, medium, and heavy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;the EIA report is held to be more accurate and comprehensive than the survey from the API&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MUSK SAYS HE PLANS TO BE AT THE WHITE HOUSE COUPLE OF DAYS EVERY FEW WEEKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924924085617750135#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:24:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924924085617750135#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MUSK SAYS HE PLANS TO BE AT THE WHITE HOUSE COUPLE OF DAYS EVERY FEW WEEKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MUSK SAYS MERGING TESLA AND XAI NOT OUT OF THE QUESTION, WOULD NEED SHAREHOLDER APPROVAL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924924014130004309#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:23:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924924014130004309#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MUSK SAYS MERGING TESLA AND XAI NOT OUT OF THE QUESTION, WOULD NEED SHAREHOLDER APPROVAL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ELON MUSK SAYS WILL DEPLOY A MILLION NVIDIA BLACKWELL AI CHIPS AT NEW XAI FACILITY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924923940264157608#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:23:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924923940264157608#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ELON MUSK SAYS WILL DEPLOY A MILLION NVIDIA BLACKWELL AI CHIPS AT NEW XAI FACILITY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Canada rate cut hopes dwindle after hotter core CPI</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-canada-rate-cut-hopes-dwindle-after-hotter-core-cpi-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:20:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-canada-rate-cut-hopes-dwindle-after-hotter-core-cpi-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-april-cpi-17-yy-vs-16-expected-20250520/&quot;&gt;Canada April CPI +1.7% y/y vs +1.6% expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurozone-may-flash-consumer-confidence-152-vs-160-expected-20250520/&quot;&gt;Eurozone May flash consumer confidence -15.2 vs -16.0 expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-hearing-that-businesses-and-households-are-holding-back-from-decisions-20250520/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Musalem: Hearing that businesses and households are holding back from decisions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-bostic-more-busiinesses-say-they-can-no-longer-delay-tariff-price-hikes-or-job-cuts-20250520/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Bostic: More busiinesses say they can no longer delay tariff price hikes or job cuts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-monetary-policy-is-currently-is-well-positioned-20250520/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Musalem: Monetary policy currently is well positioned&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/kazakhstan-has-boosted-oil-output-so-far-this-year-in-defiance-of-opec-20250520/&quot;&gt;Kazakhstan has boosted oil output so far this year in defiance of OPEC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canadian-house-prices-fell-for-the-fourth-consecutive-month-in-april-20250520/&quot;&gt;Canadian house prices fell for the fourth consecutive month in April&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-pboc-reiterates-implementation-of-loose-monetary-policy-20250520/&quot;&gt;The PBoC reiterates implementation of loose monetary policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude oil down 7-cents to $62.56&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields up 1 bps to 4.49%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold up $65 to $3293&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P 500 down 0.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CHF leads, AUD lags&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blowout in Japanese bonds and the RBA rate cut teed up a lively session for North American traders. Early on, we saw CAD jump as core CPI numbers were hotter than expected. That led to BOC June rate cut odds falling to 35% from 65% and USD/CAD to fall 34 pips to 1.3914, edging below a series of lows this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US dollar started the session out strong as yields rose but was steadily sold as the day continued. The pound sagged to a session low early in New York trade but rallied 50 pips from there to 1.3386 to finish near the European high. The euro finished at the best level of the day and just shy of Monday&apos;s peak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUD/USD was pressured after the RBA cut and said it considered a 50 bps cut but after some heavy selling in Asia and early Europe the Aussie found a bottom and bounced by 30 pips as the US dollar sagged broadly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Newsflow was light but the bond market may have seen some selling after Trump leaned on Congressional Republicans to pass the tax cut bill without any fresh cost cuts. The House is expected to vote in the week ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP&apos;S APPROVAL RATING FALLS TO 42%, REUTERS/IPSOS POLL FINDS, DOWN 2 PERCENTAGE POINTS FROM EARLY-MAY POLL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924921299047960650#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:12:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924921299047960650#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP&apos;S APPROVAL RATING FALLS TO 42%, REUTERS/IPSOS POLL FINDS, DOWN 2 PERCENTAGE POINTS FROM EARLY-MAY POLL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: EVERYTHING IN GOLDEN DOME WILL BE MADE IN USA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924920940325986370#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:11:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924920940325986370#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: EVERYTHING IN GOLDEN DOME WILL BE MADE IN USA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade ideas thread for Wednesday, 21 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-for-wednesday-21-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-for-wednesday-21-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Good morning, afternoon and evening all. Any charts, technical analysis, trade ideas, thoughts, views, ForexLive traders would like to share and discuss with fellow ForexLive traders, please do so:
 &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: TALKING ABOUT $175 BLN TOTAL COST</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924919654633312603#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:06:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924919654633312603#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: TALKING ABOUT $175 BLN TOTAL COST&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: OUR TECHNOLOGY IS MORE ADVANCED THAN THAT OF ISRAEL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924919567236661298#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924919567236661298#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: OUR TECHNOLOGY IS MORE ADVANCED THAN THAT OF ISRAEL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: CANADA SAYS THEY WANT TO BE PART OF IT

TRUMP: GOLDEN DOME SHOULD BE OPERATIONAL BY END OF MY TERM</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924919380325851548#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924919380325851548#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: CANADA SAYS THEY WANT TO BE PART OF IT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: GOLDEN DOME SHOULD BE OPERATIONAL BY END OF MY TERM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: SELECTED ARCHITECTURE FOR GOLDEN DOME

TRUMP: WILL INCLUDE SPACE-BASED INTERCEPTORS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924919222074843293#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:04:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924919222074843293#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: SELECTED ARCHITECTURE FOR GOLDEN DOME&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
TRUMP: WILL INCLUDE SPACE-BASED INTERCEPTORS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic calendar in Asia 21 May 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-wednesday-21-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:00:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-wednesday-21-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;A low key session ahead for data, but we have four Federal Reserve speakers lined up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2100 GMT /1700 US Eastern time - Federal Reserve Board Governor Adriana Kugler gives commencement address before the Spring 2025 Berkeley Economics Commencement Ceremony&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2300 GMT /1900 US Eastern time - Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco President Mary Daly and Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland President Beth Hammack give keynotes, and Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta President Raphael Bostic moderates a discussion before the 2025 Financial Markets Conference&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday we had:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-bostic-more-busiinesses-say-they-can-no-longer-delay-tariff-price-hikes-or-job-cuts-20250520/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Bostic: More businesses say they can no longer delay tariff price hikes or job cuts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-hearing-that-businesses-and-households-are-holding-back-from-decisions-20250520/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Musalem: Hearing that businesses and households are holding back from decisions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-monetary-policy-is-currently-is-well-positioned-20250520/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Musalem: Monetary policy currently is well positioned&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The times in the left-most column are GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The numbers in the right-most column are the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month/quarter as the case may be) result. The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) BITCOIN HITS $107,000</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924918157111590953#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:00:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924918157111590953#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BITCOIN HITS $107,000&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WE MUST MAINTAIN OUR STATUS AS THE WORLDWIDE LEADER IN WIFI, 5G, AND 6G</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924917940178022564#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:59:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924917940178022564#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WE MUST MAINTAIN OUR STATUS AS THE WORLDWIDE LEADER IN WIFI, 5G, AND 6G&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: WILL FREE UP SPECTRUM FOR AUCTION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924917887036178797#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:59:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924917887036178797#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: WILL FREE UP SPECTRUM FOR AUCTION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invictus Growth Partners Closes Oversubscribed Fund II with Funds Totaling $574 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/invictus-growth-partners-closes-oversubscribed-fund-ii-with-funds-totaling-574-million-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:26:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/invictus-growth-partners-closes-oversubscribed-fund-ii-with-funds-totaling-574-million-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Second flagship fund closed above the original hard cap with strong support from existing investors and new investors comprising more than two-thirds of capital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● 83% of completed investments have been sourced with in-house developed AI platform, DIANE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;● Invictus empowers previously bootstrapped cloud software, cybersecurity, and fintech companies with dedicated operating and data science resources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Invictus Growth Partners (“Invictus”), a leading private equity firm focused on growth buyouts of lower middle-market enterprise software businesses in the cloud software, cybersecurity, and fintech sectors, announced the final closing of Invictus Growth Fund II, L.P. (“Fund II”), with total capital commitments of $574 million in its core fund and related co-investment funds. Fund II was oversubscribed at $488 million in fund commitments, surpassing both its target of $350 million and the original hard cap of $450 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;&quot;We are honored and grateful for the support from our returning and new investors, which include pension plans, endowments, foundations, insurance companies, healthcare institutions, and family offices,” said John DeLoche, Invictus Co-founder and Managing Partner. “The early support and leadership from our existing investors helped to drive investor demand and facilitate a successful fundraise despite a challenging environment.” “We will continue our strategy of bringing a partnership approach and deep operating expertise and resources to our portfolio companies to help them scale,” said William Nettles, Invictus Co-founder and Managing Partner. “This includes our world class team’s stewardship, machine learning-powered GTM operational enhancements through our DIANE platform, and the support of a dedicated portfolio company success team, the Invictus Guild.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Invictus&apos; Fund II received strong support from existing investors, and new investors made up more than two thirds of total committed capital, broadening the diversification of the firm’s world class institutional limited partner base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Invictus has completed twelve platform investments and add-on acquisitions in its focus areas of enterprise cloud software, cybersecurity, and fintech. The firm targets companies with at least $10 million of annual recurring revenue that have been bootstrapped or have annual recurring revenue greater than equity capital raised. Invictus targets companies with strong product market fit that are profitable or nearly profitable at the time of investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Ten of the twelve completed investments were sourced with DIANE, Invictus’ proprietary machine learning-powered outbound sales engine for B2B use cases. DIANE is an acronym for Deal Intelligence Assessment Neural Engine, and was built in-house at Invictus starting in 2019. Invictus is now on its third generation of machine learning for operational enhancements powered by DIANE. The first generation focused on in-house investment sourcing. The second and third generations focus on GTM operational enhancements which are exclusively available to Invictus portfolio companies. Portfolio companies have seen a 90% increase in direct sales efficiency leveraging the platform, which also provides access to thousands of potential new enterprise customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Portfolio companies also benefit from access to the Invictus Guild, a team of operating executives who have experience working at some of the most successful technology companies. Invictus Guild Members operate across ten disciplines that are crucial for scaling technology companies, including sales, marketing, customer success, business development, corporate development, data science, human resources, product development, finance, and CEO coaches. They serve as mentors, operational advisors, and sources of best practices and talent for Invictus portfolio companies. They also invest personally in every portfolio company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Zaid Abdul-Aleem, Invictus Partner and Head of Partner and Capital Solutions, led the Fund II fundraise while Cooley served as Legal Advisor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;About Invictus Growth Partners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;MsoNormal&quot;&gt;Invictus Growth Partners (https://www.invictusgrowth.com/) is a buyout and growth equity firm that invests in outstanding, bootstrapped, capital-efficient, automation-enabled cloud software, cybersecurity, and fintech companies. The firm is dedicated to supporting companies seeking capital and strategic resources to accelerate their growth.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD moves above swing area  Makes new highs for the day</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-moves-above-swing-area-makes-new-highs-for-the-day-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:18:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-moves-above-swing-area-makes-new-highs-for-the-day-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;118&quot; data-end=&quot;446&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The EURUSD has made a technical push higher in today’s session, breaking above both the key swing area between 1.12657 and 1.12754, and the 38.2% retracement of the April–May decline at 1.12754. That dual-level break gives buyers added control in the short term and confirms momentum shifting back in favor of the bulls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;448&quot; data-end=&quot;747&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Yesterday’s high stalled just above this zone at 1.12876, and that level now becomes the next key upside target. A move above it would further solidify the bullish bias and open the path toward the 50% retracement level near 1.1318 and the falling trend line resistance closer to 1.1345.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;749&quot; data-end=&quot;1005&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the downside, support is now layered. The 1.1265–1.1275 area, now broken, becomes the first line of defense. Below that, the broken 38.2% at 1.12585. Below that, and the buyers are likely disappointed on the failed break with focus returning back to the 100-hour MA at 1.1210, with the 200-hour MA at 1.11989.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Bostic: More businesses say they can no longer delay tariff price hikes or job cuts</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-bostic-more-busiinesses-say-they-can-no-longer-delay-tariff-price-hikes-or-job-cuts-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:16:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-bostic-more-busiinesses-say-they-can-no-longer-delay-tariff-price-hikes-or-job-cuts-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says he hears from an increasing number of businesses who say they can no longer delay responding through changes via prices or employment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed needs to be more certain about the outlook to be comfortable with how policy should shift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US economy is going to see a slowdown in activity but how it plays out is hard to say&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Businesses say demand still strong enough to justify current workforce, though they are developing contingency&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is a lot unknown about how customers would respond to another round of inflation; could be more price-sensitive now&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US tariff level is still high enough that it is difficult to assess what will happen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Further instability in Treasury market would add to uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&apos;instability&apos; is a code word here for &apos;higher yields&apos; with US 30s flirting with 5%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil futures settle at $62.56</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6256-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:44:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-futures-settle-at-6256-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The price of June crude oil futures are settling down -$0.13 or -0.21% at $62.56. The high price reached $63.17. The low price was at $62.19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the hourly chart, the price on Monday moved back above its 100-hour moving average (the blue line on the chart above), and for most of the trading day, support buyers have been showing up against that moving average line – keeping the buyers in control from a technical perspective. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going forward, it would take a move back below the 100-hour moving average and 200-hour moving average currently at $61.82, to increase the bearish bias.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks slump lower as the battle between retail and institutional continues</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-slump-lower-as-the-battle-between-retail-and-institutional-continues-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:37:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-slump-lower-as-the-battle-between-retail-and-institutional-continues-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;We are in the midst of one of the all-time great divergences in markets right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the one hand, you have the BofA fund manager survey (and many other data points) showing that fund managers have been lightening up on the US and are as close to as bearish as they&apos;ve been.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the flipside, this was from a JPMorgan report yesterday:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;“Retail accounted for 36% of all trading volume today. Highest ever. Retail has learned the hard way, getting left behind during previous stock recoveries supported by policy puts. There is almost an unwavering commitment from retail to never make that mistake again”. &lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some jitters have kicked into stocks in the last half-hour and the S&amp;amp;P 500 is down 40 points, or 0.7%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Benjamin: Sell the dollar, Deutsche Bank says</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/breaking-benjamin-sell-the-dollar-deutsche-bank-says-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:49:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/breaking-benjamin-sell-the-dollar-deutsche-bank-says-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;199&quot;&gt;Deutsche Bank’s latest “FX Blueprint” frames the summer narrative around two central calls: a structural turn lower in the US dollar and the re-emergence of the Japanese yen as the counter-punch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;199&quot;&gt;The note has 11 themes, including buying gold and EUR/CAD but I&apos;ll highlight the main message.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;201&quot; data-end=&quot;1157&quot;&gt;The top theme is titled “Breaking Benjamin” and argues that the damage to the dollar is already visible in the flows. Deutsche Bank points to an unprecedented flip in the historical relationship between the USD and US risk assets: the currency has begun to rise and fall alongside domestic equities rather than against them, undermining its traditional safe-haven role. High-frequency data show a sustained slowdown in foreign purchases of US securities, while America’s net international investment position has sunk deeper into negative territory than any other G10 economy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote data-start=&quot;201&quot; data-end=&quot;1157&quot;&gt;We argue that the damage to the 
USD has been done and the funding of the dollar&apos;s two big holes - the budget and 
the current account - is now emerging as a market driver. In this world, relative 
interest rate differentials become less important, valuations and flow dynamics 
more relevant.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;201&quot; data-end=&quot;1157&quot;&gt;The bank argues that this twin-deficit backdrop, coupled with an expanding fiscal impulse in Europe, Canada and parts of Asia, leaves the dollar exposed if overseas investors begin to repatriate capital. They say that carry is now the dollar’s only clear support, and that it&apos;s  unlikely to offset the structural headwinds it faces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;201&quot; data-end=&quot;1157&quot;&gt;Theme #2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1159&quot; data-end=&quot;2225&quot;&gt;DB&apos;s second theme is “It’s Reigning Yen,” and the strategists recommend buying JPY against USD and, for investors wary of negative carry, against the over-valued Swiss franc. They argue that the near-perfect four-year correlation between USD/JPY and the US 10-year Treasury yield is breaking down as US exceptionalism fades and the Bank of Japan moves gradually toward policy normalisation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote data-start=&quot;1159&quot; data-end=&quot;2225&quot;&gt;It’s been a simple equation for almost four years now – USD/JPY 
has had a 95% correlation to the US10y, and the current yield at 4.4% suggests 
USD/JPY should be 150. That&apos;s well above spot, but looks like a justified breakdown 
of the relationship, as the existing regime is fading&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1159&quot; data-end=&quot;2225&quot;&gt; Inflation in Japan is proving sticky: two-thirds of the CPI basket is now rising, services PPI has held near 3 percent for a year, and corporate surveys show expectations for inflation above target. Deutsche Bank believes real yields in Japan remain far too low and notes that the BoJ’s pace of quantitative tightening already exceeds that of the Fed when scaled to GDP. On valuation metrics such as DBEER and purchasing-power parity, USD/JPY fair value is seen at 140 or lower, while Japanese life insurers still hold roughly USD 2.5 trillion in US assets; even a modest lift in hedge ratios or outright repatriation could accelerate yen strength, something we&apos;ve seen already this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;2227&quot; data-end=&quot;2554&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot; data-is-only-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;From a trading perspective, Deutsche Bank advises fading dollar rallies and positioning for yen appreciation as the most levered expression of a broader anti-dollar move. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Musalem: Hearing that businesses and households are holding back from decisions</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-hearing-that-businesses-and-households-are-holding-back-from-decisions-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:42:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-hearing-that-businesses-and-households-are-holding-back-from-decisions-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;If decisions have been somewhat paused I&apos;d expect it to affect the economic outlook&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The impact of uncertainty on economic activity tends to be pretty meaningful&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sides are getting dug in on what the tariff uncertainty really means.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian dollar bounces after rate cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-dollar-bounces-after-rate-cut-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:20:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/australian-dollar-bounces-after-rate-cut-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The big surprise today wasn&apos;t that the RBA cut rates but that they discussed going with a 50 basis point move. That has the market nearly fully priced for cuts at the next three meetings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In turn, the Australian dollar slumped and is the G10 laggard today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite that, the market has been taking a constructive view of rate cuts at the moment. They soften some of the risks around a hard landing and domestic weakness. With that, AUD/USD was able to find support just below 0.6400 and has bounced 25 pips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From here, AUD will take its cues from the risk trade. That&apos;s been a big tailwind since Trump backtracked on tariffs but it hasn&apos;t led to any kind of sustained Australian dollar rally.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Musalem: Monetary policy currently is well positioned</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-monetary-policy-is-currently-is-well-positioned-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 17:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-musalem-monetary-policy-is-currently-is-well-positioned-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;St. Louis Fed Pres. Musalem (2025 voter) is speaking and says:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monetary policy is currently well-positioned&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Balanced response to higher inflation, unemployment feasible if inflation expectations stay anchored.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If inflation expectations become unanchor, Fed policy should prioritize price stability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US economy has underlying strength, labor market stable, inflation east but above 2% goal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economic policy uncertainty unusually high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Even after May 12 de-escalation, tariffs likely to lead to labor market softening, higher prices.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs as likely to have temporary as persistent effect on inflation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If trade tensions are durably de-escalated, inflation could head back to target, labor market remain resilient, and current monetary policy would remain appropriate.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The major theme from Fed officials has revolved around &quot;uncertainty&quot; which in Fed policy terms, means policy is on hold.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A technical pattern for the US 10 year? Holding above the 200 hour moving average</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/a-technical-pattern-for-the-us-10-year-holding-above-the-200-hour-moving-average-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:50:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/a-technical-pattern-for-the-us-10-year-holding-above-the-200-hour-moving-average-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;80&quot; data-end=&quot;518&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;When I analyze a chart, I look for technical levels that &quot;do their job&quot;—levels where the market consistently reacts. On the 10-year yield chart above, the 200-hour moving average has done just that. Over the past three tests, the yield has found reliable support at the 200-hour MA, with each bounce occurring at progressively higher levels. This upward sequence has taken the yield from a low of 4.125% to a high of 4.564% so far in May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;520&quot; data-end=&quot;1011&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The most recent test and rebound occurred earlier today at 4.43%, once again at the rising 200-hour MA. Currently, the yield is trading near the session highs at 4.489%, positioned above both the 100-hour MA at 4.477% and the 200-hour MA at 4.436%. As long as yields hold above both moving averages, the bias remains firmly tilted to the upside. A break below both—specifically a move under 4.436%—would shift that bias and open the door to further downside pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GBPUSD Technical Analysis: Buyers reclaim control with work to do.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gbpusd-technical-analysis-buyers-reclaim-control-with-work-to-do-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:19:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gbpusd-technical-analysis-buyers-reclaim-control-with-work-to-do-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;99&quot; data-end=&quot;447&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The GBPUSD has reestablished a short-term bullish bias after a failed downside break last week. During that break, sellers had their shot as price moved below both the consolidation red box floor (see chart above), and then the  38.2% Fibonacci retracement (at 1.31603), but that break quickly reversed. The inability to sustain the move lower - and the base at the 38.2% after the failed break -  gave buyers the green light to step back in—and they did. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;99&quot; data-end=&quot;447&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The price moved back above the 100-hour MA (see blue line on the chart above) on Tuesday of last week, and apart from a failed break below it, and a swing level at 1.3259 on Friday, the buyers remained in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;449&quot; data-end=&quot;743&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Yesterday,  the price pushed back above the 100-hour moving average (1.3315 currently) and also away from the 200-hour moving average (1.32854 currently), confirming the rejection of the bearish move and reinforcing bullish momentum. The 100-hour MA is now acting as dynamic support, keeping the near-term upside bias intact. Staying above is more bullish. That is close support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;745&quot; data-end=&quot;1143&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The price action today (and going back to the extreme from yesterday), has seen up-and-down volatility.  There is a swing area between 1.33619 to 1.33784, which has been a messy resistance area this week with failed breaks.  However, the high price from yesterday did find willing sellers near the high from May 6 at 1.34018. That increases the levels importance going forward.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;745&quot; data-end=&quot;1143&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Overall:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Get and stay above 1.33784 adn then the 1.34018 will then target highs for the year at 1.3423, 1.3433 (high from 2024) and 1.34413 (high for the year). &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Move below the 100 hour MA at 1.3315 takes some of the wind out of the buyers sails. Below that, the 200 hour MA at 1.3285 would need to be broken to add to selling momentu. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP TO APPOINT GEN. GUETLEIN TO LEAD $831B &apos;GOLDEN DOME&apos; MISSILE SHIELD

President Trump plans to name Space Force Gen. Michael Guetlein to lead the &quot;Golden Dome,&quot; a new missile defense system aimed at protecting the U.S. from advanced threats like hypersonic weapons and low-flying missiles. The system would blend existing interceptors with satellite-based defenses.

The project could cost up to $831 billion over 20 years, with $25 billion proposed in the next budget. Guetlein, a space and missile defense expert, has warned of growing threats from China and backs increased U.S. space investments.

Trump is pushing for a fast rollout, prioritizing components that can be completed during his term. The &quot;Golden Dome&quot; will combine traditional and emerging defense technologies.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924858344243667364#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:02:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924858344243667364#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP TO APPOINT GEN. GUETLEIN TO LEAD $831B &apos;GOLDEN DOME&apos; MISSILE SHIELD&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
President Trump plans to name Space Force Gen. Michael Guetlein to lead the &quot;Golden Dome,&quot; a new missile defense system aimed at protecting the U.S. from advanced threats like hypersonic weapons and low-flying missiles. The system would blend existing interceptors with satellite-based defenses.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The project could cost up to $831 billion over 20 years, with $25 billion proposed in the next budget. Guetlein, a space and missile defense expert, has warned of growing threats from China and backs increased U.S. space investments.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Trump is pushing for a fast rollout, prioritizing components that can be completed during his term. The &quot;Golden Dome&quot; will combine traditional and emerging defense technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $AAPL - *APPLE PLAN WILL LET DEVELOPERS TAP INTO LARGE LANGUAGE MODELS  

*APPLE TO UNVEIL ITS NEW AI APP STRATEGY AT WWDC EVENT ON JUNE 9</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924857106261254421#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:57:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924857106261254421#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AAPL&quot;&gt;$AAPL&lt;/a&gt; - *APPLE PLAN WILL LET DEVELOPERS TAP INTO LARGE LANGUAGE MODELS  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*APPLE TO UNVEIL ITS NEW AI APP STRATEGY AT WWDC EVENT ON JUNE 9&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $AAPL - *APPLE TO OPEN AI MODELS TO DEVELOPERS IN BID TO SPUR NEW APPS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924856944356933634#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:57:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924856944356933634#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AAPL&quot;&gt;$AAPL&lt;/a&gt; - *APPLE TO OPEN AI MODELS TO DEVELOPERS IN BID TO SPUR NEW APPS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) HAMMACK SEES STAGFLATIONARY OUTCOME AS LIKELY SCENARIO: AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924855194946326632#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924855194946326632#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HAMMACK SEES STAGFLATIONARY OUTCOME AS LIKELY SCENARIO: AXIOS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED&apos;S HAMMACK: WHITE HOUSE TAX BILL COMPLICATES FORECAST: AXIOS

FED&apos;S HAMMACK SAYS DON&apos;T WANT TO OVERREACT TO TRADE: AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924855114759582148#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:49:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924855114759582148#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED&apos;S HAMMACK: WHITE HOUSE TAX BILL COMPLICATES FORECAST: AXIOS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
FED&apos;S HAMMACK SAYS DON&apos;T WANT TO OVERREACT TO TRADE: AXIOS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European equity close: Strong gains as Spain hits another record</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-close-strong-gains-as-spain-hits-another-record-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:37:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/european-equity-close-strong-gains-as-spain-hits-another-record-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Closing changes on the day:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX, +0.3%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC +0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK&apos;s FTSE 100 +0.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s IBEX +1.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB +0.8%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spanish stocks are up 23% from the Liberation Day low.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US SET TO EXTEND CHEVRON’S VENEZUELA WAIVER BY ANOTHER 60 DAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924851128568549409#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:34:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924851128568549409#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US SET TO EXTEND CHEVRON’S VENEZUELA WAIVER BY ANOTHER 60 DAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US HOUSE SPEAKER JOHNSON: WE&apos;RE RIGHT ON SCHEDULE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924850315787927860#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924850315787927860#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US HOUSE SPEAKER JOHNSON: WE&apos;RE RIGHT ON SCHEDULE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SCALISE: WE&apos;RE GOING TO DELIVER THIS WEEK ON TAX BILL</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1924849968914874782#m</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:29:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1924849968914874782#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SCALISE: WE&apos;RE GOING TO DELIVER THIS WEEK ON TAX BILL&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BofA: Corporates may need to hedge for more EUR/USD strength</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-corporates-may-need-to-hedge-for-more-eurusd-strength-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:23:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/bofa-corporates-may-need-to-hedge-for-more-eurusd-strength-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;66&quot; data-end=&quot;369&quot;&gt;BofA highlights that corporate hedging behavior in G10 FX, particularly in EUR/USD, may shift meaningfully if the euro continues to strengthen. Corporates appear underhedged against EUR exposure, and further euro gains could prompt catch-up hedging, influencing spot markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;371&quot; data-end=&quot;386&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;388&quot; data-end=&quot;1042&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;388&quot; data-end=&quot;576&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;390&quot; data-end=&quot;576&quot;&gt;Corporate flows dominate BofA’s proprietary FX flow data, but have been relatively light and directionless so far this year, suggesting a wait-and-see stance despite price moves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;578&quot; data-end=&quot;718&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;580&quot; data-end=&quot;718&quot;&gt;BofA identifies a notable negative EUR exposure among corporates, meaning many are short EUR or reliant on weak EUR scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;720&quot; data-end=&quot;849&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;722&quot; data-end=&quot;849&quot;&gt;That negative exposure has slightly increased in 2025, implying limited proactive hedging despite EUR/USD appreciation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;851&quot; data-end=&quot;1042&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;853&quot; data-end=&quot;1042&quot;&gt;If EUR/USD strength persists, corporates may be forced to hedge more actively, potentially reinforcing EUR upside in a nonlinear and counterintuitive way due to flow imbalances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1044&quot; data-end=&quot;1341&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1044&quot; data-end=&quot;1341&quot;&gt;Corporate FX exposure in EUR/USD is a latent market driver. If the euro continues to rally, underhedged corporates may accelerate demand for EUR hedges, introducing a positive feedback loop that could drive further EUR strength, especially in thin liquidity environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1044&quot; data-end=&quot;1341&quot;&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747839401358000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0fNnhuAYYD4ra2HI_SSSNU&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747839401358000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw0fNnhuAYYD4ra2HI_SSSNU&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial sector steadies amid mixed tech performance</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/financial-sector-steadies-amid-mixed-tech-performance-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:46:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/financial-sector-steadies-amid-mixed-tech-performance-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The technology sector today paints a varied picture. Microsoft (MSFT) and Oracle (ORCL) are down 0.71% and 0.67% respectively, reflecting some bearish sentiments. Particularly hit is the semiconductor space, with Nvidia (NVDA) facing a decline of 2.02%, signalling caution from investors about tech valuations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, the consumer cyclical sector shows some resilience, boosted by Tesla (TSLA) with a rise of 0.97%. Yet, not all experienced gains, as Amazon (AMZN) dropped by 1.09%. Communication services also faced headwinds, with both Google (GOOG) and Meta (META) showing slight dips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Financial Sector Resistance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strikingly, the financial sector remains relatively stable. JPMorgan Chase (JPM) edges up 0.40%, reflecting market confidence in financial services, while some others like American Express (AXP) dip slightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The overall market mood today seems cautious yet optimistic, with investors selectively showing confidence in industries like auto manufacturing and industrial goods. This balance highlights ongoing uncertainties, possibly stemming from broader economic factors, like interest rates and global economic recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For traders and investors, it might be wise to look into diversified portfolio strategies, emphasizing those sectors showing individual resilience. Industrial names such as Boeing (BA), up by 1.39%, illustrate potential trends for growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aligning investment strategies with these dynamics—considering high-quality financials or robust industrials—could prove beneficial. Be wary of abrupt shifts in tech sentiment or regulatory news that can impact these recovering markets intensely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This dynamic landscape suggests maintaining vigilance over real-time market data might uncover short-term opportunities. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ForexLive.com&lt;/a&gt; for continuous updates to keep your trading decisions informed 🤑.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD Technical Analysis: Price fails at ceiling again, eyes cluster of MA support</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-technical-analysis-price-fails-at-ceiling-again-eyes-cluster-of-ma-support-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:46:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-technical-analysis-price-fails-at-ceiling-again-eyes-cluster-of-ma-support-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;220&quot; data-end=&quot;566&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The EURUSD continues to trade within a well-defined range, with price action capped once again at the resistance zone between 1.1265 and 1.1275—a level that has repeatedly stalled upside attempts. Buyers briefly pushed through this zone yesterday, reaching a high at 1.1280, but failed to hold above, and the pair has since rotated lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;568&quot; data-end=&quot;975&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Despite the retreat, the downside remains limited. Today’s low was supported ahead of a key confluence of moving averages, with the 100-hour MA at 1.1207 and the 200-hour MA at 1.1199 acting as the current barometer for downside momentum. A sustained move below these levels would tilt the bias more firmly in favor of sellers, exposing support targets at 1.1145, followed by the low from last week at 1.1064.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1264&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;On the flip side, buyers still have a chance while the pair holds above the 100/200-hour MAs. To regain broader control, EURUSD would need to break convincingly above the 1.1265–1.1275 resistance zone, and then the swing high from yesterday at 1.1280, to open the door toward 1.1344 area (trend line)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1266&quot; data-end=&quot;1393&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For now, the short-term bias is modestly bullish above the key moving averages, but a directional breakout is still needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1400&quot; data-end=&quot;1417&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;🔑 Key Levels&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1419&quot; data-end=&quot;1722&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1419&quot; data-end=&quot;1593&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1421&quot; data-end=&quot;1438&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1441&quot; data-end=&quot;1593&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1441&quot; data-end=&quot;1472&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1443&quot; data-end=&quot;1472&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1265–1.1275 (key ceiling)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1475&quot; data-end=&quot;1510&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1477&quot; data-end=&quot;1510&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1280 (swing high from May 19)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1513&quot; data-end=&quot;1558&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1515&quot; data-end=&quot;1558&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1344 (trend line)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1561&quot; data-end=&quot;1593&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1563&quot; data-end=&quot;1593&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1402 (next extension target)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1595&quot; data-end=&quot;1722&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1597&quot; data-end=&quot;1611&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1614&quot; data-end=&quot;1722&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1614&quot; data-end=&quot;1638&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1616&quot; data-end=&quot;1638&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1207 (100-hour MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1641&quot; data-end=&quot;1665&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1643&quot; data-end=&quot;1665&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1199 (200-hour MA)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1668&quot; data-end=&quot;1690&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1670&quot; data-end=&quot;1690&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1145 (swing level)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1693&quot; data-end=&quot;1722&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1695&quot; data-end=&quot;1722&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.1063 (low from last week)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1693&quot; data-end=&quot;1722&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1695&quot; data-end=&quot;1722&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1.10395 (38.2% retracement)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1729&quot; data-end=&quot;1743&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;📊 Bias:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1744&quot; data-end=&quot;1865&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1744&quot; data-end=&quot;1788&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1746&quot; data-end=&quot;1788&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Modestly bullish above hourly MAs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1789&quot; data-end=&quot;1817&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1791&quot; data-end=&quot;1817&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bearish below 1.1199&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1818&quot; data-end=&quot;1865&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1820&quot; data-end=&quot;1865&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bullish breakout confirmed above 1.1280&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;REMINDER. The 2023 high price for the EURUSD was at 1.12754. The 61.8% of the range since 20220 high comes in at 1.1271. The high for the day ticked to 1.1277 and backed off.  That area increases the areas importance. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Canada rate cut odds plumment. Eyes now on next week&apos;s GDP data</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-canada-rate-cut-odds-plumment-eyes-now-on-next-weeks-gdp-data-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:37:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-canada-rate-cut-odds-plumment-eyes-now-on-next-weeks-gdp-data-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The implied odds of a Bank of Canada rate cut on June 4 have plunged to 36% from 65% following today&apos;s CPI report. The main problem was that core measures rose 0.2-0.3 pp more than anticipated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Diverging signals within today&apos;s inflation data produces a real dilemma for the Bank of Canada,&quot; writes CIBC following the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They note that headline inflation fell because of the removal of the carbon tax but core measures accelerated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;While we previously expected that a
renewed weakening within the labour market would bring a 25bp cut from the Bank of Canada at its June meeting,
that call now relies on next week&apos;s GDP data suggesting that the economy is tracking towards contraction in Q2,&quot; CIBC writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food, rent and travel-tour prices were sources of rising price pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/CAD is down 8 pips to 1.3942 today in choppy trade as Canada returns from a holiday.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The reaction to the Moody&apos;s downgrade couldn&apos;t have been worse</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-reaction-to-the-moodys-downgrade-couldnt-have-been-worse-20250520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:13:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-reaction-to-the-moodys-downgrade-couldnt-have-been-worse-20250520/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;No one cares about the deficit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, Trump is on Capitol Hill speaking with Republicans and trying to push forward his budget bill. Yet he singled out one single Republican holdout: Thomas Massie and called for him to be voted out of office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Massie&apos;s sin? He wants to see real deficit reduction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several other reports said that in the meeting, Trump told Republicans: “don’t f*ck around with Medicaid”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previously, that had been the lever to pull for at least some offsets to the deficit. I think that comment has pushed up yields and -- in particular -- gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now Moody&apos;s downgrade certainly wasn&apos;t ahead of the curve or telling us anything we don&apos;t already know but it was an opportunity to rally the deficit hawks and change course, or at least nudge it in a more-responsible direction. Instead, it&apos;s full-steam ahead on forever deficits with no credible path towards improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US 30-year yields bounced off 5% yesterday but are now up 3 bps to 4.97% today.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
