<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *S&amp;P 500 OPENS UP 0.2%, NASDAQ UP 0.4%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922645877962789044#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:31:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922645877962789044#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*S&amp;amp;P 500 OPENS UP 0.2%, NASDAQ UP 0.4%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) AMD SHARES CLIMB 6.9% TO HIGHEST INTRADAY SINCE JAN. 30</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922645853837124080#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:31:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922645853837124080#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AMD SHARES CLIMB 6.9% TO HIGHEST INTRADAY SINCE JAN. 30&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA&apos;S FOREIGN MINISTER, IN MEETING WITH MEXICAN COUNTERPART: CHINA WELCOMES MORE MEXICAN PRODUCTS INTO CHINESE MARKET, WILL ENCOURAGE CHINESE BUSINESSES TO INVEST IN MEXICO - CHINESE FOREIGN MINISTRY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922644537001877680#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:25:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922644537001877680#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA&apos;S FOREIGN MINISTER, IN MEETING WITH MEXICAN COUNTERPART: CHINA WELCOMES MORE MEXICAN PRODUCTS INTO CHINESE MARKET, WILL ENCOURAGE CHINESE BUSINESSES TO INVEST IN MEXICO - CHINESE FOREIGN MINISTRY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GERMAN DEFENCE MINISTER PISTORIUS: I AM NOT OPTIMISTIC WE WILL SEE A CEASEFIRE IN UKRAINE IN COMING DAYS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922644187935035833#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:24:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922644187935035833#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GERMAN DEFENCE MINISTER PISTORIUS: I AM NOT OPTIMISTIC WE WILL SEE A CEASEFIRE IN UKRAINE IN COMING DAYS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD Technical Analysis – Resistance holds, but buyers still eye more control</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-technical-analysis-resistance-holds-but-buyers-still-eye-more-control-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:23:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-technical-analysis-resistance-holds-but-buyers-still-eye-more-control-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;80&quot; data-end=&quot;361&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCAD remains capped by key technical barriers, with Monday and Tuesday&apos;s rally stalling near the 200-day moving average at 1.40114 and the critical swing zone between 1.40097 and 1.40268. This area has proven to be a firm ceiling for now, with sellers defending their ground. The price of the USDCAD fell yesterday and again today. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;363&quot; data-end=&quot;618&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Despite this resistance near the 200 day MA, the buyers have not given up. A bounce today - after the 2 day decline - started from the swing support area between 1.38917 and 1.3904. That suggests underlying demand remains intact. The buyers are still in play - at lease in the short term.  This zone was a ceiling until broken last week and basing.   That old ceiling/now floor is helping to define the current consolidation range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;620&quot; data-end=&quot;860&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;For buyers to reassert control, they will need to push decisively through nearby resistance at 1.3967 (200 bar MA on the 4-hour chart) to 1.3977 (high from April 15) . A break above that zone would open the path toward the more formidable confluence of the 200-day MA and the high of a swing area at 1.40268.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;862&quot; data-end=&quot;887&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;888&quot; data-end=&quot;1142&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;888&quot; data-end=&quot;930&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;890&quot; data-end=&quot;930&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 1.38917–1.3904 (swing area)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;931&quot; data-end=&quot;972&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;933&quot; data-end=&quot;972&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Immediate resistance: 1.3967–1.3977&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;973&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;975&quot; data-end=&quot;1051&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Major resistance: 1.40097–1.40268 (swing zone) and 200-day MA at 1.40114&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1052&quot; data-end=&quot;1142&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1054&quot; data-end=&quot;1142&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Cautiously bullish above 1.3904; more bullish confirmation on break of 1.40268&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1144&quot; data-end=&quot;1261&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Momentum above 1.3977 could reignite upside pressure, but failure to clear resistance risks renewed downside probing.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Jefferson: Current policy is a good place to respond to economic developments</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-jefferson-current-policy-is-a-good-place-to-respond-to-economic-developments-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:10:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-jefferson-current-policy-is-a-good-place-to-respond-to-economic-developments-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current moderately restrictive policy rate in a good place to respond to economic developments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Watching closely for signs in hard data of weaker activity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recent inflation data consistent with further progress toward 2% goal, but future path uncertainty due to tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs could lead to higher inflation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Labor market still solid&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Q1 GDP data overstated deceleration in activity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whether tariffs create persistent inflation depends on implementation, response of supply chains and other factors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a remarkable unity in this thinking at the Fed.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JEFFERSON: TARIFFS COULD LEAD TO HIGHER INFLATION, STILL UNCERTAIN IF IMPACT WOULD BE TEMPORARY OR PERSISTENT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922640535069561132#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:09:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922640535069561132#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JEFFERSON: TARIFFS COULD LEAD TO HIGHER INFLATION, STILL UNCERTAIN IF IMPACT WOULD BE TEMPORARY OR PERSISTENT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) JPM SETTLES FIRST PUBLIC TRANSACTION OF TOKENIZED TREASURIES USING ONDO PUBLIC LEDGER: FORTUNE

JPMorgan Chase has been steadily developing its own blockchain tech for years. But, instead of integrating it with public blockchains, the U.S.’s largest bank has taken what many in crypto call the “walled garden” approach and built out a private network only its customers can use. Now, JPMorgan is venturing beyond that garden. On Wednesday, it announced that it had settled a transaction on a public ledger with the help of the crypto firms Chainlink and Ondo Finance.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922640123880952024#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:08:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922640123880952024#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;JPM SETTLES FIRST PUBLIC TRANSACTION OF TOKENIZED TREASURIES USING ONDO PUBLIC LEDGER: FORTUNE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
JPMorgan Chase has been steadily developing its own blockchain tech for years. But, instead of integrating it with public blockchains, the U.S.’s largest bank has taken what many in crypto call the “walled garden” approach and built out a private network only its customers can use. Now, JPMorgan is venturing beyond that garden. On Wednesday, it announced that it had settled a transaction on a public ledger with the help of the crypto firms Chainlink and Ondo Finance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USDCHF is trading lower for  2nd consecutive day, but finds buyers near an old ceiling</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usdchf-is-trading-lower-for-2nd-consecutive-day-but-finds-buyers-near-an-old-ceiling-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usdchf-is-trading-lower-for-2nd-consecutive-day-but-finds-buyers-near-an-old-ceiling-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;73&quot; data-end=&quot;376&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The USDCHF is finding support near a prior ceiling area that has defined the lower boundary of its recent consolidation range, with buyers stepping in between 0.83184 and 0.8333. This level has provided a floor over the past few weeks and remains a critical line in the sand for near-term bullish hopes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;378&quot; data-end=&quot;663&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Despite the recent bounce, upside momentum stalled earlier in the week just ahead of the 38.2% Fibonacci retracement of the March–April decline, which comes in at 0.84823. Sellers leaned into that level, capping further advances for now and keeping the broader bearish pressure intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;665&quot; data-end=&quot;953&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;To shift the bias more definitively to the upside, bulls will need to push the pair above the 0.8333–0.8373 zone, which represents a key swing area from the daily chart. A firm break above this region would be considered a bullish development and could open the door for further recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;955&quot; data-end=&quot;991&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Summary of key technical levels:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;992&quot; data-end=&quot;1229&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;992&quot; data-end=&quot;1062&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;994&quot; data-end=&quot;1062&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Support: 0.83184–0.8333 zone (prior ceiling now acting as floor)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1063&quot; data-end=&quot;1151&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1065&quot; data-end=&quot;1151&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Resistance: 0.8373 (upper end of swing zone off daily chart), then 0.84823 (38.2% Fib retracement)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1152&quot; data-end=&quot;1229&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1154&quot; data-end=&quot;1229&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Bias: Neutral to cautiously bullish above 0.8333 (in the short term); bearish below 0.83184&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1231&quot; data-end=&quot;1395&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;A sustained move outside of the current range will likely define the next directional bias. Keep an eye on momentum and volume near the highlighted resistance zone.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) AMD ADDS TO PREMARKET GAINS, UP MORE THAN 5%, ON BUYBACK PLAN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922638419353624626#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:01:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922638419353624626#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AMD ADDS TO PREMARKET GAINS, UP MORE THAN 5%, ON BUYBACK PLAN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) AMD ANNOUNCES NEW $6 BILLION SHARE-REPURCHASE AUTHORIZATION 
$AMD</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922638214885409264#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:00:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922638214885409264#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AMD ANNOUNCES NEW $6 BILLION SHARE-REPURCHASE AUTHORIZATION &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AMD&quot;&gt;$AMD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SPOT GOLD  EXTENDS LOSSES, LAST DOWN 2% AT $3,183.90/OZ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922638037189644598#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922638037189644598#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPOT GOLD  EXTENDS LOSSES, LAST DOWN 2% AT $3,183.90/OZ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold cracks the May low and sinks further</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-cracks-the-may-low-and-sinks-further-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:59:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/gold-cracks-the-may-low-and-sinks-further-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Gold is running stops after breaking the May 1 low. It&apos;s now down $60 to $3187 after the May bottom of $3202 was breached.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold had tried to form a double bottom at $3200 but that effort has failed now in light of the climb-down in the trade war and ceasefire in India/Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The early-April high should offer some modest support at $3167 with some at $3150 as well.  Beyond that we&apos;re looking at $3100 and the big figure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many assets have retraced the &apos;Liberation Day&apos; moves and that would get back to around $3120 but technically, the post-Liberation &apos;sell everything&apos; low near $3000 looks like it&apos;s in play.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) UK MAINTAINS REFUSAL TO IMPORT US HORMONE-FED BEEF: WAPO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922636276454306282#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922636276454306282#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UK MAINTAINS REFUSAL TO IMPORT US HORMONE-FED BEEF: WAPO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SPOT GOLD FALLS BELOW $3,200/OZ FOR FIRST TIME SINCE APRIL 14, DOWN OVER 1.5% INTRADAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922634838240055499#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:47:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922634838240055499#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPOT GOLD FALLS BELOW $3,200/OZ FOR FIRST TIME SINCE APRIL 14, DOWN OVER 1.5% INTRADAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada March building permits -4.1% vs -0.5% expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-building-permits-41-vs-05-expected-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:30:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/canada-march-building-permits-41-vs-05-expected-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior was +2.9% (revised to +4.9%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Non-residential -14.5% m/m&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Residential +2.0% m/m&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Q1 permits +2.9%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The revision to the February number takes some of the sting out of this miss but it&apos;s now abundantly clear that much of the housing market is Canada is entering a period of stagnation (at best) with the condo-building industry now at a standstill. That said, the overall construction industry appears to be holding up fine.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SUPER MICRO COMPUTER SHARES EXTEND GAINS, LAST UP 17.7% PREMARKET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922630280759607622#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:29:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922630280759607622#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SUPER MICRO COMPUTER SHARES EXTEND GAINS, LAST UP 17.7% PREMARKET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmful advice for traders: Octa broker&apos;s warnings</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/harmful-advice-for-traders-octa-brokers-warnings-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:22:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/harmful-advice-for-traders-octa-brokers-warnings-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;When navigating online trading
recommendations, it&apos;s easy to come across information that goes against the
grain of conventional financial wisdom. Some of these bits of advice are
questionable, while others can be straight-up harmful to your financial outcomes.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Octa, a regulated and trusted broker, breaks
down some of the worst advice traders can follow and describes potential
consequences that can ensue while offering viable counterarguments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harmful
advice #1: forget about brokers&apos; reputation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine a trader who doesn&apos;t care whether
their broker is regulated and trusted, focusing solely on short-term financial
gains mentioned in ads. This approach can be rooted in the unwillingness to go
into too much detail when choosing a broker. After all, the difference between
regulated and unregulated brokers often becomes evident only with time. It&apos;s
not always possible to spot a difference from the get-go, especially for the
less experienced traders. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In reality, regulation plays a crucial role in
defining brokers&apos; reliability. Some unregulated brokers may engage in unethical
or illegal practices, such as unauthorised trading, churning (excessive trading
to generate commissions), or offering fake investment products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long term, a more reasonable approach
would be to choose an experienced and globally regulated broker whose
trustworthiness has been proven by traders&apos; reviews. If a broker meets the
strict criteria of multiple regulatory bodies from various regions, it is much
more likely to be a safer choice for traders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harmful
advice #2: withdrawals are always easy, don&apos;t fret about it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s only natural for those starting their
trading journey to look only one step ahead and focus on achieving financial
gains first. After all, tapping into a viable source of supplementary income is
one of the main reasons why people start trading in the first place. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may seem that once traders have reached
their financial goals, cashing in their profits should not be a problem.
However, this is where things can easily go wrong unless you have carefully
chosen your broker based on public information about its withdrawals.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By establishing a transparent, user-friendly
transactional mechanism and offering a wide variety of withdrawal options,
brokers show a client-oriented approach to business and send a clear message to
their clients about their reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To keep abreast with the industry benchmarks,
Octa, a globally recognised broker with more than 14 years of experience,
offers a fast and efficient withdrawal procedure confirmed by real-life
traders&apos; reviews. All Octa&apos;s fees and conditions are fully disclosed in the
broker&apos;s terms and conditions, creating a reliable trading environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harmful
advice #3: don&apos;t pay attention to trading conditions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, trading conditions offered by
a broker may seem a minor detail that is not worthy of consideration. After
all, if your strategy is viable and you execute it perfectly time and time
again, what can go wrong? But it is worth remembering that in trading, gains
and losses are marginal most of the time, and long-term success highly depends
on the broker&apos;s fees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When choosing a financial broker, the more you
know, the better. This is especially applicable to trading conditions. Choosing
a broker with advantageous conditions, including low spreads, efficient
withdrawals, and transparent fees, may not yield immediate gains, but will have
a considerable long-term impact on your outcomes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When starting trading with a broker, always
make sure to test their advertised trading conditions before fully committing
with your deposits. Only brokers that are fully transparent about their charges
are worth your trust. For example, Octa broker&apos;s long and successful track
record and lack of hidden fees can be verified through thousands of positive
online reviews. However, for any trader, the best way is always to test trading
conditions firsthand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harmful
advice #4: in trading, caution is for the weak&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a new trader, it may seem that risk
management tools are only applicable if you deal with extra-fast time frames or
place many orders simultaneously. Otherwise, there is no point in wasting your
time on insignificant details since a couple of high-risk trades will likely
determine your success. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it couldn&apos;t be further from the
truth. Stop-loss and take-profit orders are a must for any trader, regardless
of their style and asset preferences. When traders focus on short-term profits
and disregard the strategic aspect of trading, including using risk management
tools, they enter the realm of random outcomes, which doesn&apos;t operate in their
favour. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ignoring risk management tools and fully
trusting your emotions during the stressful moments of high market volatility
is almost like trying to extinguish fire with gasoline. Trading becomes much
less stressful and more efficient if you approach it with a cool head and use
all the tools at your disposal to navigate sudden bursts of volatility. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In trading, following the fundamental rules
from step one is essential for long-term success. These rules include choosing
a reliable broker, since this is the only way to ensure a smooth trading
experience overall. By ensuring fast withdrawals and a transparent, clearly
communicated fee structure, brokers enable their clients to achieve their
financial goals—and thus build up their reputation for the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compliance reminder: trading Contracts for
Difference (CFDs) carries a high level of risk and may not be suitable for all
investors. Emotional trading can increase this risk. Always trade within your
means and understand the risks involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About Octa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.octafx.com?utm_source=media&amp;amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;amp;utm_campaign=TrustWWS9&amp;amp;utm_content=ww_fx&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Octa &lt;/a&gt;is an international broker that has
been providing online trading services worldwide since 2011. It offers
commission-free access to financial markets and various services used by
clients from 180 countries who have opened more than 52 million trading accounts.
To help its clients reach their investment goals, Octa offers free educational
webinars, articles, and analytical tools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The
company is involved in a comprehensive network of charitable and humanitarian
initiatives, including the improvement of educational infrastructure and
short-notice relief projects supporting local communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since
its foundation, Octa has won more than 100 awards, including the &apos;Most Reliable
Broker Global 2024&apos; award from Global Forex Awards and the &apos;Best Mobile Trading
Platform 2024&apos; award from Global Brand Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The USD is lower for the 2nd consecutive day. EURUSD/USDJPY between MAs in neutral area.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-lower-for-the-2nd-consecutive-day-eurusdusdjpy-between-mas-in-neutral-area-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:17:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/the-usd-is-lower-for-the-2nd-consecutive-day-eurusdusdjpy-between-mas-in-neutral-area-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The dollar decline has continued today with the greenback falling by -1% vs the JPY. The declines vs the EUR (-0.35%) and the GBP (-0.24%) have been less (and the EURUSD and GBPUSD are off their extremes for the day). Nevertheless, after the gains on Monday after the US/China deal, the greenback has retraced those gains and more.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the EURUSD and the USDJPY, the price moves have taken the price back between the 100/200 hour MAs or into a more neutral territory. For the GBPUSD, the pair has moved back above those two key MAs putting the buyers more in control from a technical perspective. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video above, I take a technical look at those three major currency pairs to kickstart the US trading day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overnight in central bank commentary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;ECB policymaker Joachim Nagel expressed optimism that the eurozone is on track to reach its 2% inflation target, though he emphasized that uncertainty is likely to remain a persistent feature of the economic landscape. He noted that central banks must adapt to this new &quot;normal&quot; of ongoing unpredictability. Nagel highlighted the importance of upcoming staff projections in June, while acknowledging the unknown impact that tariffs could have on inflation and broader economic conditions. The ECB&apos;s June rate decision will depend heavily on incoming data. Separately, Nagel also commented on the global financial system, stating that while the U.S. dollar remains dominant, the euro is expected to gain strength as a reserve currency in the coming years.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed&apos;s Goolsbee, a 2025 voter, indicated that part of the April inflation data reflects the lagged nature of how inflation trends appear in economic reports. He emphasized that the Federal Reserve is still in a wait-and-see mode, holding off on major decisions until more information becomes available. Goolsbee noted that it will take time for current inflation dynamics to be accurately reflected, cautioning against drawing conclusions from short-term volatility. He stressed the importance of looking past the noise in the data before forming any long-term policy judgments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feds Daly (SF Fed Pres - nonvoting member) and Jefferson (FOMC Governor) are both scheduled to speak later today&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US stocks are higher after gains in the broader S&amp;amp;P and Nasdaq yesterday (the Dow fell due to UnitedHealth&apos;s tumble) with the futures currently implying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow Industrial average futures implying a gain of 21.57 points. Yesterday the index fell -269.87 points or -0.64%. UnitedHealth contributed to a decline of -400 points itself&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index futures are implying a gain of 12.45 points. Yesterday, the index rose 42.36 points or 0.72%. The S&amp;amp;P index closed positive on the year by 0.08% yesterday..&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nasdaq futures are implying a gain of  76.30 points. Yesterday the index gained 301.74 points or 1.61%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the European markets, the major indices are mixed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German Dax, -0.30%. Yesterday the index closed at a record level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC, -0.38%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE 100, +0.04%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex, +0.34%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB, +0.39%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US debt market, yields are higher&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year yield 4.013%, -0.4 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5-year yield 4.108%, -1.3 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10-year yield 4.480%, -1.8 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year yield 4.921%, -2.2 basis points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crude oil down $0.70 on -1.10% at $62.97&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Silver unchanged at $32.88&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold is down $29 or -0.91% at $3219.50&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin is trading up little changed at $104,063&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The economic calendar is light with the Canada building permits scheduled for 830. The expectations are -0.5% versus +2.9% last month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 10:30 AM ET, the weekly inventory data will be release with crude oil inventories expected to show a drop of -1.078 million. Gasoline is expected to fall by -0.561 million while distillates are expected to show a build of 0.129 million..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The private data released late yesterday showed a surprise build of 4.287 million in crude inventories. Gasoline inventories fell -1.374 million and distillates fell -3.675 million&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) SPOT GOLD  FALLS 1% TO $3,214.66/OZ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922626504145465712#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:14:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922626504145465712#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SPOT GOLD  FALLS 1% TO $3,214.66/OZ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CAPITAL OUTFLOWS FROM U.S. LIKELY TO CONTINUE AS TRADE UNCERTAINTY PERSISTS

Uncertainty around trade policies is likely to continue, weakening investor confidence in U.S. assets, resulting in capital outflows from the U.S., analysts at Amundi Investment Institute say in a note. &quot;We think a rotation out of the U.S. will continue, benefiting other regions such as Europe, Emerging Markets, and Asia.&quot; Despite the risks facing the U.S. economy, there are opportunities in some quality stocks and the sectors that are insulated from tariffs, the analysts say</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922624921449926696#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:07:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922624921449926696#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CAPITAL OUTFLOWS FROM U.S. LIKELY TO CONTINUE AS TRADE UNCERTAINTY PERSISTS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Uncertainty around trade policies is likely to continue, weakening investor confidence in U.S. assets, resulting in capital outflows from the U.S., analysts at Amundi Investment Institute say in a note. &quot;We think a rotation out of the U.S. will continue, benefiting other regions such as Europe, Emerging Markets, and Asia.&quot; Despite the risks facing the U.S. economy, there are opportunities in some quality stocks and the sectors that are insulated from tariffs, the analysts say&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEC leaves forecasts for global oil demand growth in 2025 and 2026 unchanged</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/opec-leaves-forecasts-for-global-oil-demand-growth-in-2025-and-2026-unchanged-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:06:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/opec-leaves-forecasts-for-global-oil-demand-growth-in-2025-and-2026-unchanged-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says 90 day US-China trade deal suggests potential for more lasting agreements, likely supporting normalisation of trade flows.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sees oil supply outside OPEC+ rising by 800K BPD this year (previously 900K).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sees 5% cut un E&amp;amp;P investment in non-OPEC+ producers in 2025.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trims forecast for total US oil supply growth in 2025 to 300K BPD (previously 400K).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Says OPEC+ crude output averaged 40.92 MBPD in April 2025, down 106K BPD from March.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The de-escalating trade war is certainly a positive development for the crude oil market. We are now consolidating at a key resistance zone, but a breakout and new highs look more likely.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive European FX news wrap: Dollar struggles continue amid mixed markets</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-dollar-struggles-continue-amid-mixed-markets-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:04:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-european-fx-news-wrap-dollar-struggles-continue-amid-mixed-markets-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Headlines:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/dollar-selling-picks-up-to-start-the-session-20250514/&quot;&gt;Dollar selling picks up to start the session&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolsbee-it-will-take-time-for-current-inflation-trends-to-show-up-in-the-data-20250514/&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s Goolsbee: It will take time for current inflation trends to show up in the data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecb-supervisors-step-up-checks-on-dollar-funding-at-banks-over-trump-concerns-report-20250514/&quot;&gt;ECB supervisors step up checks on dollar funding at banks over Trump concerns - report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-euro-will-become-stronger-as-a-reserve-currency-in-the-coming-years-20250514/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Nagel: Euro will become stronger as a reserve currency in the coming years&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-there-is-a-good-probability-we-will-get-to-2-inflation-target-20250514/&quot;&gt;ECB&apos;s Nagel: There is a good probability we will get to 2% inflation target&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boes-mann-uk-labour-market-has-been-more-resilient-than-expected-20250514/&quot;&gt;BOE&apos;s Mann: UK labour market has been more resilient than expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-says-china-eu-has-had-in-depth-exchanges-on-global-economic-uncertainties-20250514/&quot;&gt;PBOC says China, EU has had in-depth exchanges on global economic uncertainties&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-a-big-crypto-fan-20250514/&quot;&gt;Trump: I&apos;m a big crypto fan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-grants-first-rare-earth-export-permits-since-adding-restrictions-last-month-report-20250514/&quot;&gt;China grants first rare earth export permits since adding restrictions last month - report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/germany-april-final-cpi-21-vs-21-yy-prelim-20250514/&quot;&gt;Germany April final CPI +2.1% vs +2.1% y/y prelim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/spain-april-final-cpi-22-vs-22-yy-prelim-20250514/&quot;&gt;Spain April final CPI +2.2% vs +2.2% y/y prelim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-mba-mortgage-applications-we-9-may-11-vs-110-prior-20250514/&quot;&gt;US MBA mortgage applications w.e. 9 May +1.1% vs +11.0% prior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-april-m2-money-supply-80-vs-73-yy-expected-20250514/&quot;&gt;China April M2 money supply +8.0% vs +7.3% y/y expected&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;JPY leads, CAD lags on the day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;European equities mixed; S&amp;amp;P 500 futures up 0.2%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US 10-year yields down 2.6 bps to 4.472%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gold down 0.8% to $3,220.63&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;WTI crude down 1.1% to $62.97&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bitcoin down 0.6% to $103,920&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There weren&apos;t much significant headlines on the session and market players were left to fend for themselves for the most part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Trump is in Saudi Arabia this week, so his attention is diverted to other geopolitical matters for the time being. He offered up some comments about the Middle East and also on the potential meeting with Russia and Ukraine in Turkey. Besides that, there weren&apos;t much interesting remarks from the man today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In terms of data, German and Spanish inflation numbers reaffirmed that there is still work to be done by the ECB even if rate cuts are still set to continue. And we got some token remarks from central bank speakers from the Fed, ECB, and BOE for the most part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As for market action, major currencies are seeing decent moves with the dollar in particular standing out. The greenback is continuing to stutter and has surrendered pretty much all of its gains from the opening gap higher on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;EUR/USD moved up to a high of 1.1265 during the session but is now still up 0.3% at 1.1220 on the day. Meanwhile, USD/JPY also fell to a low of 145.60 before picking up a little to 146.16 now - down 0.9% on the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Elsewhere, GBP/USD is up 0.2% to 1.3335 while AUD/USD is marginally higher by 0.1% to 0.6472. The latter is seeing large option expiries at 0.6475 and 0.6500 in play, with the ones at the figure level limiting gains on the session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In other markets, European stocks are looking rather timid today with little conviction. US futures were down initially but have picked up a little to be up 0.2% now. The dip buying could be suggestive of a continuation of gains later when Wall Street enters the fray.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In the commodities space, gold is down alongside oil. So, that is offering up a bit more of a mixed picture in broader markets. Treasury yields are also sitting lower but are still hanging on the high side with 30-year yields hovering close by the 5% mark. So, that&apos;s still something to watch out for in the days ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) OPEC CUTS 2025 U.S. ECONOMIC-GROWTH FORECAST TO 1.7% FROM 2.1%

OPEC CUTS 2026 U.S. ECONOMIC-GROWTH FORECAST TO 2.1% FROM 2.2%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922623150493147640#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 12:00:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922623150493147640#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OPEC CUTS 2025 U.S. ECONOMIC-GROWTH FORECAST TO 1.7% FROM 2.1%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
OPEC CUTS 2026 U.S. ECONOMIC-GROWTH FORECAST TO 2.1% FROM 2.2%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) 🚨 TRUMP: MAYBE NEWS ON RUSSIA/UKRAINE HAPPENING TODAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922622811136266612#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:59:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922622811136266612#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🚨 TRUMP: MAYBE NEWS ON RUSSIA/UKRAINE HAPPENING TODAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: FRIENDS WITH QATAR FOR LONG TIME</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922622649374560579#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:58:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922622649374560579#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: FRIENDS WITH QATAR FOR LONG TIME&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany&apos;s Chancellor Merz: We&apos;re committed to avoiding protracted trade conflict with US</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germanys-chancellor-merz-were-committed-to-avoiding-protracted-trade-conflict-with-us-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:58:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/germanys-chancellor-merz-were-committed-to-avoiding-protracted-trade-conflict-with-us-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We&apos;re committed to avoiding protracted trade conflict with US.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We want to support the EU to agree to as many trade deals as possible.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We will tackle one-sided dependencies on China in the name of strategic de-risking.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We still haven&apos;t heard anything about the US-EU trade deal but it&apos;s starting to become unlikely that the EU will be able to avoid a 10% tariff. I&apos;m not sure the EU has the spine to fight a protracted trade war with the US.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB supervisors step up checks on dollar funding at banks over Trump concerns - report</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecb-supervisors-step-up-checks-on-dollar-funding-at-banks-over-trump-concerns-report-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:53:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/ecb-supervisors-step-up-checks-on-dollar-funding-at-banks-over-trump-concerns-report-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It is being reported that ECB supervisors have pressed banks in the region to assess their dollar funding needs especially if there is market distress. The idea here is that they are fearing a possible scenario in which they cannot tap into Fed facilities if Trump decides to pressure the Fed into blocking that. For some context, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-officials-concerned-over-relying-on-fed-for-usd-funding-in-times-of-mkt-stress-20250322/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;it&apos;s not the first time&lt;/a&gt; this concern has been brought up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;During times of financial stress, the Fed typically provides lending facilities to major counterparts to alleviate shortages in the dollar. But amid the erratic policy rollout by Trump, officials are fearing that this funding source could be shut down abruptly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So far, two sources said that the Fed had never suggested that it would not stand by those backstops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Funnily enough, the recent market swings seem to be suggesting an aversion to the dollar though. And at least for the time being, the ECB can take in some comfort of better developments from the US-China trade conflict. We&apos;ve definitely bought some temporary reprieve on the trade front but who&apos;s to say what might come next.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) MERZ: CHINA WILL REMAIN A KEY PARTNER FOR GERMANY AND EU</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922620915554111589#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:52:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922620915554111589#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MERZ: CHINA WILL REMAIN A KEY PARTNER FOR GERMANY AND EU&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) ECB SUPERVISORS STEP UP CHECKS ON BANKS&apos; DOLLAR FUNDING ON TRUMP CONCERNS, SOURCES SAY

SOME OF EU&apos;S LARGEST BANKS ASSESSING UNPRECEDENTED SCENARIOS OF FED NOT PROVIDING DOLLARS, SOURCES SAY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922619397568426305#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:45:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922619397568426305#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ECB SUPERVISORS STEP UP CHECKS ON BANKS&apos; DOLLAR FUNDING ON TRUMP CONCERNS, SOURCES SAY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
SOME OF EU&apos;S LARGEST BANKS ASSESSING UNPRECEDENTED SCENARIOS OF FED NOT PROVIDING DOLLARS, SOURCES SAY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $KHC - KRAFT HEINZ INVESTING $3 BILLION UPGRADING ITS 30 US FACTORIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922615478997934505#m</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:30:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922615478997934505#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23KHC&quot;&gt;$KHC&lt;/a&gt; - KRAFT HEINZ INVESTING $3 BILLION UPGRADING ITS 30 US FACTORIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC says China, EU has had in-depth exchanges on global economic uncertainties</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-says-china-eu-has-had-in-depth-exchanges-on-global-economic-uncertainties-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:12:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-says-china-eu-has-had-in-depth-exchanges-on-global-economic-uncertainties-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;China, EU discussed optimising market access&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Also discussed cooperation on sustainable finance, cross-border data flows, payment system development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Both sides are continuing to exchange pleasantries in a time when they are also facing a tough time against the US. The comments here come after a financial working group meeting held in Brussels.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US MBA mortgage applications w.e. 9 May +1.1% vs +11.0% prior</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-mba-mortgage-applications-we-9-may-11-vs-110-prior-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 11:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-mba-mortgage-applications-we-9-may-11-vs-110-prior-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +11.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Market index 251.2 vs 248.4 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Purchase index 166.5 vs 162.8 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refinance index 718.1 vs 721.0 prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;30-year mortgage rate 6.86% vs 6.84% prior&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Mortgage applications saw a minor increase in the past week, led by purchase activity as a drop in refinancing activity slightly offset the overall figure. With higher rates though, we&apos;ll see if there will be more of a crack between the lines in this space in the weeks ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A: EBC and International University of Ulaanbaatar’s Vision for Mongolia’s Youth</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/qa-ebc-and-international-university-of-ulaanbaatars-vision-for-mongolias-youth-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:48:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/qa-ebc-and-international-university-of-ulaanbaatars-vision-for-mongolias-youth-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ebcfin.co.uk/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;EBC Financial Group&lt;/a&gt; has partnered with the International University of Ulaanbaatar (IUU) to bridge
the gap between academic learning and real-world financial experience for
Mongolia’s youth. This collaboration aims to nurture the next generation of
finance professionals through internships, mentorship, and industry-academia
initiatives. Below, we answer key questions about the partnership, its
objectives, and the benefits for students and the broader financial sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is EBC
investing in Mongolia’s youth?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EBC recognises
Mongolia as a dynamic emerging market with a new generation eager to contribute
to the global financial sector. However, there is a gap between academic
learning and practical industry experience. By investing in Mongolia’s youth,
EBC aims to bridge this gap, nurture local talent, and help build a stronger
financial ecosystem for the country’s future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does the
partnership with the International University of Ulaanbaatar (IUU) involve?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EBC has signed
a Joint Cooperation Agreement with IUU to create meaningful opportunities for students.
The partnership delivers up to 10 annual internship positions at EBC’s Mongolia
office, allowing selected students to gain hands-on experience in a global
financial environment. In addition, EBC will engage with&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IUU through
lectures, workshops, and events, bringing industry expertise directly into the
classroom and fostering industry-academia collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How can
students benefit from this collaboration?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students
benefit through:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Internships: Practical experience at
EBC’s Mongolia office, with the potential for outstanding
interns to secure further opportunities within the company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Mentorship: Guidance from EBC
professionals to help navigate career choices and build professional
networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Skill Development: Access to
industry-led workshops and real-world exposure to trading, risk
management, and financial technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;•Career
Pathways: The partnership helps students become
job-ready and competitive in the global
marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How does this
fit into EBC’s global ESG goals?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This
collaboration is part of EBC’s broader mission to foster financial talent,
promote industry academia collaboration, and demonstrate leadership in ESG
(Environmental, Social, and Governance) principles. By investing in Mongolia’s
youth and supporting education, EBC is building a more robust and innovative financial
sector while advancing social responsibility and sustainable growth in emerging
markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New Standard&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through its
partnership with the International University of Ulaanbaatar, EBC is empowering
Mongolia’s next generation of financial leaders. By combining practical
experience, mentorship, and global engagement, EBC and IUU are setting a new
standard for industry-academic collaboration and youth development in the
region.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: I&apos;m a big crypto fan</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-a-big-crypto-fan-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-im-a-big-crypto-fan-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m a big crypto fan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;He&apos;s giving some general comments on various topics but given the positive sentiment in the market I wouldn&apos;t be surprised to see Bitcoin rallying just on this single comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More comments:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;I&apos;m a believer in AI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We lead China in cryptocurrency.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil is back at the key resistance zone as a breakout becomes likely</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-is-back-at-the-key-resistance-zone-as-a-breakout-becomes-likely-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:46:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/crude-oil-is-back-at-the-key-resistance-zone-as-a-breakout-becomes-likely-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The crude oil market has been battered by negative news on both the demand and supply side in April and that weighed a lot on prices. More recently, the demand side of the equation started to improve as positive developments on the trade front made the market to expect better global growth ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, we might have a doube bottom but we will need a break above the resistance to confirm that. Fundamentally, the uptrend should remain intact as long as things continue to improve. In my opinion, a rally to 72.00 looks very likely now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can see that the price is back at the key resistance zone around the 64.00 level. This is where we can expect the sellers to step in with a defined risk above the level to position for a drop back into the 55.00 level. The buyers, on the other hand, will look for a break higher to increase the bullish bets into the major trendline around the 67.00 level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 1 hour chart, we can see that we have an upward trendline defining the bullish momentum. If we get a pullback, we can expect the buyers to lean on the trendline with a defined risk below it to position for a break above the resistance. The sellers, on the other hand, will look for a break lower to increase the bearish bets into the 55.00 level next. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Goolsbee: It will take time for current inflation trends to show up in the data</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolsbee-it-will-take-time-for-current-inflation-trends-to-show-up-in-the-data-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:37:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolsbee-it-will-take-time-for-current-inflation-trends-to-show-up-in-the-data-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some part of April inflation represents lagged nature of data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed is still very much holding its breath&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Right now is a time for the Fed to wait for more information, try to get past the noise in the data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Cannot jump to conclusions about long-term trends given all the short-term volatility present&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Fed&apos;s task is to be a steady hand and not to respond to daily gyrations of stock market, policy pronouncements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;His comments continue to reaffirm that the Fed is still very much in wait-and-see mode. And that will certainly continue to irk Trump, with his latest disdain towards Fed chair Powell coming yesterday &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/trump-tells-powell-to-cut-rates-let-it-all-happen-it-will-be-a-beautiful-thing-20250513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No monetary policy comments by Waller in his speech in Morocco</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/no-monetary-policy-comments-by-waller-in-his-speech-in-morocco-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:17:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/no-monetary-policy-comments-by-waller-in-his-speech-in-morocco-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;If you&apos;re waiting on this, then it&apos;s a bit of a dud. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/speech/waller20250514a.htm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Here&apos;s&lt;/a&gt; the full speech. It&apos;s an awards ceremony so I&apos;m not sure if there will be a Q&amp;amp;A of sorts after his prepared speech here.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China April M2 money supply +8.0% vs +7.3% y/y expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-april-m2-money-supply-80-vs-73-yy-expected-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:05:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-april-m2-money-supply-80-vs-73-yy-expected-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior +7.0%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New yuan loans ¥280.0 billion vs ¥700.0 billion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prior ¥3.64 trillion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;After the big surge in March, new bank loans in China fell off with the reading even coming in well below estimates. The ramp up in Q1 comes as policymakers were ramping up stimulus in preparations of a trade war with the US. So, there&apos;s that. Still, outstanding yuan loans are seen up 7.2% year-on-year as of April.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Nagel: Euro will become stronger as a reserve currency in the coming years</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-euro-will-become-stronger-as-a-reserve-currency-in-the-coming-years-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 09:02:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-euro-will-become-stronger-as-a-reserve-currency-in-the-coming-years-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dollar is very important for the world financial system&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But the role of the euro will become stronger as a reserve currency over the next few years&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Well, the dollar has certainly lost some credibility and allure in the last two months. And this week&apos;s price action itself underscores that sentiment, with the big gains on Monday quickly being erased yesterday and today. But in terms of wider acceptance for payments, the euro itself has struggled over the past decade while dollar usage continues to dominate. The single currency used to command 30% to 35% of the share of international payments via SWIFT. However, that share has now dropped to around 21% to 23% in the past two years. Here&apos;s the latest breakdown from January this year:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of NFTs: Beyond Digital Art</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/the-future-of-nfts-beyond-digital-art-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Education/the-future-of-nfts-beyond-digital-art-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There was a time — not
long ago, and not far from here — when a JPEG of a cartoon animal could be sold
for the price of a London flat. At first, it looked like a digital renaissance,
then perhaps something more suspect. Now, with the early dust settled, what’s
left is not exactly a crash, but a pause. And in that pause, something more
sober and arguably more interesting has begun to form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NFTs — those
much-maligned and much-misunderstood tokens — are edging toward a broader
cultural role. Not just in art galleries or Twitter avatars, but in ownership
structures, digital identity, and software licensing. They are becoming less
about hype and more about utility. And as collectors shift from sensation to
substance, so too does the shape of the ecosystem. It’s not glamorous, but then
again, neither was the internet when it was mostly message boards and mailing
lists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quiet Commerce&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a quiet
diligence to the way people browse an &lt;a href=&quot;https://magiceden.io/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;NFT marketplace&lt;/a&gt; now. Less of the
speculative fervour. More patience. You’ll find a mix of seasoned collectors
and quiet optimists poring over contract terms, metadata, and artist track
records — more interested in provenance than promise. The hype hasn’t
disappeared, but it has been diluted. Replaced by a kind of forensic curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And with this shift
comes a new kind of discernment. The term &quot;NFT marketplace&quot; used to
conjure a carnival — neon, noise, velocity. Now, it&apos;s more like a secondhand
bookshop: considered, maybe a bit dusty, but sincere. People still look for beauty,
of course, but they&apos;re also looking for function. Access passes, tokenised
experiences, licencing rights. All hidden in plain sight if you know what to
look for. It&apos;s not about flipping anymore. It&apos;s about belonging. About a future
version of ownership that doesn’t feel like ownership at all — just
participation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the Frame&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Art is still the entry
point for many, and that’s fine. But NFTs are beginning to stretch beyond the
screen. They&apos;re in concert tickets, digital diplomas, domain names. Not always
called NFTs, mind you — sometimes rebranded, renamed, obscured under new language.
But the structure’s the same. A unique, verifiable token stored on a chain.
It’s not the label that matters anymore. It’s the quiet infrastructure behind
it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A growing number of
creative professionals — writers, musicians, developers — are beginning to
explore NFTs as a licensing tool. One token, one licence, no intermediaries.
It&apos;s less a revolution than a workaround. A way of owning your own distribution
without chasing ad revenue or algorithmic favour. Again, not particularly
flashy. But durable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Long View&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;re at the point now
where it&apos;s no longer &quot;What can NFTs do?&quot; but &quot;What should they
do?&quot; The tech adapts. But the culture surrounding it will decide its next
chapter. Two things loom largest: integration or isolation. Either NFTs are a
quiet component of broader systems — part of how we manage identity, contracts,
access — or they become an isolate for digital collectibles with a shrinking
audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The signs point to the
former. Financial institutions are exploring tokenisation. Universities are
testing on-chain certification. Artists are licensing exclusive works through
tokens that act as both proof and access. Slowly, NFTs are becoming less about
speculation and more about structure. A digital filing cabinet of sorts — part
record, part key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin, and the Rest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From time to time,
Bitcoin enters the conversation again. Not directly, but always there in the
background. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency&quot;&gt;The original token&lt;/a&gt;, the benchmark, the
baseline. Discussions around Bitcoin still dominate much of the financial
commentary — and not without reason. Its price movements shape sentiment across
the board. If &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/crypto-takes-another-bath-on-trump-tariff-tade-war-20250402/&quot;&gt;Bitcoin &lt;/a&gt;rallies, interest in adjacent
tokens, including NFTs, often follows. But that correlation is weakening. NFTs,
at least the more functional ones, are beginning to detach from Bitcoin’s
volatility. Not entirely, but enough to chart a slightly different course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And for all the
obsession with the valuations, many in the NFT space have learned to tune it
out. They keep one eye on the charts, yes — everyone does — but their focus is
elsewhere: on deliverables, communities, and contracts. The NFT crowd, in its
quieter corners, is maturing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Function Before Fame&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most promising use
cases now are the ones no one’s bragging about. Backend permissions for
software. Tickets that can’t be faked. Proof of attendance. Proof of
authorship. These are small, infrastructural things — not front-page headlines,
but foundations. And often, that’s where long-term value lives. Not in the
aesthetic but the administrative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is not to say the
art is done. It isn’t. But it’s becoming something else — less performative,
more embedded. NFT projects that succeed in 2025 and beyond will likely be the
ones you don’t even notice. They’ll sit quietly under the products and services
you use every day. Invisible, but integral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the End, Ownership&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At its heart, the NFT &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2021/apr/03/non-fungible-tokens-digital-art-artists&quot;&gt;is still about ownership&lt;/a&gt;. Just not in the way
it was sold to us a few years ago. It&apos;s not about bragging rights or early
adoption. It’s about clarity. Who made this? Who owns it? Who can use it, and
how? It’s about drawing lines — gently — in a digital world that’s long been boundaryless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That might not be the
revolution people were promised. But it might be the one they actually needed.
Something less cinematic. More lived-in. NFTs not as statement pieces but as
tools. Quiet, purposeful, and — in time — indispensable.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by FL Contributors at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD is approaching a key resistance amid some dollar weakness</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-is-approaching-a-key-resistance-amid-some-dollar-weakness-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:34:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurusd-is-approaching-a-key-resistance-amid-some-dollar-weakness-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;There was no catalyst for the sudden weakness in the US Dollar but this move could offer a great opportunity for dollar bulls. The short dollar trade is still a bit overcrowded and there are good reasons to see Treasury yields moving higher in the next weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m starting to doubt that we even get more than one rate cut this year but for the market to price that in we will likely need stronger 
economic data or more hawkish Fed comments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fed&apos;s Waller is set to speak in a bit. Let&apos;s see if he&apos;s going to deliver some hawkish comments (keep in mind he might not comment on monetary policy at all at this event) and give the greenback another boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we can see that the pair is approaching a key resistance zone around the 1.1275 level where we can find the confluence of the old support and the downward trendline. If the price gets there, we can expect the sellers to step in with a defined risk above the trendline to position for a drop into the 1.10 handle. The buyers, on the other hand, will want to see the price breaking higher to invalidate the bearish setup and start targeting the 1.15 handle next.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Nagel: There is a good probability we will get to 2% inflation target</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-there-is-a-good-probability-we-will-get-to-2-inflation-target-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:22:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-there-is-a-good-probability-we-will-get-to-2-inflation-target-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Current uncertainty will be the new &quot;normal&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Central banks have to get used to managing it&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expect there to be new staff projections in June&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;But we don&apos;t know the exact impact from tariffs on inflation and the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;June rate decision depends on incoming data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;At least he&apos;s trying to paint a bit more of an honest picture with these remarks. But at the end of the day, groupthink is a main issue with central banks. When the going gets tough, everyone defers to the majority view to not be &quot;wrong&quot; and to not jeopardise their reputation. Pfft. Anyway, markets are pricing in ~81% odds of a 25 bps rate cut in June currently.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German economy ministry: A renewed weakening of the economy cannot be ruled out</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/german-economy-ministry-a-renewed-weakening-of-the-economy-cannot-be-ruled-out-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:13:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/german-economy-ministry-a-renewed-weakening-of-the-economy-cannot-be-ruled-out-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Business expectations remain gloomy, particularly in export-oriented manufacturing sector&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Inflation likely to remain in the region of 2% for the remainder of the year&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Trade and economic policy uncertainty remains significantly elevated&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just some token remarks there from Germany. Despite some improvement to the outlook, the backdrop remains challenging for Europe&apos;s largest economy. Not least with inflationary pressures still holding up for the time being.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCHF returns inside the big range as the short positioning in the USD unwinds</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdchf-returns-inside-the-big-range-as-the-short-positioning-in-the-usd-unwinds-20250514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 08:11:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdchf-returns-inside-the-big-range-as-the-short-positioning-in-the-usd-unwinds-20250514/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US Dollar has been under strong selling pressure for a
 few months and eventually became one of the most crowded trades. When you get at such overstretched levels, as soon as 
conditions change, the repricing in expectations can lead to notable corrections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the last few weeks, the positive news on the trade front started to boost the greenback as the market begun to unwind those crowded dollar shorts amid a more hawkish repricing in rate cuts expectations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the peak of the trade war fears, the market went 
to price in as far as five rate cuts by the end of 2025, and now 
following the US-China news, we are down to just two rate cuts (which 
was the Fed&apos;s base case in December 2024).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We should see further gains for the greenback as the market might even 
start to doubt the need for two rate cuts, but for that, stronger 
economic data or more hawkish Fed comments might be needed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the daily chart, we can see the big range between the 0.8350 support and the 0.9250 resistance. The pair broke below the support during the April&apos;s risk-off flows but has now bounced back inside the range. We can see that we have a major trendline defining the bearish trend and from a risk management perspective, the sellers will have a better risk to reward setup around the trendline to position for further downside. The buyers, on the other hand, will want to see the price breaking higher to start targeting the 0.9250 resistance next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the 4 hour chart, we are seeing a pullback after the spike triggered by the US-China news on Monday. The buyers will likely pile in around the 0.8330-0.8380 price area to position for a rally into the major trendline. The sellers, on the other hand, will look for a break lower to extend the pullback into the upward trendline around the 0.8260 level.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Giuseppe Dellamotta at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
