<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>Eurostoxx futures +0.1% in early European trading</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:06:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/eurostoxx-futures-01-in-early-european-trading-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX futures +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK FTSE futures +0.1%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;This follows from the modest gains yesterday, with US stocks also performing decently outside of tech shares. For today, the mood music is more tentative with US futures also not suggestive of much. S&amp;amp;P 500 futures are flat currently as we look towards European trading.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barclays no longer expects a US recession in the second half of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/barclays-no-longer-expects-a-us-recession-in-the-second-half-of-the-year-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 06:04:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/barclays-no-longer-expects-a-us-recession-in-the-second-half-of-the-year-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;The change in forecast basically just speaks to the change in sentiment. Just last week, it was all still doom and gloom. So, yeah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;In any case, Barclays is now forecasting the US economy to grow by 0.5% this year and 1.6% next year. That&apos;s a step up from their previous forecasts of -0.3% and 1.5% respectively. They also see better prospects for the euro area now, expecting the economy to come in flat for the year as compared to their previous forecast of a 0.2% contraction.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One key chart to watch out for in the months ahead</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/one-key-chart-to-watch-out-for-in-the-months-ahead-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:56:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/one-key-chart-to-watch-out-for-in-the-months-ahead-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;From the previous trade embargo, it&apos;s basically a complete reversal in circumstances now. Customers and businesses are all piling in orders during this 90-day rush period. But what does it all really mean? Well, all you have to do is think back to the second half of 2020 of the Covid pandemic. We went from major lockdowns across the globe and then restarting everything again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That increased pressure on supply chains as global shipments suddenly skyrocketed again. This time around, the &quot;lockdown&quot; period is less and it mainly only pertains to China. However, that still has a major impact on supply chains and it will likely only start showing up more evidently in the months ahead and in the second half of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;And even more so when we still don&apos;t know the fate of US-China negotiations in the coming 90 days or longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;As mentioned before: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariffs-policy-can-change-overnight-but-supply-chains-cannot-20250513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Tariffs policy can change overnight but supply chains cannot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;With the easing on tariffs earlier this week, it is reported that ocean freight bookings from China to the US are already up 275% this week compared to last week (h/t @ typesfast). That&apos;s the first step of how things are going to play out as per the linked post above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Eventually, the main worry here is that all of this will be one part that leads to higher prices and in turn, higher inflationary pressures. That was part of the equation that contributed to the surge in price pressures in 2021 and 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Central banks at the time kept insisting that it was all &quot;transitory&quot; but look where we are today. Sure, it looks to be that way but nobody said anything about the timeline for &quot;transitory&quot; I guess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;So, just be wary of the situation that&apos;s unfolding now as US-China tariffs do come down for the time being. This chart above is going to be one to watch to see how material the impact might be on the supply chain, amongst other hard data.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil traders: Watch Potential U.S. sanctions Against Russia</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-traders-watch-potential-us-sanctions-against-russia-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:12:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/oil-traders-watch-potential-us-sanctions-against-russia-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Putin&apos;s Absence Raises Prospect of New Sanctions – Oil Traders Stay Alert&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vladimir Putin&apos;s recent absence from scheduled peace talks in Turkey, intended to address the ongoing conflict with Ukraine, has escalated geopolitical tensions and raised speculation about the potential for harsher U.S. sanctions against Russia. Traders and investors are now closely watching developments as Senator Lindsey Graham sponsors a new round of proposed sanctions specifically targeting Russia’s critical oil and gas refining sectors, alongside third-party nations indirectly supporting Russia by purchasing its energy products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be prepared. Should these sanctions be enacted, markets can expect volatility in oil prices. Historically, sanctions limiting Russian oil and refined product exports tighten global supply, often resulting in upward pressure on oil prices—bullish for oil futures (WTI and Brent). Conversely, Russian-linked assets, including the ruble, could face bearish pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors and traders seeking to capitalize or hedge positions should closely monitor:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. legislative updates: Signals from the Trump administration or key senators indicating movement towards sanctions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil price movements: Particularly futures contracts for WTI and Brent crude, as traders preemptively price in supply disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currency reactions: The Russian ruble may experience downward volatility, offering forex traders speculative and hedging opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the situation evolves, traders should stay alert to official announcements from Washington and Moscow, closely following ForexLive.com, evolving later this year to investingLive.com, for timely updates and actionable insights.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Kazāks: Meeting-by-meeting approach is right</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-kazks-meeting-by-meeting-approach-is-right-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:09:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-kazks-meeting-by-meeting-approach-is-right-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A lot of uncertainty around trade measures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Even if they are seemingly taking things one step at a time, they are finding it a bit tough to defy market expectations if need be. As things stand, another 25 bps rate cut in June is all but lined up. Traders are pricing in a ~91% probability of that as of now.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECB&apos;s Villeroy: We are not currently in a currency war but rather a trade war situation</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-villeroy-we-are-not-currently-in-a-currency-war-but-rather-a-trade-war-situation-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 05:06:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-villeroy-we-are-not-currently-in-a-currency-war-but-rather-a-trade-war-situation-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protectionism and uncertainty are having a negative impact on US economic confidence&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;My guess is that he&apos;s commenting on the euro&apos;s recent showing against the dollar in comparison. I think ECB policymakers can take in some comfort that EUR/USD did ease off from a high of around 1.1500 in April. But as the trade conflict is yet to be resolved, it&apos;s no time to be complacent just yet.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China vice president Han says there is ample room for collaboration between US and China</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-vice-president-han-says-there-is-ample-room-for-collaboration-between-us-and-china-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:54:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/china-vice-president-han-says-there-is-ample-room-for-collaboration-between-us-and-china-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aims for US businesses to assist in promoting US-China relations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Just a casual exchange of pleasantries with both sides still awaiting more serious talks on trade for the time being.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX option expiries for 16 May 10am New York cut</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-16-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:48:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Orders/fx-option-expiries-for-16-may-10am-new-york-cut-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;There are a couple to take note of on the day, as highlighted in bold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;They are all for EUR/USD with a mega one in particular being at the 1.1200 level. That will be of much interest in keeping price action closer to the figure level before rolling off later in the day. The periphery expiries at 1.1150 and 1.1225 should help to hold price action in range with the main draw being the huge one at the 1.1200 mark. So, just take note of that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;That being said, headline risk is still a key factor to consider as broader markets remain sensitive to trade and geopolitical headlines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;For more information on how to use this data, you may refer to this post &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Education/!/forexlive-education-option-contracts-their-impact-and-how-to-trade-off-them-20161116/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOJ&apos;s Nakamura: US tariffs policy pose greater uncertainties, serious challenges for Japan</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bojs-nakamura-us-tariffs-policy-pose-greater-uncertainties-serious-challenges-for-japan-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 04:04:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bojs-nakamura-us-tariffs-policy-pose-greater-uncertainties-serious-challenges-for-japan-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;US policy, overseas economies, FX do affect Japan&apos;s economy and prices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;So that must be taken into account in monetary policy setting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Japan&apos;s economy has recovered moderately but some weakness still seen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Economy is facing mounting downward pressure due to US tariffs policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Momentum for wage hikes has accelerated but could weaken depending on US tariffs policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Companies are increasingly adopting wait-and-see stance on capex due to US tariffs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Uncertainty over economic outlook is heightening&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Cautious monetary policy approach is necessary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;Hiking rates prematurely when growth is slowing could curb consumption&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;It is extremely unclear how trade and other policies will unfold&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-justify&quot;&gt;TLDR: US tariffs have stuck a wrench in their plans. Now, they are on the sidelines waiting to see how tariffs will impact the economy and respond accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Justin Low at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ForexLive Asia-Pacific FX news wrap: Yen ↑ then ↓, Kiwi ↑, Gold ↓↓↓</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-yen-then-kiwi-gold-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:50:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-asia-pacific-fx-news-wrap-yen-then-kiwi-gold-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-speakers-friday-include-barkin-and-daly-20250516/&quot;&gt;Federal Reserve speakers Friday include Barkin and Daly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/rbnz-2-year-inflation-expectations-229-prior-was-206-20250516/&quot;&gt;RBNZ 2 year inflation expectations 2.29% (prior was 2.06%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/banxico-governor-victoria-rodriguez-says-inflation-and-economy-slowing-20250516/&quot;&gt;Banxico Governor Victoria Rodriguez says inflation and economy slowing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-koreas-finance-ministry-says-the-economy-faces-increasing-downward-pressure-20250516/&quot;&gt;South Korea&apos;s finance ministry says the economy faces increasing&quot; downward pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-says-vietnams-trade-deficit-is-unsustainable-and-a-major-concern-amid-tariff-talks-20250516/&quot;&gt;The US says Vietnam&apos;s trade deficit is unsustainable and a major concern amid tariff talks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-centralbank-chief-economist-lane-speaking-friday-20250516/&quot;&gt;European Central Bank Chief Economist Lane speaking Friday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-policy-board-member-nakamura-toyoaki-is-speaking-soon-20250516/&quot;&gt;Bank of Japan Policy Board member Nakamura Toyoaki is speaking soon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/icymi-wisconsin-sells-entire-bitcoin-etf-position-after-early-bet-on-blackrock-fund-20250516/&quot;&gt;ICYMI: Wisconsin sells entire bitcoin ETF position after early bet on BlackRock fund&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japaneconomyministerakazawagovtwillcontinuetodemandreviewofustariffs-20250516/&quot;&gt;Japan economy minister Akazawa: Govt will continue to demand review of U.S. tariffs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71938-vs-estimate-at-72085-20250516/&quot;&gt;PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1938 (vs. estimate at 7.2085)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/goldman-sachs-raises-its-12-month-target-for-msci-asia-pacific-ex-japan-to-660-from-620-20250516/&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs raises its 12-month target for MSCI Asia-Pacific ex-Japan to 660 from 620&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-analysts-expect-bitcoin-to-outperform-gold-for-the-rest-of-the-year-20250516/&quot;&gt;JP Morgan analysts expect Bitcoin to outperform gold for the rest of the year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/singapores-april-exports-surge-124-beating-expectations-but-outlook-remains-cautious-20250516/&quot;&gt;Singapore’s April exports surge 12.4%, beating expectations but outlook remains cautious&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finmin-kato-will-seek-to-have-a-meeting-with-bessent-discuss-fx-and-other-matters-20250516/&quot;&gt;Japan finmin Kato: Will seek to have a meeting with Bessent, discuss FX and other matters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/canadian-prime-minister-mexican-president-to-strengthen-economies-against-future-shocks-20250516/&quot;&gt;Canadian Prime Minister &amp;amp; Mexican President to strengthen economies against future shocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/75bp-of-reserve-bank-of-australia-rate-cuts-to-come-reuters-poll-20250516/&quot;&gt;75bp of Reserve Bank of Australia rate cuts to come (Reuters poll)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/usdjpy-little-changed-after-the-economic-contraction-data-from-japan-jpy-up-a-little-20250516/&quot;&gt;USD/JPY little changed after the economic contraction data from Japan, JPY up a little&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/&quot;&gt;Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finance-minister-kato-says-will-discuss-fx-with-bessent-20250515/&quot;&gt;Japan finance minister Kato says will discuss FX with Bessent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/ft-trump-administration-split-on-timing-of-adding-chinese-chipmakers-to-export-blacklist-20250515/&quot;&gt;FT: Trump administration split on timing of adding Chinese chipmakers to export blacklist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/new-zealand-april-manufacturing-pmi-shows-an-uptick-in-expansion-to-539-vs-prior-532-20250515/&quot;&gt;New Zealand April Manufacturing PMI shows an uptick in expansion to 53.9 vs. prior 53.2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/hsbc-modelling-sees-usdjpy-trading-a-141-149-range-theres-a-but-20250515/&quot;&gt;HSBC modelling sees USD/JPY trading a 141 - 149 range (there&apos;s a but)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/australia-financial-media-reports-that-australia-wont-join-trump-trade-war-on-china-20250515/&quot;&gt;Australia financial media reports that “Australia won’t join Trump trade war on China”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-deputy-treasury-secretary-says-not-concerned-about-persistent-increases-in-prices-20250515/&quot;&gt;U.S. Deputy Treasury Secretary says not concerned about persistent increases in prices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-us-to-resume-tariff-talks-after-g7-summit-as-akazawa-plans-washington-visit-20250515/&quot;&gt;Japan, US to resume tariff talks after G7 summit as Akazawa plans Washington visit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/south-koreaapril-exportpriceshave-shown-their-slowestriseyysincedecember-2023-20250515/&quot;&gt;South Korea April export prices have shown their slowest rise y/y since December 2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/forexlive-americas-fx-news-wrap-dip-in-ppi-pulls-down-usdjpy-20250515/&quot;&gt;Forexlive Americas FX news wrap: Dip in PPI pulls down USD/JPY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-ceo-dimon-says-us-recession-risks-remain-high-amid-deficits-and-inflation-20250515/&quot;&gt;JP Morgan CEO Dimon says US recession risks remain high amid deficits and inflation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/major-indices-close-mixed-nasdaq-lower-as-meta-reverses-course-on-ai-problems-20250515/&quot;&gt;Major indices close mixed. NASDAQ lower as Meta-reverses course on AI problems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-friday-16-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250515/&quot;&gt;Trade ideas thread - Friday, 16 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;
From
Japan today we had preliminary data for Q1 GDP. This was very poor
data, showing the tenuous nature of Japan’s economic recovery. The
annualised q/q came in at -0.7%, its first fall for a year. Exports
fell q/q, even as almost every other country on the planet were
ramping these higher ahead of US tariffs. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
yen gained after the data, with a strong deflator result, +3.3% y/y.
The Deflator in this data is an indicator of inflation. USD/JPY dealt
down to circa 145.00. It bounced back from there to highs above
145.40 and is around 145.30 as I post. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;News
flow was light and of little impact. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
Reserve Bank of New Zealand published the results of its Q2 inflation
expectations survey. Both 1- and 2-year inflation expectations rose,
helping an already climbing NZD/USD to climb higher. NZD/USD rose
from lows around 0.5865 to highs above 0.5900 as I post. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;The
USD was a little weaker also against EUR, AUD, GBP, CAD. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;western&quot;&gt;Gold
dropped back to under USD3210. 
&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve speakers Friday include Barkin and Daly</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-speakers-friday-include-barkin-and-daly-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:31:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/federal-reserve-speakers-friday-include-barkin-and-daly-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Both of these are after markets close:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2200 GMT/1800 US Eastern time: Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond President Thomas Barkin gives commencement address at Vance-Granville Community College&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;0140 GMT/2140		Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco President Mary Daly gives commencement address at the College of Western Idaho&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBNZ 2 year inflation expectations 2.29% (prior was 2.06%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/rbnz-2-year-inflation-expectations-229-prior-was-206-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/rbnz-2-year-inflation-expectations-229-prior-was-206-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Reserve Bank of New Zealand survey  for Q2 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1-year ahead inflation expectation 2.41%, prior 2.15%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-year ahead inflation expectation 2.3% (prior 2.1%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand&apos;s economy is in need of further rate cuts but the RBNZ will not like inflation expectations edging higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand dollar higher also:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spoke about this data point earlier today and what it might mean for the kiwi $. ICYMI:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RBNZ conducts quarterly surveys to gauge inflation expectations among business leaders and professional forecasters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past three quarters, the surveys indicate a general decline in both 1-year and 2-year ahead inflation expectations, suggesting that inflation is expected to move closer to the RBNZ&apos;s target band of 1–3%. The slight uptick in the 1-year expectation in Q1 2025 may reflect short-term factors, but the 2-year expectation continued its downward trend, indicating confidence in medium-term price stability. It&apos;s the two-year period that the RBNZ focuses on most in the survey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q1 2025 (Survey conducted in January 2025)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;306&quot; data-end=&quot;548&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;306&quot; data-end=&quot;387&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;308&quot; data-end=&quot;387&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1-year ahead inflation expectation: Increased to 2.15% from 2.05% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;388&quot; data-end=&quot;548&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;390&quot; data-end=&quot;548&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;2-year ahead inflation expectation: Decreased to 2.06% from 2.12% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q4 2024 (Survey conducted in October 2024)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;602&quot; data-end=&quot;844&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;602&quot; data-end=&quot;683&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;604&quot; data-end=&quot;683&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1-year ahead inflation expectation: Decreased to 2.05% from 2.40% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;844&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;686&quot; data-end=&quot;844&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;2-year ahead inflation expectation: Increased to 2.12% from 2.03% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Q3 2024 (Survey conducted in July 2024)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;895&quot; data-end=&quot;1137&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;895&quot; data-end=&quot;976&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;897&quot; data-end=&quot;976&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;1-year ahead inflation expectation: Decreased to 2.40% from 2.73% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;977&quot; data-end=&quot;1137&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;979&quot; data-end=&quot;1137&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;2-year ahead inflation expectation: Decreased to 2.03% from 2.33% in the previous quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RBNZ closely monitors these expectations to inform its monetary policy stance. The decline in medium-term expectations aligns with the central bank&apos;s goal of maintaining inflation within its target range, potentially allowing for more accommodative monetary policy if the trend continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An upside move for the two-year should support the NZD, at the margin.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBNZ 2 year inflation expectations 2.29%  (prior 2.06%)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/rbnz-2-year-inflation-expectations-229-prior-206-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:04:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/rbnz-2-year-inflation-expectations-229-prior-206-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Reserve Bank of New Zealand &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banxico Governor Victoria Rodriguez says inflation and economy slowing</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/banxico-governor-victoria-rodriguez-says-inflation-and-economy-slowing-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 03:02:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/banxico-governor-victoria-rodriguez-says-inflation-and-economy-slowing-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Banxico Governor Victoria Rodriguez speaking in a radio interview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;the Bank will consider continuing weakness in the economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;goods and services CPI is slowing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don&apos;t have to read too far between the lines here to see further rate cuts ahead from Banco de México (abbreviated BdeM or Banxico).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll probably get sent to the naughty corner for posting this. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea&apos;s finance ministry says the economy faces increasing&quot; downward pressure</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-koreas-finance-ministry-says-the-economy-faces-increasing-downward-pressure-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:54:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/south-koreas-finance-ministry-says-the-economy-faces-increasing-downward-pressure-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;South Korea&apos;s  Ministry of Economy and Finance monthly economic report, the Green Book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;economy is facing &quot;increasing&quot; downward pressure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;due largely to a slowdown in exports amid lingering trade uncertainties and a decline in domestic consumption&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the fifth consecutive month the Ministry has made such an assessment:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&quot;The economy is facing growing downward pressure, as the recovery in domestic demand remains sluggish and job market difficulties persist, particularly in vulnerable sectors. External conditions have worsen due to U.S. tariff policies, leading to a slowdown in exports&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The US says Vietnam&apos;s trade deficit is unsustainable and a major concern amid tariff talks</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-says-vietnams-trade-deficit-is-unsustainable-and-a-major-concern-amid-tariff-talks-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:54:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/the-us-says-vietnams-trade-deficit-is-unsustainable-and-a-major-concern-amid-tariff-talks-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The US has told Vietnam that Vietnam&apos;s trade deficit is unsustainable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;a major concern amid tariff talks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vietnamese Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank Chief Economist Lane speaking Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-centralbank-chief-economist-lane-speaking-friday-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:26:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/european-centralbank-chief-economist-lane-speaking-friday-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Lane may give some clues about the next European Central Bank rate move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1500 GMT/1100 US Eastern time:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Participation by ECB board member Philip Lane in Policymaker Panel: &quot;Central Bank Communications and Uncertainty&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; at 2nd Thomas Laubach Research Conference organised by the Federal Reserve Board in Washington D.C.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Japan Policy Board member Nakamura Toyoaki is speaking soon</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-policy-board-member-nakamura-toyoaki-is-speaking-soon-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:12:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-policy-board-member-nakamura-toyoaki-is-speaking-soon-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll be interested in his take on today&apos;s awful GDP number out of Japan:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he addresses it!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We might have to wait for any following Q&amp;amp;A. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICYMI: Wisconsin sells entire bitcoin ETF position after early bet on BlackRock fund</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/icymi-wisconsin-sells-entire-bitcoin-etf-position-after-early-bet-on-blackrock-fund-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 02:02:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/Cryptocurrency/icymi-wisconsin-sells-entire-bitcoin-etf-position-after-early-bet-on-blackrock-fund-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;152&quot; data-end=&quot;541&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;ICYMI, overnight reports that the State of Wisconsin Investment Board (SWIB) has exited its position in BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust ETF (IBIT), divesting over six million shares during the first quarter of 2025. According to a recent filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, SWIB no longer holds any spot Bitcoin ETF exposure, marking a full retreat from the $355 million stake it previously held.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;543&quot; data-end=&quot;911&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Wisconsin had been among the first U.S. state pension managers to venture into Bitcoin-backed ETFs, initially purchasing $164 million worth of shares when the funds launched in early 2024. The move had positioned the state as an early adopter of crypto exposure for retirees, but the latest filings confirm a complete liquidation of that position within just one year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;543&quot; data-end=&quot;911&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Info via crypot media outlets. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan economy minister Akazawa: Govt will continue to demand review of U.S. tariffs</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japaneconomyministerakazawagovtwillcontinuetodemandreviewofustariffs-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:30:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japaneconomyministerakazawagovtwillcontinuetodemandreviewofustariffs-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan economy minister Akazawa remarks after the poor economic data earlier from Japan:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improvements in job, income conditions likely to underpin moderate economic recovery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be mindful of downside risks to economy from U.S. trade policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hit to consumption, household sentiment from sustained price rises also becoming downside risk to Japan’s economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Govt will continue to demand review of U.S. tariffs, take all necessary steps to offer liquidity aid to impacted firms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No notable impact of US tariffs on Japan’s Q1 GDP, will scrutinise various data that will become available to gauge impact on economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Domestic demand rose in Q1, while negative external demand contribution was due to rise in imports
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Government has no plan now to compile fresh stimulus package but will coordinate appropriately with ruling coalition&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Akazawa sais its important to communicate closely with other countries, when asked whether Japan was ready to coordinate with countries with big automobile plants like Mexico, Canada&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY update:&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBOC sets USD/ CNY reference rate for today at 7.1938 (vs. estimate at 7.2085)</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71938-vs-estimate-at-72085-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/pboc-sets-usd-cny-reference-rate-for-today-at-71938-vs-estimate-at-72085-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The People&apos;s Bank of China (PBOC), China&apos;s central bank, is responsible for setting the daily midpoint of the yuan (also known as renminbi or RMB). The PBOC follows a managed floating exchange rate system that allows the value of the yuan to fluctuate within a certain range, called a &quot;band,&quot; around a central reference rate, or &quot;midpoint.&quot; It&apos;s currently at +/- 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous close was 7.2067&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;more to come &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PBOC injected 106.5bn yuan via 7-day reverse repos at 1.40%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;0bn yuan mature today&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;net injection 106.5bn yuan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs raises its 12-month target for MSCI Asia-Pacific ex-Japan to 660 from 620</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/goldman-sachs-raises-its-12-month-target-for-msci-asia-pacific-ex-japan-to-660-from-620-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 01:14:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/goldman-sachs-raises-its-12-month-target-for-msci-asia-pacific-ex-japan-to-660-from-620-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs raises its 12-month target for MSCI Asia-Pacific ex-Japan to 660 from 620&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;0&quot; data-end=&quot;90&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The MSCI Asia-Pacific ex-Japan Index is a widely followed stock market benchmark that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;92&quot; data-end=&quot;476&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;92&quot; data-end=&quot;239&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;94&quot; data-end=&quot;239&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Tracks the performance of large- and mid-cap stocks across developed and emerging markets in the Asia-Pacific region excluding Japan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;240&quot; data-end=&quot;409&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;242&quot; data-end=&quot;409&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Includes countries such as China, South Korea, Taiwan, India, Australia, Hong Kong, Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand, the Philippines, and New Zealand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;410&quot; data-end=&quot;476&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;412&quot; data-end=&quot;476&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Is maintained by MSCI Inc., a leading global index provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;779&quot; data-end=&quot;969&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Why exclude Japan?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;779&quot; data-end=&quot;969&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Japan has a large, mature, and heavily weighted stock market. Excluding it allows investors to focus on emerging and developing Asia-Pacific economies without Japan dominating the index.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP Morgan analysts expect Bitcoin to outperform gold for the rest of the year</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-analysts-expect-bitcoin-to-outperform-gold-for-the-rest-of-the-year-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:59:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/jp-morgan-analysts-expect-bitcoin-to-outperform-gold-for-the-rest-of-the-year-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;JP Morgan analysts expect Bitcoin to outperform gold for the rest of the year.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Citing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&quot;debasement trade&quot; where investors buy gold and Bitcoin as a hedge against weakening international currencies has turned into a zero-sum game in 2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;gold was gaining, and Bitcoin was losing ... until recently&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;since April’s peak, gold prices have declined Bitcoin has gained&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;flow of money taken out of gold exchange-traded funds (ETFs) and being poured into spot bitcoin and crypto funds since April&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;JP Morgan also note&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Hampshire crypto bill - state can invest up to 10% of its public funds in Bitcoin and precious metals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Arizona also passed a similar law&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;as more US states rule to invest in Bitcoin, it could act as a “sustained positive” catalyst&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can track this call &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/LiveCharts&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;using our free charts&lt;/a&gt;, here is BTC/XAU: &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore’s April exports surge 12.4%, beating expectations but outlook remains cautious</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/singapores-april-exports-surge-124-beating-expectations-but-outlook-remains-cautious-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:45:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/singapores-april-exports-surge-124-beating-expectations-but-outlook-remains-cautious-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;176&quot; data-end=&quot;480&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Singapore’s non-oil domestic exports jumped 12.4% in April compared to a year earlier, far exceeding expectations and marking a sharp acceleration from March’s 5.4% rise. The latest figures, released Friday by Enterprise Singapore, showed strong gains across both electronic and non-electronic shipments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;482&quot; data-end=&quot;750&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;The result came well above the 4.3% year-on-year increase forecast in a Reuters poll and reflected solid demand from key trading partners including the U.S., Japan, and regional economies such as Taiwan and South Korea. However, exports to China and Malaysia declined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;752&quot; data-end=&quot;1267&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;Despite the upside surprise, the broader outlook remains clouded by escalating global trade tensions, particularly in light of new tariffs imposed by the United States. Singapore, whose economy is heavily reliant on external trade, has been flagged as vulnerable to a global slowdown. In response, the government recently formed an economic resilience taskforce and warned that a recession cannot be ruled out. Last month, it revised its full-year GDP forecast down to a range of 0% to 2%, from a previous 1% to 3%.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan finmin Kato: Will seek to have a meeting with Bessent, discuss FX and other matters</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finmin-kato-will-seek-to-have-a-meeting-with-bessent-discuss-fx-and-other-matters-20250516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:25:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-finmin-kato-will-seek-to-have-a-meeting-with-bessent-discuss-fx-and-other-matters-20250516/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Japan finmin Kato:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Convinced that Bessent is a reliable counterpart able to have constructive dialogue, will continue to closely coordinate with him&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
Reaffirmed with Bessent in talks on April 24 that excessive Forex volatility has averse impact on economy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will continue talks with him based on this understanding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will seek to have a meeting with Bessent, discuss FX and other matters&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;USD/JPY update, a little lower now following the poor GDP data:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/news/japan-q1-gdp-02-qq-expected-01-20250515/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot; data-article-link=&quot;true&quot;&gt;Japan Q1 GDp -0.2% q/q (expected -0.1%)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *NVIDIA REPORTS 7% STAKE IN COREWEAVE IN 13G</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923114324479869131#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:32:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923114324479869131#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*NVIDIA REPORTS 7% STAKE IN COREWEAVE IN 13G&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *ACKMANS PERSHING EXITS NKE IN Q1:13F

$NKE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923108871356166577#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:10:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923108871356166577#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*ACKMANS PERSHING EXITS NKE IN Q1:13F&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NKE&quot;&gt;$NKE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *S&amp;P 500 CLOSES UP 0.3%, NASDAQ FALLS 0.2%</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923106366782079010#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 20:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923106366782079010#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*S&amp;amp;P 500 CLOSES UP 0.3%, NASDAQ FALLS 0.2%&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HHS TO STOP RECOMMENDING ROUTINE COVID SHOTS FOR CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923103658792616242#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:50:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923103658792616242#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HHS TO STOP RECOMMENDING ROUTINE COVID SHOTS FOR CHILDREN, PREGNANT WOMEN -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *META TO DELAY ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP: WSJ

*META&apos;S &apos;BEHEMOTH&apos; WAS INTERNALLY SLATED FOR APRIL RELEASE: WSJ

*META ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP AI MODEL DELAYED TO FALL OR LATER: WSJ

$META</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923096475015274849#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:21:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923096475015274849#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*META TO DELAY ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*META&apos;S &apos;BEHEMOTH&apos; WAS INTERNALLY SLATED FOR APRIL RELEASE: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*META ROLLOUT OF FLAGSHIP AI MODEL DELAYED TO FALL OR LATER: WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23META&quot;&gt;$META&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *COINBASE HACKERS HAD ACCESS TO CUSTOMER DATA SINCE JANUARY

$COIN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923092251049177096#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923092251049177096#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*COINBASE HACKERS HAD ACCESS TO CUSTOMER DATA SINCE JANUARY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *STATE OF WISCONSIN INVESTMENT BOARD EXITS BITCOIN ETF POSITION: SEC FILING</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923090409468711385#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923090409468711385#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*STATE OF WISCONSIN INVESTMENT BOARD EXITS BITCOIN ETF POSITION: SEC FILING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US-UAE AI CAMPUS WILL PARTNER WITH &apos;SEVERAL&apos; US COMPANIES</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085920363831532#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:39:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085920363831532#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US-UAE AI CAMPUS WILL PARTNER WITH &apos;SEVERAL&apos; US COMPANIES&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *DOJ PROBING IF HARVARD ADMISSIONS DEFRAUDED GOVERNMENT: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085187870576740#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085187870576740#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*DOJ PROBING IF HARVARD ADMISSIONS DEFRAUDED GOVERNMENT: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *STATE DEPARTMENT IS LEADING CAMPAIGN ACCUSING EUROPE OF LIMITING FREE SPEECH AND PROMOTING CENSORSHIP -- WSJ

*ADMINISTRATION SEES EU AS PART OF ‘GLOBAL CENSORSHIP-INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX’ HURTING U.S. TECH -- WSJ</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923085085919641778#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:36:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923085085919641778#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*STATE DEPARTMENT IS LEADING CAMPAIGN ACCUSING EUROPE OF LIMITING FREE SPEECH AND PROMOTING CENSORSHIP -- WSJ&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
*ADMINISTRATION SEES EU AS PART OF ‘GLOBAL CENSORSHIP-INDUSTRIAL COMPLEX’ HURTING U.S. TECH -- WSJ&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *RUSSIA DEPLOYS 640,000 TROOPS IN WAR AGAINST UKRAINE: MILITARY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923074660993835285#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:55:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923074660993835285#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*RUSSIA DEPLOYS 640,000 TROOPS IN WAR AGAINST UKRAINE: MILITARY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE LEGAL HEAD CALLS SEC INVESTIGATION A RELIC OF PAST ADMINISTRATION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923072444299915747#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:46:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923072444299915747#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE LEGAL HEAD CALLS SEC INVESTIGATION A RELIC OF PAST ADMINISTRATION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) COINBASE CHIEF LEGAL OFFICER: REPORTED SEC INVESTIGATION IS A HOLD-OVER FROM PRIOR ADMINISTRATION ABOUT A METRIC WE STOPPED REPORTING 2.5 YEARS AGO</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923072369427354065#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:45:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923072369427354065#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;COINBASE CHIEF LEGAL OFFICER: REPORTED SEC INVESTIGATION IS A HOLD-OVER FROM PRIOR ADMINISTRATION ABOUT A METRIC WE STOPPED REPORTING 2.5 YEARS AGO&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068895058854237#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: PROBABLY GOING BACK TO DC TOMORROW, THOUGH DESTINATION UNKNOWN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923068603189940352#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: THINK AI PROJECT WITH UAE WILL BE SPECIAL, NVIDIA&apos;S HUANG WAS HERE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $NVDA - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923067390608236656#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23NVDA&quot;&gt;$NVDA&lt;/a&gt; - TRUMP SPEAKS WITH NVIDIA&apos;S CEO HUANG IN THE UAE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $COIN - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066478888104404#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23COIN&quot;&gt;$COIN&lt;/a&gt; - *SEC INVESTIGATING WHETHER COINBASE MISSTATED ITS USER NUMBERS:NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:22:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923066353805647975#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FTX: FTX RECOVERY TRUST TO DISTRIBUTE MORE THAN $5 BLN TO CREDITORS IN SECOND DISTRIBUTION ON MAY 30&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade

🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:54:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923059327721480549#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. Seeks EU Talks on Agriculture, China, Digital Trade&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 The U.S. asked the EU to discuss agricultural tariffs, trade barriers, economic security (mainly China concerns), and digital issues in upcoming trade talks.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 A document outlining these topics was shared with the EU.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 EU Trade Commissioner Sefcovic confirmed ongoing discussions but declined to comment on the U.S. proposal.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1923058881128772082#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RUBIO SAYS WE DON&apos;T HAVE HIGH EXPECTATIONS FOR UKRAINE TALKS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
