<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>No name</title>
    <link>https://example.com/feed2</link>
    <description>RSS feed merged from source 2</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>US stocks close sharply higher on US China tariff news</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-close-sharply-higher-on-us-china-tariff-news-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:30:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-stocks-close-sharply-higher-on-us-china-tariff-news-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The major US stock indices are sharply higher on US/China tariff news. Over the weekend the US slashed tariffs for the next 90-days on China goods from 145% to 30% inclusive of a 20% tariff due to fentanyl. The news led to sharp buying which did not abate. The broader S&amp;amp;P and Nasdaq indices had their 2nd best days going back to 2022.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final numbers are showing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dow industrial average rose 1160.7 2.2 or 2.81% to 42,410.10.  That was the second-best day going back to November 6, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;S&amp;amp;P index rose 184.28 points or 3.26% at 5844.19. That was the 2nd-best % day going back to November 10.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NASDAQ index rose 779.43 points or 4.35% at 18708.34. That was the second-best day since November 30.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Russell 2000 rose 16.12 points or 3.42% at 2092.19. For that index, it was a second-best day since November 6, 2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the bigger winners today included:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;73&quot; data-end=&quot;111&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;75&quot; data-end=&quot;111&quot;&gt;Shopify Inc   +13.71%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;112&quot; data-end=&quot;150&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;114&quot; data-end=&quot;150&quot;&gt;First Solar  +11.07%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;151&quot; data-end=&quot;181&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;153&quot; data-end=&quot;181&quot;&gt;Block   +9.29%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;182&quot; data-end=&quot;219&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;184&quot; data-end=&quot;219&quot;&gt;Lam Research   +9.18%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;220&quot; data-end=&quot;256&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;222&quot; data-end=&quot;256&quot;&gt;Amazon.com   +8.09%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;257&quot; data-end=&quot;297&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;259&quot; data-end=&quot;297&quot;&gt;Meta Platforms   +7.92%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;298&quot; data-end=&quot;327&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;300&quot; data-end=&quot;327&quot;&gt;Arm   +7.77%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;328&quot; data-end=&quot;359&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;330&quot; data-end=&quot;359&quot;&gt;Micron   +7.49%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;360&quot; data-end=&quot;396&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;362&quot; data-end=&quot;396&quot;&gt;Papa John’s   +7.26%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;397&quot; data-end=&quot;429&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;399&quot; data-end=&quot;429&quot;&gt;Gilead   +7.12%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;430&quot; data-end=&quot;461&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;432&quot; data-end=&quot;461&quot;&gt;FedEx   +6.94%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;462&quot; data-end=&quot;491&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;464&quot; data-end=&quot;491&quot; data-is-last-node=&quot;&quot;&gt;Tesla   +6.82%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at some of the other leading gainers:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alphabet +3.74%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft, +2.40%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nvidia, + 5.44%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nike  +7.34%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) AMAZON STRIKES A NEW PARTNERSHIP WITH FEDEX AFTER UPS PULLBACK - BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922026103784321333#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:28:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922026103784321333#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AMAZON STRIKES A NEW PARTNERSHIP WITH FEDEX AFTER UPS PULLBACK - BUSINESS INSIDER&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic calendar in Asia Tuesday, May 13, 2025 - Bank of Japan policy meeting summary</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-tuesday-may-13-2025-bank-of-japan-policy-meeting-summary-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:05:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/economic-calendar-in-asia-tuesday-may-13-2025-bank-of-japan-policy-meeting-summary-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The Bank of Japan &apos;Summary of Opinions&apos; for its most recent meeting, April 30 - May 1, is today.  Policy was left unchanged at this meeting:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/bank-of-japan-leaves-policy-unchanged-as-widely-expected-20250501/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;follow&quot;&gt;Bank of Japan maintains its short term rate at 0.5%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The BoJ cited growing headwinds from higher US tariffs. The Bank cut its 2025 and 2026 economic growth forecasts in its quarterly outlook report.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;ll get more info on this meeting with the Summary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;---&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;The Bank of Japan (BOJ) releases a &quot;Summary of Opinions&quot; after each monetary policy meeting. It serves as a record of the discussion and views of the Policy Board members on various economic and financial issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key points about the Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The summary includes the views of the Policy Board members on economic conditions, both domestically and globally. This includes assessments of economic growth, inflation, and employment trends, among other indicators.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The summary also outlines the Policy Board members&apos; views on the effectiveness of the BOJ&apos;s current monetary policy measures, including interest rate policy, asset purchases, and yield curve control. Members may discuss the pros and cons of these policies and their potential impact on the economy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The summary includes discussions on the outlook for monetary policy and the potential risks to the economy. Board members may express their views on the appropriate timing and direction of future policy changes, as well as the potential impact of external factors such as global economic conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The summary also includes any dissenting views among the Policy Board members. If a member disagrees with the majority view on a particular issue, they may express their own opinion and rationale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a few week&apos;s time we&apos;ll get the Minutes of this meeting. The Minutes are a more detailed record of the discussions and decisions made during the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;text-align-start vertical-align-baseline&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Minutes include a more complete record of the views expressed, including any dissents or alternative opinions that may not be included in the summary.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Summary of Opinions is typically released a few days after the policy meeting, while the Minutes are published about a month later. This means that the Summary of Opinions can provide more up-to-date information on the BOJ&apos;s current stance and view on the economy and monetary policy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Summary of Opinions is usually written in a more accessible language, making it easier to understand the BOJ&apos;s views on monetary policy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Minutes, on the other hand, are often more technical and may require a deeper understanding of economics and financial markets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Summary of Opinions is typically shorter than the Minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This snapshot from the ForexLive economic data calendar, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/EconomicCalendar&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; title=&quot;Click here!&quot;&gt;access it here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The times in the left-most column are GMT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The numbers in the right-most column are the &apos;prior&apos; (previous month/quarter as the case may be) result. The number in the column next to that, where there is a number, is the consensus median expected.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade ideas thread - Tuesday, 13 May, insightful charts, technical analysis, ideas</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-tuesday-13-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:05:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trade-ideas-thread-tuesday-13-may-insightful-charts-technical-analysis-ideas-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Good morning, afternoon and evening all. Any charts, technical analysis, trade ideas, thoughts, views, ForexLive traders would like to share and discuss with fellow ForexLive traders, please do so:
 &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Eamonn Sheridan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EURUSD Technical Outlook: Sellers Take Control Below 200-Bar MA on 4-hour chart today</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-technical-outlook-sellers-take-control-below-200-bar-ma-on-4-hour-chart-today-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:58:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/eurusd-technical-outlook-sellers-take-control-below-200-bar-ma-on-4-hour-chart-today-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;191&quot; data-end=&quot;480&quot;&gt;The EURUSD moved decisively lower today after breaking below a key support confluence on the 4-hour chart, which included the 200-bar moving average and a swing area between 1.12657 and 1.1273. That breakdown gave sellers the technical green light to extend the move to the downside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;482&quot; data-end=&quot;714&quot;&gt;The next key target for sellers lies at the 38.2% retracement of the January–April rally, which comes in at 1.10395. A move below this level would strengthen the bearish bias and open the door for further downside potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;716&quot; data-end=&quot;909&quot;&gt;If the price remains below the broken 1.1273–1.12657 zone and the 200-bar MA, sellers retain control in the short term. Holding below that area will be crucial for maintaining bearish momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;911&quot; data-end=&quot;923&quot;&gt;Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;924&quot; data-end=&quot;1090&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;924&quot; data-end=&quot;982&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;926&quot; data-end=&quot;982&quot;&gt;Broke below 200-bar MA and swing zone at 1.12657–1.1273.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;983&quot; data-end=&quot;1040&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;985&quot; data-end=&quot;1040&quot;&gt;Next target: 1.10395 (38.2% retracement of 2025 rally).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1041&quot; data-end=&quot;1090&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1043&quot; data-end=&quot;1090&quot;&gt;Staying below 1.1273 keeps bearish bias intact. One&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *UAE CHIP DEAL &apos;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS&apos; OF GPUS: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922016641228976315#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:50:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922016641228976315#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*UAE CHIP DEAL &apos;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS&apos; OF GPUS: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *US MULLS LARGE CHIP SALE TO EMIRATI AI FIRM G42: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922016471397372338#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:50:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922016471397372338#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*US MULLS LARGE CHIP SALE TO EMIRATI AI FIRM G42: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ on pace for the second best day going back to 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/nasdaq-on-pace-for-the-second-best-day-going-back-to-2022-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:40:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/nasdaq-on-pace-for-the-second-best-day-going-back-to-2022-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Both the S&amp;amp;P and the NASDAQ indices surged on April 9 on the rebound from Liberation Day on April 2. For the NASDAQ index the price rose 12.16% on that day. For the S&amp;amp;P index the index rose 9.52%. If April 9 was the largest gain, today&apos;s gains in both those broad indices represent the second-largest gains going back to 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, the S&amp;amp;P is up 3.04%. On November 30, 2022 the index rose 3.10%. The NASDAQ index is up 4.01%. On November 30, 2022 the index rose 4.41%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, both the S&amp;amp;P and NASDAQ indices are closing above both their 200 and 100 day moving averages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; For the S&amp;amp;P index, the 200 day moving average comes in at 5750.30. The 100 day moving averages at 5773.88. The current price is at 5831.11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For the NASDAQ index, the 200 day moving averages at 18321.35. The 100 day is at 18477.63. The current price is at 18653.00&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the gains can be sustained into the close it would represent the first close above those moving averages since February 25. That would be a bullish development technically. &lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Tax Bill: Exempt workers from tips, with exceptions. SALT deduction $30K from $10K</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/house-tax-bill-exempt-workers-from-tips-with-exceptions-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:01:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/house-tax-bill-exempt-workers-from-tips-with-exceptions-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;US House Republicans tax bill:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Would exempt workers from tips from income and tax with exceptions (through 2028&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Includes exemption on workers overtime pay with exceptions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced deduction for senior citizens by $4000 with exceptions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raising cap on state and local tax deduction (SALT deductions) to $30,000 from current $10,000 with exceptions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;does not include millionaire tax bracket&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Republican tax bill raises debt limit by $4 trillion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *TAX BILL OMITS TRUMP PROPOSAL FOR MILLIONAIRE TAX BRACKET</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922003610021310516#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:59:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922003610021310516#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*TAX BILL OMITS TRUMP PROPOSAL FOR MILLIONAIRE TAX BRACKET&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *REPUBLICAN TAX BILL RAISES DEBT LIMIT BY $4 TRILLION</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922003557055639806#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:58:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922003557055639806#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*REPUBLICAN TAX BILL RAISES DEBT LIMIT BY $4 TRILLION&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed&apos;s Goolbee: Tariffs on China would still have a stagflationary impulse</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolbee-tariffs-on-china-would-still-have-a-stagflationary-impulse-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:57:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/feds-goolbee-tariffs-on-china-would-still-have-a-stagflationary-impulse-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariffs and the uncertainty around President Trump’s policies still risked a combination of higher consumer prices and slower growth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;On China, it is definitely less impactful stagflationarily than the path they were on.  Yet it’s three to five times higher than what it was before, &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It is going to have a stagflationary impulse on the economy. It’s going to make growth slower and make prices rise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The way that we’re doing this is not free for the economy,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Businesses he has spoken to want to make big investments and hire people, but the prospects that any of these negotiated tariff truces could lapse have made decisions like that much more difficult.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;US/China statements are coming with explicit recognition that this isn’t permanent and that it’s going to be revisited in the near future.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Part of those announcements are explicitly putting off into the future major decisions, so that’s why it feels like there is in corporate America a lot of sitting on the hands. If they’re sitting on their hands, that backs into the wait-and-see posture of the Fed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fed could afford to take its time before making any policy decisions. The labor market is still in solid shape, and there are not yet acute signs of strain. But the risks to inflation are not negligible, and it is still possible that tariffs of the nature that Mr. Trump is willing to keep in place could lead to a much more persistent problem&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;what would concern him was if either the labor market started to deteriorate notably or expectations about inflation over a longer time horizon started to rise significantly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stagflation is a very uncomfortable situation for a central bank&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) PENTAGON CANCELS ALL GENDER AFFIRMING HEALTHCARE FOR TRANSGENDER TROOPS AS IT MOVES TO KICK THEM OUT OF THE MILITARY, MEMO SEEN BY REUTERS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002831847854223#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002831847854223#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PENTAGON CANCELS ALL GENDER AFFIRMING HEALTHCARE FOR TRANSGENDER TROOPS AS IT MOVES TO KICK THEM OUT OF THE MILITARY, MEMO SEEN BY REUTERS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Apple will never leave China</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/why-apple-will-never-leave-china-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:55:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/why-apple-will-never-leave-china-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Patrick McGee writes in the Times of London today about the complexity of the relationships between Apple and China and how it contributed to China&apos;s rise while making Apple the most-valuable company in the world. Neither could have happened without the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;There is zero chance that Apple will ever leave China,&quot; writes McGee, who tomorrow will be out with&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.ca/Apple-China-Capture-Greatest-Company/dp/1668053373&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt; a book&lt;/a&gt; on Apple&apos;s rise in China. &quot;America lacks the experiential know-how, the dense population, the
 low wages or even the infrastructure to be competitive in manufacturing
 smartphones as complex as Apple’s.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple recently announced it would move assembly for its US-sold iPhones to India by 2026 but this aims to obfuscate that the components will still be built in China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, President Trump highlighted that he spoke with Apple CEO Tim Cook this morning ahead of the tariff announcement. That&apos;s an acknowledgement that Apple had lobbied hard for the tariffs to go down and the company won. A frequent talking point of the tariffs was that &apos;no one wanted a $2000 iPhone&apos;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is home to 90% of Apple&apos;s production, according to McGee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Washington has good reason to want to untie this knot, to convince
 Apple it should train workers in Ohio, not Zhengzhou. But the supply 
chain in question is the result of decades of Chinese investment, focus 
and tailor-made policies, supported by cutting-edge robotics, skills and
 experience.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apple shares are up 6.1% today.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GOP TAX BILL CALLS TO END ELECTRIC VEHICLE TAX CREDIT EARLY</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002171203055726#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:53:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002171203055726#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GOP TAX BILL CALLS TO END ELECTRIC VEHICLE TAX CREDIT EARLY&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE REPUBLICANS SEEK &quot;ENHANCED DEDUCTION&quot; FOR SENIOR CITIZENS BY $4,000, WITH EXCEPTIONS -BILL TEXT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922002130732245429#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:53:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922002130732245429#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE REPUBLICANS SEEK &quot;ENHANCED DEDUCTION&quot; FOR SENIOR CITIZENS BY $4,000, WITH EXCEPTIONS -BILL TEXT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) GOOLSBEE: TARIFFS WILL STILL HAVE STAGFLATIONARY IMPLUSE: NYT</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922000611878355067#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:47:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922000611878355067#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GOOLSBEE: TARIFFS WILL STILL HAVE STAGFLATIONARY IMPLUSE: NYT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL INCLUDES EXEMPTION ON WORKERS&apos; OVERTIME PAY, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1922000568353980860#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1922000568353980860#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL INCLUDES EXEMPTION ON WORKERS&apos; OVERTIME PAY, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil settles at $61.95</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-settles-at-6195-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:44:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/crude-oil-settles-at-6195-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Crude oil futures are settling at $61.95. That is up $0.93 or 1.52%. The high price reached $63.57. The low price was at $61.04. The price is up for the third consecutive day. Since the low reached on May 5, the price is up 11.48%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the daily chart, there is a swing area between $62.46 and $65.29 (see yellow area on the chart above).. In between that area lies the 50% midpoint of the range since the 2020 low. That level comes in at $64.71&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL WOULD EXEMPT WORKERS&apos; TIPS FROM INCOME TAX, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921999715534561550#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:43:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921999715534561550#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. HOUSE REPUBLICANS&apos; BILL WOULD EXEMPT WORKERS&apos; TIPS FROM INCOME TAX, WITH EXCEPTIONS, BILL TEXT SHOWS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) *HOUSE REPUBLICANS RELEASE TEXT OF TAX BILL SOUGHT BY TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921998714861662449#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:39:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921998714861662449#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;*HOUSE REPUBLICANS RELEASE TEXT OF TAX BILL SOUGHT BY TRUMP&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed: Senior Loan Officer Opinion Survey on Bank Lending Practices released</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/fed-senior-loan-officer-opinion-survey-on-bank-lending-practices-released-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:26:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/fed-senior-loan-officer-opinion-survey-on-bank-lending-practices-released-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;71&quot; data-end=&quot;92&quot;&gt;Business Lending:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;93&quot; data-end=&quot;980&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;93&quot; data-end=&quot;484&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;95&quot; data-end=&quot;111&quot;&gt;C&amp;amp;I Loans (Commercial and Industrial loans):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;114&quot; data-end=&quot;484&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;114&quot; data-end=&quot;169&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;116&quot; data-end=&quot;169&quot;&gt;Lending standards tightened for firms of all sizes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;114&quot; data-end=&quot;169&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;116&quot; data-end=&quot;169&quot;&gt;% of Banks tightening was the highest in more than a year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;172&quot; data-end=&quot;289&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;174&quot; data-end=&quot;289&quot;&gt;Loan terms also tightened: smaller credit lines, higher premiums, stricter covenants and collateral requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;292&quot; data-end=&quot;348&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;294&quot; data-end=&quot;348&quot;&gt;Demand weakened significantly across all firm sizes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;351&quot; data-end=&quot;484&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;353&quot; data-end=&quot;484&quot;&gt;Key reasons for tightening: uncertain economic outlook, regulatory concerns, industry-specific problems, and reduced risk appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;486&quot; data-end=&quot;980&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;488&quot; data-end=&quot;529&quot;&gt;CRE Loans (Commercial Real Estate):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;532&quot; data-end=&quot;980&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;532&quot; data-end=&quot;623&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;534&quot; data-end=&quot;623&quot;&gt;Tighter standards for construction &amp;amp; land development and nonfarm nonresidential loans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;626&quot; data-end=&quot;679&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;628&quot; data-end=&quot;679&quot;&gt;Multifamily loan standards were mostly unchanged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;682&quot; data-end=&quot;784&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;684&quot; data-end=&quot;784&quot;&gt;Demand was mixed: weaker at most banks, but some large and foreign banks reported stronger demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;787&quot; data-end=&quot;906&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;789&quot; data-end=&quot;906&quot;&gt;Over the past year, banks tightened loan-to-value ratios, debt service coverage, and reduced interest-only periods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;909&quot; data-end=&quot;980&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;911&quot; data-end=&quot;980&quot;&gt;Office loans saw the most tightening across all queried policy areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;982&quot; data-end=&quot;1004&quot;&gt;Household Lending:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1006&quot; data-end=&quot;1549&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1006&quot; data-end=&quot;1278&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1008&quot; data-end=&quot;1050&quot;&gt;Residential Real Estate Loans (RRE):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1053&quot; data-end=&quot;1278&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1053&quot; data-end=&quot;1145&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1055&quot; data-end=&quot;1145&quot;&gt;Lending standards mostly unchanged, except modest tightening for non-QM jumbo mortgages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1148&quot; data-end=&quot;1200&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1150&quot; data-end=&quot;1200&quot;&gt;Demand weakened across most mortgage categories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1203&quot; data-end=&quot;1278&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1205&quot; data-end=&quot;1278&quot;&gt;HELOC standards were stable, but demand for HELOCs modestly strengthened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1280&quot; data-end=&quot;1549&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1282&quot; data-end=&quot;1303&quot;&gt;Consumer Loans:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1306&quot; data-end=&quot;1549&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1306&quot; data-end=&quot;1386&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1308&quot; data-end=&quot;1386&quot;&gt;Credit card lending standards tightened slightly (especially credit limits).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1389&quot; data-end=&quot;1458&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1391&quot; data-end=&quot;1458&quot;&gt;Auto and other consumer loan standards remained mostly unchanged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1461&quot; data-end=&quot;1549&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1463&quot; data-end=&quot;1549&quot;&gt;Demand weakened for credit card and other consumer loans; auto loan demand was stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) $AAPL - APPLE PLANS AI-POWERED BATTERY MANAGEMENT MODE FOR DEVICES IN IOS 19</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921994052645408782#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:21:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921994052645408782#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8080/search?q=%23AAPL&quot;&gt;$AAPL&lt;/a&gt; - APPLE PLANS AI-POWERED BATTERY MANAGEMENT MODE FOR DEVICES IN IOS 19&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) U.S. POSTS $258B APRIL BUDGET SURPLUS, UP 23%

Strong tax payments and record import tariffs boosted the U.S. April surplus to $258B, Treasury reported.

🔸 $16B in customs duties, up $9B from last year.
🔸 U.S. collected $500M/day from tariffs, far below Trump&apos;s $2B/day claim.
🔸 Tariff revenue will fall as U.S.-China agreed to cut tariffs (U.S. to 30%, China to 10%) for 90 days.

For fiscal 2025 (Oct-Apr):

🔸 Deficit: $1.049T, up 23%.
🔸 Receipts: $3.11T, Outlays: $4.16T — both April records.
🔸 Adjusted for timing effects, the deficit rose 4%.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921989411522146372#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:02:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921989411522146372#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;U.S. POSTS $258B APRIL BUDGET SURPLUS, UP 23%&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Strong tax payments and record import tariffs boosted the U.S. April surplus to $258B, Treasury reported.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 $16B in customs duties, up $9B from last year.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 U.S. collected $500M/day from tariffs, far below Trump&apos;s $2B/day claim.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Tariff revenue will fall as U.S.-China agreed to cut tariffs (U.S. to 30%, China to 10%) for 90 days.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
For fiscal 2025 (Oct-Apr):&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Deficit: $1.049T, up 23%.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Receipts: $3.11T, Outlays: $4.16T — both April records.&lt;br&gt;
🔸 Adjusted for timing effects, the deficit rose 4%.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) US BUDGET SURPLUS RISES 23% TO $258 BILLION IN APRIL, CUSTOMS REVENUE SURGES

The U.S. government posted a $258 billion budget surplus for April, up 23% from a year earlier, reflecting strong tax receipts in the final month of the tax season and surging collections of import duties, the Treasury Department said on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921988910256738470#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921988910256738470#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;US BUDGET SURPLUS RISES 23% TO $258 BILLION IN APRIL, CUSTOMS REVENUE SURGES&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The U.S. government posted a $258 billion budget surplus for April, up 23% from a year earlier, reflecting strong tax receipts in the final month of the tax season and surging collections of import duties, the Treasury Department said on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US April federal budget +258B vs +256B expected</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-federal-budget-258b-vs-256b-expected-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/us-april-federal-budget-258b-vs-256b-expected-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;March was -161B&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last April was +210B&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;April is always the best month of the US for the US budget due to income tax receipts. Even on those terms it ranks as the second-best April on record. That said, timing shifts around Easter and how the days of the week land in any given month can affect how many pay periods there are. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These budget numbers are rarely a market mover but they&apos;re a good reminder that Congress will one day have to bring down spending or raise more money.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goldman Sachs: Upgrades CNY forecasts, now sees USD/CNY at 7.00 in 12 months</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-upgrades-cny-forecasts-now-sees-usdcny-at-700-in-12-months-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:41:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/goldman-sachs-upgrades-cny-forecasts-now-sees-usdcny-at-700-in-12-months-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;82&quot; data-end=&quot;330&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs shifts to a stronger Chinese Yuan outlook, now forecasting USD/CNY to reach 7.00 by 12 months, citing Beijing’s preference for currency stability and alternative policy support over depreciation amid tariff stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;332&quot; data-end=&quot;347&quot;&gt;Key Points:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;349&quot; data-end=&quot;1113&quot;&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;349&quot; data-end=&quot;565&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;351&quot; data-end=&quot;565&quot;&gt;Stable Fix Signals Policy Intent:Despite high tariffs, the PBoC’s consistent USD/CNY fix indicates a preference for exchange rate stability to avoid spooking markets or triggering capital outflows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;567&quot; data-end=&quot;775&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;569&quot; data-end=&quot;775&quot;&gt;Policy Support Comes Elsewhere:China is opting for monetary easing and aggressive government bond issuance as stimulus tools, rather than using currency depreciation to absorb trade shocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;777&quot; data-end=&quot;967&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;779&quot; data-end=&quot;967&quot;&gt;New Forecast Path:Goldman revises its USD/CNY trajectory to 7.20 (3M), 7.10 (6M), and 7.00 (12M) from its earlier 7.30, 7.35, 7.35 path—highlighting a firmer Yuan outlook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;969&quot; data-end=&quot;1113&quot;&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;971&quot; data-end=&quot;1113&quot;&gt;FX Strategy Implication:The firm sees value in downside USD/CNH exposure, as markets may still be overpricing depreciation risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1115&quot; data-end=&quot;1363&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1115&quot; data-end=&quot;1363&quot;&gt;Goldman’s upgraded forecasts reflect Beijing’s strategic restraint on currency weakening, with the USD/CNY now expected to grind lower as China leans on domestic stimulus and strives to contain capital flight risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=&quot;&quot; data-start=&quot;1115&quot; data-end=&quot;1363&quot;&gt;For bank trade ideas, &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747158049307000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw1ZzWOLKyb76VaJpOrVIRJa&quot;&gt;check out eFX Plus&lt;/a&gt;. For a limited time, get a 7 day free trial, basic for $79 per month and premium at $109 per month. &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-saferedirecturl=&quot;https://www.google.com/url?q=https://plus.efxdata.com/ad/track/4655172E54F06040571CD0AB083845AD&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1747158049307000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw1ZzWOLKyb76VaJpOrVIRJa&quot;&gt;Get it here&lt;/a&gt;.

&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) CHINA TRADE EASING DOESN&apos;T MEAN A QUICK FED CUT: DEUTSCHE BANK

A big drop in U.S.-China trade barriers lessens the prospects of a serious inflationary supply crunch. Even so, inflation remains stubborn enough that the Fed probably still won&apos;t be in a rush to cut interest rates, economists at Deutsche Bank write. Despite the trade war&apos;s easing, &quot;policies are likely to keep inflation at uncomfortably high levels for the Fed,&quot; Deutsche&apos;s team suggests. &quot;This announcement therefore reinforces our view that the Fed is going to be slow to cut rates this year.&quot; Deutsche&apos;s baseline assumption is that the Fed&apos;s next rate cut won&apos;t come before December</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921976766329192614#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:12:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921976766329192614#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CHINA TRADE EASING DOESN&apos;T MEAN A QUICK FED CUT: DEUTSCHE BANK&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
A big drop in U.S.-China trade barriers lessens the prospects of a serious inflationary supply crunch. Even so, inflation remains stubborn enough that the Fed probably still won&apos;t be in a rush to cut interest rates, economists at Deutsche Bank write. Despite the trade war&apos;s easing, &quot;policies are likely to keep inflation at uncomfortably high levels for the Fed,&quot; Deutsche&apos;s team suggests. &quot;This announcement therefore reinforces our view that the Fed is going to be slow to cut rates this year.&quot; Deutsche&apos;s baseline assumption is that the Fed&apos;s next rate cut won&apos;t come before December&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECBs Nagel: We shouldn&apos;t overreact to individual announcements</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-we-shouldnt-overreact-to-individual-announcements-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:10:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/ecbs-nagel-we-shouldnt-overreact-to-individual-announcements-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;ECBs Nagel is on the wires saying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We shouldn&apos;t overreact to individual announcements.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, ECBs Escriva says:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;They must be humble in assessing the current situation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 rallies to the highs of the day, futures pear the peak as well</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-500-rallies-to-the-highs-of-the-day-futures-pear-the-peak-as-well-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:09:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-500-rallies-to-the-highs-of-the-day-futures-pear-the-peak-as-well-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The S&amp;amp;P 500 is at the highs of the day, up 3.1% while the Nasdaq is up 4.2% as buying turns into a feeding frenzy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next mark to watch is the futures overnight high of 5865 as we&apos;re about 6 points from that now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s an impressive rally as the early sellers have been overcome by fresh money.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold on pace for its worst day since November 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-on-pace-for-its-worst-day-since-november-2024-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:08:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/gold-on-pace-for-its-worst-day-since-november-2024-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The flight into gold is having a tough time today after the weekend news on tariff relief at least for the next 90 days between the US and China. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The price is currently down -$101 or -3.06% at $3224.21. The dollar decline is the largest one-day decline on record. On a percentage basis, the decline is the worst since the price fell -3.35% back on November 25.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the daily chart, the low price from May 1 reached $3202.03. The low price today reach $3207.95 so far. Moving below that level should open the door for further downside momentum with the 38.2% retracement of the move up from the November 2024 low the next major target at $3132.16. Below that a trendline cuts across at $3082.,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; It would take a while to get to the rising 100 day moving which is currently at $2953.80. That is also near the swing low going back to April 7 (I guess it wasn&apos;t that long ago).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the trading year, the price of gold is still up 22.83% after rising 27.22% in 2024 and 13.16% in 2023. If tariff risks decline, we could see a liquidation of the precious metal.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOE Taylor: We are a long way from neutral level of interest rates</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-taylor-we-are-a-long-way-from-neutral-level-of-interest-rates-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:35:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/centralbank/boe-taylor-we-are-a-long-way-from-neutral-level-of-interest-rates-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;BOE Taylor says: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We are a long way from the neutral level of interest rates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Neutral rate for me is 2.75 – 3% in the UK.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Erosion of business confidence in the UK has continued in REC and PMI surveys..&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is a sense of precaution and concernt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tariff shock was bigger than anyone expected.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Although there are signs of a pause, we don&apos;t know where it will go.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wage settlement data is coming in line with expectations for slower wage growth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Central forecast of BOE had quite mild treatment of global trade situation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The UK/US trade deal is quite slender.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, the Bank of England reduced its base interest rate by 0.25 percentage points to 4.25%, marking the fourth cut since August 2024. The decision was made amid easing inflationary pressures and concerns over global economic uncertainties, particularly stemming from recent U.S. tariffs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Monetary Policy Committee&apos;s vote was notably divided. The decision was supported by five members: Governor Andrew Bailey, Sarah Breeden, Megan Greene, Clare Lombardelli, and Dave Ramsden. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two members including  Swati Dhingra and Taylor, advocated for a larger 0.5 percentage point cut, citing concerns over subdued inflation and potential impacts from global trade tensions. Taylor&apos;s comments support his bias.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, Catherine L. Mann and Chief Economist Huw Pill voted to maintain the rate at 4.5%, expressing worries about persistent inflation pressures, particularly from wage growth and services inflation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This three-way split underscores the MPC&apos;s differing views on balancing inflation risks against economic growth considerations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While inflation stood at 2.6% in March, the Bank anticipates a temporary rise to 3.5% in the third quarter due to factors like higher energy prices, before returning to the 2% target by early 2027 . The Bank also highlighted that recent U.S. tariff increases are expected to weigh on global growth, adding to the cautious outlook for the UK economy .&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NZDUSD moves to new lows for day and lowest level since April 14</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nzdusd-moves-to-new-lows-for-day-and-lowest-level-since-april-14-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:31:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nzdusd-moves-to-new-lows-for-day-and-lowest-level-since-april-14-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;182&quot; data-end=&quot;412&quot;&gt;The NZDUSD has shifted lower after breaking beneath a key support confluence, including the 200-day moving average at 0.5883 and a price floor near that level. The move signals growing bearish momentum as sellers gain control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;414&quot; data-end=&quot;780&quot;&gt;Support is now found at the swing area between 0.5852 and 0.5860, with the pair testing the low of that zone. A move below would target the 200-bar moving average on the 4-hour chart, which comes in at 0.5847. Below that, the 38.2% retracement of the April move up, at 0.58204, serves as the next critical downside level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;782&quot; data-end=&quot;995&quot;&gt;To sustain the bearish shift, NZDUSD needs to stay below the 0.5852–0.5860 area, or more conservatively for sellers looking for more downside, the 200 day MA at 0.5883. Staying below would ultimately need a break and hold under 0.5820. Failure to do so could invite dip buyers and shift control back toward the bulls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;997&quot; data-end=&quot;1009&quot;&gt;Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1010&quot; data-end=&quot;1236&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1010&quot; data-end=&quot;1063&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1012&quot; data-end=&quot;1063&quot;&gt;Broke below 200-day MA at 0.5883 and support floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1064&quot; data-end=&quot;1100&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1066&quot; data-end=&quot;1100&quot;&gt;Swing area support: 0.5852–0.5860.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1101&quot; data-end=&quot;1182&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1103&quot; data-end=&quot;1182&quot;&gt;Key downside targets: 0.5847 (200-bar MA on 4H) and 0.5820 (38.2% retracement).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1183&quot; data-end=&quot;1236&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1185&quot; data-end=&quot;1236&quot;&gt;Staying below 0.5820 would confirm seller control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Were the last six weeks all a bad dream?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/were-the-last-six-weeks-all-a-bad-dream-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/were-the-last-six-weeks-all-a-bad-dream-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;For the last six weeks, everyone in markets has been contemplating a reordering of world markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, we&apos;re back to where we started in tariff rates and in markets. That has Deutsche Bank wonder: What was the point of all of this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They note that the latest data shows China exports to the US on a steady decline with April 2025 imports at the lowest in real terms since 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;Previously, we were convinced they were likely
to be very hawkish towards China and the two nations would continue to decouple
and that the massive imbalance between the two nations&apos; manufacturing output
and the national security concerns would ensure the ideology remained
throughout the term,&quot; writes DB multi-asset strategist Jim Reid.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;I&apos;ll be honest – I have more questions than answers at
the moment but it seems that: (1) more pragmatic voices in the US
administration have taken control again; (2) the near-term economy is being
prioritised over the long-term security agenda; (3) the US needs trade to
continue for now, and perhaps overestimated the leverage high tariffs would
give them in extracting concessions.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;So were the last six weeks all a bad dream? Will the
unpredictable nature of US policy continue or are we now on a more conventional
path? Not sure I have the answers this morning but, if you&apos;re looking for
positives, US policy does seem to have galvanised Europe, is encouraging China
to rebalance towards consumption and Bessent has even discussed how the trade
deficit may be partly being caused by the fiscal deficit. So maybe US policy
has been a force for good?&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s a common sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European indices close higher. German Dax closes at a new record level.</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/european-indices-close-higher-german-dax-closes-at-a-new-record-level-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:01:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/european-indices-close-higher-german-dax-closes-at-a-new-record-level-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Major European indices are closing higher on the day. The German DAX closed at a new all-time high at 23551.54. Spain&apos;s Ibex closed at its highest level since 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A snapshot of the close levels shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;German DAX +52.21 points or 0.22% at 23551.54.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;France&apos;s CAC, +106.35 points or 1.37% at 7850.11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UK&apos;s FTSE 100 +50.18 points or 0.59% at 8604.99.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spain&apos;s Ibex +101.22 points or 0.75% at 13655.31.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Italy&apos;s FTSE MIB +551.60 points or 1.40% at 39921.60&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the daily chart of the German DAX, the price is moving away from the swing high going back to March 6 at 23475&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDCAD stretches above 1.4000 for first time since April 10</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-stretches-above-14000-for-first-time-since-april-10-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:39:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/usdcad-stretches-above-14000-for-first-time-since-april-10-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;142&quot; data-end=&quot;530&quot;&gt;The USDCAD has extended its gains and pushed above the key 1.4000 level, reaching a high of 1.40043. The next upside target comes in at the 200-day moving average at 1.40106, followed by resistance at 1.40268, a prior swing area high. Beyond that, the 38.2% retracement of the decline from the March 2025 high sits at 1.40525, marking a more significant hurdle for buyers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;532&quot; data-end=&quot;765&quot;&gt;The earlier dip in price found support at 1.3977, the April 15 swing high, where buyers leaned in and reasserted control. That successful retest reinforced the bullish bias and helped fuel the move back toward and through 1.4000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;767&quot; data-end=&quot;1040&quot;&gt;While the break above 1.4000 is constructive, buyers still have work to do. A sustained move above the 200-day moving average, and ultimately the 1.40525 retracement level, is needed to confirm a stronger upside shift. For now, momentum remains with the buyers.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff uncertainty will be a drag on competitive dynamics</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariff-uncertainty-will-be-a-drag-on-competitive-dynamics-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:32:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/tariff-uncertainty-will-be-a-drag-on-competitive-dynamics-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;If you&apos;re an executive right now, what are you focused on: tariffs or competing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Capitalism works best when companies have a clear set of rules and can fight for market share. Today&apos;s news is undoubtedly good on tariffs but it&apos;s a 90-day pause, similar to the &apos;liberation day&apos; climb-down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In today&apos;s environment there is so much uncertainty. There are few executives with international supply chains that are right now focused on gaining market share. Instead, they&apos;re trying to navigate changing rules, stockpile and manage inventories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, there are probably opportunities to undercut competitors but if competitors can&apos;t respond and the moves are temporary, does that really create sustained disinflation? I&apos;d argue that it simply leads to turmoil in pricing that resets with weaker competitive dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My guess is this is how the Fed sees it as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recipe right now isn&apos;t there for disinflation in the world as companies are writing tariff clauses into contracts and stuffing warehouses. Right now they have to decide if they want to pay 30% tariffs on Chinese goods or risk waiting around for a better/worse deal later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bull case now for risk assets and the US dollar is the massive tax cut package that Republicans are working on. I&apos;d say a good deal of that is already priced in but certainly not all of it. It&apos;s looking like it will be paid for via Medicaid cuts and massive deficits. Even with that it&apos;s mostly a continuation of the regime that&apos;s already in place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when you look out further at some point you need to price in a tightening fiscal regime. The US is running at deficit at 7% of GDP and tariffs and DOGE aren&apos;t going to pay for much at all. The Joint Congressional Committee on Taxation is just out with an analysis saying the tax bill will cost $4.9 trillion over 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;d imaging there will be cheers in markets when that&apos;s passed but at some point, it will need to be paid for so at some point you need to price in some level of austerity.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) FED’S KUGLER: I AM ONE OF THOSE WHO BELIEVES THERE COULD BE SOME PERMANENCY FROM PRICE INCREASES RELATED TO TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921947847651447018#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:17:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921947847651447018#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FED’S KUGLER: I AM ONE OF THOSE WHO BELIEVES THERE COULD BE SOME PERMANENCY FROM PRICE INCREASES RELATED TO TARIFFS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ breaks key moving averages, bullish trend in place</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nasdaq-breaks-key-moving-averages-bullish-trend-in-place-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:05:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/technical-analysis/nasdaq-breaks-key-moving-averages-bullish-trend-in-place-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p data-start=&quot;162&quot; data-end=&quot;501&quot;&gt;The NASDAQ Composite Index has broken back above the 200-day moving average (green line on the chart at 18,320.79) and 100-day moving average (blue line at 18,476.49)  —a technical development that marks a shift in the medium-term trend. These MA levels were broken for the last time (to the downside) on March 6 and had not traded above since that day. The price gapped above the MAs today off of the weekend news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;162&quot; data-end=&quot;501&quot;&gt;The NASDAQ index is currently up 630.2 or 3.5% at 18557.63 above both those moving averages&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;503&quot; data-end=&quot;802&quot;&gt;With the index breaking back above those MAs, they become the bias-defining levels today and going forward.  Staying above is more bullish with a swing area between 18599 and 18832 as the next area to get and stay above (see yellow area on the chart above).  A move above those levels takes the price back into the all-time upper extreme that peaked at 20204.58 back on December 16, 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1003&quot; data-end=&quot;1015&quot;&gt;Summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-start=&quot;1016&quot; data-end=&quot;1291&quot;&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1016&quot; data-end=&quot;1091&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1018&quot; data-end=&quot;1091&quot;&gt;100-day and 200-day MAs between 18320.88 and 18,476.49 have been broken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1092&quot; data-end=&quot;1144&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1094&quot; data-end=&quot;1144&quot;&gt;Bullish bias now in place with buyers in control above the moving averages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-start=&quot;1145&quot; data-end=&quot;1221&quot;&gt;&lt;p data-start=&quot;1147&quot; data-end=&quot;1221&quot;&gt;Key upside targets are between swing area at 18598.87 and 18831.91&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The S&amp;amp;P index has also broken above its key 200-day moving average at 5750.18 and it&apos;s 100 day moving average at 5773.64. The current price trades at 5811.31 up 151.42 points or 2.67%. There is a swing area between 5782.02 and 5878.47 which if broken would take the price into the upper all-time extreme that peaked at 6147.43.&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Greg Michalowski at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) TRUMP: BELIEVES RUSSIA WILL AGREE TO 30 DAY CEASEFIRE</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921941129492128001#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:50:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921941129492128001#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TRUMP: BELIEVES RUSSIA WILL AGREE TO 30 DAY CEASEFIRE&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech sector surges: Investors flock to Apple and Amazon in today&apos;s bullish market</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-surges-investors-flock-to-apple-and-amazon-in-todays-bullish-market-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:46:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/stock-market-update/tech-sector-surges-investors-flock-to-apple-and-amazon-in-todays-bullish-market-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;Sector Overview&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&apos;s market is buzzing with positivity, driven by standout performances in the technology and consumer cyclical sectors. The technology sector is seeing remarkable gains, spearheaded by industry giants Apple (AAPL) and Microsoft (MSFT). Meanwhile, the consumer cyclical sector is thriving, with Amazon (AMZN) leading the charge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technology Advances: Apple, with an impressive increase of 5.17%, and Microsoft, up by 1.07%, are elevating the technology sector. Other notable contributors include Nvidia (NVDA) with a 3.23% rise and Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) which is up by 4.45%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consumer Cyclical Gains: Amazon is witnessing a substantial boost of 7.06%. Tesla (TSLA) follows closely with a gain of 5.46%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communication Services: This sector is also enjoying a favorable day, with Meta (META) jumping 5.65% and Google (GOOG) up by 2.56%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Market Mood and Trends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The overall market sentiment today is highly optimistic, fueled by robust earnings reports from key players and increasing consumer confidence. Investors are eagerly embracing tech stocks, indicating a strong belief in the sector&apos;s growth potential amid evolving market dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic Recommendations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors might consider bolstering their portfolios with tech and consumer cyclical stocks given today&apos;s favorable movements. Specifically, Apple&apos;s and Amazon&apos;s strong performances suggest potential long-term growth. However, it&apos;s vital to remain vigilant and diversify holdings to mitigate risks, particularly considering the volatility in sectors like healthcare and utilities. Stay informed and responsive to real-time market shifts to ensure strategic decisions align with evolving trends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Explore &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forexlive.com/&quot;&gt;ForexLive&lt;/a&gt; for more insights and the latest updates on market activities. 📈📊&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Itai Levitan at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIA PM MODI: NO NUCLEAR BLACKMAIL WILL BE TOLERATED BY INDIA</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921939904042262880#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:45:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921939904042262880#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIA PM MODI: NO NUCLEAR BLACKMAIL WILL BE TOLERATED BY INDIA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(My Local Feed) INDIA PM MODI: PAKISTAN CONTACTED OUR MILITARY OPERATIONS CHIEF ON MAY 10</title>
      <link>https://x.com/DeItaone/status/1921939428181774674#m</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:44:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/DeItaone/status/1921939428181774674#m</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INDIA PM MODI: PAKISTAN CONTACTED OUR MILITARY OPERATIONS CHIEF ON MAY 10&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump with more on China: I think we will have a deal</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-with-more-on-china-i-think-we-will-have-a-deal-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:40:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/trump-with-more-on-china-i-think-we-will-have-a-deal-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;I think we&apos;ll have a deal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;China tariffs will go up without a deal, won&apos;t go all the way to 145%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;All the comments are so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Iran/Russia:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;So far Iran is acting intelligently&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Iran is being reasonable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Believes Russia will agree to a 30-day ceasefire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is the latest from Fox Business&apos; Charlie Gasparino:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; In talking to sources who run small businesses the pause w China came just as their company is were on the precipice of disaster since they source so much of their material from China and the containers coming from China were coming back empty. If you want to know why we were as desperate for a deal as the Chinese, it’s because small businesses — a key MAGA constituency— was about to get crushed&lt;/blockquote&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 falls into the opening gap</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-500-falls-into-the-opening-gap-20250512/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:36:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.forexlive.com/news/sp-500-falls-into-the-opening-gap-20250512/</guid>
      <description>
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;The problem with this rally is that it was front-run hard. The tide really turned on the market after Bessent&apos;s private comments and the White House private meeting with Walmart, Target, Home Depot and other retailers. A hint of that was that shipping out of China has spiked in the past two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a lingering sense that too many people knew this was coming and that much of the buying the past three weeks was in anticipation of today. Yes, the details are probably better than expected but there may have been some massive leveraged trades betting on exactly this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now they&apos;re taking profits in an economy that&apos;s still wracked by turmoil and uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I still think the path is ultimately higher but is there enough here to chase markets to fresh all-time highs?&lt;/p&gt;
                            This article was written by Adam Button at www.forexlive.com.
                        
                        </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
